<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 30 Nov.; Ned. Oorl. Transportschip Heldin, comm. Lambert, Bat. - China, Tofield, Japan. - Quartet, Mulder, Bat. - Meppel, Stikkel van Dam, Buenos-Ayres. - Fosca Helena, Manje, Suriname - Anna en Maria, Jager, id. - Agatha, Zeijlinga, Curacao. - Gezusters, Ridder, Laguayra. - Seenymph, Held, Cienfugos. - Cardenas Packet, Fraay, Havana. - Boutry, Repsdorph, Kust van Guinea. - AlessandriDa, Astarita, Napels. - Neanthes, Williams, id. - Christina Jacoba, de Groot, Lissabon. • Martha &amp; Ellen, Crabtree, Londen. - Cappelen,Walker, Liverpool. - Kate Sophia, James, Dublin.- Cycloop, S., Koningsb. VLIE, 28 Nov.; Stoomvaart, S„ Hamburg. DELFZIJL, 20 Nov.; Sevirins, Heyen, Papenberg. - Hoffnung, Denekamp, Leer. - Aurora, Helmers, id. —21 Nov.; Trientje Veltkamp, Koopman,Weener. — 24 Nov.; Maria, Minke, Rheede. - Gesiena, Hesse, Einden.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Nov.;lsaac da Costa, Klein, Batavia via Brouwersh. - Rotterdam, S., Midd. Zee. - Catharina Lonisa, v. Aalst, Gibraltar. - Vereeniging, v. Duffelen, Lissabon. - Orion, Buiten, Nantes. - Admiraal Ver- Heull, S., Havre. - Maria Stuart, S, Leith. - Albert, S., Huil. BRIELLE, 30 Nov.; Prins yan Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Ravensbnry, S-, Harwich. BREMERHAVEN, 29 Nov.; Compagnie, Nett, Amsterdam. - Agatha, Wortel, Groningen. ELSENEUR, 26 Nov.; Elisabeth, Nepperus, Petersburg n. Aberdeen. COLCHESTER, 28 Nov., zeilkl.: Jantina, Lohman, Dantzig n. Londen.- Margrietha Hendrika, de Boer, Newcastle. HULL, 28 Nov.; Wicherdina, Dijken, Sevilla. CROMARTY, 27 Nov.; Diana.Kraan, Sunderland. ROCHESTER, 28 Nov.; John and Charles, Charlton, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 28 Nov., zeilkl.: Anna, Hoetjer, Civita Vocchia. WORKINGTON, 30 Nov.; Vartry, S., Rott. ANTWERPEN, 30 Nov.; Martha, Topzant, Bremen. GIBRALTAR, 17 Nov., zeilkl.: Eltica Meezenbreek, Vegter, t*en na. - Clio, Roskamp, Fernambuck. —20 Nov.; Le», Jongebloed &quot;Ancona. CADIX, 15 Nov.; Hollander, Kruyt, Montevideo. - Maria Margaretha, SURINAME, 27 Oct.; Martina Adriana, van &apos;t Hoff, Amsterdam. SAMARANG, 11 Oct.; Dageraad, Dninker, Nederlana.</p>
</text>
