<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Junij; Violet, Narnn, Sunderl. - Alida, van eter Veen, Archangol. - 3 Brödre, Ivensen, Fredcrikst. - Christiaao, Niclscn, Osterriisoer. VLIE, 21 Junij; rere de Familie, le Vieux, Newc. - Céline Amada, Legain, id. - Hclena Christina, Leurs, id. - Zwaluw, de Boer, Arch. - Renska. Voogdt, Riga. - Dina, van der Lcij, Sundswall. - Antina, Leewog, Stettin. - Neptunus, van Gorkum, Rcndsburg. - Terra Nova, Abel, Fredcrikst. - Amsterdam, S., Hamb. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 22 Junij; Almonde, Pijl, Batavia, via Brouwershaven. - County of Lanark, Battersby, Glasgow. - Wilhelmina Adriana, Bot, New-Castle. - Familictrouw, Woortmau, id. - Nijverheid, Schaap, id,-Adlcr, iStröm, id. - Johanna, Luther, id, - Courier, Meuldijk, Sunderland. - Albcrt, S. Huil. - Sprnijt, Pott, Petersb. - Jacoba Alida, v. d. Laan, Riga.-Magdalena, Bruining, id. - Cornelia, Jager, id. - Old Ambt, Schotema, id. - Johanna Paulina, Wcssels, id. -Concordia, Knijpenga Jzn., Stockholm. -Ernst, Midialis, Stettin. - Thetis, de Zeeuw Baggus, Tromsoe - Herman Wedel, Kjiir, Holmstrand. - Nidelvcn, Holst, id. * Hammonia, S. Hamburg. BRIELLE, 22 Junij; Admiraal Vcr-Huell, S., Havre. - Prins van Oranje. S., Duinkerken. - Waterl.o, S., Londen. - Amant, Pederson, Newc. - Pacific, S., Harwieh. - Elisa, dc Boer, Archangel. - Anna, Hoekstra, Heppeus. - Etta, Freeseman, Avontuur. MAASSLUIS, 22 Junij; Hcnriette, Johnson, Newc. - Christian, Johnson, Hartlepool. - Horta, Ridder, Shields. - Albion, Mullenst, Yormouth. - Jacobina, Poelman, Archangel. - Zcba, Pedersen, Stavangcr. - Anna, Albers, Hcppens. - Aspirant, Hcillesen, Armsburg. - Algemeen Belang, Deineke, de Noordzee. - Catharina, Drok, Avontuur. - Blyham, Lunsing, id. DANTZIG, 19 Junij; Catharina Elisabeth, Lever, Grimsby. ODENSEE, 9 Junij; Caroline Marie, Rode, Nederland. — 12 Junij; Nooit gedacht, Bakker, id. PAR, 19 Junij; Auspicious, Langard, Dordtrecht. HULL, 20 Junij; Emilie, Jager, Christiania. - Anna, S., Bergen. CARDIFF, 19 Junij; Diana, Kraan, Hamburg. SHIELDS, 20 Junij; Eliza fr Mary, ..... Dordt. GENT, 21 Junij; Harmonie, Lange. Avontuur. BORDEAUX, 20 Junij; Rozinante, Zomerdijk, Tampico. VILLA REAL, 10 Junij; Wesp, Zomerdijk, Faro. KONSTANTINOPEL, 22 Mei; Wilsons, Rich, Amst.</p>
</text>
