<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>Burgerlijke _£tanö. Van 6 tot en met 13 Augustus 1868. BEVALLEN: C. Niemeijcr, geb. van der Weyden, D. —,J. M. Susan, geb. Meijer, Z. — 11. G. «an de Laar, geb. van Moerkerken, Z. — M. J. Staats, geb. Lokkers, Z. — L. Pardon , geb. Stek weg, Z. —C. Langezaal, geb. Wellaard , Z. — S. Vallcnlgoed, geb. Collel, I). — G. M. Maarlense, geb. Gans, D. — C. Sierag, geb. Erades, D. — J. Dubbeldeman, geb. Duiveman, Z. — G. Braxhonn, geb. Lepelaar, Z. — M. J. Pont, geb. Lenzen , Z. — M. C. Ketienis, geb. van Zijp, D. — C. van der Huizen, geb. Groenendijk, D. —J. van Wijk, geb. Stephanus, Z. — J. M. J. Sciaroni, geb. Schretlen , D. — C. Zaalberg, geb. Iloogendoorn .Z.— S. H. Hoek, geb. Hoog, Z. —C. Rodenburg, geb. van der Poel, D. — 11. E. Robyn , geb. Frankhuizen, D. —- E. A. Frank , geb. Schrender, D.— J. Bolslier, geb. Kenbeek, Z. —J. Tegelaar, geb. van den Ouweelen, Z. —J. Simons, geb. Breedeveld, D. —T. van der Staay, geb. van der Pol, D. GEHUWD. J. Bink, wed&apos;, en J. P. de Lange,jd. —J. H. Rozier, wed.en 1.11. Raars. jd. — P. J. Bolslier ,jm. en C. J. Jonker, jd. — 11. van Toorn, jm. «n J. C. Boom , jd. — W. van Gasteren, jm. en P. M. van Maassen, jd. — W. Latnan, wedI*, en J. Jongkind!, jd. — A. W. Randoe.jm. en 11. .1. C. Halderiet, jd. — W. H. Jongmans, jm.en A. E. M. Verbrugge, jd. — J.J. Hnygens.jm. enT.J. Koenen, jd. —A. L. Reimeringer,jtn. en J. F. 11. Reuier, jd. OVERLEDEN: M. 11. Kiel, D., 8 m. — A. Vink, 43 j. — D. van der Linden, Z.|2jm. —J. Stouien, D.,8 m. —H. Verhoeven, D.,5 ui. —F. M. Meerburg, D.,l}j. — J.F. Montaiius, Z.,2m. — M. L. Dcc, D..22J. — D. J. Versluis, D.,3m. — S. van Dissel, wed. A. Frankluiyzen, 71 j. — L. Gaykema, Z.,&apos;l j. «i 7 tn. — P. J. A. Bronsgeest, Z., 10 m. — E. G. Wyzenfeld , D., 17 j. —S. &apos;an Meygaarden, Z.,5 m. —J. Ouwerkerk ,46 j.— W.van der Vos, D.,3 m. — H. E. Pech, wed. J. vanden Burg, 66 j. — C. C. deNie, D., 2j. en 3 m. — J. Sinleur, D.,2m. — Il.Tuurenhout, Z., ruim 3m. —C. Heymans, D.,2 m. — •l.&apos;an Duuren , D., ruim 3m.•— J. Korenhof, D., ruim 10 m. —A. M. Pommee, D.l j. _p. C. Hakkeuberg,Z.,sm.— L.P. Schollen, Z., 3m. — M.C. Harlog of Hertog, geb. van der Linden, 74 j. - - A. M. Plyfler, D., 10 m. — P.C. Webbers, geb. Britiyn, 36 j. —W.H. J. van Es, D., 14 j.</p>
</text>
