<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Ang.; Havana Packet, de Boer, Havana.-Perseverance, Elliott, Londen. - Marsden, Dybell, Newc. - Swan, Annison, id.- Caradoc, 0., Sunderl. - Allport, Amon, id. » Zenobia. Child, Yarmouth. - Flora, Nyman, Sundswall. - Cliristiane Sophie, Bruun, id. - Alice, Oelsen, Oostzee. - New Scotia, Bruun, Frederikstad. - Deodata, Holst, id. - Jorgen Lorentzen, Kjduiug, 1 Irammen. - Petrus, Johnsen,id.- Dam, Hausen, id. - 6 Söstre, Erichsen, Noorwegen. - Belfast Lass, Nichols, Maassluis. - Rebccca, Dam, Avontuur. VLIE, II Aug.; Stoomvaart, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 11 Aug.; Prins &apos;van Oranje, S., Duinkerken.- Seftj-ull, S.. Huil.-William Coleman. S. Goole. —12 Aug.;Claymore, Hadden, Otago. - Feijenoord, S., Lon-len. -Seabird, Nuttall, Jersey.- Johan, Cliristiansen, Berwick. - Jnpiter, Peters, Riga. - Junior, Gram, Elsêneur.- Noordster, Schaap, Frcderikst.- 12Briidre,Buil,id.-Marie Coralie, Bakker, id. - Merwestroom, de Ligny, Bergen. -Clio, Tobiassen, I-J ooi-wegen. - Constance, Maheo, Hcppens. BRIELLE, 12 Aug.;Bradford, S., Grimsby. MAASSLUIS, 12 An-?.; Maris Stella.Blaiichert, Neweastle.-Remen- Dranche, Profit, id. -Diana, lbschen,id. - Waterwichs, Bonghe.id. - James, Wade, id. - Bose, Ollive, id. - Edith, S., Huil.- Mary &amp; Arm, Richardson, id. . Jane, Rowland, Sunderland. -Leo,Robertson.Seaham. - Otto, Itasinussen, Hartlepool. - Roseland, Barn, Stockton.-MargaretMilne, Morek, Christiania. - Patriot, Midbie, Skudeness. - Hendrika, Plukker, Elsêneur. - Johanna Maria, Fcnega, Avontuur.-Catharina, Bekkering.id. I&apos;RAVEMUNDE, 10 Aug.; Nachina Laminechina, Rijnberg, de Oostz. SWINEMUNDE, 9 Aug -, Vier Gezusters, Wagenmakur, Bremen. DANTZIG, 9 Aug.; Christine, Bruhu, Amsterdam. SARPSIIORG. 1 Aug.; JanHs, Sorensen, Nederland. TONNINGEN, 9 Aug.; Geertrnida, Rasker,Dantzign. Amst.- Allegonda Magrieta, Gort, VVolgast naar Maldon. - Catharina Margaretha Riebeling. Rostock n. Hamburg. LONDEN, 11 Aug.; Catharina, Boon. Kroonstad.- Grietje, Lukkien, id. DEAL, 10 Aug.; Rota, Hausschel, Bat. «&apos;IIAUI.KSTOWN. 10 Ang.; Maroim,Kuiper, Wadsoe. St. MA WES, 10 Aug.; Juhus, Grocnewoldt, Greenock. FALMOUTH, 9 Aug.; Sirius, Doewes, Liverpool.-ElsinaGeertrtiida, Mulder, Dublin. - Vooruitgang, Lukeus, Stokholni. - de Zwerver, Hagedoorn. Londen. WORKINGTON, 9 Aug.; Jantina, Tak, Riga. - Drie Gebroeders, Feninga. id. GRIMSBY, 10 Aug.; Agina Undina, Brouwer, Petersburg.- Geertrnida * emina, Bakker. Nerva. SUNDERLAND, 9 Aug.; Hawthorn, Truttles, Rott. - Port Wallace, kayers, Nieuwe Diep. - Sultana, Bell, id.</p>
</text>
