<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL 13 Oct.; Nicot, Amesz, Bat. vertr. 20 Junij. - Fanny, Wuift, id. - Verwisseling, Boon, Ibraïla. - Alert, S., Huil. (Benevens het schip per - telegr. gemeld). „ „ „ . VLIE, 12 Oct.; Zenobia, Child, Yarmouth. - Jonge Pieter, Colle, Petersburg. - Foreningen, Larsen, Riga. - 3 Gebroeders, Feninga, id. — 13üct.; Seenymph, Held, Bremen. -:&apos; AMELAND, 8 Oct; Gesina, Boeker, Hamburg. —9 Oct.; Sieier,Beents, id.-Dirkje,Poort,Bremen. OSTMAHORN, 9 Oct.; Adonis, Boeking, Maldon, als bijlegger. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Oct,; Normantum, Kingman, Caüao, laatst v. Brouwershaven. - F. W. Gnade, Gehni, Ibraila.- Esperanza, Brahms.Licata, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Feyenoord, S., Londen. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Anna, b., Bergen. -Voor Pampus ten anker: St. Jan, Lonimerse, Ba&apos;avia. BRIELLE, 13 Oct.; Leo, S., Londen. - Orion, S., id. - Zealous, 0., BROUWERSHAVEN, 13 Oct.; Lammiena Elizaboth, Pott, Bat. n. Rott. vertr. 14 Junij. - Goffredo, Gallas,Enos n.id. BREMERHAVEN, 11 Oct; Catharina Cornelia, Borst, Petersb. HAMBURG, 12 Oct.; Hambourg, S., Havre. - Goedo \ erwachtmg, Mulder, Bremcrh. - Anna Maria Henriette, de Jong, Porto Cabello. - Lucia Hendrika, Dekker, Malaga. &apos; . , ,„ STA VANGER, 10 Sept.; Oernen, Lindtner, Schiedam. - CortAüler, Arhjürnsen, id. — 13 Sept.; Avance, Nygaard, Rott. BERGEN, 23 Sopt.; Merwestroon, de Goede, Dordt. i CHRISTIANIA, 29 Sept; Wilhelm Carl, Gudmundsen, Harl.-30 bept.; Helga, Nielsen, id. — 3 Oct.; Fórtuna, Andcrsen, Amst. - Alida, Feiken, Delfzijl. - Sophie, Hansen, Petersburg. . - &apos; KOPENHAGEN, 10 Oct.; Albertina, Scherpbier, Maroim. - Columbus, Zomerdijk, Petersburgn. Londen. . ? &apos;? , Bij KOPENHAGEN, 10 Oct; Venus, Anthomssen, Petersb. n. bchied. KIEL, 11 Oct.; Jantina, Blaak, Stettin. . STETTIN, 10 Oct.; Concordia, Naatje, Dordt. - Etta Johanna, bronewold, Amst. -Catharina, Westerhrink, Bremen. BOLDERA, 7 Oct; Zorgvlied, Garnaat, Rott. HERNOSAND, 23 Sept.; Europa, Olsen, Nederl. KROONSTAD, 11 Oct.; Wilhelmina, Swart, Amst. HELSINGFORS, 26 Sept.; Rapide, Anderson, Amst. ELSENEUR, 10 Oct.; Gepasseerd: Wicherdina, van Dijken, Nerva n. Huil. - Lambertha, Hitman, Dantzig n. Grimsby. HOLTENAU, 8 Oct.; Gepasseerd: Christina Wubbegma, van der Werp, Faxoe h Amst -Trientje Meiju-.Tonkens, Stettin n. Groningen, • Geerdma, Krook, Stolpenmnde n. Zwolle. - Dieverdina, de Jonge, id. n. id. — 10 Oct.; &apos;t Huis Garrelsweer, Vink, Petersburg n. Bremen. — 11 Oct; Alida bara, Mooi, id. n. de Weser. SUNDSWALL, 19 Sept.; Mercur, Zermchow, Nieuwe Diep. - Hedwig, Torgesen, id. - Pax, Krijger, id. — 23 Sept.; Caroline, Abrahamsen, Delfzijl. LONDEN, 12 Oct.; Lucia Jantina, Liel&apos;fijn, Genua. - Anna Gesina, barrels, Anclani. DEAL 12 Oct.; Elisabeth&apos;Rönneberg, Donesen, Santos n. liott. Bij WIGHT, 10 Oct.; Ouderkerk a./d. Amstel, Dingemans, Rott. n. Bat. FALMOUTH, 12 Oct.; Jantina Alida, Pybes, Venetië. GRIMSBY, 10 Oct.; Aphrodite, Roostee, Dan&apos;zig. HARWICH 11 Oct.; Zaanstroom, Visser, Amst. - Harmma, van der Meulen, Groningen n. Londen. - Twee Broeders, Kempema Workum n.id. ALLOA 9 Oct.; Grietje Tersman, Rasker, Grangemouth. - Jonge Lietfert Bakker, id. — 10 Oct.; Margaretha, Huizinga, Antwerpen. MISTLEY, 11 Oct.; Anna Gesina, de Vries, Engclholm. SHIELDS, 11 Oct.; Anneehina Henriette, van der Meulen, Lynn. - Nicoaas, Rijft&apos;, Harlingen. YARMOUTH, 11 Oct.; Edelme, Ibsen, Hoorn. YARMOUTH (wiqht), 11 Oct.; Index, Long, Amst. n. Dublin. GRANTON, 8/9 Oct.; Mary, Mouldsen, Leith n. Rott. SWANSEA, 11 Oct.; Masonio, Lonford, Schiedam. NAI&apos;ELS, 0 Oct.: Rhóne, S., Kotterdam. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 13 Oct.; Minister van Staat Roehusson, Kayser, Bat. - Magnet, S.. Londen.&apos;- Hollander, S., Huil. „&apos;-&apos;&apos;, VLIE 12 Oet -Theresia, Schulte,Riga.-Embla, Christensen, Drammen.- Thetis,Matthisen,id. - Hendrik Jan Nassau, Roelfsema, Avontuur. — 13 Oct.; Willem, Kröger, Hamburg. AMELAND, 7 Oet.; Hilke de Vries, Katt, Heppens.—9 Oct.; Ahida Ikca, Tonningen. - Heinrlch, Luken, Altona. - Margaretha, Strohschmeder, id.-Étticna,Heinrichs,Elmshorn. OSTMAHORN, 11 Oct.; Immanuel, Strackholder, Avontunr. — 12 Oct.; 4 Gebroeders, Heida, Denemarken, Catharina, Ewen, Makkum n. Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Oct.; Wilhelmina, v. d. Weyden, Gibraltar. - Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Tweed, Woodburn, Mnldlesbro.-Melby, Edwards, Sunderl. - Cornelia, v. d. Velde, Stettin. - Edith Owen, S., id.- Hillechina, Pott, id. - Camilla, Nielsen, Frederikstad BREMERHAVEN, 12 Oet.; Geertje Dijkstra, Venn.nga, Riga. - WierdinaFokkelina.de Groot, Amst. „..„..&quot;. T. m ¦ HAMBURG, 12 Oet.; Colima, Burfemd, Makassar. - Johannes, Henning, Genua. • Elve, S., Rott. „¦¦—•&quot;, TT , „„ .-, . BERGEN, 21 Oct,; Madura, Steffens, Hamburg n. Hongkong. — 22 Oct.: Vlaardingen, Goudswaard, Nederland. — Telina, Dekker, id. - Geertiena Sprik, Riga. ? „ STETTIN, 10 Oct.; Jan Hendrik, Slager, Gron. DANTZIG 10 Oct • Jansjen, Meijer, Roven. - Martha, Postema, Dordt.- Battruida Battruida, Kladder, Amst. - Jonge Aukjen, Balk Groningen MEMEL 9 Oct.; Anja Sietzia, Huisman,Harl. - Bonna Roemelmgh, Visser Grietzijl - 4 Gebroeders, Blok, Elsfleth. - Johanna Maria, Kappen, Gran gemouth. - Saramacca, de Vries, Grimsby. - Alphard, Puister, Londen. _ BOLDERA, 8 Oct.; Hillechina Wilkens, Karssies, Elseneur. - Catharina Slinger, id. - Gertrude, Kramer, id. - Adolph, Kramer, id. KROONSTAD, 7 Oct.; Zwaluw, Blomberg, Londen. - Mmerva, Doyen id - Eendragt de Boer, Grimsby. - Wilh. Drent, Kuen Rz., Newc. - Catha rina Elisabeth, Lever, Macdnff. - Nieuwendam, de Jonge, Aberdeen. - Marii lielena, Teerling, id. - Gesina, deßoer, Amst.-Rcyna, de Jonge, id. - Nij verheid&apos;, 80.-isinga, id. - Gcertiuida Anna, Schrikkema, id. - Cappellen, Wal ker, id.&apos; - Zeevaart, Engelsman, Gron. - Johanna Maria, Fenonga, Dordt. Keiuia; Zeeman, Leer. - Louisa Geerdiena, Wever, Kopenh - Hesperus Jiolsch&apos;er, id. - Gerharda Hendrika, Glim, Kiel. - Cornelia Jacoba, van de &quot;&apos;&apos;-Teer Koningsbergen. &quot; SUNDSWALL, 18 Sept.; Paul Fredrik, Naess, Nederland. — 19 Sept IHvfrnen, Backe, id. — 21 Sept.; Ambrosia, Buil, id. — 22 Sept.; Titanis LONDEN, 12 Oct. Zeilklaar: Jauntje Martens, Ates, Rostok.- Astrei Ileikema, Cette. - Ulrika, Dik, Avontuur ROCHESTER.iI Oct.; Alida Dijk, de Haas, Gron. „.-._. VLYMOUTH, 12 Oet.; Herman, Nieboer, Kroonstad. - Maria, Koste Dantzig. , . DUBLIN,II Oct.; Naphtali, Jones, Dordrecht. LIVERPOOL, 11 Oct.; Arm Beer, Hansen, Dordrecht. GLASGOW, 10 Oct.; Aquarius, Altmann, Demerary. BALTIMORE, 26 Sept.; Isabella C. Joncs, Shaw, Rott. . SHANGHAE, 5 Aug.; Argonaut, Drayer, Luzon.</p>
</text>
