<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 9 April; Zireon, Prentiee, Santos, 1. v. Falniouth HELLEVOETriLUIS, 9 AprH; Constancc, Coucli, Nantès -Anna Dofl&apos; wes, Rédon.-Leo, Robertson, Sunderland.-Seahoi.e, S., Hull.-llammonia S* Hamburg. BRIELLE, 9 April; Levant, S., Havre.- Prins van Oranje S Duinkerk.&apos; Cologne, S., Londen.-Norfolk, S., Goole.-Colletis, S., Goole. BREMERHAVEN, 8 April; Catharina Maria, de Roth, Amst HAMBURG, 7 April; Tietje, Visser, Delfzijl.&apos; CUXHAVEN, 7 April; 3 Gebrüder, Kat, Rott. — 8 April Cycloop, S- Messina. - Elve, S., Rott. - Adclaidc, de Haan, Malaga &apos; EMDEN, 4 April; Ebonezcr, Mudder, Gron. AARHUUS, 30Maart; Catharina, ..., Dokkum. ELSENEUR, 6 April; gepasseerd : Dina, van der Loy en Hercule* Mooi. TONNINGEN,. 5 April; Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Amst n Aarhiutf-&apos; Tncntje Meijer, Tonkens, Dokkum n. Kopenhagen. - Bvka, Gort Amst- o- Aarhuus. LONDEN, 8 April; Maria Beerta, Roosjes, Groningen. Bij DEAL, 7 April; Hendrika Margaretha, Freye, Rott. n Bari Bij het NOORD-VOORLAND, 7 April; Vriendschap, Elles, Amst. &quot;• Bordeaux. Bij DUNGENESS, 6 April; Burgemeester Dannenberg, Visser Groei&quot;&apos; genn. Bristol. Bij PORTLAND, 7 April; Arm. Hermina, Stuitvoet, Amst. n Nantes. Bij PLYMOÜTH, 6 April; Sopliie, Collberg, Java n. Amst. ROCHESTER, 7 April; Dina Adriana, Kwint, Portland. LIVERPOGL, 7 April; in lading: Jantina, Douwes, Petersburg DUNDEE, 7 April; Zeeploeg, Luders, Londen. SANDWICH, 4 April; Anna, ..., Groningen CIIARLESTOWN, 6 April; Hordaland, olseii, Rotterdam. HARWICH, 7 April; Vr. Geertruida, Heyinga, Groningen SUNDERLAND, 6 April; Bermuda, Cliappcl, Rotterdam MIDDLESBRO, 7 April; Cornelia, Fagge, Rotterdam. SHIELDS, 7 April; Iduna, Trapp, Amst. - de Zwaan, Ricdijk, Dorilf;&apos; Christina Jacoba, de Groot, Schiedam. - Leo Smni&lt;?e Karsies id - Ma&apos;&apos;9&apos; Pronk, Delfzijl. BORDEAUX, 5 April; Dankbaarheid, Lover, Cardiff. - Catharina J°&apos; hanna, Mulder, Ardrossan. BATAVIA, 15 Febr.; Maria Anna, van Monnom, Rotterdam —17 &quot;s&amp;&quot;* Drie Gezusters, Fiseher, Amsterdam. - Jacob, Mulder, Rotterdam - Ö6&quot;&apos; rietto Elisabcth Susanna, Meybo&apos;om, id.—lB Febr.; Baron van Hardenui&apos;&lt;&quot;*&apos; van Rossuin, Kaap do Goede Hoop. - Admiraal PietHein Priebee Amst-&quot;&apos; 20 Febr.; Ida Maria de Raath, de Boer, Rott, — 21 Febr ■ Hercules Det«f&apos; ding, Liverpool. — 23 Febr.j d« Hoop, van Duyn, Nagasaki. STRAAT SUNDA, 14 Febr.; Jan van Galen, Braat, Rott. n. Singapore Christina Maria, de Veer, Newcastle n. Cheribon. — 16 Febr.; Ellina, La&apos;&quot;&apos; mers, Rangoon n. Hongkong. - Alexander, Dekker, Boston n. Batavi*&apos; Singapore, Stoop, Rot&apos;, n. Singapore- Cornelia Hendrika, van Straat6* Newcastle n. Tagal. - Celebes, Reuvekamp Giïle, Amst. n. Socrabaya. SOERABAYA, 9 Febr.; Nieuwe Waterweg, van Linden] Rott, SUMANAP, 7 Febr.; Stad Enschede, Kretschmer, Maeao &apos; MACASSAR, 28 Jan.; St. llclena, Pille, Soerab., laadt voor Macao;</p>
</text>
