<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 24 Maart; Jacoba Cornelia, Jansen, Batavia, vertr. 26 Nov.- Ondine, S., Bordeaux. - Lambton, S., Sunderland. - Alert, S., Huil. - Henrietta, Kjöele, Christiania. - Drammen, Frost, Drammen.- Familicn,Andréassen,id. YLIE, 23 Maart; Boreas, Munneke, Newcastle. HELLEVOETSLUIS,24 Maart; Sophia Amalia,Lourens, Batavia vertr. 10 Nov. - Cortgene, Schey, Banjoewangie 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Brederodo, Kruimel, id. 1. v. id. vertr. 9 Nov. - Cornelia, S., Midd. Zee. - Hollander, S., Bordeaux. - John &amp; Charles, Thomson, Rochester. - Gazelle , Seagcr, Sho~ reham. - Thomas Varcoe, Couth, Par. - Arm Davies, Davios, PortMadoc. - Thetis, Butterill, Newcastle. - Elizabeth Mary, Jameson, id. - Belladona, Copland, id. - Van, Thompson, id. - Princess, Parker, id. - Hubertus Pearson, Sunderland. - Betsy, Mordey, id. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Eagle, Hawkius Ipswicii.</p>
	<p>BRIELLE, 24 Maart; de Maas, S., Londen, is derwaarts teruggekeerd - Albert, S., Huil.- Zealous, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 24 Maart; de schepen per telegram . VLISSINGEN, 24 Maart; het schip per telegram gemeld. BERGEN, 4 Maart; Aaltje Willemina, Jurrema, Dundee. SE AFORD, 22 Maart; Henricus Gerardns, vau der Zee, Padan* n Amst. Bij MUMBLES, 22 Maart; Gesina, Gortmaker, Port Talbot n Vmenh EXMOUTH, 22 Maart; Secundus, Rozema, Groningen. . LIVERPOOL-, 22 Maart. In lading: Sappsmeer, Rosenberg Porto Cabcllo. °</p>
	<p>DUBLIN, 22 Maart; Agatha, .... Odcasa. CHARLESTON, 21 Maart; Columbus, Zomerdijk, Bnrnt Island. - de Sperwer, Schaap, Harlingen. - Drie Zusters, Dijkstra, id,-Hillochina, Seherphuis, Delfzijl.</p>
	<p>FRASËRBURGH, 20 Maart; Maria, Krohn, Dordrecht. ABERDEEN, 21 Maart; Hendrika Magaretha, Stel, Amst. SHIELDS, 22 Maart; Harmonie, de Weerd, Harlingen. - Broedertrouw, Vos, Leer. - Jenne Nollen, de Goede, Rott,- Gesina Hendrika, , Col • eb 68 ter HARTLEPOOL, 21 Maart; Crown, Filleul, Amst. — 22 Maart; Jacoba Margaretha, Rozenveld, Christiansand. DARTMOUTH, 21 Maart; Gesina Antina, van Klooster, Gron. HARWICH, 22 Maart; Zwaantina Margaretha, de Vries, Dovern, .... ANTWERPEN, 21 Maart; Nicolaas Albert, de Jonge, Buenos-Ayres. HAVRE, 21 Maart; Levant, S., Rott. BORDEAUX, 22 Maart; Vertrouwen, Moesker, Amst. CAMARET, 19 Maart; Maris Stella, Blanchet, Redon n. Rott. —• 20 Maart; Venise, Guehet, Nantes n. id. - Sarcelle, Lancelot, id. n. id. MARSEILLE, 22 Maart; Thorbecke, Witting, Bahia. SANTANDER, 20 Maart :in lading: Remda, Bakker, Antwerpen. GIBRALTAR, 11 Maart; Thetis, Baggus, Palermo. - Courrier, v. Vliet, id. (vertr. beiden n. Vlaardingen) — 14 Maart; Fennechina, Koetze, Triest. - Hendrika, Visser, id. (vertr. beiden n.Eernambuck). - Sirene, Bradhering, id. (vertr. h. Bordeaux). — 16 Maart; Irene, S., Amst. (vertr. n. Genua). TRIEST, 18 Maart; Juffer Zwanette, Pekelder, Amst. NEW-YORK, 11 Maart; in lading: Emil, Borman, Amst. - Magdalena, Henke, Rott.</p>
</text>
