<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 Sept., W. Z. W.; Messenger, Pommery, Taganrog. - Andreo, Ladanza, Alicata. - Indian, Prowcliffe, Newc. - Noordster, Niemann, Archangel. - Bjarke, Rasmussen, id. - Familien, Andreassen, Drammen. VLIE, 6 Sept., Z. W.; Zwerver, Visser, Petersburg. - Aaltje, Hoedemaker, Riga. — 7 Sept.; Christina, Staal, id. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. ZOLTKAMP, 4 Sept.; Jorgen Oben, Boije, Archangel. — 5 Sept.; Wilhelmiua, de Jonge, Flensburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Sept., W.—W. Z. W.; L. J. Enthoven, Koens, Bat. 1. v. Brouwersh. - Annie Fleming, Watson, Akyab 1. v. id. - Alexander 11, Linorollo, Taganrog 1. v. id. - Julia, Jacobsen, Girgenti 1. v. id. - Cycloop, S., Middell. Zee 1. v. id. - Osborne, S., Leith. BRIELLE, 7 Sept, W.—Z.; Edith, S., Huil; den Bsten Sept. derwaarts teruggekeerd. — 8 Sept.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken.-Waterloo, , Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 7 Sept, W.; Tolriodsende, Mathiassen, Grimstad. — 8 Sept; Margareth, Emmerson, Newc. n. Dordt. - Minerva, S., Rott. n. Hamb.; heeft de reis voortgezet. BREMERHAVEN, 7 Sept; Dirktje, Poort, Amsterdam. Op de ELVE, 6 Sept.; Friesland, Sipkes, Akyab. - Cathariiia (Ned. kof), Londen. — 7 Sept; Amsterdam, S., Amsterdam. - Verdandi, Lofquist, Soerabaya. BOLDERA, 31 Aug.; Lucas Wildervank, Ricks, Bumt Island. - Mentor, Schuring, Duinkerken. — 1 Sept.; Ida, van der Molen, Dockum. —2Sept; Hester, de Jong, Schiedam. ULEABORG, 16 Aug.; Waterloo, Rodenburg, Vlaardingen, (23 dezer il6r\v_i_irts zoilkliiüT.. LAURVIG, 28 Aug.; Trekvogel, Heikema, Delfzijl. — 29 Aug.; Jan Gijsbert, Smit, Termunterzijl. DRAMMEN, 26/29 Aug.; Lymfa, Allurn, Purmerend. ARENDAL, 27 Aug.; Anna Margaretha, Hoekstra, Petersburg. LONDEN, 6 Sept.; Catharina, uilenburger, Rio-Grande. DEAL, 6 Sept.; Sirius, van Wijngaarden van Rees, Amst. n. Batavia. — 7 Sept.; Bristolian, White, Rott. n. Cardiff. Bij NOORD-VOORLAND, 6 Sept.; Bellatrix, Haacke, Amst. n. Soerab. PORTLAND, 6 Sept.; Pleiaden, de Jonge, Amst n. Buenos-Ayres. In het KANAAL, 3 Sept.; Oceanus, Springer,...&apos;_. Cardiff. WIGHT, .. Sept; Elise Susanna.jNidschelra, Rott. n. Genua. MARGATE, 6 Sept; ter reede: Johanna Elisabeth,Valom, Rott. n. San Sebastian.</p>
	<p>AYR, 6 Sept.; Klasiua, Dik, Dantzig. GLASGOW, 6 Sept.; Pavadette, Pot, Ibraila. LIVERPOOL, 7 Sept; in lading: Macassar, den Exter van den Brink, Onrust (Java). IPSWICH, 6 Sept; Eagle, Hawkins, Rott. SUNDERLAND, 5 Sept; Sultana, Bell, Rott. — Sophie, Johansen, Dordrecht. - Hendrika, van der Veen, Londen.</p>
	<p>SHIELDS, 6 Sept.; Victoria, Schultz, Rott.- Sancto, Nelson, id.-Catharina Rucardi, Meijer, Groningen. - Martha, Topzant, Delfzijl.- Jane, Eobson, Nieuwediep. - Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Harlingen. - Burgemeester van Setten, Holvast, Antwerpen. NEW-YORK, 25 Aug.; Europa, Hauseu, Manilla.—26 Aug.; Baltiraore, Meijer, Rott. SAN FRANCISCO, 4 Aug.; Japara, Laversteyn, Hongkong. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 8 Sept, W. Z. W.j Bérénice, S, Middell. Zee. - Whim, Smitb, Yarmouth.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 6 Sent, Z. W.—W.; Gebroeders, Loodijzen, Petersb. — 7 Sept; Piet Hein, Meijer, id. -Remelia Geertruida, de Boer, Sundswall.-Anna Luitzia, Jager, Frederikstad, — 8 Sept.; Alfen, Strömsten, Wasa. - To Sodskende, Svane, Christiania. - Varigt Venskabet, Dahl, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Sept, W.-.W. Z. W.; Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Annie, S., Goole. - Bradford, S., Grhiisby. - Levant, S., Gothenburg. BRIELLE, 7 Sept,, W.-Z.; Avalon, S., Harwich. BRAKE, 7 Sept.; Anja, Meijer, Avontuur. HARBURG, 6 Sept.; Hendrika Jeltina, Lukkien, Rott. D ANTZIG, 5 Sept; Herstelling, Lukkien, Petersburg. - Amicita, Gortemaker, Sunderland. WIJBURG, 17 Aug.; Martha Theresia, Visser, Purmerend. LONDEN, 6 Sept; Vertrouwen, Moesker, Elseneur. - Mentor, Toering, Worcum. PLYMOUTH, 4 Sept.; Seanymph, Cobden, Amst. ABERDEEN, 6 Sept.; Hendrika Margaretha, Freye, Peterhead. GLASGOW, 6 Sept.; Paulus Meintz, Vonema, Port au Prince. FORTRESS MONROE, 25 Aug.; Anton , Rott. BALTIMORE, 24 Aug.;Louis, ... „Rott.</p>
</text>
