<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 26 Julij; Jane &amp; Arm, Hoeken, Galatz. - Titia Susanna, Potjer Nerva. - Helge Eleonora, Aabeye, Drammen. - Wilhelmina, Nielsen, Porsgrund. — 27 Julij; Fosea Helena, Ridder, New-York. - Lion, S., Londen. - Middlesbro&apos;, S., Middlosbro. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Enigheden Jacob.«en, Drammen.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 26 Julij; 1 _x, Mellema, Memel.- Elora, Tonnc-sen, Koningsbergen. Jonge Jaeob, Hernam, Erederikstad. - 4 Gebroeders, Woudstra, Christians HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Julij; Zephyr, S„ Londen.- Sara, S., id.- Holyrood, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc.</p>
	<p>BREMERHAVEN, 26 Julij; Juliane, Oltmanns, Amst. - Twee Gezusters, Geltes, Groningen.</p>
	<p>ELSENEUR, 21 Junij; Gepasseerd: Kong Sverre, Walloe, Riga n. Amst. Cornelia, S., Rott. n. Petersburg. - Leonida, Bredenberg, N. Diep n. Sundswal. - Christine, Harris, id n. id. - Zeelust, Eeun, Harlingen n. Dantzig. - Heinrich, Jaeobson, Rott. n. de Oostzee. - Anna, Hendrika, Ebling, id.n. id. TONNINGEN, 23 Julij; gepasseerd: Elschlea, Albers, Praestoe&apos;n. Zaandam. - Telina, Dekker, Memel n. Bremen. - Onrust, Slankenberg, Hamburg n. Koningsbergen. - Catharina, Springer, id. n. Stettin. — 24 Julij; Geertje, Parijer, Stettin n. Oldenburg.</p>
	<p>ELSFLETH, 26 Julij; Maria Edina, Hoegeman, Drammen</p>
	<p>LONDEN, 25 Julij; Eendragt, Bijkerk, Worcum. - In lading: Karsina, Okers, Amst. - Rosa, Tasker, Middelburg.</p>
	<p>Bij St. ALBANSHOOFD, 23 Julij; Arnold Böninger, Steenken, Baltimore n. Rott. Bij DOVER, 24 Julij;Helena en Anna, van Aalborg, Amst. n. Bat. Bij het ZUID-VOORLAND, 25 Julij; Zeepaard, Crucq, Middelburg n. Bat. - Julius Schuurman, Amst. n. Liverpool. Pij PETERHEAD, 25 Julij; Augustina, Cheyne, Amst. n. Groenland. FALMOUTH, 26 Julij; Herstelling, Ligthart, Port au Prince. LIVERPOOL, 25 Julij; Anna Helena, Jansen, Matanioras. -Alida, Borgman, Pomaron. - Concordia, Wijgers, Groningen. DUNDEE, 25 Julij; Amicitia, Gortmaker, Koningsbergen. BERWICK, 25 Julij; Alpha, Puister, Petersburg. SUNDERLAND, 25 Julij; Betsy, Patterson, Schiedam. BELFAST, .. Julij; General Lee, S., Rott. HOLYHEAD, 25 Julij; Canulla, Sarvent, Workington n. Rott. CARDIF, 24 Julij; Anna Maria, van der Kooy, Antw. SHIELDS, 25 Julij; Cappeln, Walker, Schiedam. HARTLEPOOL, 25 Julij; Marianne, Lecurieux, Rott. OSTENDE, 26 Julij; Zeeploeg, Lodeling, Riga.</p>
</text>
