<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Nov.; Lion, S., Londen. - Perseverance, Elliot, id. - Vesper, Withe, Sunderland. - Gerberdina, Das, Archangel. - Ora en Labora, Christen&apos;sen, Gothenburg. - Haldis, Cappelen, Frederikstad. - Büyard, Christen; sen, id. - Alexandra, Hansen, id. - Westphalia Arvesen, id. ZOLTKAMP, 31 Oct.; Martha, Banting, Newcastle. VLIE, 1 Nov,; Nora, S„ Londen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Nov.; Kensington, King, Mauritius, 1. v. Brouwerhaven. - Glen Monarch, Lewis, Callao, 1. v. id. - Hooyland, Mc&apos; Kenzie, St. Mare, 1. v. Quccnstown. - Zephyr, S., Londen; - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Storm Queen, S., Hartlep. - Pleiades, Jessen, Ystad. - Harmonie, Dik, Dantzig n. Antw., als bijlegger. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Nov.; Duisburg, Holljes, Baltimore n. Rott. - Martha, Postema, Dantzig n. id., eenigzins lek, hebbende op de Middélplaat aan den grond gezeten. CUXHAVEN, 1 Nov.; Roelfina, Prins, Bremen u.Malmö.- Catharina Alida, Pronk, Newc. n. Leeuw. - Immanuel, Markmann, Bandh. n.Zaandam. BREMERHAVEN, 1 Nov.; &apos;t Huis Garreweer, Vink, Kroonstad. - Geertruida, Rasker, Hamburg. KALFSUND, 22 Oct.; Jonge Jan en Margaretha, Jelies, Amsterdam n. Kopenhagen.</p>
	<p>FREDRIKSff AVN, 26 Oct.; Vesta, S., Koningsb. n. Amst. STOLPEMUNDE, 25 Oct.; Hilke Albcrdina, do Vries, Wolgast. DANTZIG, 3&apos;&gt; Oct.; Edith Owen, S., Rott. - Maria, Koster, Toulon. ELSENEUR, 30 Oct.; gepasseerd: Arendina Jacoba, Monzes, Ara-&apos;*&apos;&quot;&apos; Windau. . , TONNINGEN, 28 Oct.; gepasseerd: Meinsina, Klontje,Kieln.OW* burg. - Arnoldus Willem Nanninga, Top, Petersburg n. Weser. — 30 0-*&apos; Harmonie, Lever, Koningsb.n. Varel. —31 Oct.; Jantje,Zuidland,An&quot;&apos; n. Lubeck. RENDSBURG, 29 Oct.; gepasseerd: Willemina, de Jonge, Koningsb &quot;* Gron. — 30 Oct.; Aurelio Gruno, Stuitje, Memel n. Harlingen. SVENDBORG.26 Oct.; Battruida, Jonkhoff, Engeland. BORGA, ...; Alka, Sjöberg, Amst. , HELSINGFORS, Aug./Oct.; Rapide, Anderson, Amst. (vertrok n. AM* Onni, Ahlberg, id. LONDEN, 31 Oct.; Diana, Jongebloed, Petchora. „, GRANGEMOUTH, 27 Oct.; Antoinette Elise, Struving, Antw.-&apos;&quot; Oct.; Amicitia, Gorteraaker, Leith. DARTMOUTH, 31 Oct.; Corinan, S., Bordeanx n. Amst. (om kolen i&quot;&quot; nemen.) SHIELDS, 31 Oct.; Wietska, Bos, Pcterhead. BELFAST, 1 Nov.; General Lee, S., Rott.</p>
</text>
