<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 Maart; Lion, S., Londen. - Swanland, S.. Huil. - Minister Thorbecke, S., id. DELFZIJL, 5 Maait-, Maria, Jungerhaus,Rheine. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Maart; Gironde, S., Bordeaux. - Zephyr, S., Londen. - Hamburg, S., id. - Lord Raglan, S„ Newc, BRIELLE, 8 Maart; Orion, S., Londen, is derwaarts teru&lt;wekeerd DEAL, 7 Maart; Kortenaar, Schuchard, Rott. n. Cardiff SOUTHAMPTON, 6 Maart; Alida Dijk, de Haas, Nederland. FALMOUTH. 6 Maart; de Vrede, Niekus, Rio-Janeiro. PLYMOUTH 6 Maart, Balmoral, S., Eott. n. Bristol. iPSWICH 6 Maart; Eagle, Hawkins, Eott. - Thames, Cracknell, id. -j?.. LJHEAP,6 Maart; fjetska, üoewes, Liverpool n. Matanzas. Bn O-LOL CESTEE, 6 Maart; Afien Smit, Boswijk, Delfzijl. RYDE. 6 Maart; A. H. Locke, Collins, Liverpool n. Dordt. SWANSEA, 5 Maart; Zeemeeuw, Bontekoe, Bamstople. SOUTHAMPTON. 6 Maart; Alida Dijk, de Haas. Nederland. BRISTOL, 6 Maart; Klasina, Brouwer, Groningen. —7 Maart; Cer| nelia, van de Velde, Antwerpen. CARDIFF, 5 Maart; Agra, Evans, Nieuwe Diep. - Lnctor &amp; Emergo, de Vries, Middelburg. LIVERPOOL. 6 Maart; in lading: Fenna Gesina, Jonker, Vera Cruz. NEW-CASTLE, 3 Maart; in lading: Twee Gebroeders, Bakker, Kiel. - ; Jeannette, Wessels. Bergen. &apos;[ NEWPORT, 5 Maart; de Sckelde, Hoffman, Amst. - Fortuna, Busch Keyzer, Liverpool n. Para, CAMARFT, 2 Maart; Cora Léon, Roussel, Vannes n. Schiedam. SUNDERLAND, 5 Maart; Reynolds, Taylor, Nieuwediep.- Betsy .Mordey, id. - Czarni, Churnside, id. - Vivid. Beddlingfield, id. - Hillechina, Hooghoudt. Alkmaar. - Froukina Hillechina, Oosterhuis, Maldon. SHIELDS. 6 Maart-, De Zwaan, Riedijk, Amst.- Claudine, Birkenhead, id, - Zoe. Proud, Rott, - Pieter, Hoogerwerf, id. - Woodhouse, Lamb, Nieuwediep. - Jeannette Marianne, Timmermans, Antwerpen. - Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, Yarmouth. - Wailaroo. Davis, Eott, - Suzanna, j Claringbold, Nieuwediep, - Maid of Perth,Mc. Nish, id. ! St. NAZAIEE, 6 Maart; Diana, Schut, Rott, • Dieverdina Alida Pot, ! Meyering. Londen, LISSABON, 2 Maart; Twee Broeders, Prins, Hnll. - Thetis, Bagges, Newcastle. GIBRALTAR, 25 Febr.; Levant, den Breems, Vlaardingen. CADIX, 2 Maart; Helena, Pybes, Cardiff. NAPELS, 8 Maart; Venus, . i3ser. Newcastle. ALICANTE. 3 Maart; Redite, Hove&apos;ing, Cardiff. BAHIA, 11 Febr.; in lading; Ida, Hazewiukel, Falmouth. - Marchina, Msppej-us.id, tt.. _-. _, „. AJf__Aß, 23 Dcc; Hebe.Kiehl, Singapore.— 8 Jan.; President Plate, Julius, id. — 20 Jan.; Diana, Teengs, Rott,-Guurtje en Maria, Flens, Singapore. (Allen laden voor Europa.) l-ANGOON, vóór 28 Jan.; D. T. Visser, v. d. Linden, Singapore (laadt voorindie. SINGAPORE 21 Jan.; Neèrlands Vlag, van den Broek Humfrey. Saigon. —22 Jan.; Mary Goddard, Nouhuys, Rott.—24 Jan.; Chewfoo, Pohl, Hongkong (vertr. 1 Febr, n. Falmouth).- 20 Jan.; Mathilda, Storm, Bat. MACASSAR, 17 Dcc; Indus, Foulard, Soerabaya (laadt voor Amst.)</p>
</text>
