<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TTr-T™,. BINNENGEKOMEN. HELLEVOETSLUIS, N. N. 0., 27 Febr.;Garibaldi, Dahlstedt, Passaroeang, 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Express, Jleldrum, Taganrog, 1. v. id.-Lord Raglan, S., Newcastle. - Thames, Crasknel, Ipswich. -Hammonia, S., Hamburg. Së^^rMvT.0,--^7 Febiv&gt; lorence, S., Londen.-Avalon,S..Harwich. ÏS9-_S-?SH^EN&apos;27 Feblv&lt;MeSLse&apos;Tiun&apos;Newcastle n.Eott. HAMbURG, 25 i ebr.; Maria, Cadee, Messina. - Elve, S., Rott. - Maria Gesina, Heimer», Londen. _£Kl£XIt^!ÜINl)&apos; 11 Febr/&gt; Thctis&apos;fle Zeewßagges, Vlaardin gen £?Pt™£AGEN&apos; n Febr-&quot;&gt; Provincie Drenthe, Westenberg, Newc ¥r.„i.(A(*&apos; ?,4 Ft&apos;br-! Phoenix, Glim, Koningsb. n. Antwerpen. VAREL, 18 Febr.; Johanna, Brouwer, Rendsburg. LONDEN, 26 Febr.; Gothenburg, S., Hamburg (laadt voorGothenb.). RAMSGATE, 25 Febr.; Antje, Scholtens, Groningen n. Homiour. TORBAY. 24 Febr.; 1 .vadette, Pott, Antw. n. Galatz. - Louise Geerdina, Wever, Amst. n. Napels. Bij de SORLINGS, 22 Febr.; Johanna Antonia,Withoff, Rott.n.Singap. SOUTHAMPTON, 25 Febr.; Concordia, Wijgers, Kusténdje. BARCELONA, 20 Febr.; Slartenshoek, Schut, NeWc, n. Slahon. LISSABON, 20 Febr.; Slorgenster, van Dijk, Oporto. ZANTE, 15 Febr.; Hendrika, Walvius, Cephalonia. KAAP HAÏTI, 19 Jan.; Geert Herwig, Pik, Port-au-Prince n. Hamburg (wegens ziekte van den kapitein). BATAVIA, 29 Dcc; Pri-ices Amalia, v. Rijn v. Alkemade, Nagasaki.— 2 Jan.; Sophia Amalia, v. Overklift, Hongkong, 6 dito n. Tjilatjap uitgeklaard. - Louis Sleijer, Holtgreve, Singapore. — 3 Jan.; Libra, Dirksen, Hongkong. — 4 Jan.; Zr. Sis. oorlog stoom-transportschip Java, kapt.- Imt.Modderman,Texel. — 5 Jan.; Zr.Sis. stoomfregatWillem, kapt. Geeriing, id. - Eipress, Kraft, Bangkok, 11 dito n. Cheribon vertr. — 8 Jan.; Cornelis Wernard Eduard, Swart, Rott, —10 Jan.; Minister Fransen v. d. Putte, Bouwmeester, id. - Jacob, Sluller Drenth, Hongkong. — 11 Jan.; Electra, Landweer, Amst. r* 12 Jan.; Henriette, Drijver, id.- Stad Leyden, van de Poll, id., 14 dito n. Samarang vertr. - Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Rott. - Diana, Teengs, Newc. - Louisa, Slellema, Slontevidoo. — 13 Jan.; Alida, Visser, Amst. - Robertus Hendrikus, Slulder, id. - Sirius, v. Wijngaarden v. Rees, id. HONGKONG, 5 Jan.; Nijverheid,&apos; Schaap, Newport. — 5 Jan.; President van Ryckevorsel, Vogelensang, Amboina. — 9 Jan.; Jacoba Cornelia, Jansen, Turon. — 11 Jan.; Henriette Elisabeth Susanna.Meijbooui, Saigon.</p>
	<p>MACAO, 30 Dec. in lading. H. Liduina, van Brink, Havana. - Onrust, Weigsenbruch, id.</p>
	<p>FOO-CHEW-FOO, 4 Jan.; Cornelia Slathilda, Wulp, Shanghae. SHANGHAE, 29 Dcc; Batavia, van Dolder, Nagasaki. — 6 Jan.; Bengalen, Hjelmström, Hongkong. MANILLA, 4 in lading : St,</p>
</text>
