<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 April; Fortuna, Nieman, Ismael. - Lucie, Malgorn, Nantes. - Ronaldus, Kilvington, Hartlepool. VLIE, 7 April • Leentje, Hoedemaker Nz., Hartlepool. - 4 Broeders, Emmelkamp, Bandholm. - Jantje Dina, Poppelmeijer, Bremen. • Willem I, S., Hamburg. AMELAND, 5 April; Rensina Willemina, Kramer, Bremen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 April; Petite Paysanne, Tesserot, Rédon. - Queen, S., Dundee. VLISSINGEN, 8 April; Lisette, Velt, Buenos-Ayres. FALMOUTH, 5 April; Maria, Scott, Bat. - Gesina, Lindeboom, Galatz. — 6 April; Marianne, Meijer, Pisagua. — 7 April; Margaretha, Boer, i have, Rio-Grande. B_ FALMOUTH, 7 April; Jeannette Marianne, Timmermans, Buenos- Ayres n. Antwerpen. Bij WIGHT, 6 Am-il; Concurrent, de Jonge. Antw. n. Montevideo. LIVERPOOL, 7 April; Doethea Christina, Poelman, Mexico. CARDEFF, 5 April; Helena Paulina, Wenk, Rott. BRISTOL, 6 April; Vigo, Farnill, Amst. MIDDLESBRO, 6 April; Gesina Jantina, Bekkering, Leer. GRANGEMOUTH, 6 April; Louise, S., Rott. IPSWICH, 6 April; Vr. Geertruida, Heijenga, Gron. NEW-CASTLE, 4 April; in lading: Mercurius, Both, Paramaribo. - De Hoop, van Gijzel, Dantzig. - Hfllechina, Gruppelaar, Koningsbergen. -Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Helsingborg. - Jacobus Anthonie, Mellcma, Kopenhagen. — 5 April; Enjetta, Boswijk, Malta en Triest.- Alida.Veen, Riga.- Belina, Pot, Malmoe. - Aikea, Dijk, Bergen. - Johanna Pctronella, Hillebrand, Kopenh. - Catharina,Wilkcns, Lissabon. SHIELDS, 6 April; Frau Maria, Voss, Amst. - Unie, Parrei, id. - Adelheid, Cramer, id. - Archimedes, Fretwurst, id. - Jan en Jacob, Burghardt, ïd. - Grietje de Weerd, Pothuis, id. - Baron van Pallandt van Rosendaal, Hoogenstraten, Rott. - Maria Reifina, de Groot, id. - Peru, Brardt, id. - Castle Eden, Hunter, id. - Zwaantje Elisabeth, Jager, Gron. - Hillechina, Brakke, Delfzijl. - Twee Gebroeders, Persoon, Middelburg. - Courier, Meuldijk, Hellevoetsluis. - Geertruida Anna, Schrikkema, Zuidbroek. - Van, Thompson, Dordt. - Prince, Parker, Schiedam. HARTLEPOOL, 5 April; Johanna, van Wijk, Middelburg. - Johanncs, Waltman, Dordr. SUNDERLAND, 6 April; Gesina, Hansen, Middelburg. - Pilos, Ogelvy, Schiedam.- Thomas, Sandersen, id. , SWANSEA, 6 April; Catharina, de Boer, Londen. BORDEAUX, 5 April; Cornelia, Teensma, Drontheim. PALERMO, 31 Maart; Rotterdam, S., Messina TTSSATtfrw l ADril-de Hoop, Ouwehand, Porto. PATRAS,I7 Maart; Argo, Brouwer,Smirna,(vert.2l damDragomcstrc.) Si. JAGO DE CUBA, 7 Maart; Marianne, Sippel, &lt;t/ar-ditl BATAVIA 15 Febr • Maria Anna, van Monnom, Rotterdam.—l7l ebr.; Drie to^F^cher Amsterdam. - Jacob Mulder,Botterdam ;;-Henriette Elisabeth Susanna, Meyboom, id.—lB ïfe^w* van Rossum, Kaap de Goede Hoop. - Admiraal PietHcm, Pnebee. Anut. ■- 20 Febr.; Ida Maria de Raath, de Boer, Rott. - 21 Febr ;_Hercules, Deterding, Liverpool. — 23 Febr.; de Hoop, van Duyn, Nagasaki STRAAT SUNDA, 14Febr.; Jan van Galen, Braat, Rott. n. Singapore.- Christina Maria, de Veer, Newcastle n. Cheribon. — 16 Febr.; Elima, i_amfflers, Rangoon n. Hongkong. - Alexandcr, Dekker, Boston n. Batavia. - Singapore, Stoop, Bot!, n. Singapore. - CorneliaHendrika, van Straaten, Newcastle n. Tagal. - Celebes, Reuvekamp Gille, Amst. n. Socrabaya. SOERABAYA, 9 Febr.; Nieuwe Waterweg, van Lindern, Rott. SUMANAP, 7 Fchr.; Start Enschedé,Kretschmer, Macao.</p>
</text>
