<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 Mei; Hensiena, Meeter, Nantes. - Vriesland, Boontje, Londen. - Frouw Dieuwke, Feenstra, id. - Europa, Zielcke, Dantzig. - Albion, Todt, id. - Urania, Svanen, Christiania. - Lympha, Allurn, Frederikstad.- Christiania, Halvorsen, Drammen, VLIË, 11 Mei; Ivanhoe, S., Leith.—l2 Mei; Laurence.Andersen, Christiania.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Mei; Orion, S., Londen. - Fern, Varnell, Workington. - Queen, S., Dundee. - Henriet, S., Middlesbro. - Seahorse S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. BRIELLE, 13 Mei; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken.- Ravensbury, S., Harwich.</p>
	<p>BEOUWEESHAVEN, 13 Mei; Three Bells, Simpson, Banjoew. n.Eott. vertr. 4 Jan. - Gijsbert Karel Graaf van Hogendorp, Fabritius, id. n. id. vertr. 29 Dec.</p>
	<p>KROONSTAD, 5 Mei; Weltevreden, Kieft, Amst. — 11 Mei; Piet Hein, Meijer, dito. C UXHA VEN, 12 Mei; Stoomvaart, S., Amst. y EMDEN, 6 Mei; Vier Gebroeders, van der Horst, Amst. - Suzanna, Barghoorn, G roningen. KIEL, 7 Mei; Reina, Kruisinga, Amst. DANTZIG, 10 Mei; Zaanstroom, Visser, Amst. - Albion, Meycring, Eotterdam.</p>
	<p>BOLDERA, 7 Mei; Jonge Lieffert, Bakker, Haugesund. — 8 Mei; Jan Visser, Boon, Bergen. — 9 Mei; Elisabeth, van Wijk, id. STOKHOLM, 5 Mei; Theodor Dill, Wulff, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN. 10 Mei; Margaretha Hendrika, Datema, Sunderl. n. Koningsb. - Jacob, Frey, Delfzijl n. de Oostzee. - Albert, Jaski, Liverpool n. Petersb. - V. endelina, Hillbrands, Sevilla n. id. Bij DEAL, 11 Mei; Wilhelmina, van der Weyden, Vlaardingen n. Gibraltar. — 12 Mei; Ten anker: Gouverneur Schomerus, Turfboer, Eott. n. de Kust van Guinea. FALMOUTH, 1&quot;, Mei; Fenneehina, Koetze, Babia. LIVERPOOL, 11 Mei; Cito, Mooi, Nantes. QUEENSTO WN, 11 Mei; Jacoba, Reinders, New-York. SHIELDS, 11 Mei; Sarah Ellen, Sainthill, Amst- Eden, Romans,Rott.- Grimaldi, HUI, Dordt. - Lucy Paul, Schut,id.- Webfoot, Sturrock, Nieuwediep. - Vr. Anna, Meuldijk, Zierikzee. - Neeltje Cornelia, Portman, Londen. SUNDEELAND, 11 Mei; Libanon, Philips, Nieuwediep. SANTANDER, 9 Mei; Klazina Jantina, Brouwer, Liverpool.-Arendina Eoelfina, Boon, id. ALICANTE, 5 Mei; Henderika, Pybes, Grimsby. LICATA, 25 April; Pomona, Haddemann, Malta. BATAVIA, 29 Maart; Dordrecht, Loos, Rott., 1. v. Portsm. STRAAT SUNDA, 24 Maart; Adriana Johanna, Nolles, Bat. n. Amst. — 29 Maart; Aria &amp; Betsy, Haverbult, Amst. n. Bat.</p>
</text>
