<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 23 Julij; Andreas Ar Caroline, Haraldsen, Sundswall. - 24 July; Triton, Andersen, id. - Carl Friedrich, Jahnke, Dantzig. VIJE, 23 Julij; Vriendschap, de Vries, Riga. ZOLTKAMP, 22 Julij;Kirstinc, Clausen, Archangel. HELLEYOETSLUIS, 24 Julij», Bittern, S.. Liverpool. - Therese.S., Granizemouth. - Cito, Tobiassen, Riga, - Margaret, Mörck, Sundswall. BBOÜWI&apos;ESHAVEN, 24 Julij; Kgrct, S.. Bolt. n. Liverpool. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 20 Julij;Geertrnida, Mandema, Petersb. - Alida Margaretha, Dik. Biga n. Dokkum. - Catharina vCalcar Meyer. id.n. Eott - Gcsina, Stenger, Schiedam n. Riga - Efcsabet 1, Steffene, Petersb. n Amst - Lucas Wildervunk, de Groot h, Antw. n. de Oostzee. &apos;BWINEMüNDE 20 Julij; Annachiena Henriétte, v.d. Meulen, Snnd BMJ_BRAA 15 Julij; 2 Gebroeders, Hillenins. Amsterdam. - Johan.a AdAmttsittes id. -Cbri-tian August, Evcnsen, Nieuwe Diep - T lieo- Aonana, oißKis, iv. &lt;-/• ... . norne ia jentsema, id. ¦ Zeeploeg, dora Lucretia Grummels, Utimy. &apos;-&apos;&quot;&apos;&quot;^, ¦ ¦_? 16 Juin» Luder, Stockholm. - Jantje Berg, van Dne-ten, Phjcrpen.- ibjuiy, Leentie, Hoedemaker, Amsterdam. — 17 Julg; -da $- Cornelia, Schenk, I Aberdeen. LONDEN, 23 July; Twee Broeders, Kempema, Worcum. - Eendragt, Smid, Stolpeinuude. FALMOUTH, 23 Julij;Nova Zembla, Mammes, Akyab. IN VEEKEITHING, 21 Julij; Hillechina, Hooghoudt, Krooustad. ALLOA, 20 Julij-, de Vlijt, Engelsman, Kirkaldy. CAEDIFF, 20 July&apos;; Amalia Ochring, Haynie, Eott. CHAELE3TOWN. 20 Julij; Jantje Tiddens, Hazewinkel, Leith. - Eiewertdina, Kievit, id. SWANSEA, 21 Julij; Collina, Gallaway, Eott. LIVEEPOOL, 22 Julij; Affghan, Fisher, Eott. YARMOUTH, 21 Jnlij; Zenobia, Child, Medemblik. WEST-HARTLEPOOL, 21 Julij; John and Mary, Walker, Nieuwed. TBOON, 23 Julij; Vertrouwen, Middel, Clyde. QUEENSTOWN, 21 Julij; Klasina,Dik, Baltimore. NEW-CASTLE, 20 July», In lading: Catharina Elisabeth, Krukkenberg, Singapore. - Leonore, Jongebloed, Cadix. - Martenshoek, Schut, Petersburg. - Eieka, Puister, Kroonstad. - Margrieta Antina, Speelman, Eendsbnrg. - Drie Gebroeders, de Groot,</p>
</text>
