<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 24 Julij; Perscverance, Elliot, Londen. - Amelia, Horrochs, Bristol. - Brittanma, Valk, Dublin. - Indus, Foulard, Newc. - Magrietha, de Vries, id. - Venskabet, Lorensen, Sundswall. - Hedvig, Torjesen, id. - Christiane, Mickelsen, id.- Valkyrien, Bjouess,Elseneur. - Nordstjernen, Christensen, Drammen. - Grevende Karen Wedel, Boed, id. - Norr, Seeberg, id. - Mindei, Arvesen, id. - Sophie, Siireusen, Tonsberg. - Skulda, Hansen, id. - Germania, Möller, Avontuur. BELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 Julij», Batavier, S., Londen. - Brothers Snccess, Hobart, Eochester. - Alexander, Larby, Oardiff. -OldGoody, Miler, Newc. - Volunteer, Purvis, id. - Geziena.&apos;Suur, Middlesbro. - I&apos;nomas Eising, Barnaby, Ipswich.- Arm White, Philips, id.- Godolevus, de Boer, Petersburg. - F. G. Schmall, Glies, Eiga. - Vasco de Gama, van Gelderen, Eanea. - Eudolf, Moesker, Dantzig. - Emanuel, Beckmann, Stettin. - Trofart, Torgesen, Elseneur. - Amicitia, S., Bergen. - Urda, Bernard, Drammen . - Jcseph, Lebihan, Heppens.- Anna Helena,Nieland,Petersb. BRIELLE. 24 Jnlij; Zealous, S., Harwich. MAASSLUIS, 24 Julij; Orion, S., Londen. - CatharinaLouise, v. Aalst, Avontuur. BEOUWEESHAVEN, 24 July; Samarang, de Groot, Eott. n. Bat. DANTZIG, 21 Julij; Geertruida, Easker, Amst. BOLDERAA, 16 Julij; Emma, Ber;&apos; Amst. • Nestor, Hemmes, Delfzijl.- Nooit Gedacht, Nanning, de Weser.- Eendragt, Kok Houwink, Élseneur.- Annagiena Elsiena, Kuy per, id. - Wilhelmine, Buuie, id. - Gandal, Sandved, Nederland. - Anna Luitsia, Jager, id. - Engelina Petrouella, Brouwer, Engeland. BEEMEEHAVEN, 23 Julij; 23 Julij; Grietje Wolters, Albers, Amst. - Hillechina, Wynstok, id. LONDEN, 23 Julij; Hillechina Margaretha, Joosten. Harburg. FALMOUTH, 20 Julij; Diana, Teengs, Eott., 1. v. Akyab. -Cycloop, S.,Middell.Zee. FOWEY, 21 Julij; Oporto, Granville, Dordt. - Ossena, Hill, Ziezikzee. GEEENOCK, 21 July», Vertrouwen, Middel, Troon. MONTEOSE, 21 July; Cornelia Jacoba, van der Meer, Frederikstad. HARWICH, 20 Julij: Affiance, Arnold, Amst. LEITH. 21 Julij; Neptunus, van Gorkum, Inverkeithing. NEW VORK, 10 Julij. Zeilklaar: Cama, Holg, Eott.</p>
</text>
