<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 6 Maart, 0. N. O.; Veracity, Greenor, Newc. - European, S., Huil.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 4 Maart, 0.N.0.-, Willem, Kröger, Hamburg. - Zwaantina Margrietha, de Vries, id. - Elsiena, Vlieger, id. — 6 Maart; Boreas, Munneke, Leith. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Maart, 0.N.0.-, MegLeo, Tinn, Newc. l.v. Brouwershaven. - AÏpha, Thielcke, Ystad. BRIELLE, 6 Maart, O. N. O.; Florence, S., Londen. - Ravensbury, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Maart, O. N. O.; Egret, S., Bott. n. Liverpool. BREMERHAVEN, 5 Maart; Twee Gezusters, Meijer, Burnt, Island. Op de ELVE, 5 Maart; Willem I, S., Amst. GOTHENBURG, 28 Febr.; Barbara Jonker, Oltmans, Newcastle. HELSINGBORG, 27 Febr.;GeertjeDijkstra, Veninga,Huil.-Hilma, Nordström, St Übes. SWINEMUNDE, 4 Maart; Eotterdam, S., Rotterdam. PILLAU, 3 Maart-, Amalie, Steen, Messina. TONNINGEN, 1 Maart; gepasseerd: Gesina, Deen, Anclam n. Londen. LONDEN, 5 Maart; Catharina van Calcar, Meijer, Groningen. GUERNSEY, 28 Febr.; Rollo, Schep, Rott. en Jersey. LIVERPOOL, 4 Maart; Jantje Martens, Ates, Barcelona. WEST-HARTLEPOOL, 3 Maart; Bernard &amp; Agnes, Stapelman, Amst, IPSWICH, 3 Maart; Eagle, Hawkins, Rotterdam. GRIMSBY, 4 Maart; Hillechina Hillechina, Oosterhuis, Amst. SUNDERLAND, 3 Maart; Sigismunde, Long, Amst. — 4 Maart; Elisabeth, Ward, Nieuwe Diep. - Blackness, Hughes, id. LEITH, 4 Maart-, Johanna, Muller, Havre. HAVRE, 4 Maart; Beniflcium, Kramer, Gron. - Ida, Wilde, Pillau. MALTA, 27 Febr.; Boreas, de Jonge, Vlaardingen. CAPE CO AST CASTLE,...; President Benzon, ... CARDENAS, 31 Jan.; Duiveland, ITummcr, Boston. MONTEVIDEO, 21 Jan.; Alida, Zellicn, Cadix; vertrok den volgenden dag n. Buenos-Ayres. —25 Jan. In lading: Telemachus, Visser, Antw. STKAAT SUNDA, 19 Jan.; Kosmopoliet,, de Groot, Bat. n. Nederl. - Johannes Martinus, Dolloyaux, Rott, n. Singapore. SOERABAYA, 22 Jan.; Admiraal de Ruijter, Witting, Amst. PADANG, 15 Jan.; Padang-Packet, Huidekoper, Amsterdam. AMOY, vóór 9 Jan.; Sophia Koningin der Nederl., Klein, Soerabaya. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 6 Maart, O. N. O.; Anna Geertruida, v. Ingen, Messina. - Helena Florentina, Rosenbeek, Livorno. - Diana, S., Londen. VLIE, 4 Maart, 0.N.0.; Eendragt, Kok Houwink, Libau. - 2 Gebroeders, Hillenius, Leba. OSTMAHORN, 3 Maart; Maria, Jungerhaus, Leer. — 4 Maart; Hermanus Wieher, v. d. Laan, Avontuur. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Maart; O. N. 0., Johannes Anthonius, de Voogd v. d. Straten, Bat. via Brouwershaven. - Susanna Johanna, Peeters, id. via id. - Vlaardingen, Goudswaard, St, Übcs. - Swanland, S. Huil. - Annie, S., Goole. - Leeds, S., Grimsby, EMDEN, 3 Maart; Gebrüder, de Vries, Antwerpen. - Annechina Hartoina, Zuidema, Avontuur. CUXHAVEN, 1 Maart: Anna Elisabeth, Dik, Avontuur. KOPENHAGEN, 1 Maart; Broedertrouw, Woltman, Oostzee. STRAALSUND, 27 Febr.; Friederike, Zeplien, Nederland. — 28 Febr.; &quot;Wilhelm, Zebel, id. PAIMBOEUF, 3 Maart; Bonne Esther, Gueno, Rott. - Diligent, Jouan, Groningen. NANTES, 3 Maart; Coquette, Ordronneau, Groningen. LISSABON, 27 Febr.; Maria Johanna, van Gelderen, Vlaardingen. - Hermanus Theodorus, Wilmink, Falinouth. - Rbóne, S., Genua. CIENFUGOS, 30 Jan.; Dankbaarheid, Koor, Casilda. MONTEVIDEO, 25 Jan.;La Plate, Kuiper Antwerpen. HAVANA; 7 Febr.; Arion, Mulder, New-Orleans. BALTIMORE, 14 Febr.; Duisburg, Holljes, Rotterdam. SOERABAYA, 23 Jan.; China, Smith, Nederl.</p>
</text>
