<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>YBIE, 4 Jumj; Hillechina Gesina, Pik, Archangel. - Zeehond, Feninga, Petersburg. - Lambertha, Karst,id.-Jacoba Lucretia, Maas, Windau - Cathalina van Calcar, Meijer, Riga.- Vriendschap, de Vries, id. - Severus Kohn, Riga. - Soranus, Poelman, Flcnsburg. - Union, Melgesen, Drammen. - Alwine, Hertzer, Hamburg. -An ja Sietzia, Huisman, Avontuur. - Vrouw Martha, Ebes, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Junij; Maria Johanna, v. Gelderen, Gibraltar.- Maassiuis, Kuchler, Sunderland. BRIELLE. 5 Junij; Ravensbury, S.. Harwich. CUXHAVEN, 3 Junij; Themis, Buiten, Curacao. - Amalia &amp; Arm, Hormes, Groningen. BREMERHAVEN, 3 Junij; Elschlea, Albers, Amst. - Rensina Willemina, Kramer, id. WABNEMUNDE, 1 Junij; Immanuel, de Jong, Londen. - Margaretha Meijering, de Jong, id. DEAL, 4 Junij; de Vrede, Nickus, Londen n. Buenos-Ayres YARMOUTH, 2 Junij; Fockelina Emmelina, Folkers, Shields. ABERDEEN, 1 Junij; Elisabeth, Nepperus, Leith. DUNDEE. 1 Junij; Stad Enschedé, Veldhuis, Zwolle. LIVERPOOL, 1 Junij; Jacomina, Kuiper, Nerva. - Isaac Sannes, de Jonge, Koningïb. —3 Junij; Pelican, S., Rott.- Zeilkl.: Catharina, Visman, Bat. - Ahena, Koops, Vardoe. ROCHESTER, 2 Junij; Barend, Hoekstra, Newcastle. PAIMBOEUF, 31 Mei; Schnellpost, Deege, Kampen. NEW-YORK 16 Mei; zeilkl.: Wilhelmina&amp;Elise,Wiersma,Stettüj (via Porto Cabello). BBASSEIN, 14 April; Johannes, Zetteler, Falm. — 19 April; Cornelia. Croes, id. &quot; MAURITIUS, 21 April; S. van Heel, Dietz, Java n. Rott. BATAVIA, 15 April; Julie, Cherpion, Padang. — 19 April; Zeenymph, Graadt van Roggen, Nederl. — 23 April; Oceaan, Smit, id. - Cornelis Wernard Eduard. Swart, id. PASOEROEAN,9ApriI; Argo, Ankringa, Nederl. -11 April; Neerland s vlag, van den Broek Humfrey, id. BANJOEWANGIE, 3 April; Jan Daniel, van IJzendoorn, Amst. - Johanna, Verduin, Rott. — 4 April; Minister van Hall. de Haas. Amst.— 7 April; Willem en Carel, Steenveld, Melbourne. — 9 April; A. R. Falck, van der Plas, Nederl. - Medea. van Teutem. Rott. SOERABAYA, 17 April; Willem Daniël, Zeylstra, Nederl. PADANG, 11 April; Johannes Lodewijk, van Delft, Rott.</p>
</text>
