<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>MfEEfEITIE-f. . BBERIftTo ÏIWE 5 PCT. TBRRSCHE MMM 1867 (groot £ 500,000 of ƒ 6,000,000 Holl. Courant). a 265/16 pCt per £ 100, tegen het £ 12 Guldens. Amstekdam, 24 November 1867. (29570) SEDERT EUIM EEN JAAR IS HET VOOR DE TWEEDE KEER GEBEURD, DAT KWAADWILLIGEN ZONDER DE MINSTE AANLEIDING EN ALLEEN MET HET DOEL , OM DEN ONDERGETEEKENDE TE BELASTEREN EN TE BENADEELEN, HET GERUCHT ALGEMEEN HEBBEN VERSPREID, DAT HIJ ZIJNE BETALINGEN HEEFT GESTAAKT. AANGEZIEN DE AVET DEN KOOPMAN TEGEN ZULKE MISDADIGE POGINGEN NIET GENOEGZAAM BESCHERMT, BLIJFT AAN DEN ONDERGETEEKENDE NIETS ANDERS OVER, DAN OPENLIJK ONMIDDELIJKE BETALING AAN TE BIEDEN AAN EEN lEDER DIE VAN HEM lETS TE VORDEREN HEEFT. (28565) JULIUS O. FREIWALD. OTTCMIWAIGERTIFÏGATIM van ©paansclie COUPONS. Het COMITÉ VAN SPAANSCHE FONDSENHOUDERS, te Amsterdam, meent in verband met hare annonce dd. 9 November ter kennisse van belanghebbenden te moeten brengen de volgende mededeelingen van de Heeren JAMES CAPEL en Baron LIONEL DE ROTHSCHILD, door wie ingevolge het besluit der Algemeene Vergadering van houders van CERTIFICATEN, gehouden te Londen, op 25 September 11. de Vergoeding is vastgesteld, waarvan in die annonce sprake was. 5. TgROGMORTON S-KEET, LONDON, Octeber, 1867. To the Holders of English, Dutch and Spanish CERTIFICATES. As the suggestor of the issue of the Certificates to represent the 50 per cent. of the Coupons not funded at the settlement of the Spanish Debts in 1851 (at which time I was the Chairman of the Bondholder&apos;s Committee), and being now one of the Trustees holding the books and Counterfoils neces&apos;sary to verify those Certificates, I venture to address you. You are aware, that a Committee was appointed by the Public Meeting of Certificate Holders in 1856, to cary on the negotiations with the Spanish Governraent to obtain a settlement for these Certificates, and that certainVoteswerecarried to pay any expenses arising from the carrying on of their mission, and also to give them some reaiuneration for their services; and after eleven years have passed and a settlement being at length obtained, these Votes were confirmed at Meetings lately held. Koyever, in consequence of the Royal Order frem the Queen of Spain, the Trustees cannot part with the books and counterfoils to enable a réduction to be made from the amount granted to the Holders of the Certificates, nor will the Spanish Financial Commissioners allow of any réduction from the amount (being £ 55 lls.ld.Stock for each £ 100 Certificate on which a half-year&apos;s Dividend at the rate of three per cent. per annum will accrue on the Ist of January next). Under these circnmstances a voluntary Subscription becomes necessary to enable the Committee to defray the amount they have expended, and to give them some moderate remuneration for their aar VXflfiß For their expenditure, and that of the Dutch Committee, they will require from £10,000 to £11,000, without affording any renumeration to the Committee; and lam of opinion that a contribution of 5s npon each £ 100 Certificate may be fairly asked for frem the Holders which I have reason to believe will be willingly paid by many of the large Holders. The contribution, if not paid Defore , might be conveniently paid out of the Dividend payable in JanlSubscriptions will be received bij the LONDON AND COUNTY BANK, in the names of JAMES CAPEL and JOHN FIELD, Esq. (the Deputy Chairman of the Committee). I am, Gentlemen, Your most obedient Servant, (Signed) JAS CAPEL. New Coüet, Oct. 30th, 1867. In answér to your letter of the 25th instant, I beg to say that I am quite willing to recommend the Holders of the Spanish Certificates to pay, after the conversion of the same into a Three per Cent. Stock, the 5«. per £ 100 Certificate as suegested by you, and intend also to pay the same on those belonging to myselt. I remain, Sm, yours truly, (Signed) &apos;LIONEL DE ROTHSCHILD. To John Field, Esq. , ? ? Het Comité voornoemd, tot ontvangst der vastgestelde vergoeding blijvende vaceeren, acht zich tevens verpligt, onder de aandacht van Houders van Certificaten te brengen, dat de termnn voor de conversie dier Certificaten vastgesteld, 18 December e.k. eindigt en dat alle Certificaten, welke voor of op dien datnm niet mogten zijn ingeleverd, van de conversie zullen zijn uitgesloten. Amsterdam, Het Comité van Spaansche Fondsenhouders 21 Nov. 1867. te Amsterdam. JOH. WERTHEIM. (28567) G. L. WCRFRAIN.</p>
</text>
