<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>UITGEZEILD. „ . v TFXFL 7 Oct.; Lammcchiena, Duit Jr., Koningsbergen. - Eider, Knutbt Bergen. - Fem Söstre, Knudsen, Frcdenkstad.-Ircya, Olsen , VUpafi Oct • Boreas. Manneke, Newc. - Willem Carel, Gudmundsen , Chri_tia&apos;nia -&apos;Èmerentia, Christensen Drammen. -Hoabet, bjomiess, doorwegen&apos;-Bordeaux.Ouendag Azn., Avontuur HIOTI F VOETSLUIS, 6 Oct.; Comely, Bules Grangemouth. -Fry, öSurt idl^SeaeulhS? Hal. - Sarah Kin?, Wathwortl., I pswich .- Svii, V&apos;,,i&apos; Drammen - 7 Oct.; Bordeaux, 8., Bordeaux. - Admiraal Ki: -^ Hwre-Feyeuoord,S„Londen.- Aurora,S.;id.-Oleopas Kbui&apos;S.&apos;CGene,il Lee, S Dublin - Maria Staart, S., Leith. - BROUW^tó _ MAASSLUIS 7 Oct;Swanland, SJ Bristal.- Harrison, Fox, Stockton.- B«, Stading, id. - Louis Joseph, Lcroux, Newc.</p>
	<p>BREMERHAVEN,6 octi Anja, Meyer.Frederikstad.-Sophio Elisabeth, de Groot, Memel.</p>
	<p>EjiIDEN, 4 Oct.; Gebroeders, v. d. Harst, Gron.- Susauna, Earghorn, id. Louise Sopltia, Hollander, Londen. WOLGAST, 3 Oct.; Jacoba Gesina, Ueins, Oldciiburg. STETTIN, 4 Oct.;Ann.t, Kuiper, Odcnse.-5 Oct.; Sikko, JouVcr, Pernau. DANTZIG, 4 Oct.; Gouverneur van Ewyck, S„ Amst. BOLDERA, 30 Sept.; Anna Augusta, Kuiper,Nederland.-Antje Visser, de Jong, Elseneur. - Dankbaarheid, Dirksen, id. — 3 Oct.; Carolina, Cupido, id. ODEN SE, 26 Sept.; Elschlea, Albers, Nederland. - Addy, Olsen, id. — 27 Sept.-, Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge id. THISTED. 25 Sept.; Skjold, Hansen, Nederland. DRAMMEN, 21/22 Sept.; zeilkl.: Astrea, Andreassen, Amst. KROONSTAD, 2 Oct.; Geertruida Speelman, Lever, Amst. - Godelevis, Boer, de Maas. - Hendrika, Glimmenga, Harlingen. - Alida, Nagel, Gron.- Alberdina, Lodewijks, id. - Immanuel, de Jonge, id. - Gezina, Krook, Leeuwarden.-Maria, Kuppor, Nicolaistad -Catharina, Lohman, Rouaan. - Noordstar, Harting, Antwerpen. - Anna Margaretha, Oltraans, Londen. - Wilhelmina, de Groot, Kopenhagen. - Enjetta, Boswijk, id. - Cornelia, Boon, id. - Alberdina, van den Bos, id. - Engelina Pietronella, Brouwer, id. - Rieka, Puister, Elseneur. - Grietje, Lukkien, id. Catharina, Boon, id. - Johanna Maria, Feninga, id. - Johanna Wilhelmina, Faber, id. - Stclla Marie, Harding, id. FALMOUTH, 5 Oct.-, Sympathie, Bakema, Antwerpen. PORT MADOC, 5 Oct.; Quarry maid. Williams, Rotterdam. SUNDERLAND, 5 Oct.; Vivid, Beddingfield, Nieuwe Diep. CADIX, 30 Sept. Zeilklaar: Gesina. de Jonge, Montevideo. ILOILO, 5 Aug.; Catharina Maria, Braudts, Shanghae. LISSABON. 29 Sept.; Catharina Louise van Aalst, Villa Nova. SINGAPORE, 23 Aug.; Kortenaar, Schuchard, Batavia. PASOEROEAN, 7 Aug.; Willem Kroonprins der Nederlanden, de Bourghelles Zetteler, Nederland. HONGKONG, 22 Aug.; Oceanus, Dirksen, Java. SHANGHAE, 10 Aug.; Ilcrmine Maria Elisabeth, Dyker, Nagasaki. — 17 Aug.; Minister Pahud, Lippes, Java. YOKOHAMA, 1 Aug.; Gloria, Puister, Nagasaki.</p>
</text>
