<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>l_.A_.l_, 15 Mei, O.; San José, Gorono, Bilbao.-Nautilus, Patterson, Newc. - European, S. Huil. - Maria Anna, Paosch, Windau. - Rhóne, S., Dantzig. - Elisabeth /even. id. - Margaretha An Una, de Boer, id. - Caroïue Marie Rode, Veile. - Hermanos, Oelsen, Christiania. - Johanna Gesina, v. d. Veen, id. VLIE, 14Mci, O. Z. O.; Maria, Albcrts, Dantzig.- Sophia, Vonk, Amst. zenBcSauU.bUleKger »*»» **«&quot;**- 15 Me!; Haabet, Lorent„P.EK„SPÜI.&apos; P &apos;_ _,&quot;&apos; °&apos;; Sapere, Stoop, Tjilatjan. - PiotaSSS_ÜSftStf Ha&apos; &quot;&apos;■ -,0 Mrf! Maria-*■■«Bor.ffwi_4&amp; - Anna Catha- VEILE, 4 Mei; Meinskink, OlJeiibu-g, ■ K c k KOPENHAGEN, 10 Mei. Ter Eeede: Anna Catharina Anker*. „ Malaga. -11 Mei; Tjakicna, v. Sluis, Cardiff n. Petersburg &apos; Ankersen&apos; Bij KOPENHAGEN, 12 Mei; Aflena, Broeckema, Horsen, n Memel «ANDERS, 4 Mei; Weldaad, Pik, Kopenhagen. emeK ÜD-^NSEE, 29 April; Agnese LVdcrs, Troest, Schiedam. Oost_eV NDE&apos; &apos;2 ter&quot;S UU t 66 &apos;&apos; AUia llondrika- MeÖer, n. de XfeaaMv??. &apos;.°£e _Fna Elisabeth, Smit, Dantzig. SANDHAMN, BMei; Roelfiua, de Groot Amst ERIEDERICIA, vóór 6 Mei; Nooit Gedacht,&quot; Bakker, Hamburg - 8 Mei; Peter &amp; Jens. Meinertz, Amst. n. Nybor&quot;- &quot; ELSENEUR, 10 Mei; gepass,: Jantina Christina, Bekkering, Koningsb n. Newc. - Jan Fredenk, Menborg, id. n. Sundswal. - Aurora, vfal man id n. Rott. - Alberdina, WoUttmmer, Memel n. Emden. - Veendam Pik, Antw.n.Petersb.-Reiziger, Dnk„ternii^ id niH n.-.ii!_S■ j &apos; de Joode, id. n. id. -11 Mei; 2w_lu w, Vis ë N ■ &apos;vé , ,id - St^ id. n. id. - Margaretha Hillechiena. P.kelder!--W n de&quot;óS___^ &apos; RKNDSBüf.G, 11 Mel^pa-aeer«l:Eamaietro.^de^rm»»h„™ n. 1 .-iedericia. -12 Mei-, Cittarina, Poppen, Amst. n Kopénb&apos; Uambuii» LONDEN, 14 Mei; de Hoop, Visser, W orcum. - Gesma, Bontekoe Gro ningen. &apos; By DUNGENESS, 12 Mei; Maria Regina, Ouwehaud, Banioewan™ n Amst.- Althéa, Morck, Rott. n.Shediae. .oettangien. GRANGEMOUTH, 12 Mei; Geertruida Jacoba, Bontekoe. Gothenburc Bü SCILLY, 11 Mei; Havana Pack t, de Boer, Amst. n. Havana. ALLOA, 11 Mei; Alberdina, Lodewijks, Leith. - Jantje, Meijer, id. DUNDEE, 13 Mei; Anna Elisabeth, Dik, Aarhuns. LIVERPOOL, 13 Mei-, Ousel, S., Rott. MIDDLESBRO, 13 Mei; St. Etienue, Aiistin, Gron. - John Pardew, Guswcll, Dordt. - Stclla, Hayman, id. - Margaretha, de Vries, Nederland. HARTLEPOOL, 11 Mei; Anna Catharina, Ohlsen, Rott.— 12 Mei; Vertrouwen, Moester, Zwolle. - Christine, Lund, Schiedam. SUNDERLAND, 13 Mei; Adrienne, Chauvelon, Zwolle. . SHIELDS, 13 Mei; Albert, Wiese, Amst.- Whampoa, Janses,Rott.-lsabella Sarah, Hall, id. - Zcphirus, Elliott, Nieuwediep. - Karen Sophie, Sorensen, Schiedam. - Anna Charlotte, Jen. en, id. - Automatia, Burton. Dordt. - Eendragt, Doornbos, Harlingen. - Deborah, Kuiper, Saudef jord Presto, Roelfsema, Bremen. LEITH, 13 Mei; Jacoba Lucretia, Maas, Windau. Bij St. ALBANSHOOFD, 13 Mci; Sliedrecht, Borchers, Amst. n Saraarani». ST. NAZAIRE, 12 Mei-, Goertruida Speelman, Lever, Amsterdam. LISSABON, 9 Mei; Dons, Haverkamp, Rio Janeiro. -Voorwaart» Schouten, Vlaardingen. &gt;&quot; «,_._...-, NEW-CASTLE (N. S. W.), 21 Febr.; Voornit, Uggor, M. 1-ourne (vertrok 25 Maart n. Manilla).</p>
</text>
