<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TH^nHrt^_!?S^n__^ïêl!S?leHrun,Cardiff -Bro- Christenscn, Riga. - Médéa, S., Stettin. - Lourense, Andersen, Christiania. - Norske Klippe, Pedersen, Fredeiikstad. -1 April; Alert, S., Hull. — 2 April; Waterloo.Abrahamsz, Bat.-Geesiena Maria, Rom, id. - Teelkina Meiskina, de Haan, Napels. - Eleanor, Adams, Newc. -Ü- Philips, Sunderland. - Maria Adolfina, Blom, id. - &apos;Galilei, van der Mey, id. - Fagel, van Duyn, id. - Sultana, Bell, id. - Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg.</p>
	<p>_on_T_-l Maart; Noordstar, Brouwer, Windatt. - Antje Visser, _e *en «tB*- - Ulrika, Dik, Dantzig, - Alb erdina Edzina, Uchtman, Ber- Seai&apos;iii 00!llvaart, S., Hamburg. - Arcndina Jacoba, Menzes, Avontuur. - ven ir &apos;• Ëefting, id. - Hendrik Jan Nassau, Boelfsema, id. - Vollenhoïr r°&quot;,nS. id. - Catharina Visser, de Vreeze, id. toJÏ^VOBTSLUIS, 31 Maart; Tuisko, Dannemann, New-York, via JÜf^r^ven. - St. Clemens, Schmidt, Triest. - Hortense, Wcnneker, 1&apos; &apos;^eP^yr&apos; &quot;•» Londen. - Pelican, S., Liverpool. -Louise, S., Gran- Ver • 1 &quot; ¦ljord Raglan, S., Newc. - Mars, Cummings, id. - Leveret, Carg 7. &quot;•- Albert H. Locke.Collins, id. - Leipzig, S., Hartlepool. - Colletis, •, uoole. - Eagle, Hawkins, Ipswich. — 1 April; Feyenoord, S., Londen.-gaYfy&apos; §•¦ Dublin. -Kinghorn,S., Leith.-Seagull,S., Hull.-Swallow, Knel &quot; &quot;fctfgaretha, Kappen, Avontuur. — 2 Aprü; Invicta, Hopkins, Moii &apos;• &quot; Hensiua, Meeter, Oostzee. - Engelina, Smith, id. - Jarnia RPTiPatoma&apos; &gt;d. - Terug uit zee: Hortense, Wenneker, n. Lissabon. iJn^Lld.. 31 Maart; Waterloo,S.,Londen.-Ravensbury,S.,Harwieh. üKOUWEBSHAVEN, 1 April; Willem &amp; Clara, S., Londen. .JJ^ISSINGEN, 2 April; Willem Frederik, Visser, Bergen. 21 Maart; Petrus, Jahnsen, Nederl. öMOEEHAM, 28 Maart; Jantina Alida, Texer, Fayal. *ALMOUTH,29Maart; Frouwina, Duit, Maroimn.Kopenhagen.— Y^aït; Randolph, Wannell, Iquique n. Eott. feONDONDEEEY, 28 Maart; Albert, Jaski, Liverpool. S£P&quot;BOEUF, 28 Maart; Engelina, Konter, Harlingen. _ i,öIJEINAME, 20 Febr.; Gerberdina &amp; Jeannette Emilie, Kuyper, amst. — 23 Febr.; zeilkl.: Anna Lena, Visser, Amst.</p>
</text>
