<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 30 Junij, N. N. VV.—W.N.W.; Laura &amp;Adèle, Pohlnicyer, voor wijlen Lund, Banjóer,., 1. v. de Simons-Baai. - Jane, Flemming, Sund.erl.- Vèr .city, Groener, Newc - Vivid, IMlingfiehl, Sunderl. - Cassandra, Laiiler, id. - Georgo Siuith, Marshall, id. - Blackiiess, Hnghes.id.- Alliancc, Lewis, Mid-; i&apos;shro. - M mister Thorhecke, S.. Huil. VLIE, 29 Junij, N.Z. W.; Eeudragt, Dorenbos, Newc. - European.S., HÊLLEVOETSLü 13, 30 Junij, N.N.W.-W.; Libra, Dirksen, Tjilat. jap. - Winds_r,_.,pLe_sii. - S.ahorse, S., Huil. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. - Ellida.Larsen, Ciiristincstad. !¦ •_,_•-,, _ BRIELLE, 30 Junii, W. N. W.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Ravensbury, S., Harwieh, ¦ ? , ¦ ZIERIKZEE, 29 Junij, N. O.; Elizabeth &amp; Mary, Th. Arno, Newc.— 30 Junö; Elisabeth Han&apos;iilton, White,&apos;Baltim. ri.Rott. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 27 Junij; Jantina Roelhna, Broekema, Stokholm n.Maldon. . _.... &apos;&lt;* &apos;.7 __;_ , SANDHAMN, 24 Junij; Reiziger,Dijkstcrhms, Petersburg. DRONTHEIM, 13 Junij; Elisabeth, Nepperus, Amst. -VEILE, 22 Junij; Elschlea, Albers, Amst. . UDBYHOI, 16 Junij-, Renske, Nepperas, Newc. —24 Jumj; Jantje, oe Groot, Schiedam.-Eureka, de Groot, Engeland. Bij DUNGENESS, 28 Junij; Giacomo, Solan, Montevideo n. Amst. - Candati, Krijnen, Amst. n. Macassar. - Elisabeth, de Jonge, Liverpool n. P g t c r si) ur f?» Bij PORTLAND, 27 Junij; Julia, van Loon, Rotterdam n. Singapore en PLYMOUTH, 28 Junij; Balmoral,?., Rott. • . Bij PLYMOUTH, 23 Junij; Lodewijk, Bax, Rott. n. Congonvier. RÓCHESTFR, 23 Junij-, Br others Success, Hobarth, Rott. FALMOÜTH, 28 Jnnij-, Nicoletta, Olivari, Nicolajeff n. Rott. BELEAST, 28 Junij; Vartry, S Rott. HARTLEPOOL, 28 Jimtj-, Wiliiam Pitt, Wilson, Rott.. SHIELDS, 28 Junij; Gaucha, Nelsou, Rott. - Oronoco,Vint, Scmedam.- Pollv, Hvid, Zierikzee. - Charles, Wallace, Nicuwediep. NEW-YORK, 17 Junij; Alblasserwaarct, van Lindern, Padang. rr a T.TT. A_. 6 Junii: Acadia. Boer, Deirshaven.</p>
</text>
