<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Aug.; Middlesbro, S., Middlesbro. - Irwell, S„ Hnll. VLIE, 31 Julij; Elltn Susan, Lorenzen, Charlestown. - Rudolph, Brandt, Newcastle. - Boreas, Munneke, id. - Eupatoria, Hutchinson, Kroonstad. - Mercurius, de Boer, Sundswall. - Solon, Otterbeek, Gefle. - Catharina, de Vries, Stokholm. - Froukje, Koops, Kopenhagen. - Willem, Jansonius, id. - Freyer, Pedersen, Christiania. - Remelia Geertruida, Katoen, id. - Soeblomsten, Holm, Bergen. - Ebenezer, Stephensen, id. - Terra Nova, Abel, Frederikstad. Catharina Elisabeth, Pot, id. - Alida Giezen, Nieland, id.-Cornelia, Dekker, id. - Dirkje, Burghout, id. - Lympha, Allurn, Drammen. - Foreningen, Seeberg, id. - Coallier, Lorenzen, id. - Grietje, Nieboer, Osterrisoer. - Castor, Olsen, Aasgaardstrand. - Jan Visser, Boon, Avontuur. -Neeltje Cornelia, Postema, id. — 1 Aug ; Geertruida, de Groot, Laurvig. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Aug.; Bilderdijk, Vietor, Bat. via Brouwersh.- Tollons, Verhagen, New Vork via id. - Earl of Auckland, S., Londen.- Batavier, S., id. - London, S., Dundee. - Sentinel, S„ Newc. - Seahorse, S., Huil. - Walter Stanhope, S., Goole. - Gironde, S., Petersb. - Rotterdam, S , Dantzig.</p>
	<p>HAMBURG, 31 Julij; Juffer Aaltje, Martens Gron. — 1 Aug.; Diana, Kraan, Anstrnther. - Neptunus, v. Gorcum, Schotland. CUXHAVEN, 1 Aug.; Catharina Annegina, Alberts,Friedericia.-Catharina Groenewold,Velvis, id. - Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Rendsburg. - Maria, v. d. Plas, Rio Janeiro.</p>
	<p>BRAKE, 23 Julij; Jacoba Marchiena, Kuil, Bremen. SWINEMUNDE, 29 Jnlij; Wieka, Eoftingh, Unica. CAROLINERZYL, 30 Julij; Madonna, Holthuis, Londen. BOLDERA, 28 Julij; Collegie Voorzorg, Hubert, België. - Gesina, Roskamp, Gent. - Jeltina, Korter, Elseneur. - De Trouw, Bosk er, België. NERVA, 20 .lulij; Zaan3troom,Visser, Schiedam. - Tuhalkain, Cain, Nederland. — 21 Juüj; Alfen, Knudsen. Zaandam. - Drie Gebroeders, Jansen, Kampen. — 22 Julij; Hercules, Koster, Amst.- Vertrouwen, Pot,Löwestoft. 24 Julij; Kemda, Bakker, Dundee. ARCHANGEL, 18 Julij; zeilkl.: Hollander,Kruit,Schiedam.- Economie, Swart, Petorhead. —■ 19 Julij; Pcrsa, Drent, Hnll. STOKHOLM, 25 Julij; zeilk.: Concordia, Knijpinga, Rott. LONDEN, 1 Aug.; zoilkl.: Frouke, Heins, Amst. - Geerdina, Nieboer; Avontnur. GRAVESEND, 31 Julij; Maria Hendriks, Hes, Koningsbergen. LIVERPOOL, 31 Julij; Wildervank, Walvius, Petersb. - Gesina Jantina, Bekkering, id. HARTLEPOOL, 30 Julij; Eendragt, Smit,Flensburg. MARSEILLE, 31 Julij; Johanna, Wilmink, Falmouth.- Oceaan, Hughes, Reunion. KONSTANTINOPEL, 20 Julij- 11. D. Pooh, Fienga, Amst. — 22 Julij; Salvatore, Menalla, id. — 27 Julij; Shearwater, Askan, Galatz n. id.</p>
</text>
