<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 27 Dcc, Z.0.—0.N.0.; Mentor, Toering, Londen. — Gist nog: HendrikPieter, Bakker, Riga. -.«.va. VLIE,27 Dcc, N.; European, S„ Huil. - Elisabeth, Nepperus, JSer. HELLEVOETSLUIS , 27 Dcc; Seagull, S., Huil. - Lammecm Duit Jr., Riga.-Mettje Schönfeldt, van Dijk, id. - Annette, Wacn»^ n. Gend, als bijl. - Catharine, Ganthier, Windau. - Johann, •va,go-•va,gorfloid. - Ceres, Reckless, Libau. - Eendragt, Kok Houwink, Dantzig- -&quot; lic, Thorsen, id. - Columbo, Knuth, Straalsund. - Elve, S., Hamburg- SHIELDS, 24 Dcc; John klsabella, Younger, Rott.- Bonne Josej . Barba, id. — 25 Dcc; Pandora, Bureau, id. - St. Jean, Arme-»* Achille Marie, TeSserat, id.-Temperauce Star, Meen, id. - Siciiy. ¦. id. - Supply, Lucas, Schiedam. - Pauline, Alberts, Dordrecht.. Be8_, SUNDERLAND, 24 Dcc; Clarissa, Samzun, Rott. - Hyacintn, ie id. — 25 Dcc; Neeltje Cornelia, Postema, Dantzig. . GRANGEMOUTH, 24 Dcc; Herstelling, Lukkien, Kragoroe. BELFAST, 27 Qec; Vartry, S., Rotterdam. PEN ARTH, 23 Dcc; Corsock, Warden, Rott. FRASERBURGH, 24 Dcc; Hcndrika, Schmidt, Amst. STOCKTON, 25 Dcc; Expeditive, Maria, Rott. „„ing-e»n&apos; Bij BROADSTAIRS, 25 Dcc; Broedertrouw, Woltman, Urom«e Bordeaux. . ? &apos;¦ _? T.nctor? BATAVIA, 1 Nov.; Paul Johan, Kooy, Pomt de Gallc.- » yer- Eraergo, Ouwehand, Singapore, 9 dito n. Padang vertr.&apos; Jon.a°&quot;&apos;Eleo-&quot;e&apos;Eleoduin, Tagal, 5 dito n. Nederl. vertr. - 2 Nov.; Pauline Constant .. nore, Kuiper, Singapore. - 4 Nov.; J. C Schotel, Chevalier, V. n«&apos; yO9 Allegonda Jacoba, Mammes, Singapore. — 7 Nov.;Jacob -wg»&quot;: _,aporf&gt; v. Harken, Samar., 10 dito n. Nederl. vertr. - Java, Changenr, »-&quot;&amp; ƒ_._.&apos;. 13 dito n. Bourbon vertr. - Snea, Brodin, Pekalongan, 11 dito n. Tertr. _ 8 Nov.; Australië, Jochems, Amst. - Staatsraad v. iiwij^ . .... id. - Petronella, Leieher, Rotterd. —12 Nov.; Doolwijk, Hoetuwn,_ _.r Cornelia Mathilde, Wulp, Shanghae. - 13 Nov.; Ary &amp; Betsy, ü»T Singapore. —14 Nov.; Rotterdam, Janzen, id. c..„__ Dor SUNDA, 29 Oct.; Schelde, Hoffmann, Newp. n. bing»r- HONGKONG, 5 Nov.; Amazone, Kramer, Singapore. wchyi^&apos; SWATOW,SNov.; Henr. Elisabeth Susanna, Meiboora,ne* ligt in lading n. Singapore. — 1 Nov.; Constance, Schroot, onei</p>
</text>
