<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Aug., Z.Z.W.; Almelo, Tjebbes, Bat.; vertrok op 14 April. - Prince Alfred, Robinson, lquiqne, 1. v. Falmouth. - Commewijne, de Lang, Suriname. - Anna Lena, Visser, id. - Carbon, S., Newc. - Hawk, Morgan, id. — Gisteren nog: 3 Gebroeders, Bijkerk, Londen. - Sophie, Paulsen, Riga. - G. B. Lavarella, Peragallo, Taganrog; 1. v. Falmouth. - Pet, Reid, Ibraïla.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 21 Aug, Z. Z. W.; Elisabeth Hendrika, Janknecht, Newc. - Zenobia, Moss, Yarmouth. - Margaretha, Stnitvoet, Archangel. - Zwaluw, Brongers, Petersb. - 3 Gebroeders, Jansen, Nefva. - Baudina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Sundswall. - Elisabeth, Ladiges, Rostock. - Vrouw Clara, Bakker, Christiania. - Agina Undina, Pekelder, Frederikstad. - Johanna Gesina, van Bijssum, id. - Creole, Larsen, Drobach. - Johann Heinrich, de Jong, Aasgaardstrand. - Zwaantje Groenendal, Top, Laurvich.- Amsterdam, S., Hamburg.</p>
	<p>HELLE VOETSLUIS, 22 Aug., Z.W.; C. F. Ivers, Pust, New- Vork. - Rudolph, Beek, Londen. - John &amp; Charles, Charlton, Rochester. - Margareth &amp; Jane, Parry, Whitehaven. - Maria Sophia, Evertsen, Libau. — 23 Aug.; Avalon, S., Harwich. - Kjerteminde, Olsen, Petersburg. BRIELLE, 22 Aug., Z.W.-W.; Ary Scheffer, S., Havre.— 23 Aug.; Waterloo, S., Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN. 22 Aug.; Atlas, Koren, Rangoon n. Rott. - Niord, Schröder, Akyab n. id. - Baggiero, Baggiero, Taganr. n. id. - Try, Depbly, Londen n. id. - Grand Duc Alexis, S., stettin n. Dordt. ZIEBIKZEE, 22 Aug., W.; Heiress, Harris, Liverp. - Pally, Hem, id. - Hannah, Filmer, St. Davids.</p>
	<p>BREMERHAVEN, 21 Aug.; Industie, Hikken, Nieu wed. SWINE MUNDE, 20 Aug.; Emilie, S., Rott. ELSENEUR, 18 Aug.; Carolina, Cupido, Wyburg n. Amst. LONDEN, 20 Aug.; Geertje Dijkstra, Feninga, Petersb. - Hoop, Steffens, id. - 2 Broeders, Prins, id. Bij DUNGENESS, 20 Aug.; Elsiena Geertruida, Mulder, Petersb. n. Penzance.</p>
	<p>Bij de OWÊRS, 16 Aug.; Candati, Krijnen, Rott.n.Macassar. SHIELDS, 20 Aug; Adriana Francisca, v. Eyk, Middelburg. MIDDLESBRO, 20 Aug.; Anna Geertruida, Kempen, Gron. BRIDLINGTON, 20 Aug.; Hero, Burlinson, Nieuwediep n. Sunderland. - Waters, Rayne, Rott. n. Newc. - Sancho, Nelson, id. n. id.</p>
	<p>HARWICH, 20 Aug.; Pride of Mistley, Monnt, Dordrecht n Newcastle.</p>
	<p>Bij PORTLAND, 21 Aug.; Mathilda, Fekkes, Tjilatjap n, Amsterdam.</p>
	<p>ANTWERPEN, 22 Aug.; Gezina, Rozema, Bremen. St. NAZAIRE, 16 Aug.; Martha, Postema, Amst. NANTES, 20 Aug.; Oostzee, v. d. Weyden, Stettin. BARCELONA, 15 Aug.; Reinhold, Muller, Cardiffn. Port Mahon.</p>
	<p>BELIZE, 19 Julij; Alida, Visser, Liverpool. Bii St. HELENA, 25 Julij; Ellina, Lammerts, Bassein n. Falmouth. — 27 Julij; Golden Dream, Wise, Batavia n. Amst.</p>
	<p>Si. HELENA, 16 Julij; Sumatra. Buyser, Bassein n. Dordt. — 17 Julij; Lady Love, Gladstone, Nagasaki n. Amst. — 24 Julij; Jupiter, Kieviet, Bat. n. Amst., hebben de reizen voortgezet. BATAVIA, 29 Junij; Dordrecht, Verhoeven, Rott.— 1 Julij; Bilderdrjk, Viëtor, Amst. - 3 Julij; Azia, Trappen, id. — 4 Julij; Eresident Plate, Julius, id. — 7 Julij; Maria Veronica, Schol, Auet. • Copuixiüus, Algra, Rott.—B Julij; Houdjil», vaa d«r Valk, Rott. - Iduna, du Sar, id; - Cornelia, Croese Amst. - Vertrouwen, Seinstra,.id. - Galilei, v. d. McV, id. - Finella, Murray, Newo. — 10 Julij: Eensgezindheid, v: d. Waal, Amst. SOERABAYA, 21 Junij; L. J. Enthoven, Koons, Newcastle.--2 Junjj; Nederland en Oranje, Haasnoot, Shields. —26 Junij; Elisabeth, Tryselius, Sunderland. STRAAT SUNDA, 28 Junij; Cornelis Smit, Weidenaar, Bat. n. Rott. — 29 Junij; Jacoba &amp; Christina, Gaaff, Amst. n. Samar. PADANG, 22 Junij; Minister Thorbecke, Kaunegieter, Bat.--23 Junij; Maarten van Kossem, la Seur, Samarang. MANILLA, 22 Junij; Jan v. Schaffelaar.v. Duyn/Hongkong. YOKOHAMA, 16 Junij; Arsronaut, Visser, Hiogo.</p>
</text>
