<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Aug., Z.Z.W.; Buffel (Ned. oorl.-ramsch.), Hugenholtz, Birkenhead. - Hollandia, S., Londen. - Lion, S., id. - Nina, Earl, Newc; de 3 laatsten zijn teruggekomen. - Amphitrite, Ohlsen, Wyburg. - Daphne,&apos;Fredriksen, Geffle. - Frederikke, Mathiessen, Chrisliama. - Agina, Knijpinga, Avont. VLIE, 21 Aüg., Z.Z.W.; Johannes, Kauscher, Petersburg. — 22 Aug; Coop Boelf, Sikkens, Schaaf, Leith. - Fenna, Coerkawp, Petersb. - 2 Gebroeders, de Groot, Stockholm.- Broedertrouw, de Groot, Norrköping. - Mercurius, Jansen, Memel. - Trijntje Meijer, Tonckens, Kendsb. - Willem. Swarts, Christ. - Gebr. Fokkés, Fokkes, id. - Hillechiena Oatharina, Hesseling, Frederikstad. - Adriana, Meijer, Avont. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 22 Aug. Z.W,; Josie Mildred, Herriman, Boston A., Olga, S., Londen. - James Rankins, S., Glasg, - Windsor, S., Leith. - Lord Eaglan, S., Newcastle - Urania, St., Hamburg. - 23 Aug.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Seahorse, S., Huil. - Albert, S., id. - Annie, S., Goole. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. BRIELLE, 22 Aug., Z.W.—W.; Leo, S., Londen. - Brother&apos;s Success, Wellard, Rochester. - Zealous, S., Hanvich. BREMERHAVEN, 20 Aug.; Ila Gezina, Egberts, Stockh. PILLAU, 20 Aug.; Jutland, S., Rott. - Biene, Roelofs, Harlingen. St. DAVIDS, 19 Aug; E^etta, Boswijk, Petersb. - 2 Gebroeders, Waterborg, Riga. . SIMONSBAAI, 21 Junij; Ned. oorl. corvet van Speyk, kapt.-luit. Jhr. J. E. W. F. v. Ra&apos;ders, Texel n. Bat. BATAVIA, 29 Junij; Nederland &amp; Oranje, Kramer, Nederl. - 1 Julij; Scheveningen, Annokkee, Golf van Persie. — 2 Julij; Medea, v. Teutem. Nederl. — 4 Junij; Napier, Siuclair, id. — Princes Amalia, v. Bentveld, id. SOERABAYA, 20 Junij; Helena en Henriette, Deterdi ng Nederl. via Menado. — 26 Junij; Wijk aan Zee, Mannoury, China.</p>
	<p>PADANG, 16 Junij; Schoonderloo, v. Leeuwen, Nederl. HONGKONG, 2 Julij; Adriana Petronella, de Breuk, Bat. — 3 Julij; Admiraal de Ruyter, Witting, Manilla. FOÖ-CHEW-FOO, 26 Junij; Katharina Maria, Brandts, Melbourne.</p>
	<p>YOKOHAMA, 25 Junij; Pinses Amalia, Driest, Nagasaki.</p>
</text>
