<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 18 Nov.; Roso ofDenmark, Ellis, Newport. —19 Nov.; Ellen,. Miehason, SunderJand. - Emma Bauer, Falk, Riga. - Cornelia, S., Koningsbergen . HELLEVOETSLUIS, 19&apos; Nov.; Verwisseling, Nottmeyer, Villanova.. Willem &amp; Clara, S., Londen. - John Stonard, Hodgson, Workington, l.v. Brouwershaven. - Queen, S., Dundee. - Storm Queen, S., Hartlepoól. - Leipig,S.,id. BRIELLE, 19 Nov.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Cologne, D. Londen. - Ravensbourne, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 19 Nov.; Nouvelle Undor, Robert, Quimper n. Rott. VLISSINGEN, 19 Nov.;Depositum, Nieveen.Fray Bentos. - Henderika, Glimmeijer, Villanova. - Johanna Maria, Schummelketel, Bordeaux. BREMERHAVEN, 18 Nov.; Afina, Brockema, Heppens. LEER, 17 Nov.; Thedina, Beerthuis, Bremen. HAMBURG, 17 Nov.; Jonge Andries, Steffens, Brugge. - Hamraonia- S.,_..ott. HARBURG; 11/17 Nov.; Thorbecke, Witting, Peterhead. -Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Leeuwarden. - Dorothea, Kramer, Par. CUXHAVEN, 17 Nov.; Amsterdam, S., Amst. TRAVEMUNDE, 17 Nov.; Harmonie, Lange, Newc. SWINEMUNDE, 17 Nov.; Vesta, S., Amst. BOLDERA, 13 Nov.; Elisabeth, van Wijk, Dysart.&apos; - Trijntje Gcsim. Boye, Duinkerken. — 14 Nov.; Lammechina, Duit, Londen. GOTHENBURG, 14 Nov.; Remelia GeerUuida, Katoen, Memel. — 1* Nov ; Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Randers. ELSENEUR, 16 Nov.; gepasseerd: Willem van der Voort, Carst, PeSar*burg n. Duinkerken. LONDEN, 18 Nov.; Gebroeders Smit, Smit, Baenos-Ayres. BRISTOL, 17 Nov.; Dauntlcss, Riever, Rott. CARDIFF, 16 Nov.; Titonia, Olsen, Amst. HOLYHEAD, 17 Nov ; Tecla Maria, Muller, Minatitlan n. Liverpool. SHIELDS, 17 Nov.; Norden, Lundquist, Amst. - Gesina Dorothea, de Boer, id. - Anglia, Wilson, id. - Caroline Victoire, Lemctais, Rott. - Pilades, Parker, Schiedam. - Pleiades, Jcrson, Vlaardingen. PAIMBOEUF, 16 Nov.; Titia Jacobina, Klein, Amst. CAMARET, 13 Nov.; Heureux Retour, Couédel, Amst. n. Nantes. RIO JANEIRO, 15 Oct.; Geertruida en Janna, v. Heiningen, Liverpool.--18 Oct; Amica Manu, Peper, Buenos-Ayres. RIO GRANDE, 27 Sept.; Eersteling, Schuring, Rio Janeiro. — 30 Sept.; in lading: Elisabeth Helena, Coerkamp, Falmouth, - Anna Geertruida, van Ingen, id. - Jeannette Marianne, Timmerman, id. - Catharina, de Boer, id. BUENOS-AYRES, 29 Sept. ;JKarel August, Meermans, Rott. — 2 Oct. i Jacoba, Reinders, Londen. NEW-YORK, 2 Nov.; Arnold Eömngcr, Steenken, Rott. - CoHco_dia« Zeef, Rio Grande. Bij ASCENSION, 4 Oct.; Maria Magdalena, Willenbrink, Samarang 0- Rott.</p>
	<p>St. HELENA,7 Oct.; Andromede, Dannberg.Samarangn.Rott.— BOct. Maria Catharina, de Bos, Bat. n. Amst. (heeft den volgenden dag de rei-j voortgezet.) i Bij St. HELENA, 7 Oct.; Loopuyt, v. d. Hidde, Samar-np n. SchiedamJ</p>
</text>
