<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 16 April, W. N. W.—N. N. W.; Alphonse Marie, Henry, Nantes. - Lumiey, S., Sunderland. - Hawk, S., Hull. - Wilhelm Tersmeden, Christophersen, Drammen. — Gisteren nog : Sterling, Hulchinson, Sunderland. - Soeblomsten, Pedersen, Frèderikstad. VLIE, 15 April, N. W.; Margaretha, Hansen, Kiel. - Jalie, Bruun, Frèderikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 April; Gironde, S., Bordeaux. - Admiraal Ver-Huell, S., Havre. - Zephyr, S., Londen. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. - Gottfried, Eggers, Stettin. - Grand Duc Alexis, S., id. BRIELLE, 16 April; Leo, S., Londen. BROUWERRHAVEN, 16 April; Maria Elisabeth, Bonjor, Banjoew. n. Rott., vertr. 18 Dee. - Jannetje, v. Striemen, id. n. id. - Euxine, Evans, Callao n. id. - St. Jan, Lonimerse, Rott. n. Bat. - Willem de Derde, S., id. n. Koningsb. VLISSINGEN, 16 April; Catharina, Visman, Buen.-Ayres. - Rio de la Plata, Hörner, id. HEPPENS, 9 April; Essea, Gerdes, Rott. - Andreas, Greiff, id. — 10 April; Margaretha Johanna, Meiners, id. KOPENHAGEN, 11 April; Urania, S., Amst. - Catharina, de \&apos;ries, Riga n. Dordrecht. PILLAU, 13 April; Anna Paulowna, S., Amst. Bij D iINGENESS, 9 April; Paramaribo, Jaski, Amst. n. Suriname. — 13 April; Willem Jacobns, de Vries, Surin. n. Amst. Bij WIGHT, 11 April, Doris, Haverkamp, Bremen n. Savanilla. Bij WEYMOUTH, 13 April, Isabella, Tippet, Rott. n. Glasgow. GREENOCK, 14 April; Ida, Berg, Matanzas. INVERKEITHING, 13 April; Christina Jacoba, de Groot, Amsterdam. PLYMOUTH, 14 April-, Jason, S., v. Amst.n.Liss.-Jantina, Lunenborg, Ipswich. FALMOUTH, 14 April; Iris, Lubbering.Cette (n. Hamburg). CARDIFF, 14 April; Kinderdijk, Verdoes, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 14 April, in lading; Gesina, Rutgers, Santos. HULL, 14 April; Jonge Albert, Kwint, Groningen. WEST HARTLEPOOL,I3ApriI; Annechina Harmina,Stuitvoet, Amst. SHIELDS, 14 April;MargarethaMathilda. Beek, Ringkjobing. - Twee Gebroeders, Persoon, Harl. - Christina Agatha, Weadman, Holmstad. - Gesina, Deen, Nyekjobing. VENETIË, 11 April; Triest, S., Rott. - Berenice, S., id.</p>
</text>
