<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 7 Nov.; Magnet, S., Londen. - Maria, Storm, Newc. - Betsy and Jane, Torpe, id. - James, Baxter, Huil. - Pilgrim, Erichsen, Drammen. - Sophie, Paulsen, Porsgrund. - Gratitude, Gj ertsen, Tonsberg. - Shanghae, Schultz, Avontuur. VLIE, 5 Nov.; Ivanhoe, S., Leitk. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 7 Nov.; Nina, Huisman, Kio de Janeiro. - Speculant, Nyland, Bahia. - Möwe, Kiilm, Boston A. - Menno, Potj er, Triest.- Naphtalie, Jones, Gloucestcr. - Idea, Delahoydo, Nenc. - Perseverance, Simpson, id. - Elizabeth, Nounundale, id. - Favorite, Alexander, id. - Sir Henry Have&apos;ock, Mato, id. - Seaflower, Chappel, id. - Elizabeth, Normanby, id. - Vlaardingen, Goudswaard, Bergen. - Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg. - Janus, Sörensen, Drammen. - Economie, Olsen, id. - Maria, Killam, Brouwcrs_i_iY_/ii * BRIELLE, 7 Nov.; Cologne, S., Londen, - Batavier, Sv id. - Zealous, S., Harwich. _ ?._,. MAASSLUIS, 7 Nov.; Venus, Anthonissen, Newc. - Granville, Robinson, Sunderland. - Eweretta, Annis, id. - BROUWERSHAVEN, 7 Nov„* Sara, S., Londen. - Leo, &amp;., id. HAMBURG, 5 Nov; Geertruida Kramer, Folkerts, Nederland. CUXHAVEN, 4 Nov.; Czerina, Rees, Nieuwe Diep. — 5 JNov.; U-sar Godefroy, Decker, Moreton-Baai. - Valparaiso, Jeusen, Valparaiso, - Johannes, de Boer, Harlingen. - Theodora Lucretia, Gru__._-.els, Delfzijl. • Catharina Alida Pronk, Leeuwarden. - Trijntje Meijer, Tonkens, Groningen. - Immanuel, Markmann, Zaandam. ? BREMERHAVEN, 6 Nov.; Aaltina Hendrika, Meijer, Hamburg. - Pie tertj e, Kramer, Rott. ? ;_ . ,-¦_ KOPENHAGEN, 4 Nov.; Gretina, Gortemaker, Landscrona, om daar voor Engeland te laden. 4C , , __ , .., T , _ STOKHOLM, 30 Oct.,zeilklaar: Vriendschap, Lodewijks, Londen. FLENSBURG, 2 Nov.; Gebr. Coerkamp, Hoeksma, Riga.—i _Nov.; tTnie, Parrei, Zweden.— 4 Nov.; Alida Ikea, Pieper, id. SWINEMUNDE, 3 Nov.; Cornelia, S., Koningsbergen. KROONSTAD, 31 Oct.; Economie, Swait, Londen. LONDEN, 7 Nov.; Vartry.S., Rott. LIVERPOOL, 4 Nov.;Amisia, Sap, Rio Janeiro. — Zeilkl.: Ceres, Boog, Villa Nova. ALLOA, 5 Nov.; Margaretha, Heyenga, Christiania. BRISTOL, 4 Nov.; Anna. Kroon, Dantzig. HULL, 5 Nov.; Neptunus, Scholtens, Cette. HOLYHEAD, 4 Nov.; Polly, Hird, Liverpool n. Zierikzee. SUNDERLAND, 4Nov.; Vendore Amst. PORTSMOUTH, 4 Nov.; John Frascr, Galloway, Callao n. Kott.— 5 Nov.; Edwin, Burdett, Rotterdam n. New-York, (heeft een gedeelte der lading vcrstuwd). HARTLEPOOL, 4 Nov.; Anna Catlïarina, Huges, Sovilla. LEITH, 3/5 Nov.; Noordstar, Hartog, Lissabon. St. NAZAIRE, 2 Nov.; Harmonie, Boer, Liverpool. LISSABON, 2 Nov.; Anton en Jacob, Ouwehand, Amst.</p>
</text>
