<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 Aug., Z.Z.0.—0.; Sippe Visser, de Jong, Londen.-John Howard, Crabtree, Leith. - Margherita Borzone.Valle, Newc- Blackness, Hughes, Sunderland. - Janssen, Meijer, Engeland. - Justitia, Jacobsen, Elseneur. S&apos; . , -r. . VLIE, 12 Aug., Z.Z.0.-, Vriendschap, Ellis, Newc.&apos;- Broederschap, Bakker, Petersburg. - Wilhelmina, Schuring, Frederikstad. - Wubko Veltman, Kraai, id. - Pieter, Oostervink, Osterrisoer. - Minerva, Busch, Holmstrand. - Tjadda Gezina, Staal, Avontuur. — 13 Aug.-, Anje.Munning, Predrikstad. &apos; &apos;-&apos;r Z&apos; &quot; -ö ZÜLTKAMP, 12 Aug.; Maarbuizen, Kladder, Newc. - Sperwer, Boer, Osterrisoer. ¦¦ , ¦ &apos; . ~ ? BEIELLE, 13 Aug., Z. 0.; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Batavier, b.,id.- Omnibus, Evans, Findhorn. - Eavensbury, S., Harwich. - Nymph, Ooultons Storm, Engeland. TV« MAASSLUIS, 13 Aug.; Laurens, de Kromme, Lissabon. - Jef.Mangerien, Newc. - De Spruit, Pot, id. -Jenne Nollen, de Goede id- Olaf Metsen, Easmussen, id. - Gills.Mann, Stockton.- Bree, Woodall, ïd.-Oldambt, Schotema,Pitea.-Broedertrouw, Zeven, Bergen.- Balder, Svelen, Stavanger. - Johanna, Lange, Avontuur. - Mider, v. d. Veen, id. BREMERHAVEN, 12 Aug.; Maria Cornelia, Bakker, Kom- Hero, Groothuis, Erederikshald. - Johanna Carolina, de Boer, Groningen. - Lubina, Hazelhoff, Koningsbergen. FALMOUTH, 11 Aug.-, Zeemeeuw, v. d. Meer, Rio Grande n. Hamburg. CARDIFF ioAug.;Clemence, Bouwens. Lissabon. GRIMSBY, 10 Aug,; Jacob f Titia,Prak, Petersburg. - Dageraad, van HARTLEÏPOOL, 9 Aug.; Battruida, Jonkhoff, Petersburg. INVERKEITHING, 10 Aug.; Vier Gebroeders, Woudstra, Hobroe. NANTES, 9 Aug.; Jacques Paul, Dupont, Rotterdam. CADIX 6 Aug.; Arion, Mulder, v. New-Orleansn St. HELENA, 29 Junij; Mary #¦ Hillegonda, Wolters, Bat. n. Rott. - Kennington, Howard, id.n. Amst. „ , r, ? ALGOABAAI, 17 Junij; Friesland, Sipkes, v. Akyab n. Falmouth. PROBOLINGO, 11 Junij; Haemstede, ter Marsch, Nederland. .. HONGKONG, 21 Junij; Bengalen, den Broeder, Saigon. — 24Ju~nij; Maria Eiisabeth, v. d. Gevel, Whampoa. MACAO, 11 Junij; Jacoba Helena, Swart, Batavia. .. MELBOUENE, 27 Mei; Zeelandia, Botesz, Sydney. — 3 Junij; Jonan: nes Lodewijk, van Delft, id.</p>
</text>
