<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>JEXEL, 10 Julij, N.N.0.-N.N.W.; Garland, Gibon, Newc. - Bynhone Leslie, Sunderland. - Ceres, Brand, Riga. - Julie, Bruun, Frederikstad— Gisteren nog: Columbus, Schröder, Sandefiord. VLIE, 9 Julij, N.; British Qnoen, Rosevaer, Newcastle.- Gesina Jantina Bekkering, Petersb. - Etina, Puister, Dantzig. - Willemina, Haak Geestemunde. - Gouverneur v. Ewijck, S., Hamburg. &apos; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Julij, N. O.; Condor, Voss, Riga -Ellida Pedersen, id. - Heinrich, Agrell, Pernau. - Elenore v Flotow Ahivnds irl&apos; BRIELLE, 10 Julij, N.ïfo.; Ravensbury, S„ Harwich &apos; &apos; LEER. 7 Junij; Pietronella, Kort, Amst. - Alida, Scheepers Delfziil MAASSLUIS, 10 Julij; Cologne, S., Londen. OLUeePers&apos;UQm --• HAMBURG, 10 Julij; Willem I S., Amst. - Jonge Barend, Prins, Termunterzijl. - Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Altona. TRAVEMUNDE, 8 Julij; Martha, Siemers, Amst. — 9 Juin- Onrust Mudder, Bremen. *&quot; &apos; BTETTIN, 8 Julij; Rhöne, S., Amst. DANTZIG, 8 Julij; Drie Gebroeders, Leffers, Amst wiiEEVj^ 2 Ju„j; Arend&apos;Fijn&apos;LiverP°ol*- 3 Julij;Cornelia, Suzanna, Wfjtsma, Bremerhaven. &apos; f?SïèS?£L&apos; BTJulij;8TJulij; L* Otto-Warbelow, Bradhering, Dordrecht. LAURVIG ,28 Junij ; Ettina Christina, Schoon, Termunterzijl — 29 Junij; Aaltje, Koning, id. - Gesina, Schoon, Delfzijl. — I Julij; Jantina do Jonge, Nederland. - Geerdina, Wijpkes, id. - Fortuna, de Groot id - Theodora Lucretia, Grummels, id. - Johanna Catharina, van Veen ia &apos; LANGESUND, 29 J-unij; Messina, Veldman, Termuterzijl. AREND AL, 30 Junij; Huil Paket, Bentsen, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 8 Julij; Eppo, Nanninga, Delfzijl n. de Oostzee Ida Berendina, Stel, id. n. id. - Sikko, Jonker, Koningsb. n. Amst. ELSENEUR, 8 Julij; gepasseerd: Drie Gebroeders, Fenenga, Amst. n Lulea. - Alexander, Rairden, Rott. n. Swartwick. - Herstelling, Lukkien. Dantzig n. Boness. LONDEN, 8 Julij; Rachel, Fletcher, Rott. - Twee Zusters, Feenstra, Worcum. Bij GOUDSTAART, 7 Julij; Macassar, Vitringa Coulon, Samarang n. Amst. Bij DUNGENESS,.. Julij; Apollo, Caflero, Licata n. Dordrecht. FALMOUTH, 9 Julij; Amicitia, Arends, Rio Janeiro. - Meeden, Mantjes, Laguayra. LIVERPOOL, 8 Julij; Nicolaas Heinburger, Bloemen_aal,Maracaibo. RUNCORN, 1 ulij; Forester, Johns, Rott. HARWICH, 8 Julij; Christina de Vries, van Dorp, Rochester n SHIELDS, 8 Juhj; Zr. Ms. ramtorenschip Prins Hendrik der Nederlanden, luit. ter zee, Jansen, Liverpool. NANTES. 7 Julij; Memorare, Cabelduc. Amst. GIBRALTAR, 29 Junij; Petronella Knijpinga. Klofkorn, Salonica (vertrok naar Falmouth.) - 30 Junij; Neptunas, Scholtens, Triest (vertrok 1 Juhi n. Bahia.) LISSABON, 3 Julij; Pomona, Haddeman, Rott. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 10 Julij, NN.O.-N.N.W.; Willem v. d. Voort, Jaski, Ancona.- Diana, S., Londen. - Chiüa, Smith, Cardiff.- Veracity,Greener,Newc.- Lily, Watsoen, id. - Marwood, Wilson, Sunderland. - Vivid, Bedlingfield, id. - Cassandra, Laidler, id. - George, Smit, Marehall, id.-Jane,Flemming, id. - Blackhess, Hughes, id. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Heekman, Ingleley, Londen n. Hamburg. VLIE, 10 Julij, N.; Nora, S., Londen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Julij, N. O.; Osborne, S., Leith. - Areta, Mars. hall, id. - Dragoon, S., Newc. - Sheron, Mitchell, id/- Glean,Milburn, id.- Flash, Porter, id. - Gem, Carr, id. - Seahorse, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. - Levant, S., Gotheburg. BRIELLE, 10 Julij; Troubadour, S., Londen. — Gisteren nog: Waterloo, S., id. - Batavier, S., id. - Avalon, S., Harwich. MAASSLUIS, 9 Julij; Niohe, S., Hul). De buiten geankerde schepen , . Marie, Eyra, de Unie en Jeannette, zijn heden door de Sleepboot Voorne en Putten 11, in zee gesleept. LEER, 6 Julij; Helena Johanna, Rosenboom, Harl. — 7 Julij; Remgien, Beerthuis, Groningen. BREMERHAVEN, 9 Julij; Eotterdam, S., Rott. BRAKE, 9 Julij; Trekvogel, Heikema, Noorwegen. EUGENWALDE, 2 Julij; Heidewika Regina, Pekelder, Engeland. NERVA, 4 Juin; Twee Gezusters, Koning, Schiedam. - Reinelia Geertruida, de Boer, Harlingen. — 5 Julij; Hoop, de Boer, Amsterdam. - Titla Margaretha, Schaap, Edam. STOKHOLM, 29 Junij; Zwaantina, Gruppelaar, Engeland. GOTHENBURG, 4 Julij; Geertruida Jacoba, Bontekoe, id. LONDEN, 9 Julij; de Waarden, Agtien, Rio-Janeiro. GRIMSBY, 7 Julij; Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Petersburg. PAIMBOEUF, 6 Julij; Grietje, Legger, Liverpool. GIBRALTAR, 2 Julij; zeilkl.: Hillechina Scholtens, Scholtens, Hamb. GENUA, 3 Julij; Louise, Lammerts, Buenos-Ayres. St. ÜBES, 3 Julij; Zeevaart. Eitzes, Archangel. ALEXANDEIE, 28 Junij; Harmonie, Luders, Falmouth. BANGKOK, 9 Mei; Catharina Elisabeth, Krukkenberg, Hongkong.</p>
</text>
