<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Mei; Felicitas, Wildeboor, Curaeao 1. v. Havana. - Mathilda, Valabona, Ibraïla. - Anna Tedora, Kuiper, Londen. - Ivanhoe, S., Leith. - Elianor, Adams, Nevvcastlc.-Como On, Balton, Sunderland. - Warrior,C.owford. id. - Alert, S., Huil. - Tonkea, Busch, Koningsbergen, (benevens do schepen per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 11 Mei; Baudina, Pool, Bo&apos;ness. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 11 Mei; Augusta, Nylen, Chcribon; vertr. sJan.- Malangen, Sörensen, Manzanilla. - Oroe, Thoroc, Ystad. - Lena, Madsen.id.- Odensce, Hansen, OJensee. - Edeline, Ipsen, Frederikstad. — 12 Mei; Vereeniging, van Noord, Palermo.- Feijenoord, S., Londen- Holyrood,S.,Leith.- Van, Thompson, Newcastle. - Thames, Longstoff, id. - Admiral Cator, S., llartlepool. - Eagle, Hawkins, Ipswich. - Sophia, Martensen, Libau.-Haabet, tÏs™t t 2densee-&quot;Ida en Peter- Arnold, Randers. _,o ,&apos; &apos;^Mei; de Maas, S., Londen, der waarts terugeekeerd.-Killar»ey, &amp;., Goole. - Paci6c, S., Harwich. f&apos;S i?_W-&apos;_? _&amp; Marshall, Gehm, Stettin n. Rott. Tt ilrmmo ?/&gt; «Mel.kin* Meinskina, do Haan, Aux Cayes. HAMBURG, 10 Mei Catharina, Poppen, Rott - Orion Buitpn llarhortr \ll Mei; C«h_rin_, Koops, Bltóoth. - B^&amp;LföSSSiSK^&apos; CUXHAVEN, 10 Mei; Wendelina Jacoba, Schnuur, Livorno. • Amalia Sinnige, Jansen, Vourla. STETTIN, 9 Mei; Johanna, Wilmink, Liverpool. STOLPEMUNDE, 6 Mei; Byka, Gort, Aarhuus. DANTZIG, 9 Mei; Wilhelmina, Oortgieze, Newcastle. BOLDERA, 6 Mei; Jantina, Boon, Antw. - Maria, Heyen, Gent.—7 Mei; Wilhelmina Deterding, Top, Rostock. - Heyo _■ Dieke, Doycn, id. HOLBECK, 5/8 Mei; Harmina, Tunteler, Kopenhagen. - Annechien en Jantje, Venema, id. HORSENS, 1/6 Mei; Agatha Jacobina, Kramers, Amst. ELSENEUR, 8 Mei; gepasseerd: Jantina, Ecfting, Windau n. Amst. — 9 Mei; Willem, Gollards, Pillau n. Koogerpolder, HOLTENAU, 7 Mei; gepasseerd: Zwei Gebrüder, Ulrichs, Veilen. Amst. - Taletta, Groenewold, Frcdcricia n. Groningen. - Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Odensé n. id. - Eliza, Duinkcr, Korsocr n. Nedecland. — 10 Mei; Drie Gebroeders, de Groot, Dantzig n. Leeuwarden. - Trientjo Meijer, Tonkens, Stolpemunde n. Schiedam. LONDEN, 11 Mei; Clipper Galjoot, Hazewinkel, Einden. - Jonge Albert, Kwint, Kjogc. Bij WIGIIT, 4 Mei; Estafette, Oepkos, Amst. n. Samarang. GLASGOW, 10 Mei; Wilhelmina, Puister, Messina. LEITII, 10 Mai; Cloas Tholen, Geerdes, Messina. ALLOA, 9 Mei; Lina Menberg, Iloyer, Schiedam. BONESS, 9 Mei; Prinecss Royal, Eich, Eott. LIVERPOOL, 10 Mei; inlading: Concordia, Addens, Riga. SHIELDS, 10 Mei; Pcerlcss, Evans, Rott. - Sophia. de Haan, Pomaron. SUNDERLAND, 9 Mei; Belt, Freeman, Nieuwediep. - Vivid, Beddingfield, id. ANTWERPEN, 12 Mei; Hermina Maria Elisabeth, Bonjer, Port au Prince. NANTES, 9 Mei; Pctite Paysanno, Te^serot, Rott. CIVITA VECCHIA, 6 Mei; Bérénice, S„ Amst. MALAGA, 2 Mei; Geertruida, Stuit, Huil. NEW-YORK, 29 April; in lading; Courier, Brandlioff, Rott. - von Schack Reichendorft&apos;, Uruss, id. MANZANILLA, 7 April; Margaretha, Thcsing, Kanarische Eilanden.</p>
</text>
