<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>w f v&apos; 7 ?, • &quot;•M. °.i Margareth Potter, Chalmers, Lond. - Liir, Watoon, Newc. - Marmood, Wilson, Sunderl. - Reinbrandt, S., Konings. w W 26« JTUDIj&apos;, N-N-0-; Maria Beerta, Tap, Christiania -27 jfnij.; Hollandia, S.. Londen. --_y, ZOLTKA MP 24 Juuij; Juffer Esse Mensinga, Ecfting, Dantzig. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Junij, N N. 0.; Zephyr, S., tonden.- üsborne, S, Leith. - Mars Mc. Alhster, Newc. - Mary Elizabeth, Rurrence, id. - Flash, Porter, Middlesbro. ?ëpSïï?nl?AVEN&apos;?7r. ™*K°&quot;NymPa- Storm&apos;^ewc.n. Dordt. AK _UAJN(-ül., 25 Junij; Fortnna, Busch Keyser, Rotterdam. BREMERHAVEN,26 Juuij; Jehanna, Brouwer, Antw. EMDEN, 24 Junij; Sjouke, Voss, Amst. AARHUUS, 14 Junij; Catharina, Snitjer, Amst. GOTHENBURG, 20 Junij; Gothenburg, S., Rott. LONDEN, 25 Jnnij; Drie Broeders, Bijkerk, Worcum. — 26 Junij; Vr. JL*I6U Wjt&quot;, J_ GcllStl&apos;3,, ld» Bij DUNGENESS, 25 Junij; Zaanstroom, Driest, Falmouth n. Amst. - Ridderkerk, Bunk, Amst. n. Bat. — 26 Juuij; Laura fr Adèle, Lund, Bat. (laatst van de Simonsbaai) n. Amst. JERSEY, 23 Junij; Rollo, Schep, Rott. Bn LIZARD, 21 Junij; Cynthia Palmer, ..., Philadelphia n. Rott. SEAHAM, 24 Junij; St. Matthew, Watson, Nieuwediep. CARDIFF, 24 Jnnij; Wilhelmina, Backer, Hamburg. - LIVERPOOL, 25 Juuij; San J05é,..., Amst. —iv lading: Wildervank, Giezen, Curacao n. Maracaibo. - Agatha, Zeilinga, Laguayra en Porto- Cabello. - Antje Haverbult, van Heuvelen, Petersb. - Posseidon. Deddes St. Thomas. &apos; IPSWICH, 25 Junij; Alida Dijk, do Haas, Engelholm. MIDDLESBKO, 25 Jnnij; Elisabeth Geertruida, Bonker, Hartlepool. - Geertruida, Lindeboom, Papenburg. - Gesina, Lindeboom, id. - J. &amp; A Brown, Wells, Dordrecht. SHIELDS,2S Junij; Claudine, Burkinshaw, Amst.-Agenoria, Pitt id- Palladium, Nesworthy, Nieuwediep. - Rurick, Hindom, ïd.-Drie Gebroeders, Hawkins, Carolinerzijl. ANCONA, 19 Junij; Gesina fr Jansje, Siegel, Rott. OPOItTO, 21 Junij; Colibri, Riednk, Rott. NEW-YORK, 12 Juuij; Crest of the Wave, Allen, Rott. BATAVIA, 7 Mei; Gelderland, Mulder, Amst. - Cornelia, Croese, id. - Cornelia Adolfina, de Roever, id. — 9 Mei; Argo, Ankringa, Rott. SOERABAYA, 1 Mei; Nederland en Oranje, Mulder, Nederland. BANJOEWANGIE, 16 April; Henriette Maria, Tjebbes, New-castle (Z. Z. W.) -18 April; Bilderdijk, Vietor, Lydney. STRAAT SUNDA, 28 April; Koophandel, Muller, Shiels n Sin-ap - County of Ayr, Spittall, Soerabaya n. Rotterdam.</p>
</text>
