<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>id. - Pollux, Sehröder,Nerva.-Penelope.Hutchinson,Riga.— 14 Aug.; Tjetska, Doewes, Wilmington. - Whim, Smith, Yarmouth. - Anna Mana, v. d Kooy, Archangel. - Clans Thomasson, Oelsen, Lulea. - Soeskumraeren, Lerentzen, Sundswall. (Benevens het schip per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 13 Aug.; Nora, S., Londen. -Wilhelm, Ringmacher, Petersburg.- Voorwaarts, Doewes, id. - Jacoba, Klaasscn, id. - Crescendo, Vos, id.- Alida Giezen, Nieland, Riga.- Wilhelmiua&amp; Ëiize. Wiersma, Stettin. - Salamander, Abrahamsen, Frederikstad. — 14 Aug.; Barteld Herman, Raskur, Petersburg. - Minerva, Schuurman, Arendahl. - Niord, Wilhemseu, Drobach. ZOLTKAMP, 12Aug.; Jantina, Smeltekop, Petersburg. - 4 Gebroeburg, Blok, id. - Jantje, Nijhoff, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 14 Aug.; Pelican, S., Liverpool. - Catharina, Wilkens, Newc. - Hawthorn, Trattles, Sunderland. - Anna, de Weerd, Petersburg. - Clara, Kraeft, Riga. - Zeemeeuw, Swart, id, - Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg. HAMBURG, 12 Aug.; Stoomvaart, S, Amst. ELSÊNEUR, 10 Aug.: gepasseerd: Arendina Catharina, Leeuwes, Dundee n. Kroonstad. - Jonge Jacob, Herman, Rott, n. Dantzig. Gezina Jantina, Albers, Gron. n. de Oostzee. - Familien, Aas, Dordrecht n. Sundswall. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 9 Aug.; Enjetta, de Boer, Grimsby n. Petersb.- Neerlands Vlag, Meeter, Zwolle n. id. - Adieu, Buchholtz, Frederikshaven n. Aaist. - Pieter, Oostwvink, Riga n. Edam. —10 Aug.; Maria Hm richs, Hes, Gloucester n. Koningsbergen. — 11 Zeemeeuw, v. Wijk, Petersburg n. Londen. - Johanna,Wilkens, Livorno n. Petersburg. - Aurora, de Jonge, Schiedam n. de Oostzee. - Anna Geertruida, v. Ingen, Newhaven n. id. - Orion, Braamhorst, Leer n. id. - Gesina, de Boer, Harlingen n.Petersburg. &lt;M .&apos; iv.&apos;/ BINNENGEKOMEN. TEXEL, 13 Aug.-, Sjonkina, de Jenge, Petersb. - Margaretha, Panman,</p>
	<p>FLENSBURG, 10 Ang.; Alf, Hansen, Amst. DANTZIG, 10 Aug.; Ondine, 8., Amst. BOLDERA, 8 Aug.; Jantina, Boon, Liverpool. — 9 Aug.; Freia, Olsen Amst. - Christiane, Michelsen, Nieuwe Diep. - Anna, Bleckert, Dordrecht. - Geziena Antina, v. Klooster, Aalborg. LONDEN, 11 Aug.; Herman Albert, Potjewijd, Petersburg. Bij DEAL, 10 Aug.; Ida Elizabeth, Dooren, Shields n. Bat. Bij DOVER. 12 Aug.; Kanagawa. Ouwehand, Newc. n. Bat. Bij de OWENS, 12 Ang.; Rota, Hanschell, Londen n. Bat. ROCHESTER, 12 Aug.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rotterdam. WHITEHAVEN, 11 Aug. Terug uit zee: Arm, Hughes, Rotterdam. EALMOUTH, 11 Aug.; Rosinante, Zomerdiik, Suriname met Order n. Bristol. —12 Aug,; Neptunus, van der Gaast, Havana. MACDUFF, 7 Aug.; Johanna Geerdina, Schoon, Dantzig. LIVERPOOL, 11 Ang. In lading: Janna Adriana, Franken, Suriname. HARWICH, 11 Aug.; Ouse, Mitchell, Amst.— 12 Aug.; Friesland, Boontje, Worcum n. Londen. II&apos;S&apos;WIOH, 11 Aug.; Niessina Jacoba, B-irelds, Passage. SHIELDS, 10 Aug.; Adriana Petronella, de Breuk, itott. - Claudine, Burkinshaw, Amst. -Catharina Johanna, Mulder, Petersburg. — 12Aug.; Vier Gebroeders, Woudstar, Dantzig. - Frouwina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Antwerpen. Euretta, Annis, Rott. GIBRALTAR, 6 Au.; Kleinkinderen, van der Wal, Vlaardingen. CADIX, 9 Aug.; Meppel, Stikkel van Dam, Antwerpen. NEW-YORK, 28 Julij; Arendina, Boerhavc, Sevilla. CALLAO, 30 Julij; Albertina, Brandt, Chinchos; (vertrok 5 Julij n. Hambnrg). SURINAME, 14 Julij. In lading: Cornelia Hendrika, Teensina, Amst. - Albatros, Koch, id. St. HELENA, 27 Junij; Zeenimph, Graadt van Roggen, Bat. n. Amst. - Cornelis Wcrnard Eduard, Swart, id. naar Rott. - (hebben de reis voortgezet.) SYDNEY (N. Z. W.), 27 Mei; Doesborgh, Spaanderman, Bat.</p>
</text>
