<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Mei; Stradella, Vick, Kustendje, 1. v. Falmouth. - Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, Londen. - Anna, Veltkamp, id. - Wilhelmina, Schuring, Frederikshald. - Balmoral, S., Rott. (benevens het schip per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 1 Mci; Nora, S., Londen. - Geertruida, de Groot, Oudsoen. HELVÖETSLUIS, 2 Mei; Pcnna, de Jong, Triest. - Levant, v. Gelderen Sr., Palermo. - Albatros, S., Liverpool. - Princess Royal, James, Whitehaven. - Albion, Mallet, Boness. - Palladium, Gray, Newc. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Mei; Gothenburg, S., Gothenburgn. Rott. LEER, 29 April; Helena, Gurseky, Groningen. ELSENEUR, 28 April; gepasseerd: Hendrika Frouwma, Muller, Stettin n. Londen. • Müwe, Kranse, Koningsb. n. Amst. HOLTENAU, 28 April; gepasseerd: Elisabeth, Schoon, Grenae n. Nederland. LONDEN, 1 Mei; John Howard, Crabtree, Amst. - Corneha, de Jonge, Worcum. - Lion, S., Harlingen. - In lading: Roelfina Johanna, Drewes, Amst. - Margaretha Mcijering, de Jonge, Dantzig. Bij TORBAY, 27 April; Loveley, Marcusscn, New-York n. Rott. Bij DEAL, 29 April; Minister Thorbecke, Kanuegieter, Rott. n. Buenos- Ayres. - Verwisseling, Scholten, Newport n. Elseneur. —30 April; Lichtstraal, Wierikx, Rott. n. Bat. - Ida Elisabeth, Doorcn, id. n. id. Bij WIGHT, 29 April; Aurora, Laarman, Cardiff n. Hamburg. Bij GOUDSTAART, 28 April; Anna Catharina, Huges, Bordeaux n. Rotterdam. CARDDjT, 28 April; Mc. Gillery, Nichols, Rott. GOOLE, 29 April; Trial, Johnson, Groningen. PORTSMOUTH, 29 April; Hillechien Wolkammer, Vos, Groningen. SHOREHAM, 30 April; Petronella Gesina, Stapert, Guernsey n. Amst. POOLE, 29 April; Margaretha Hendrika, do Boer, Southampton. GRANGEMOUTH, 28 Aprilf John and Harriet, Joy, Amst. HARWICH, 29 April; Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, Londen n. Worcum. NEWCASTLE, 27 April; in lading: H. Vincentius van Paulo, Nagel, Kroonstad. - de Zwerver, Schut, Malta. - Hendrika, Plukkor, Petersburg. - JohannaGeerdina,Schoon,id. , ii «&apos;&apos;&quot;&quot;&apos; m SHIELDS, 30 April; Gratitude, Bernard, Amst. - Elisabeth, Storm, id. - Alida Margaretha, Eisscs, Lynn. FALMOUTH, 29 April; Secundus, Rozema, Pentowan n. Stettin. HARTLEPOOL, 28 April; Beate, Jensen, Schiedam. GIBRALTAR, 22 April; Triton, de Jonge, Triest (vertrok n. Bordeaux). MALAGA, 24 April; Irene, S., Cagliari (vertrok n. Rott.) BOSTON (A), 15 April; Vereeniging, Kramer, Amst.l. v. New-York.</p>
</text>
