<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10 April; N. O.—N., Eubbens, S., Pillan. — Gisteren uog: Scotia, Lorentzen, Krageroe. YLIE, 9 April, N.N.0.; Onderneming, Kooiman, Osterrisoer.- Agina Undina, Pekelder, id.—lo April; Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 11 April, N.N.0.; Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Balmoral, S., Bristol. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. BREMERHAVE-.. 9 April; Geertruida, Rasker, Tonningen. FREDEEIKSTAD, 26 Maart; Simon &amp; Martina, Oldenburger, Nieuwediep. FEEDEIKSHAVN, 31 Maart; Geziena, Deen, Nyekjöb. n. Engeland. SWINEMUNDE, 8 April; Astrea, S., Amst, DANTZIG, 7 April; Alida Adriana, Kramer, KieL MEMEL, 5 April; Agina, Knijpenga, Purmerend. ELSENEUE, 7 April, Compasrond; Geziena Jantina, Bekkering, Stettin n. Leven. - Aikea, Dijk, Newc. n. Memel. LOiN DEN, 8 April: Karsina Harmina, Waterborg, Gron. HAETLEPOOL, 8 April; Princes Royal, Gibbs, Amst. SUNDEELAND, 7 April; Cornelia Catharina Hagedoorn, Harlingen. — 8 April; Zwaantina Margaretha, de Vries, Boul. SHIELDS, 6 April; Betje Pronk, Vos, Nieuwediep. Hendrika Ebeliena, Jonker, Eotterd. - Lambertha, Karst, Gend. — 7 April; Lncretia, Bracht, Harling.- Anna, Korf ker. id. - Alice, Smith, id. - Sunside, Tart, id. -EnaElisabeth, Smit, Dordr. — 8 April; Albert, Jaski, Amst. - Orion, Braamhorst, Schiedam. - 2 Broeders, Prins, Dordrecht. - Ardwell, Car, Zieriksee, - 2 Gezusters, Wolthuis, Maldon. BLYTH, 8 April; Grietje.de Weerd, Pothuis, n. Gothenb. LEITH, 8 April; Freundschap, Tobbens, Harlingen LI VEBPOOL, 6 April; Lucas Wildervank, Biks! Harlingen N EWPORT, 7 April; Gepbina, Lohman, Gloucester. &quot; Bij SCILLY, 6 April: Anaromache, . ? Padang n Rott Bij POETLAND, 8 April; Paulus Meintz, Venema, Antwerpen n. Cardiff. Bij WIGHT, 7 April; Lynet, Aarve, Samarang n. Amst. Bij DEAL, 1 April; Henriette Amalia, v. Uffelen, Memel n. Tabasco. _ Bij GOUD STAAET, 7 Aprü; Daniel Eankin, Hartwell. Banj oewangie n. Amst- Bij LIZAED, 6 April; Alhambra, Moulton, Banjoew. n. Amst. Bij LANDS END, 6April; Fearless,...,Montevideo n.Amst.</p>
</text>
