<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 24 Sept.; Adriana Johanna, de Vries, Buenos-Ayres. - Ondme, S., Bordeaux. - Fern, Turncl, Liverpool. - Volunteer, Purvis, Newc. - Professor Schwcigaard, Smidt, id. - Veracity, Gremer, id.- Triumph, Harris, id.- Zephyrus, Elliot, id.-Venus, Plogg, id. - Progress, Cocking, id.- Marwood, Runcoy, Sundcrland. - Port Wal lace, Taylor, id. - Benige, Lamb, id. - Sultana, Bell, id. - Premium, Adamsen, Seaham. - Hawk, S., Hull. - Simon &amp; Martina, Oldenburgcr, Riga.- Caroline, Gundersen, Sundswall.- Nina, S., Stockholm.- Freija, Gjersoe, Frederikstad.- Sylvia, Smit.Drammen. - Jenny, Oelsen,id.- Walhalla, Abrahamsen.id.-Adjutor,Erichsen, id. - Christiane, Hageusen, id. - Drafna, Nicolaysen, id. - Thetis, Hovpaard, id. - Doris, Becker, Avontuur. - Hiliechiua Gezina, Pik, id. VLIE, 23 Sept.; Cherubin, Ohman, Sundswall. - Jonge Rieka, Klef*, Christiania. - Elisabeth, Kuiper, Frederikstad. - Annechicna Engelina, Kuiper, id. - Vr. Martha, Ebes Jr., id. - Jonge Willem, Jager, id. - Sara„ Sikkes, Avont. - Fleur de Marie, Clems, id. - Leentje, Hoedemaker, id. llKLLEVOETSLUlS,24Scut.;AlidaCatharina,Nagel,Buenos-Ayres.-- Arnold Bóninger, Steenkcn, New-York, via Brouwershaven. - Acadie, Boer, St. John&apos;s, (Newfoundland). - Amalia Sinnige. Jansen, Triest.- Nieuwe Maas, v. d. Valk, Gibraltar. - Seine, S., Bordeaux. - 7 Sterrenr Hemmes, Cardiff. - Maria, Beekman, id. - lda Maria de Raath, de Boer, id. - Scottish Chief, Shilstone, Liverpool. - 4 November, Abrahamsen, Newc. - Favor, Sannes, id. - Ewcretta, Annis, id. - Utility, Ashcroft, id. - Friend of the Isles, Cooper, id. - Foam, Donough, id. - Jessie, Griffitbs.id. Star, Prince, id. - Conford, Matthews, id. - Thames, Cracknell, Ipswich. - Vernis, Gram, Noorwegen. - Aurora,Heeren, Hamburg. MAASSLUIS, 24 Scpt.; Elisabeth, Turner, Londen.- Bcliamy, v.Driesten, Newcastle. - Antje, Scholten, id. - Hensina, Meeter, id. - Juno, Bell, id. - Ocean, Storm, id.- St. Clair, Ross, id.-2 Frères, Marshall,id. Springflower, Pritchard, id. - Elisa, Oornish, Sundcrland. -Hunter, Sinclair.id.- Herman, Nutbroek, Hartlepool. - Allport, Annon, Seaham.- Bessie, Morday, Shields. - Elisabeth and Jane, Esson, Belfast.-Colonel Evaus, , Ryc. - Heinrich, Röttgers, Riga. - Barend, Hoeksema, Falkenberg. - Pax, llellema, Avontuur. -Diana, Schut, id. - Oostwolde, de Beer, ia. - Hermann, Tliede. Id. BROUWERSHAVEN, 24 Sept.; Bildcrdijk, Vietor, Rotterd. n. Bat. - Albrccht Beyling, v. d. Burg, n. Samar. GENT, 22Sept.; Wilhelmina, Poolman, Avontuur. N ANTES, 22 Sept.; Sarcelle, Lancelot, Rott.</p>
	<p>VIGO, 6 Sept.; Olasina, Sannes, Cadix.</p>
</text>
