<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Nov., W.—Z.O.; Rhöne, S., Middl. Zee. -Antoinette, r» curich, Newo. - Dorothea, Pedersen, id. - Cesaro, Vianello, id. - M»&apos; 0,. Purvis, id.- William &amp; Sarah, Rollason, id.- Peder Aneus, Buckhola*. . Heron, Lawson, Sunderland. - Elisabeth, Ward, id. - Brairly Hill, &quot;. jj, id. - Vivid, Dedlingfield, Seaham. - John Henry Yates, Toovey, id- &apos;£&apos;$,&apos; Smit, id. - Hubertus, Nichols, id. -Emilie Heyse, Lucas, Engeland.- *•-, man, Ingleby, id. - Hermnos, Haraldsen, Christiania.- Lougen. Job»&quot;&apos; . id. - Niels, Mörck, Frederikstad. - Christiane,Haagensen,Dram&quot;-*1.-j, 17de May, Knudsen, Arendahl.-Odin, Jörgensen, id.-Sverige.AndeïS^1* , HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Nov., Compasr.; Arendina, Boerhave, d^ . Ayres. - Pera, Pettersen, id. - Schiller, Minnemann, New-York. - J-*?^&apos;. de Jonge, Genua. - Morgenster, van Dijk, Gibraltar. - Star of the »» fc Carl, Londen. - Fidelity, Cole, id. - Usella, Hikken, id. - Argo, R&apos;c sbyv Nevvc. - Highland Maid, Backer, id. - Elizabeth, Cole, id. - Eva, Li&quot;&quot;1, .. id. - Bilpoint,, Johnson, id. - Alma, Lockyer, id. - Germauia, Tilm°&apos;pep Prince of Wales, Barlow, id. - Speedwell, Reddin, id. - Island Queen,* g, perell, id. - Spring, Bobertson, id. - Nicolaas, Rijf, id. - Clotilda, P*D{L,»-ham, id. - Julie, W ijken, id. - Harriet, Robinson, id. - Earl Grey, \\0v id. -F. Danovaro, Montano, id. - Hoffnung, Sonne, id. - Elizabeth, *s cfcr id. - Triton, Hoenke, id. - Martha Eding, Sprenger.id.-Baroness, &quot;c**jo(fr Sunderland. - Marg. West, Duchman, Middlesbro. - J. H. Eppiug, i&gt;&quot; ;n»f Engeland. - Emilie Farnum, Lord, id. - Anna Bertha, Halsert, id. -» Farm, id. - Jenny Lind, Oostborg, Koningsbergen. - Loreley, StoW&apos;.jj,, Oostzee. - Odin _¦ Catharine, Sylvertsen, Frederikstad.-Thor,o^. Drammen. - Fenua, Anderson, Heppens. - Germania, Blume, Avont&quot; , Brenda, Rolff, id. - Iramanuell, Groenewold, id. - Mary Arm, Krinkel» Maria Elisabeth, Sume, id. - Bazard, Christensen, id. BRIELLE, 12 Nov., Compasrond; Ravensbury, S., Harwich. , „jr, MAASSLUIS, 12 Nov.; Leo, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. - J°-j,op, Eisen barth, Cardiff. - Johanna, Lange, id. - Lisetta, Lunning, id.-M&apos;P,, J, Vuyk, id. - Janot Shennon, Pitt, Sunderl. - Eaglet, Bradbury, id. vL&apos;je, Enthoven &amp; Zn., Stomp, Newc. - Christine, Pedersen, id. - Meta, *&gt;.&apos;&apos;^ id. - Ano, Winther, Hartien. - Catbrine, Andorsen, id. - George e* ,-i^d*- Brown, Shields. - Alice, Ydam, Windau. - Ville de Pontersan, R°u.^, Avont. - Martha, Burichsen, id. - Adèle, Grovalet, id. - Jacob, Frue, Jeune Fanny, Matturin, id. „ netd&apos; BROUWERSHAVEN, 12 Nov., Z 0.; Bosphorus, Mc.Nabb, »olv&gt; n. Newc.</p>
	<p>FALMOUTH, 10 Nov.; Ceres, Meuldijk, de Weser. CARDIFF, 9 Nov.; Marie Elise, vau Deursen, Bombay. SWANSEA, 8 Nov.; Celeritas , Bahia. LIVERPOÓL, 9 Nov.; Zeemanshoop, Dekker, St. Thomas. CADIX, 5 Nov.; Speculant, Nylant, Bahia. BILBAO, 3 Nov.; Goede Bedoeling, Brummer, de Clyde. VENETIË, 8 Nov.; de Vlijt, Engelsman, Triest. TRIEST, 5 Nov.; Cycloop, S., Rott. . nr&gt;r.Oce*° NEW-YORK, 26 Oct,; zeilkl.: Salicr, Miesgaes, Rott. —28 Oct., &lt;- Star, Cavall, id. *</p>
</text>
