<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 17 Aug., W. Z. W.; Medea, van Teutem, Bat. - Industrie, Hikken, Baltimore. - Freija, Mulder. Odessa. - Gcertruida, Pot. Lissabon. - Cuba Packet, Rapp, Havre. - Vrodclust, Brouwer, Duinkerken. - Maggie Lorimer, Taylor, Londen. - 2 Broeders, Stenders, id. - Hoop, Visser, id. - Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, id. - Perseverance, Elliott, id.-Grace, Barrow, id. - Sir John Bowes, Wright, Newc. - Margareth. Chambers, Sunderl. - Hylton Maid, Anderseu, Seahara. - John Henry Yates, Toovey, id., met verlies van voormarssteng en ra, en met meer andere schade. - Christinn, Petersen, Archangel. - Piet Hein, Visser, Petersburg. - Triton, Eurghout, Riga. - Pekela, Jonker, SöndswalL — Gisteren nog: Agatha Ebeling, Hoeksma, Londen. VLIE. 17 Aug., W. Z. W.; Eendragt. Dorenbos, Newcastle. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 17 Aug., W. Z. W.; Bordeaux, S.. Bordeaux. - Sylphide, Marshal. Londen. - Alice. Warel, Rochester. - Ariel, Cappock, Poterhead. - Violet, Richardson, Newcastle. - Princess, Purkes, id. - Fricnd of the Isle, Cooper, Helinsdale. — Gisteren nog: Mereure, Masalin, Vlissingen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 17 Ang., Germania, Uhabrock, Baltimore n. Rott. - Eulalia, Westerlund, New-York n. id. BIRKENHEAD, 16 Aug.; Maria Regina, Ouwehand, Amst. St. THOMAS. 19 Julij; Zeenimph, Schipper, Cardiff. — 22 Julij; Augnata, van Veen, Liverpool. SURINAME, 4 Julij; Dolphijn. Bryant, Liverpool. LONDEN, 15 Ang.; Alice, Beliard, Rott. - John Allan, Hom, id. Bij DUNGENESS, 14 Aug.; Alida, Visser, Amst. n. Buenos-Ayres. FALMOUTH, 16 Aug.,- Br», ö, Albrecht, Taganrog n. Rott. DEAL, 14 Aug.; Catharina, Thaden, Amst. n. Napeh. — 16 Aug; Vooruit, ..., Stokholmn. Beyruth. CHARLESTOWN, 14 Aug.; Caroline Kirstine, Larsen, Amst. - Fenna, Woudsma, Newbnrgh. LEITH. 15 Aug.; Vertrouwen, Wesseling, Cambns. SHIELDS, 15 Aug.; John &amp; Arm, Ford, Rott. -Providentin. Arens- Schiedara. - Rndolp Donovaro, Croco, Amst.- Vriendschap, Ellis, id. William &amp;¦ Sarah, Rolason, Dordt.- Maarhnizen, Kladder, Groningen. &quot; Mngdalena Sophia, Pauken, Nieuwediep. - Ellen, Bang, Rott. - Richard Cobden. Jacobsen, Schiedam. HARTLEPOOL, 14 Aug.; Beuedicte, Thorgesen, Schiedam. SEAHAM, 14 Aug.; Jane Spoors, Brunning, Schiedam. GIBRALTAR, 8 Aug.-, Giulia, Jacobsen, Girgenti n. Rott. St. ÜBES, 10 Ang.; Levant, Stam, Malta. DEMERARY, 22 Jnlrj; Zr. Ms. stoomschip Vice-Admiraal Rijk, comm. van Wilgen, Suriname.</p>
</text>
