<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 20 April; Jane, Rolleson, Newc. - Nummer Eins, Brokschjw- Elise Francoise, Ledante, Sunderland. • Ronaldus, Kilvingston, Hartlepool- Bosphorus, Holst, Grimstad. „ ... VLIE, 20 April; Elisabeth Lollina, Carst, Yarmouth. - Remeha _W« trnida, Katoen, Christiania. - 2 Frères, Lomele, Newc. - Jonge &amp;&lt;*&quot; Wondsma, Arendahl. ZOLTKAMP, 19 April; Ecliptica, Hoeksma, Londen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 20April; Batavia,Zwanenburg,Newc- Weiva»&apos; Ekamp, id. - Albert, S., Huil. - Magrietha, Kapper, Windau. - Zeemeem» van Wijk, id. - Nation&apos;s Hope, Lake, Gothenburg. - Elve, S., Hemburg. BROUWERSHAVEN, 20 April; Princes Amalia, v. Rijn v. Alkenwaiv Rott. n. Bat. y. MAASSLUIS, 20 April; Triumph, Gaze, Newc. - Fifteen, Fender^w&gt; Maris Stella, Blanchet, id. - Louwina, Heerma, Leith. - Zwaantje^ Heijenga, Avontuur. - Govert van Wijn, Versteeg, de Noordzee. - tu»nu Maatschappij, Schep, id. - De Hoop, v. d. Wind, id. (allen wel in zee). ARENDAL, 4 April; Maria, Meinsma, Harlingen. LONDEN, 18 April; zeilkl.: Catharina Ricardi,Meyer, Coldmg. -wu» en Clara, Stasse, Aarhuus. — 19 April; Annctte, Wachter, Koningsberg»- WHITEHAVEN, 18 April; John and JameS, Clayton, Rott. PAIMBOEUF, 15 April; Alfred, Ledere, Rott. — 17 April; Annecnw Hermina, Zuidema, Amst. St. NAZAIRE, 18 April; Mystcre, Emère, Nederland. CADIX, 15 April; Antonius, Gonningen, Hamburg. m GIBRALTAR, 10 April; Voorwaarts, Douwes, Falmouth. - Aren*&quot;&apos; Boerhave, Rio Grande.</p>
	<p>NAPELS, 9 April; Irene, S., Messina. BALTIMORE, 5 April; Duisburg, Hollj es, Rott. ■ NEW-YORK, 7 April; zeilkl.: Vereeniging, Kramer, Boston, na gc° digde reparatie. , ,f. BUENOS-AYRES, 1 Maart; Maria Cornelia, Bnnkennk, Paysanau-2 Maart; Catharina Hermanna, Douwe Visser, Antwerpen. — 6 Maart; Robert Peel, Lange, Oost-Indie. nf «atU 810 JANEIRO, 12 Maart; Gesina, Olthuis, Fernambuck. — 13 W» Friesland, Sipkes, Amst. n. Batavia (na geëindigde reparatie). — 21 M*» Anton en Jacob, Ouwehand, Hamburg.</p>
</text>
