<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>. TEXEL, 5 Junij, Z. W.*, Diana, S., Londen. - Norval, Sacky, Ne we.&apos; Countess of Zetland, Baynes, Seaham. - Jane, Flemming, Sunderl. - European, S., Huil. - Hawk, S., id. - Erqilie, S., Stettin n. Rott., als bijlegger. • J. D. Caroline, Abrahamsen, Osterrisoer. VLIE, 4 Junij, W.Z.W.; Nora, S., Londen, - Leentje, Hoedemaker, Memel. — 5 Junij; Jan &amp;• Androas, Doyen, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Junij, W.; Margaretha, Meincke, Manzanilia. • Pioneer, S., Londen. - Superior, Hitchins, Runcorn. - Rosé, Champlia Boness. - James, Sterry, Newc. - Malcolm, Pattison, id. - Sliedrecht, S. id. - Ardwell, Walker,id.-Baltic, Milburn,id. Arthur Fawcus, Dixon, - Middlesbro. BRIELLE, 5 Junij, W.—Z.; Aveion, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 5 Junij, W.; Scandia, Olsen, Malaga n. Rott. ZIERIKZEE, 5 Junij, Z. W.; Alexandra, Voccos, Odessa n. Rott. Temperance, Keams, Runcorn n. Dordt.- Isabella, Storm, Newcastle. HAMBURG, 3 Junij; Willem I, S., Amst. — 4 Junij; Drei Gebrüder Gierz, id. HOYER, 30 Mei; Wilhelmina, Meyer, Franeker. DANTZIG, 1 Junij; Harmina, Emmelkamp, Harburg. MEMEL, 30 Mei; Alberdina Fokkelina, Schuur,Rostock. — 31 Mcii Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Lübeck. - Roelfina Johanna, Drewcs, Stettin.- Jacoba Catharina, Geltes, id. STOKHOLM, 28 Mei; Frouwina Elisabeth,Schenk, Amst.- Janti_i» Roelfina, Broekema, id. SANDHAMN, 30 Mei; Anrelio Gruno, Stuitje, Amst. WIND AU, 28 Mei; Loreley, Stoorman, Amst. BOLDERA, 30 Mei; Carolina, Cupido, Amst. —31 Mei; Richard Cobden, Stibolt, id. KROONSTAD, 4 Junij; Phenix, Veldhuis, Newc. Bn&apos; KOPENHAGEN, 3 Junij; Heinrich, Koster, Harl. n. Riga. - Jouge Andries, Steffens, Amst. n. Petersb. KOPENHAGEN, 3 Junij; Drie Gezusters, Plukje, Dokkum. - Arme Maria, Mannoe, Amst. . LONDEN, 4 Junij; Zwaantina Margrietha, de Vries, Oscarshamn. • Twee Zusters, Feenstra, Worcum. PLYMOUTH, 3 Junij; de Waardon, Agtien, Buen.-Ayres (om order). FALMOUTH, 3 Junij; Jessiana, Andrews, Java n. Amst. - Wildervauüi Giezen, Rio-Grando (om order). SEAHAM, 2 Junij; Juan, Soloman, Dor.lt. CARDIFF, 1 Junij; Balmoral, S., Bristol. _ _ LIVERPOOL, 2 Junij; Sarah and Jane, Turgose, Amst. - Gandet, b. Rotterdam. WEST-HARTLEPOOL, 3 Junij; Geertjedina, de Buhr, Heppens. SUNDERLAND, 1 Junij; Cassandra, Laidler, Nieuwediep. SHIELDS, 3 Junij; Jantina, Pekelder, Schiedam. - Renske, NeppeiU&apos;. Sandwich. LEITH, 1 Junij; Bessie Jamieson, West, Rott. SHEERNESS. 2 Junij; Willemina, de Jonge, Groningen. Bij OUEENSTOWN, 4 Junij; Charlotte Lee, Wilson, Trinidad n. Amst GIBRALTAR, 26 Mei; Everhardus, Vos, Triest n. Hamburg. PALERMO, 24 Mei; Bérénice, S., Messina. KONSTANTINOPEL, 25 Mei; Archimedes, S., Taganrog; vcrtroiï n* NEW-YORK, 21 Mei; Amalia, Silberschmidt, Boston (omvoorßoü te laden). __ _, __. 11en Hoorne, Frudden, Havana.</p>
</text>
