<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 29 Atig , N.W.-.N.; Ada, Roberts, Euncora.-Hawk, S., Hnll. — 30 AttffJ Holyrood, S., Leilh. VLIE, 28 Ausr., N. W.; Johanna Jnhl, Schilder, ArcbanmL - Anna, Jiahlsc-n, Stockholm. - Geertje Pot, Tan, Memel. ZOLTKAMP, 26 Ang.; Eureka, de Groot, Areh. — 27 Aug.; Piefcerrie, Kramer. Newe. - Martha, Nieboer, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 29 A«&amp;, N.W.;Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Batavia, 1. v. Brouwershav.; verte, 9 Mei. - Burn L&apos;rae, &apos;i&apos;ucker, St. Anna, 1. y,id.-Sv«Sge,BadiaNawTorlr,l.v.id.*Seine, S., Bordeaux. — Gisteren nog: Albert, S.,Hull. — 30 Aug.; Invicta, Hopkins, Éócheater, - S.WMiland, S., Hall. - Gottfiied, Jongebloed, Ai&apos;ehange]. — Gisteren nog.- Admiraal Ver-HueL S., ïlavre. - Anna Harboe, iicrborl, Arcli. BRIELLE,3O Aug., W.; Watcrloo, S., Londen.-Sheffield, S., Grimabv. - Zealous, S„ Harwie-fa- BROUWERSHAVEN, 39 Ang.. N.W .;Expert Husher, Newcastle n. Rott. — 30 Ang.-, Slisawu, Wray, ïd. u. id. - CjpüaD, Cbristianseu. Sundssv. n.Dordt. LEER, 26 Ang.; GeertraJds, Pronk, HarL KOPEHHAGEN, 27 Aug.; Sophie, Arnesen, skelettea naar Dordrecht, . HEPPENS, 24 Ang.: Arlelbeid, Chnstoffers. Bott. MEMEL. 25 Ang.-.Tjakina de Boer, Dost, Renasburg. WINDAU. 19 Aug.; Hoop, Boer, Rott. BOLDERA, 24 Ang.; Wodan, Memders, Ainsterd. - Johanna Adriana, Sikkens.id.&apos; „ KROONSTAD, 24 Ang.; Zwerver. Hagedonrn, layerpi Antje, Oostenreld, Newe. — 35 Aug.; Alphard, Puister, Burnt- Eilaud. - Eersteling, Wiersuia, Gritnsby. SHIELDS, 26 Aug.; Jobn &amp; Mm. 1 riieinan.Rott.roöt verlies van groote steng. - Isabella, Pnrkess, /lierikzee.— 27 Aug.; Annachiona, Jonker. Londen. , „ , GUEENSEY, 26 Ang.. Eollo, Schep, Rott PALMOüTH.27Aug.;Mej.Piet&apos; Jl&apos;O-nga.Kßfkon», Lissabon n.Pcterêb.—23 Aiig.; JautmaMargaretha,Vos Peper, Rio Gr.&apos; , MESSINA, 2i) Aug.; Krommenie, Engelsman, Rofcfc, KALXAB,2oAng.;Otto,Sap* Lagnayra „.i; KONSTANTDJOPEL. 15 Ang.: Btepno, Potjer.Cardiir.— 16 Ancr.-. Ma, Bielich, Beidianaki n. Bott •VORK, 15 Ang,; Aunie Troop, droop, Rott</p>
</text>
