<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen. BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 4 April, Compasrond; Meiea, S., Dantzig. - Fem Södstre, Knudsen, Frederikstad. - Mabella, Christophersen, Drammen. — öApril; Alphonse Marie, Lapré, Nantes. -Swan, Davison, Newc. - Marcareth Potter, Chambers, Middlesbro. - Hawk, S., Hull. VLIE, 4 April, Z. 0.; Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. - Hereende, Towning, Middlesbro. HELLEVOETSLUIS. 4 April, N. W.; Louise &amp; Arm, James, St. Valery. - Thomas Varcoe, Couth, Liverpool. - Maria, Sörensen, Windau.- Rotterdam, S-, Pillau.-Franz, Perrau, Stettin.— 5 April; Cornelia, Nieboer, Nantes. -Willia-n George, Wales, Cowes.-Swanland, S., Hull. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. - Elwine, Schwanck. Stockholm. - Martha, Nieboer, Dantzig. - Willem de Derde, S., Stettin. - Ridderkerk, Bunk, Nieuwediep. — Gisteren nog: Ary Seheffer, S., Havre. BRIELLE, 5 April; Z.W; Prins v. Oranje, S.. Duinkerken.- Waterloo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. ZIERIKZEE, 2&apos;April, N. 0.; Grimaldi, Hill, Liverpool.— 3 April; Mary, Lovell, Newcastle. EMDEN, 30 Maart; Aurora, Gerhards, Borkum. - Elisabeth, Visser, id. — 31 Maart; Harmina, Staghouwer, id. BREMERLiAVEN, 2 April; Maria Catharina, Koops, Delfz. HAMBURG, 2 April; Johanna, Brouwer, Amst. KOPENHAGEN, 31 Maart; Gezina, de Boer, Dokliuni. DANTZIG, 1 April; Alida, Borgman, Termunterzijl. - Antje, Leeuw, &apos;\ntwerp. - Adriana, Meijer, Newc. PILLAU, 1 April; Altnon, Me&apos;ijering, Londen. MEMEL, 31 Maart: Ulrika, Dik, Libau. ELSENEUR, 1 April; Afiena, Meilema, Wolgast n. Antw. — 2 April; Willem de Derde, S., Stettin n. Schiedam. RENDSBUBG, 30 Maart; Harmina, Emmelkamp, Kiel n. Rochester. — 1 April; Trijntje Meijer, Tonckens, Hamburg n. Nyborg. — 2 April; Catharina, Ulrichs, Dokkum n. Svendb. - Antje, de Boer, Assens n. de Maas. LONDEN, 2 April; Kathleen, Chappel, Rott. - Vesper. Armitage, id. - Martenshoek, Schut, Groningen.- Catharina Houwink, Wiersina, Leeuwarden.—3 April; Eendragt, Willinga, id. Bij DOVER, 2 April; Vlaardingen, v. d. Boogert, Newc. - Riek&apos;a, Puister, id. n. Porto, Bij EDDYSTONE, 1, April; Haemstede, Geerling, Rott. n. Middelburg. - Susan, Spencer, id. n. Halifax. Bij DUNGENESS, 31 Maart; Catharina, Thaden, Hull n. Barcelona. Bij GOUDSTAART, 30 Maart; Ymuiden, de Jong, Bat. n. Amst, — 1 April; Volharding, Pander, Middelb. n. Liverpool. BRISTOL, 2 April; Jacoba, de Weerd, Grouingen. CARDIFF, 2 April; General Shipley, Dinsmore, Rott. LEITH, 1 April-, Anna Augusta, Kuiper, Terschelling. SHIELDS, 2 April; Jansjen, Meijer, Zwolle. HARWICH, 2 April; Eagle, Hawkins, Rott. BORDEAUX. 2 April; Gironde, S., Rott. MALTA, 18 Maart; Annachiena, Smit, Barletta. ANCONA. 21 Maart; Triton, de Jonge, Tromsö. DARDANELLEN, 21 Maart; Reppen, Coruelius, Ibraila n. Rotterdam. „ KONSTANTINOPEL, 23 Maart, Isabella, Smith, Galatz n. Schiedam. BATAVIA, 17 Febr.; Princes Amalia, v. Bentveld, Liverpool. — 18 Febr.; Tollens, Verhagen, Cardiff; 23 dito n. Cheribon vertr. — 21 Febr.; Christina, Remeeus, Amst.; 26 dito n. Soerabaija vertr.— 22 Maart; Sumatra, Ned. Oorl. Stoomschip, luit. ter zee lste kl. Dronkers, Hellevoetsluis.— 24 Febr.; Java, Ned. Oorl. Stooin-transportschip, kapt. luit. ter zee Damme, Texel. ----------------------------------------------------|</p>
</text>
