<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 3 Dcc; Maria Catharina, de Bos, Bat., vertr. 14 Aug. - 3 Gezusters, Fischer, id., vertr. 25 Aug. - Australië, Lucas, id., vertr. 26 Aug. - Hendrik Jan Nassau, Roelfsema, Riga. .V, Schack Retzendorf, Bruss, id. - Vulcan, Nielsen, Hudickswall. VLIE, 1 Dec.; Jacoba Catharina, Wildeboer. Petersb. - Jacoba Lncretia Maas, Riga. - Agatha, Schuar, Dantzig. - Alida Sinnige, Dik, Stettin. Anneehina Elsina, Kuiper, Gothenb. - Gustaaf, 3e Jong, Frederikst. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 3 Dcc; ZuidLaren, Drenth, Triest. - Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Enjetta, de Boer, Newc. - Hope, Couch, id. - Alida, Sprik, Petersb. - Jonge Rieka, Klei&quot;. Windau - Persa, Drenth, Riga. - Verwisseling, Kar.ten, id. - Concordia, Aden, Libau.- BRIELLE, 3 Dec.; Cologne S Londen. - Ravensbury, S., Harwich BROU WERSHAVEN Androineda, Dannberg, Samarang n. Rott., vertr 16 Augustus. VLISSINGEN, 3 Dcc- Johanna, Udema, D.ntzig. - Reinier, de Jonee Libau. - Katharina, Culberts,Wyborg- - Sara, Smit, Riga.. Tjadda Ge.ma&apos; Staal, R&apos;ga. &apos; BREMERHAVEN, 2 Dcc • Confiance, Brongers, Petersburg. . Lambertha, Karst, id. HAMBURG, 1 Dcc; I.aac Sannes, de Jonge, Sevilla.. Jacobu3, Lanker Brazilië. —2 Dcc; Jonge Arie Collentenr, Malaga. ulker&apos; CÜXHAVEN, 1 Dcc; Diana, Fijn, Dantzig. - Imanael, Markman Amst n. Aarhuus. EMDEN, 25 Nov.; Gesina, Hesse, Sneek. KOPENHAGEN, 30 Nov.- gepasseerd: Reval, Gühlstorff, R*2a n Amaf LONDEN, 2 Dcc: Arendina, Boerhave, Rio Grande. - Bro.dertronw Vos, Petersburg. - Herman Wieher, van der Laan, Gron.- Vissch.riPor tuin, Worcum. - Herstelling VaD &apos;t Veer, id. &quot;&quot;!&gt; *or Bij DUNGENESS, 1 Dei- Jacob en Titia, Prak, Hambllrg n G;b.„ltnr 30 Nov.; Onderneming, Feenstra, Anfw. n. Buenos- FALMOUTH, 2 Dcc; Rböne, S., Amst. n. Genua. PoirDiL/6^ Dordt. - Arm Beer, HansS^S; ROCHESTER, 1 Dcc; Brothers Success, Hobart, Rott.. john *. rh , Carlton id - Alida Dijk, dc Haas, Gron. - Gesina Jantina, Be^&quot; «f* Gebroeders Visser, Faber id &gt; &quot;«&quot;Kering, id. YARMOUTH, 1 Dee./Anna Meta, Ulrich, Gron. SUNDERLAND, 1 Dec.; Messenger, Payne, Nieuwedien -C_r_i;_. Agnes, Croft, ,d. -HWd_ika, Visser, Amst. - J _e. Gesina,,,., Lbeck? • BORDEAUX, 1 Dec.; Albertha Roemeling, de Vries, Big». • 0&amp;&amp; Jantina, Kwint, id. - Broederschap, Bakker, id. MARSEILLE, 30 Nov.; Irene, S., Amst. VENETIË, 27 Nov.; Vertrouwen, Kal, Hammerfest.&apos;- Annegin»»&apos;1-&apos; ker,id. BUENOS-AYRES, 15 Oct.; Anna Maria, van der Kooy, Cardifl-25 Oct.; Concurrent, de Jonge, Paranagua.— In lading: Noordhofl.&apos;*&apos; Leeuwen, Antwerpen. - Stella Matutina, Beekman, id. RIO JANEIRO, 25 Oct.; Udo Frederik, van der Werff, Buenos-Ay«s&apos; 1 Nov.; Castor, Kloppenburg, Cardifl. FERNAMBUCK, 1 Nov.; Gezina, Doekes, Antwerpen. RIO GRANDE, 3 Oct.; Hermine Sc Elise, Olderding, Glasgow. „„ MONTEVIDEO, 21 Oct.; Wilhelmina &amp; Elise, Wiersma, Londen. * tharina, Stuven, Patagonie. — 23 Oct.; de Vrede, Niekns, Buenos-Ayr«Si 25 Oct.; Kaapstad Facket, Niewold, Rott. BAHIA, 27 Oct.; Marchina, Nepperus, Rio Grande. HAVANA, 9jNoy.; in lading: Havana Packet, Harken, Antwerpen.</p>
</text>
