<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>VLIE, 17 April; Magnet, S., Londen. - Nijssina, Prak, Christiansand. OSTM AHORN, 14 April; Pietronella, de Vries, Newc. - Gesiena Jantina Alberts, id. — 15 April; Familieiishaab, Meinertz, Aarhuus. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 18 April; Philips van Marnix, van Ruijven, Banjoew., 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Annachiena, Buil, Rügenwalde. BRIELLE, 18 April; Albert, S.,Hull. BROUWERSHAVEN, 18 April; Bidderkerk, Molenaar, Bat. n.Rott., vertr. 23 Dec. - Princes Amalia, v. Rijn v. Alkemade, Rott. n. Bat. - Hendrik Ido Ambacht, Bijl id. n. id. VLISSINGEN, 18 April; Eendragt, Kamminga, Greifswald. CUXHAVEN, 17 April; Gouverneur van Ewijck, S., Amst. BREMERHAVEN, 15 April; Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Hamburg. - Aaltina Hendrika, Meijer, id. S WINEMUNDE, 14 April; Hermanna Das, Das, Nowc. ■ Jantje, Muller, Bergen. DANTZIG, 14 April; Hillechina Catharina, Boekhont, Vlissingen.- Araicitia, de Groot, Delfzijl. — 16 April; Vriendschap, Visser, Amst. LEBA, 14 April; Twee Vrienden, Ebes, Amst. GOTHENBURG, 11 April; Gakthea, Wcsterberg, Messina. WARGÖ, 6 April; Amsterdam Racket, Thiis, Amst. RIISOER, 1 April; R&apos;enske, Pot, Delfzijl.— 3April; Helena Gesina, Sehrcudcr, id. - Cornelia, Jcntscma, id.-6 April; Pieter, Oostervink, Edam.- Aiien Smit, Boswijk, Brake. - Aaltje Bloema, de Jonge, Delfzijl. - Jan Gijsbert, Smit, id. - Catharina Luitgardina, Bos, id. - Aldershof, Dijkstra, id. — 7 April; Wilhelm, dc Boer, Harlingen.- Geerdina, Duintjer, Delfzijl. - Prince Albert, Svcndsen, Dordt. KOPENHAGEN, 12 April; Annechien en Jantje, Venema, Antwerpen.- Eendragt, de Boer, id. ELSENEUR, 13 April; Gepasseerd : A ctiv, Kronberg, Malmoe n. Nederland. — 15 April; Jacobus Antonie, Mellema. - Aaltje Brongers, Kuperus. - Barteld Herman, Rasker. - Lubbegina, Borgman. TONNINGEN, 13 April; gepasseerd: Anna, Kuiper, Amst.n. Stettin. 14 April; Concordia, Speelman, Groningen n. Seeland. - Jansima, Buisman, Breinen n. Stettin. - Alida Ikea, Pieper, id. n. Kopenhagen. TONNINGEN, 14 April; Reinegina, Tonkens, Amst. LONDEN, 17 April; Stad Worcum, Stendei-, Worcum. - Jonge Ank je Balk, Dokkum. - Antina, de Vries, Gron. - Jacobus Begeman, Reijer, id. - Vier Gebroeders, Blok, id. - In lading: Anna, Veldkamp, Am.t. - Elisabeth, Timmens, id. - Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, id. - Annette, Wachter, Koningsbergen. Bij FALMOUTH, 14 ApriljCuracao, Takcs, Curacao n. Amst. FALMOUTH, 16 April; Maria, Scotto, Java n. Amst. - Gesina, Lindeboom, Galatz n. Koogerpolder. Bij DEAL, 15 April; Nina, Huisman, Brazilië n. Antw. —16April; Nicoline, Winter, Java n. Amst. DOVER, 16 April; Vr. Elisabeth, Top, Gron. Bij DOVER, 15 April; JoUanna Jacoba, Velt, Marseille n. Yarmoutb. Bij DONGENESS, 15 April; Staatsraad van Ewijck, Ham, Amst. n. Bat. - Anna Sophia, Hoekstra, id. n. id. - Raphael, van de Velde Smit, id. n. Bü9LL_ARD, 13 April; FlyingEagle, ...., St. Domingo n. Rott.&quot; BRISTOL, 16 April; Burgemeester Dannenberg, Visser, Groningen. HARWICH, 16 April: Frouke, Hein., Groningen. - Hoogezand, van Driesten, id. , _ . .. ._ , YARMOUTH, 15 April: Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Newburg. - 16 April; Jonge Pieter, Kolle, Harlingen. . , , _, MACDUFF, 15 April; Dolphijn, Hazcwinkel, Genua. MIDDLESBRO, 15 April; Cornelia, Cramer Rott. SIIIELD3, 13 April; Catharina, blmger, Harl. — IG April; Joh.Wühelinina, Faber, Amst. - Fame, Hcnrichs, id.-Keiiitjc,Teeiisma, id. - Zwaantin.., Gruppelaar, id. - Sara, Visser, id. - Kedite, Hoveling, id. - Alexander Ahrenberg, id. - Die Palme, Gallas, id. - Alida Pronk, Scholtens, Hamb. ■ Britannia, Clayton, Rott. - Elizabetb, Yallop, id. - Prornetheus, Bradhering, id. - Prudence, Bruining, Zwolle. - Fenna, Coerkamp, Alkmaar. - Aurora, de Jong, Schiedam. - Eersteling,Wiersma, id. - Maria,Tuuteler, id. - Advena Hales, Nieuwediep. - Qucen of Tyno, Bedlington, id. - Zephyrus, Elliot, id. - ; Christino. Voss, Middelb. - Alma, Bowbyes, Zierikzee. - Dirkje, Burguout, Harl. - 11. Viiieentius van Paulo, Nagel, Antwerp. - Proteus, Zeven, Dordt. NEWCASTLE, 11 April, In lading : Helena Christina, Leurs, Dantzig.- Lucretia, Bracht, id. - Stella Maris, Harding, Koningsbergen. - Crescendo, Vos, Elsenenr. — 12 April; Petronclla, Leieher, Bat.- Gesina Jantina,Kboster, Petersb. - Wilhelmina, Oortgicse, Dantzig.- AnnaCath., de Vries, Riga.- Henriette, Smit, Bergen. — 13 April; Galilei, Vos, Carthagena. - Aukje, Teensina, Petersburg. - Dirkje, Burghout, Memel. - Vesta, Tobbens, id. - Zwaan, Riedijk, Lissabon. S UNDERLAND, 15 April; Olivia, Ordronnean, Rott. - St. Jean, Jugeau, id. - Guilia R-, Repetto, Amst.</p>
	<p>ROCHESTER, 16 April; John and Charle., Hopkins, Eott. • Anna He* drika, Mulder, Groningen. | __\\ I WELLS, 16 April; Voorwaarts, de Vries, Gron;ngen. STOCKTON, 15 April; Hopewell, Pearson, Rott. GIBRALTAR, 8 April; Alwina, Bette, Livorno. — 10 Ai ril; Arenoia»! Boerhave, Triest. - Voorwaarts, Douwes, id. MALAGA, 9 April; Rotterdam, S., Palermo (vertrok n. Rott.) mTJ_.TiM.TT •&gt;. Anril-TTn/nrd.Koster. Triest.</p>
</text>
