<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen. BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 17 Oct.; Gerredina Wilhelmina, v. d. Zee, Padang. vertr. 2&apos; Junij; Irene, S., Middell. Zee. - Sophia Maria, Teensma, Petersb. - Ja«°&apos; bus Anthonie, Mellema, Riga. - Bulgerstein, v. Wijngaarden, Sundswal- - Lougen, Johansen, id. - Enigheden, Gullichsen, id.- Scandinavien, AugeD* sen, Sundswall. VLIE, 16 Oct.; Sappemeer, Rosenberg, Petersburg. -Fortuna, Zwaai&apos; Riga. - Jonge Jacob, Herman, Frederikstad — 17 oct.;Hollandia,S-i Londen. - Hermanus Gerhardus, Mulder, Middlbr. - Jonge Pieter, Col&apos;9&apos; Petersburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 17 Oct.; Louis, Bolwin, New-York. - Georg * Emily, Brown, Taganrog, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Highland Maid, Baker, CaeH- Zephyr, S., Londen.- James Eankins, S., Glasgow.- Lord Raglan, S., Ne*[ Castle. - Bradford, S., Grirasby. - Rotterdam, S., Stettin. — Gisteren n&lt;&gt;Ép Maarten van Rossem, Wiebenga, Bat., l.v. Brouwersh. - Anna Maria, H» 1&quot; bye, Petersb. BROUWERSHAVEN, 17 Oct., Z.W; Cortgene, Wemmerus Pzn, B»»&apos; joewangie n. Rott; vertr. 6 Julij. - Wilhelmina, Willenbrinck, Newyor* n. id. - Ceres, de Haan, Livorno n. Dordtrecht. MBREMERHAVEN, 16Oct.;Lubina.Hazelhoff,Memel.-Aukje.de Bo9f&apos; Smith, Hamburg. — Reina, Kruisinga, id. HAMBURG, 15 Oct.; Hammonia, 8., Rott. DRAMMEN, 5 Oct.; Anna, Andersen, Nieuwediep.-Lympha, Eliasse»&apos; Purmerende. BERGEN, 1 Oct.; Noordstar, Hartogh, Antwerpen. Bij! KOPENHAGEN, 12 Oct.; Ems, Eilers, Petersb. naar Zaandam- •*&quot; 13 Oct.; Hansine, Thomsen, id. n. Dordt. - Meta, Ratje, id. n. de Maas. -&quot; 15 Oct.; Engelina, Kouter, id. n. id. - Oostzee, v. d.Weyden, id. n. Dordt-&apos; Titia Margaretha, Schaap, id. n. Malmö. KOPENHAGEN, 15 Oct.; Modcratie, Scholten, Petersburg. STOCKHOLM, 8 Oct-, Redite, Hoveling, Petersb. S ANDHAM, 11 Oct.; Alberdina, v. d. Bos, Petersburg. ELSENEUR, 14 Oct.; Anna. Klontje, Petersburg n. Nederland. LONDEN, 15 Oct.-, Wilhelmina, de Groot, Groningen. LEITH, 14 Oct.; Frouwina Elisabeth, Schenk, Nerva. —15 Oct.; Ede»» Smith. Amst.</p>
	<p>Bij DEAL, 15 Oct.; Malaga, Gerloff, Eott. n. Bucnos-Ayres. , , SHIELDS, 15 Oct.-, Boreas, Munneke, Harl. - Fanny, Playlc, Amst. Sisters, Prych, id. - Ecliptica, Hoeksema, Gron. - Samuel &amp; Sarah, Lip?&apos; Nieuwe Diep. - Melby, Edwards, id.-Rose, Douglas, id. - Jane Selktf*&apos; Wheatloy, id. - Harmony, Wilmut, Rott. - Seanymph, Crosby, id. -Ma» &apos; Grovich, id. - Ophir, Hein, id. - Carl Milberg, Schmidt, Schied - John 9 Isabelle, Younger, id. - Ronaldes, Green, id. - Voorwaarts, de Vries, l)en zijl. - Elise, Stolp, id. - Wereldburger, de Velde, Gron. - Alma, Lockyer. Zierikzee. r.. -? ?&lt;r. SUNDEÏ.LAND. 15 Oct.; Sophia, Aaske, Nieuwe Diep. - Ihorniej&apos; Brown. id. - Cassandria, Laidler, id. - Heron, Lawson, id. - Cathann»- Limschau, Schied. - Bessie, Mordey, Rott. - Gaspar, ..... id. - Ehzabet» Brodie, Brodie, id.- Port Wnlhxce, fttyers, id.</p>
	<p>GIBES&apos;B\0feMeplo,la&apos;Neal9.^weDieP. Jong,id. °Ct,; Pomona. Haddeman, Vlaardingen. - Boreas,de den dag n. St. ThomLs11*^61&apos; Weaterling. Amst; (vertrok den volgen- PHIfADELPHIA, 2 (icte Royal, Charlie. Botterdam.</p>
</text>
