<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>VLIE, 3 Sept.; Argo, Olsen, Newcastle. - Otto Olof, Erichsen, id. -Jo hanna, Berg, Petersburg. - Equator, Huisman, Riga. - Welgelegen, N-etS».. id. - Amphitrite, Christophersen, Wyburg. - Genius, Feindt, Stokholny Gesina, Krook, Wismar. - 3 Gebroeders, Leffers, Rostok. - Geertruida, a» Groot, Fredcrikstad. - Fanny, Unger, id. - Maria, Meinsma, id. - Elisabeth, Kjoning, id. - Josephine, Kansen, id. - Johanna Elisabeth, Helmers, id. ■ Enigheden, Jaeobsen, Drammen. - Helga &amp; Eleonora, Aabijc, id. - Theti-, Hofgaard, id. - Coallier, Lorentsen, id. - Morgenster, Christensen, id. - j_ reningen, Seeberg, id. - Geertruida Elisabeth, Bontekoe, Arendahl. - Creole, Pedersen, Drobach. - Minerva, Boe, Holmstrand. - Minerva, Schuurman, Christiansand. - Jolund, Christensen, Tonsberg. - Vrouw Helena, Kraan. Avontuur.-Vrouw Geertruida, Heijenga, id. — 4 Sept.; Alyda Anten.». Visser, Petersburg. - Anje, Munning, Arendahl. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Sept.; John Gibson, Harrison, Newc. - Rauma, Nielsen.Wyburg. BRIELLE, 5 Sept.; Cologne, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. - De Maas, S-, id. - Mary, S, id. - Pacific, S., Harwich. - J. C. Maclean, Webster, Heppens. MAASSLUIS, 5 Sept.; Alette, Thomsen, Newc. - Minerva, Henricbsen. id. - Flora, Thygesen, id. - Minerva, Frost, Hartlepool. - Condor, Kadingi Dantzig. . BREMERHAVEN, 4 Sept.; Cornelia Jantina, Kwint, Avontuur. - Al&apos; berta Romeling, de Vries, id. - Elisabeth, Stcffens, id. - Frau Foskca, F- ?&quot; ster, Amst. - Friederike, Kramer, id. - Catharina, Slinger, Avontuur. - Dank&apos; baarheid, Schollcma, Hamburg. - Johannes, Klockgeter, Baltimore. - A-* Meiners, id.</p>
	<p>BOLDERA, 29 Aug.; Tordenskjold, Jensen, Nederland. ELSENEUR, 2 Sept.; Hilkelina, Lupkes, Huil. LONDEN, 3 Sept.; zeilkl.: Vereeniging, Klijn, Suriname. - Aukje Gepk«&apos; lina, Duintjer, Elseneur. - Katharina, Bakker, Riga.</p>
	<p>FALMOUTH, 2 Sept.; Bérénice, S., Middell. Zee. COWES, 3 Sept.; Jacobus, Wegener, Girgenti n. Londen. LIVERPOOL, 2 Sept.; Elisabeth, Coll, Dordrecht. SHIELDS, 3 Sept.; Elisabeth,. .., Rott. PAK, 3 Sept.fLucy, Mc Ivor, Dordrecht. SUNDERLAND, 3 Sept.; Harmina, Emnielkamp, Swinenmnde. BRUSSEL, 4 Sept.; Anna, Jongebloed, Avontuur. TRIEST, 30 Aug.; Fenna, de Jonge, Falmouth. - Suzanna, Moes_ef&apos; Maranham. RIO GRANDE, voor 31 Julij; Alida, Baas, Falmouth.</p>
</text>
