<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 30 April; Visscherij, Fortuin, Londen. - Sippe Visser, de Jong, idem. - Stad Workum, van&apos;t Veer, id. - Hudgill, Breems, Newcastle.- Maria. Patterson, id. - Diadem, Buchart, id. - Robart Stride, Cobon, Seaham, - Alpha, Niolsen, Tvedestrand. - Vrouw Helene, Kraan, Lauvrig. VLIE, 29 April; Salis, Tieraan, Mollerup. - Zeelust, Keun, Arendahl.—• 30 April; Christina Jacoba, Ploeg, Christiansand. - Catharina Visser, de Vreeze. Oudsoen. DELFZYL, 26 April; Bouwina, Heins, Leer. —27 April; Gesina, Niezen, Bremen. - Frederike, id. — 28 April; Grietje, Kuiper, Bremerhaven. Maria, Minke. Rheine. . TERMUNTERZYL, 22 April; Maria, Pasma, Oldenburg. - Maria, Ebkes, id. — 23 April; Jeltiena, Bloem.Langesund, is 27 dito n. Krageroe vertr. - Thelka, Schier, Harburg, is 25 dito n. Leer vertr. — 24 April; Geertje Pot, Tap, Krageroe, is 27 dito n. Riga vertr. - Nvssina, Veldman, Langesund, is 27 April n. Laurvig vertr. - Ykelina, de Vries, Hanover. — 25 April; Margaretha, Klokgeter, id. ¦__.__&quot;___ _ HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 April; Clio, Roskamp, Philadelphia A. - Batavier, S., Londen. - Ida, S., Liverpool. - Therese S., Grangemoutli. FREDERIKSHAVN, 21 April; Drie Gebroeders, Fenenga, Charlestown n.Kroonstad, met eenige schade. , _,-_. D .RDANELLEN, 11 April; Juffer Zwaanettc, Pekeler, S_ields. TRIEST, 29 April; Crou.menie. Engelsman, Bahia. 1 UITGEZEILD.. TEXEL, 30 April; Gleaner, Thompson, Liverpool.- Sophia, Olsson , Newcastle.-Hart,Cloak,id.-Coi-nelia,S.,Koningsb. VLIE, 29 April; Ncptunus, van der Gaast, Havana. - Amsterdam, b., DELEZYL, 26 April; Hillechiena Wolkammer Vos, Noorwegen. - Cor nelia, Lecuwe, id. - Eendragt, de Witt, id. - Gatharma, Dykema, id. - Maria, Jungerhaus, Norden. —28 April; Catharina, Springer, Hamburg. TERMUNTERZYL, 26 April; Agnes Thecla, Holte,Krageröe. ANTWERPEN, 29 April; Gesina Dorothea, de Boer, Eageland. ROYAN, 27 April. Elisabeth Stephens, Petersb. • Tobina, Wortelboer.id. , , _ MARSEILLE, 27 April) BériSnice, de Boer, Livorno,</p>
</text>
