<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Julij,N.N. O.; Triton, Burghoudt, Nerva. - Speranza, Simonsen, Riga. - Alfen, Knudsen.Sundswal. - Emanuel, Walloe, id. - Johanna Smidt, Thuss, id. - Zeepaard, Tobiassen, Abo. - Oscar, Jacobsen, Swartvick. - Agina, Knijpinga, Sarpsb. VLIE, 30 Junij, N.; Mercurius, Both, Nerva. - De Hoop, Giezen, Riga. - Niórd, Bjornstadt, Christiania. - Raven, Morck, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, lJalij, N.N.0.; Lordßaglan,S.,Newc Mary&apos;s.Ward, id.- Zealous, S., Harwich.- Bonjour.Groth, Riga.- Antje, Velt, id. - John, Inge, Libau. - Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg, 1. v. Brouwersh. — Gisteren nog: Balmoral, S., Bristol. - Edith, S., Huil. BRIELLE, 1 Julij, N.0.; Florence, S., Londen. BROüWEESHAVEN,lJulij,N.N.O.;Warwick,Willey,Newc.- Thames, S., Middlesbro n. Dordt. PILLAU, 29 Junij-, Alberdina, Lever, Burnt-Eiland. MEMEL, 27 Junij; 4 Neeltjes, Koenes, Kopenh. LONDEN, 29 Junij; Jonge Ida, Carst, Gron. - Wilhelmina, Meijer, Riga. — 30 Junij; de Hoop, Telsma, Worcum. Bij DEAL, 29 Junij; Doesborgh, Spaanderman, Amst. n. Samarang. Bij DUNGENESS, 27 Junij; Muscovado, Fritas, Schiedam n. Dcmerara. WARKWORTH, 29 Junij; Tweo Gebroeders, Persoen, Vhs singen.</p>
	<p>NEWHAVEN, 29 Junij; lutegrity, Hamden, Rott. ROCHESTER, 28 Juny; John k Charies, Charlton, Rott. RYE, 29 Juny; Colonel Évans, Bagley, Rott. FALMOÜTH, 27 Junij; Staatsraad van Ewijck, Ham, Java n. Amst; BÜISTOL, 29 Juuij; Maria, de Jonge, Huelva. GLASGOW, 29 Junij; Vooruit, Hilbfands, Messina.-Meteor, S.. Dublin.</p>
	<p>Bij HOLYHEAD, 23 Junij; Joh. Christina, Rösing, Liverpooi n. Bat. IPSWICH, 28 Junij; Emma. Bell, Rott.&apos; GRANGEMOUÏH&apos;, 27 Junij: Gustav Adolph, Vork, Harl. HARTLEPOOL, 28 Junij; Zeidina, Jansen, Duinkerken. - Twee Broeders, Prins, Malmo, SHIELDS, 29 Junij; Termoüde, de Boer, Christiania. CAÜIX, 24 Junij; Antje Spithorst, Freese, Sevllla, LICATA, 21 Junij; Archipel, v. d. Gaauw, Malta. TRIEST, 24 Junij; Goorecht &amp; Oldambt, Rentema, Troon. KONSTANTINÓPEL, 22 Junij; Pet, Reid, Ibraila, vertrok ü. Amsterdam. BOSTON, 15 Junij-, DuiVeland, Plttmef, Montevideo. CURACAO, 20 Mei; Santaßosa, de Waard, Amst,</p>
</text>
