<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>_Li&lt;_____, lObcpt.; Hoop, Jelsnia, Londen Tint-;,- o, ¦ phyru^EUiovSunderland. ~11 Sept • Juno w,„ -;„ V*? Slu,a&apos;id&apos;&quot; Za&apos; CoWtS_Goede-rouw, de Vries, id.P-Gu tav cöu\„ .w^7**&apos; 4 Mei&apos;&quot; yfcmi, M „e&amp;&apos;den. - Vesper, H__n%, S-, Hall. - Seotia, l£inSranJ. f - -lb6rt&apos; de-rc%_i&apos;per&apos;.a!&lt;^fr gemeld.) henzen, Drammen. (Benevens y/l|.E,lo#jp; ;&lt;Anke;-.in, S., HuraUirg. j !___ ¦ &gt;_ - I</p>
	<p>AMELAND, 8 Sept.; Margaretha, Strohschieder, Hamburg. - Ida Chris; tina, Brinkema, id. - Voskea, Fahnster, Bremen. -;Alida Adriana, Kramer, ; id. - Berendjedina, Roskamp, Rhauderfehn. - Alida Adriana, Kramer, Carolinerzijl. i OSTMAHORN, 8 Sept.; Jantina Catharina, van Dijk, Aberdour. - Anna, : j Lnken, Bremen. - Siefer, Reents, Leer. - Gesina, Böker, id. DELFZIJL, 5 Sept.; Maria Edina, Hegerman, Laurvig.— 6 Sept.; Maria . i Gebina, Jengerhans, Papenborg. - Goede Hoop, Greven, Dorumerzijl. - Helena, Cordos, Soltburg. — 7 Sept.; Maria, Minke, Rhe.ede. — 8 Sept.; Industrie, Wilkens, Leer. • Vr. Wiehertje, Luikinga, id. - Uit Vriendschap, Bolmeijer, id. - Maria, Pasmann, id. ; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Sept.; Codan, Bottcher, Bat. - Seaharse, S., &quot; Huil. —11 Sept.; Botty, Sylphau, Santos 1. v. Falmouth. - Wilhelmina, At, kinson, St.John&apos;s. - Jeune Hermine, Tattevin, Rédon. - Earlof Auckland, S., Londen. - Rollo, Schep, Guernsey. - Louise, S., Grangemouth. BRIELLE, Il Sept.; Mary, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. BROUWERSHAVEN, 11 Sept.; Maria, v. Wulven, Rott. n. Japan. (Be&apos; nevens de schepen per telegr. gemeld). OSTERRISOER, 27 Aug.; Christine, Bolwin, Gothenburg n. Amst. I CHRISTIANIA, 31 Aug.; Nachiena Lammechina, Rijnberg, Petsrsb. - Elieser, L»rsen, Rott. HELSINGBORG, 28 Aug.; Eendragt, Martens, Newcastle. Bij DUNGENESS, 9 Sept.; Colombine, Malbranc, Shields n. China. CAMARET, 3 Sept.; Jeune Hermine, Tattevin, Rédon n. Schiedam. - Emanuel, Baron, Vannes n. id. . GALATZ, 24 Aug.; Catina, Maffia, Amst.</p>
</text>
