<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Maart, Z. O.; Agatha, van Wijle Jr., Carditf. -Alida, Sprik, Jnvernool. - Anna VYilh&apos;elinina, Zeven, Newc.-Neptunus, do Vries, id.- Dorette, Westenderii&apos;, id. - Hsanrich TlieoJor, Voss. id. - Veracity, Groetier.id. - Meindina, Siemors, id.-Rolf, Luiter, id.-Syivia, Smith, Namsos.- Wvdel Jarlsberg, Backer, id.- Annettc, Gam&apos;sfc, Kopenhageti .-Maria Lehmann. Möller,id.- Fromaren, Trilstad. Ohrisf-ianin. &apos;•■. &apos;.gel, Freelerikstad. - HalfarO, Cappoien, id. - Christina Alida, [.&apos;eiken-; J.aurvieii. - Chri I .. v..nfuur. - Maria Eei&apos;iua, dc Groot, i.). - Maarhuizen, Fladder, id. - Alberdina, Loman, id. - Aurora, van ©ijk, ia. VLIE, 21 Maart; Ivanhoe, S., Leith. - Mary Arm, Simpsca, i edniand. - Diana, v. d. Ley, Hbrséns. — 22 Maart; Willem, Janzouias, Lcba. - Jan &amp; Burghardt, Mymel. 11E ELE V OEI SL Ui S, 22 Maart, 0. Z. O.; Maria Elisa beth, Boni er, Bat. vi:r Brouwershaven. - Yartry, S., Dublin. -Ecliptica, Hoeksma, Newc. - Christina Jacoba, de Uroot,&apos;jd. - Ceres, lücklefis, Libau. - Vriendschap, Kruize,FrSderikstad. -Mathilda, Wiersn»,id. MAASSLUIS, 22 Maart: Edith Owen, 5.,11n11. -Jntegrity-, Ilarndcn, Newhav&apos;en.- Anna Margaretha, Ho Sewc. -Volleniioven, Koning, ir!. - Albert, de Vries, id. - Eersteling, Wiersma, id.r Johanacs, Rauscher, id. •■ Enjsta, Bassin*, Avontuur. - Wilhelmina Petronella, Bijl, id. - Cath. Cornelia. Asteling, ïcI. HAMBURG, 21 Maait-, Harmonie, S.,Rott. - Nautilus, Gütjens, Nederlar.&apos;l. DRAMMEN, 8 Maart, Zeïlkl.: Dan, Niqlsen, Nederl. - Aurora, Christensen, id. LONDEN, 2,1 Maart: zeilklaar: Vertrouwen, Middel, Bnenos-Ayrcs. • PORTLAND, 20 Maart; de Hoop, Manneke, Palermo n. Vlaardingen. - Mina, vau Keulen, Lissabon ri. id, J&apos;LYMOUTH, lö Maart; Mari iiaLlovd, Lloyd, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 20 Maart; Navigator, Bloom, Harlingen. LiTTLEHAMPTüN, 20 Maart; Drie Gezusters, Breeland, Avontuur. IPSWICH&apos;, 20 Maart; Diana, Kroon, Schotland. - Do Hoop, Loor, Harwieh. REDON, 10 Maart; Jeune Narcisse, Dupont, Rott. - Jeune Henri, Lottin, Schiedam. BINIE, 18 Maart; Camelius, Mathurin, St. Malo n. Rett. PORTIMAO, 16 Maart; Catharina Louise, van Aalst, Rott. RIO JANEIRO, 16 Febr.; Hendrik Pieter, Bakker, San Francisco.</p>
</text>
