<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>[ TEXEL, 29 Maart, Z.W.—W.; Vriesland,Boontje, Londen.-Mentor, . loering, id. - Wieberdina Martent, Looinan, id. - Kathleen, Chappel, , W iesbeach. - Ivanhoe, S., Leith. - Blackney, Hughes, Newc; benevens de . schepen per tel. gemeld. VLIE, 29 Maart, Z. W.; Eendragt, Doornbos, Newc. - Alice, Udam, Windau. ; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 23 Maart, W. Z. W.; Catharina Wilhelmina, de Boer, Bat. 1. v. Brouwersh. - Constantia, Brinkerink, Passar 1 v id - Emerald, Hilgesen, New-York, 1. v. id. - Margaroth, Evans, Port-Madoc. - Adnana Francisca, &apos;t Hart, Newc. - Gisteren nog: Colletis S Goole BRIELLE, 29 Maart; W—Z.; Feijenoord, S., Londen. -Settètili S Huil. - Eheffield, S„ GiïmsW, - Ravensbury, S., Harwich. ° &apos; BROUWERSHAVEN, 29 Maart; Conntyof Argyle, Edington, Soerabaya n. Rott., vertr. 23 Oct. (Benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld) EMDEN, 24 Maart; Jonge Wioka, de Vries, Delfzijl. — 25 Maart&apos; Margaretha, Mudder, Amst. HAMBURG, 28 Maart; Elsina, Vlieger, Amst. - Fraukea, Fahnster J_ akkuni. - Antina, Bartels, id. BBEMERHAVEN, 28 Maart; Fenna, Dirks, Amst. - Sophia, Bisze, Delfriil. - Johanna Carolina, de Boor, Gron. - Roeltiua Jolianna, Drewes, Londen. BÖ KOPENHAGEN, 27 Maart; Emilie, S„ Stettin n. Rott. TONNiNGEN, as Maart; gepasseerd: ïeiina, Dekker, Inverkeithing n. Bendsburg. DEAL, 27 Maart; ten anker: Bato, Huizin?, London n. Montevideo. DARTMOUTH, 27 Maart; Tasmania, Driver, Rott. n. New port. Bij DARTMOUTH, 27 Maart; Tasmania, Douwt., Fernambuck. - FJ LMOUTH, 28 Maart; Silentium, Schagen van Leeuwen, Boston. NEWPORT, 26 Maart; Arthur, Schaeifer, Rott. GOOLE, 27 Maart; Titia Jacobina, Klein, Antwerpen. HARTLEPOOL, 26 Maart; Anna Catharina, de Vries, Leer. SIHELDS, 27 Maart,; Maarhuizen, Kladder, Amsterd. - Anna Wilhelmina, Zeven, id. - Drie Gebroeders, Feninga, id. - de Zwerver Ates.id.- Jabina, Schmidt, id. - Jantina, Schleinhage, id.-Dorette, Westéudorfl&apos;,id.- Geertje Elisabeth, van den Borg, Schiedam. - Herstelling ,id.- Wilhelmina Petronella, Bijl, id. - Enjetta, Boswijk, id. - Anna Margaretha, Hoeksema, id. - Harsina Harmina, Waterborg, Gron. - Alberdina, Looman, Koogerpolder. - Alida Dijk, Vessen, id. - Catharina Luitgardina, Bos, Delfzijl. - Onon, Lindeboom, Duinkerken.- Eendragt, van Hoorn, id.- Thiesina, Poorta, Colchester. BERWICK, 26 Maart; Progress, Cocking, Rott. CADIX, 21 Maart; Adriana Wilhelmina, v. Dij Newc. —22 Maart- Cornelia Maria, Timmer, Amst. LIVORNO, 18 Maart; Rhöne, S., Amst. ALICANTE, 24 Maart; Familietrouw, Jonker, Liverpool. AMOY, 3 Febr.; Constance, Mulder, Macasser. UITGEZEILD. VLIE, 29 Maart, Z. W.; Elisabeth &amp; Christina, Visser, Leba. ; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 29 Maart; W. Z.W.;California, Berkhout, Gibraltar. - Zeus, van der Tas, St. Übes. -Thetis, de Zeeuw Bagges,&apos;id. - Doris, Rocker, Newc. - Aurora, Vaalman, Koningsbergen. MAASSLUIS, 28 Maart.; Avalon, Bi&apos;, Harwich. PLYMOUTH, 27 Maart; Jessie Samison, West, Bat. n. Rott. - Cleughs, Mc, Bay, Java n. Amst. - Petronella, Strootman, id. n. id. - Jack Tarr, Quincq, Runcorn n. Dordrecht. - Carry Winch, Barrott, Lidney n. Rott. St.MAWES, 27 Maart; Drie Znsters, Dykstra, Lissabon h. Amst. - Geertruida, Pott, Licata n. Rott. - Hendrika Margaretha, Bakker, Triest n. Amst. - Hermanus Theodorus, Wilmink, Lissabon n. Elseneur. - Geert Herwig, Smit, Port au Piïnce n. Antwerpen. FALMOUTH, 27 Maart; Felicia, Mavor, Java n. Amst. - Breeze, Scardefield, Galatz n. Rott. - Dolphyn, Hazewinkel, Liverpool n. Wolgast. - Jantje, Smit, Triest n. Huil. NEWPORT, 26 Maart; Autumna, Lee, Dordrecht. SEAHAM, 26 Maart; Veracity, Dixon, Schiedam. — 27 Maart; J. 11. Yates, Toovey, Nieuwe Diep. ™ANtsK._27^laart; Johanna, Hildebrandt, Car.iffi YARMOUTH, ï/.vh.art; Whim 6___ith Ükthaar | JUIDDLÊbBIvO, 27 Maart; Fraucis.Hardy, Dordrecht.</p>
	<p>SUNDERLAND, 27 Maart; Alberdina Edzlna, Uchtrnan, Stettin. . Neeltje Cornelia, Ppstema, id. LEITH, 27 Maart; Ena Elisabeth, Smith, Dantzig. St. NAZAIRE, 26&apos; Maart; Agnes ..fraser, Waghtin, Rott. - Perrinne, Raoul, id. - de Weldaad, Pik, Kopenhagen. PAIMBOEUF, 26 Maart; Adnen, Chauvelon, Zwolle. PALERMO, 15 Maart; Boreas, de Jonge, Rott. I TRIEST, 21 Maart; Bérénice, S„ Rott. BANGKOK, 31 Jan.; Admiraal de Winter, Dill, Ningpo.</p>
</text>
