<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 29 Dcc; Ferdinand en Louis, Nolting-Batavia. - Pelicitas, Wilde hoer, Curacao. - Satnrn, Löhdstrom, Odessa. - De Hoop, Ouwehand, Lissabon, 8 d. reis, (benevens dc schepen per tel. gemeld). VLIE, 28 Dcc; 2 Gebroeders, Butter,Engeland. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 29 Dcc; Cornelia Mathilda, Wulp, Batavia 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Thetis, de Zeeuw Baggus, Villanova. - Zeemeeuw, Swart, St, Übcs. - Zephyr, S., Londen. - Feyenoord, S., id. - Kinghorn. S., Leith. - Hawk, S., Huil. - Colletis, S., Goole. BRIELLE. 29 Dcc; Orion, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 29 Dcc; het schip per telegramgemeld. BREMERHAVEN, 28 Dcc; Emilie, Meijer, Richmond. HAMBURG, 28Dec; Trijntje Meijer, Tonkens, Leer. ALTONA, 28 Dcc; Margaretha, Gust, Leeuwarden. IQEL, 27 Dec.; Sjoukolina, Dirks Oclensce. ELSENEUR, 26 Dec-, gepasseerd: Rubbens, S., Pillaun. Amst.-Hvidt, S., Dantzig n. Schiedam. BRAKE, 28 Dec-, Onrast, Slangcnberg, Antwerpen. LIVERPOOL, 27 Dcc; Margaretha, Boerhave, Livorno. SWANSEA, 24 Dcc; Themis, Bloos, Marseille NEWPOItT 26 Dcc; Burgemeester van Middelburg, Hoek, Rott. SHIELDS, 27 Dcc; Renske, Noppcrus, Ipswich. - Adriana Franciska, van-yk, Vlissingen. . „. _u &apos;CADIX, 22 Dcc; Verwisseling, Notmcijcr, Rott. GIBRALTAR, 19 Dcc; Jacob en Titia, Prak, Hamburg. — 20 Dcc, Dankbaarheid, van der Wal, Vlaardingen. ZANTE, 5 Dec.;Arcntina, Smit, Patras. NAGASAKI, 16 Oct.; Jan van Galen, Braak, Yokohama. KELUNG, 21 Oct.; Adeline, Wybrands, Shanghae. UITGEZEILD. &apos;HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 Dcc; Albert, S., Huil. __ BREMERHAVEN, 27 Dcc; Jaeoba Marchina, Kuil, Hamburg. HAMBURG, 28 Dcc; Gepbina Helena, do Vries, Montevideo. DANTZIG, 24 Dcc; Médéa, S., Amsterdam. FALMOUTH, 27 Dcc; Antje Haverbult, van Heuvelen, Maroim. LIVERPOOL, 26 Dcc; zeilklaar: Nicolaas Heinberger, Koster, Porto-Rico. WIYENHOE, 25 Dec-, Jacobina, Maathuis, Gron. - Soranus, Poelman, idem. SUNDERLAND, 27 Dcc; Betsy, Middleton, Nieuwe Diep. DEAL, 27 Dcc; Elsina Geertruida, Mulder, Vera Cruz. - Wilhelmina; tlö Groot, Cctte. - Jacomiua, Kuipers, Ferrol. HARWiCH, 27 Dcc; Vr. Anna, Hospes, Worcum n. Londen. - Vrouw Dieuwkn, Feenstra, id. n. id* GLASGOW, 27 Dcc; Orion, Lindeboom, Troon. ANTWERPEN, 28 Dcc; H. Vincentius van Paulo, Nagel, Schiedam. - 29 Dcc; Maria Adolphina, Meuldijk, Newc. BORDEAUX, 23 Dcc; Clasina Aidina, Wirtjcs, Amst. LIVORNO, 12 Dcc; Grietje, Legger, Londen. NEW-YORK, 14 Dec;&apos;zeilkl.: Germania, Francke, Baltimore. — 15 Dcc; FlyingEaglc, Ratscher, Rott. SINGAPORE, 18 Nov.; Neêrlands Vlag, van den Broek Humfrey, Saigon. NAGASAKI, 18 Oct.; D. T. Visser, van der Linden, Yokohama.— 29 Oct.; Libra, Dirksen, Foo-Chcw-Foo.</p>
</text>
