<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 25 Julij, Z. W.-Z.;Hollandia,S., Londen.- Gisteren no»* ! ftrageroe, Nielsen, Riga. - Immanuel, Bjertness, Holmstad. - Soeriddèr«n, Jurgensen, Stockholm. VLIE, 24 Julij, Z. Z. W.; Lene, Brinck, Petersburg. - Helena, Tito, id. - : ¦Noordster, Schaap, Nerva. - Remelia Geertruida, de Boer, id. - Jantje gniit, id. - Pieter, Oosteryink, id. - Helena, Niemeijer, id. - Emilie, Dinze femel*. - Johanna, Oldenburger, id. - Broederschap, Bakker, id. - Maria «prik, Frederikst. - Concordia, Hendriksen, Oudsoeu. — 25 Julij; Johanna Elisabeth, Helmers, Nerva. , HELLEVOETSLUIS, 25 July,W; Deborah Pennell, Dumming, Baltim i* v- Zierikzee. - Cingria, S, Odessa 1. v. id. - Zephyr, S., Londen. - King- j ho!?, S., Leith. - Hester, de Jong, Pernau. - Carl Gustav, Thiese, Libau. I &apos; . BROUWERSHAVEN, 25 July, W.Z.W.; William $r Sarah, Rolland-B°ö. Newc. n. Dordrecht (benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld). „ZIERIKZEE, 25 Julij, W.Z.W.; Walcheren, v. d. Borden, Menado n. &quot;otterdam. kfETTIN, 22 Julij; Elsiena, Vlieger, Amsterdam. ] &gt; DANTZIG, 22 Jülij; Johann Wilhelm, Lundie, Rott. - Ter Reede: &quot;Jtina Christina, Bekkering, Flensburg. ¦ .__ _ STOCKHOLM, 21 Julij; Catharina Cornelia, Borst, Petersburg.</p>
	<p>SHNDSWALL, 2 Julij; Fr. Maren, Fjelstad, Nieuwe Diep. GAMLE CARLEBY, 3 Julij; Onderneming, Feenstra, Rott. AKOHANGEL, 24 Julij; Jautina Maria, Keizer, Groningen. - Antje Spithorst, Freese Jr., Bergen. LONDEN, 24 Julij; Gebroeders, Muntendam, Groningen. Bij DUNGENESS, 23 Julij; Triton, Sandberg, Torrevecchia n. Riga. CHAELESTO WN, 22 Julij; Margaretha, Huizinga, Hamburg. Bij LYMINGTON, 23 Julij; Adoram, Jones, Rott. n. Liverpool. Bij HOLYHEAD, 23 Julij; Sarah, Matthias, Liverpool n. Rott. - Union. Pilcher, id. n. Dordt. B.ONESS,2I Julij; Herstelling, Lukkien, Dantzig. WIbBEACH, 23 Julij; Catharina Ricardi, Meijer, Koningsb. DIEPPE, 20 Julij; Fricndship, Ridgway, Rott. .DUINKERKEN, 22 Julij; Elisabeth, Boon, Dantzig. KONSTANTINOPEL, 13 Julij; J. H. Epping, Bulow, Marianopel n. ST. HELENA, 11 Junij-, Cornelis &quot;Wernard Eduard, Swart, Bat. n. Rott. — 14 Junij; Sirias, v. Wijngaarden v. Rees, Bat. n. Amst.; sedert gepraaid. —15 Junij; Koning Willem 11, Besseling, Bat.n. Amst.-Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Bat. n. Rott. — 17 Junij; Mentor, Butenuth, Padangn. Amst. — 19 Junij; Batavia, Grell, Bassein n. Falmouth. — 27 Junij; Médea, v. Teutem, Bat. n. Amst. - Mary &amp; Hillegonda, Wolters, Bat. naar Rott.; hebben de reis voortgezet. Bij St. HELENA, 27 Junij; County of Ayr, Spittal, Java n. Rott. ASCENSION, 10 Junij; Triton, Schey, Bat. n. Rott.</p>
</text>
