<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 Mei; Diana, S., Londen. — 14 Mei; Anna, Bok, Singapo1* Reinhardt, Muller, Buenos-Ayres. - Maria Geertruida, Caspers, Lirorn ■ Vrouw Dieuwke, Feenstra, Londen. - Hoop, Jelsma, id. - Kon. Ned. Ï^J , club, Zwart, Newc. - Piro, Wilson, id. - Elisabeth, Pigot, id. - Richard 0° den, Stibolt, Riga.-Hermanus, Olscn, Sundswall. ■ Alma, Foyen, Christi»»18, Lyna, Knudsen, Drammen. - Alfen, Knudsen, id. . , VLIE, 13 Mei; Nimrod, Rennenberg, Windau. - Geessiena, Riks, B&apos;S8&apos; Catharina Elisabeth, Pot, id. - Geertruida, de Groot, id. - Claus Thomes™ Nielscn, Sundswall. - Wilhelm Carl, Gudmundsen, Christiana. - Mystc.&apos; Hemery, Noorwegen. — 14 Mei; Hope, Cook, Gloucester. - Stoom vaart, »•&apos; Hamburg. __^. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 15 Mei; Henriette Gerardina Susanra, Dam-P tavia. - Noach, Lupcko, id., via Brouwershaven. - Feijenoord, S., Lonuf &apos; Elisabeth Littlle, Derby, id. -Mozart, Smith, Cardiff.-Berkley, Goole, r&gt;* castle. - Jane, Hartman, id. - Oscar, Calabre, Elseneur. - Familiën, Gorna» Stockholm. - Minerva, Boe, Holmstrand. BRIELLE, 14 Mei; Elisabeth Davis, James, Newcastle. ... MAASSLUIS, 14 Mei; Darly, Nichols, Whitby.- John &amp; James, WV Newc. - Habit, Brinck, id. De gisteren gemelde eu al do buiten geank6 schepen zijn wel in zee. BREMERHAVEN, 13 Mei; Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Hamburg- . LEER, 6/12 Moi; Harmko, Harkema, Groningen. - Uit Vriendschap- K meijsr, id. - Vr. Geertruida, Pronk, Harlingen. • Jantina Afina, Vc&lt;i°n Bremen. „e. HAMBURG, 13 Mei; Agatha, Wortel, Rott. - Johan Cornelis, GroBU woud, Avontuur. - Antjc, Mulder, Buenos-Ayres. SWINEMUNDE, 10 Mei; Elisabeth, van Wijk, Petersburg. DANTZIG, 11 Mei; Twee Gebroeders, de Groot, Groningen. TONSBERG, 28 April; Richard ,j- Clara, Olsen, Nederland. ODENSE, 3 Mei; Nieolinc, Ander.en, Nederland. UDBYHOI, 5 Mei; Nicoline Christinc, Reisbeek, Nederland. CARDIF, 11 Mei; Johanncs Lodewijk, van Delft, Manilla. LIVERPOOL, 12 Mei; zeilkl.: Gesina Alida, Meijer, Riga. GRANGEMOUTH, 12 Mei; Elisc, dc Vries, Koningsbergen. v^/, NEWPORT, 11 Mei; Catharina, French, Dordt. - Kingof Fore**, * Dordt. PORT MADOC, 12 Mei; Charles Sanchay, Timothy, Rotterdam- GIBRALTAR, 6 Mei; zeilkl.: Antilope, Reimers, Genua. BORDEAUX, 12 Mei; Maria, Anna, Trcraentin, Amst. _mif»8&apos; BATAV. A, 30 Maart; Java Packet, Hellingman, Nederland. -A?&quot;&apos; (fi» de Euyter, Mollinger, id. — 31 Maart; Eduard, Lubben, Ameri^.kj, Indramayoe). -zeilklaar: Maria Anna, van Monnom, Nederland. - J 18&quot; Mos, id t (fi» TAGAL, 25 Maart; Cornelia Hendrika, van Straten, Nedcrlan&quot; Soerabaija.) &lt;ei«v SOER4BAYA, 22 Maart; Ouderkerk a/d. Amstel, DingcmanV land. — 24 Maart; Dordrecht, Loos, id. (via Panaroekan). PASOEROEAN, 24 Maart; Emilic, Liudström, Nederl.&apos; MACASSAR, 21 Febr.; St. Helena, Dille, Macao. HONGKONG, 13 Maart; Candate, Bosscher, Ticntsin.</p>
</text>
