<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Mei; Hênriette Geertruida, Colier, Banjoew., vertr. 2 Dec. • Elisabeth, Scarth, Odessa, 1. v. Queenston. VLIE, 12 Mei; Cailoff, Egholm, Kjertcminde. — 13 Mei; Amsterdam, S. Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13Mei; Superior,Hutchinson, Par.-Sara Davies, Davies, Whitchavcn.- Diana, Brooks, Rnncorn. - Valkyrien, Lund, Nyburg.- Elve, S., Hamburg.— 14 Mei; Bildcrdijk, Viëtor, Banjoew., 1. v. Zierikzec, vertr. 28 Jan. - Marianne, Vlas, Aarhuus.- Hercules, Hehlberg, Torbecksminde. BRIELLE, 13 Mei; Swallow, S, Hnlh 14 dito derwaarts teruggek. — 14 Mei; prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Cologne, S , Londsn. - Zealous, S., Harwich. BREMERHAVEN, 13 Mei; Johanna, Scheffer, Bat.-Klasina, Klein, Amst. - Gertrudc, Lindeboom, Middlesbro. LEER, 8 Mei; Jantina Anna, Veenhuis, Antw. — 10 Mei; Catharina Imkina, Hulzebus, Amst. - Onrust, Muddcr, id. - Aurora, Brinkman, Boncss. ; HAMBURG, 12 Moi;WillcmI,S., Amst.-Indti3trie,Wichers,Makkum.- Hendrika, Pybes, Smirna. — 13 Mei; Nooit Gedacht, Bakker, Rott. - Ilammonia,S.,id. ALTONA, 12 Mei; Gesina, Meijer, Hamburg. CUXHAVEN, 13 Mei; Everhardus, do Boer, Palcrmo. - Antonius, Gonningen, Cadix. - Sirene, Schippers, Triest. STRAALSÜND, 9 Mei; Zwaantina, Gruppelaar, Newc. WOLGAST, 11 Mei; Jantina Alida, Texer, Londen. SWINEMUNDE, 11 Mei; Scino, S., Rott. — 12 Mei; WillemIII, S., Amst. DANTZIG, 11 Mei; Noordstar, Brouwer, Dysart. - Reinegina, Tonkens, Kopenh.ngen. ° &apos; &apos; I BOLDERAA, 9 Mei; Jacobus Antonie, Mollema, Kopenhagen. - Amici ia, Heyn, Stettin. b GOTHENBURG 8 Mei; Jantina Rosina, Broekerna, Amst. - Celeritas, van der Leest, Delfzijl. . ,LANG,?SUND&apos; 5 Mei; Gesina Jantina, Pot, Termunterzijl. - Harmonie, Albers, Weener. RIISOER, 26 April; Medea, Olsen, Purmerend. - Sieka, Douwes, Harlingen. — 5 Mei; Cornelia, Jentsema, Delfzijl. - Eva, Bakker, id. UDBYHOI, 6 Mei; Hendrika Ellida, Kuiper, Amst. RENDSBURG, 8 Mei; gepasseerd: Zwei Gebriider, Ulrichs, Veile n. Amst. — 9 Mei; Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Odense n. Gron. - Eliza, Duncker, Korsoer n. Neder}. —10 Mei; Annette, de Wall, Praestoe n. id. — 11 Mei; Drie Gebroeders, de Groot, Dantzig n. Leeuwarden. - Trientje Meijer, Tonkens, Stolpemunde n. Schiedam. LONDEN, 14 Mei; Cornelia, de Vries, Colorados. - Maria Anna, ,</p>
	<p>Barbados. • In lading! Jeannette, Duiven, Aspinwall. • Gesina J»» Albers, Petersb. DEAL, 13 Mei; Batavia, Zwanenburg, Shields n. Bat. Bij DEAL, 12 Mei; Margaretha, Pot, Galipoli n. Petersb. Bij DOVER, 12 Mei; Alblasserwaard, Zack, Java n. Nederland. DARTMOUTH, 12 Mei; Cornelia Jantina, Kwint, Gron. FOWEY, 12 Mei; Grimaldi, Hill. Par n. Dordrecht. BRISTOL, 13 Mei; Junior, Tunteler, Smirna. DUBLIN, 14 Mei; Generaal Lee, S., Rott. SHIELDS, 12 Mei; Maria Stuart, Hansen, Rott. rf ANTWERPEN, 14 Mei; Hermine Marie Elisabeth, Bonj//r, Port»&quot; Prince. NANTES, 11 Mei; Lucie, Malgom, Amst. - Gebpina, Lohman, Rott. GIBRALTAR, 6 Mei; Dankbaarheid, v. d.Wal,Vlaai-dingen. VERA-CRUZ, 13 April; Zeeploeg, Siegers, Liverpool. . _ SINGAPORE, 6 April; In lading: Singapore, Stoop, Hongkong.-J» van Galen, Braat, id. - Alexander, Dekker, id. - Jacob &amp; Anna, fionger. f mouth. - Watergeus, Giezcn, Belle-Isle. , BATAVIA, 30 Maart;Zr. Ms. schipCoehoorn.dc Vriese, Buenos-A}&apos;re&apos; STRAAT SUNDA, 26 Maart; Baron v. Heemstra, Nepperus, Row&apos; Batavia. oj MELBOURNE, 12 Maart; Maria Dicdcrika, van Marion, Rott. - Blaar ; Susanna, Vonck, id. PORT PHILIP, 25 Maart; Emilie, Bruynseels, Rott.</p>
</text>
