<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Julij;lrene, S., Middell. Zee. - Perse-verenee. Elliot. Lonilen. - Whim, Smith, Yarmouth. - Aftiauce, Arnold. Harwich. - Gezina, Boer, Petersburg. - Rebecca, Dahn, Nerva» - Otto, Christensen, Riga.- Echo, Bjüness, Umea. - Oscar, Nielsen, Geffle.-Houtvaart, Visser. Sumlswall. - Maria, Bergh, id. - Drammen. Trost. id. - Vcstalindeu. Mörck, id.- Olivia, Quisling, id. - Miucrva, Rafen, Ljusne. - Undine, Bonde, Frederikstad. VLIE. 20 Julij; Afiena, Goosens, Petersburg. - Onderneming, Kooiman, Frederikstad. -&apos;Terra Nova, Abel, id. -PetroneUa Georgiua.Krijnen, Helgoland. HELLEVOETSLUIS. 21 Julij», Hopewell. Pearsoii,Londen.-Intregritj-, Haradcn, Rye. - Arm, Emery,Newc.-Thomasandlsabella,Nicholion, Diana. Isbehn. Archangel. - Dolphyn. Hazewiukel, Riga. BROUWERSHAVEN .21 Julij; Mary, LovcJl, Newc, n.Rott.-2 Brödre, Buil, Frederikstad n. id.- Junior. Gram. Hudickswaï&apos; n. id.- i&apos;rederike Marie. Spreneer, Riga n. Donit. - Samarang. de Greot, Rott. n. Bat. GRIMSBY, 19 Julij; Knjetta, de Boer, Hull, laadt voor Petersburg. SUNDERLAND, 19 Jniij; ChristinaWobbegina, v. d. Werp.Boulogne.- Anna Uliiylotta, Jansen. Hamburg. SHIELDS, 19 Julij; Elizabeth, Tosh, Rott. - Diana,Brooks, Dordr. - JimCrow. Garrod. iel. LEITH, 18 Julij; Neptunus, van Gorcum, Rostock. FINDHORN, Mi July-.Sieka, Douwes, Petersb., OUEENSTOWN, ..; Royal Mint. ..., Oud Calabar n. Rott. JERSEY, lti Julij», Rollo, Schep, Rott. FALMOUTH, 19 Julij; Honigbij, Valk, Akyab. — 20 Julij; Michiels Loos, Parmentier, dito. - Catharina, Fokkes, Raneoon. SOUTHAMPTON. 19 Julij; FackelinaEmuielina.Folkerts, Gron. Bij WICHT, ..; Vico-Admiraal May, Oudshoorn dc Groot Stiffry, Amst. n. Bat. LONDEN, 19 Julij», Voorwaarts,deVries, Bremen.— 20 Julij; Comelia, de Jong.Workum. - Stad Workum, van &apos;t Veer, dito. VIGO, 12 Julij; Maria, v. Duivenbooden, Amst. n. Porto. LISSABON. 16 Julij; Oolibri, Riedijk. Rott. DARDANELLEN, 8 Julij; Karma, de Jonge, Galatz n. Holland.</p>
</text>
