<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 9 Aug.; Magnet, S., Londen, - Pero.Wilson, Newc. - Alpha, Hagcmari, Skeen. - Ve.ta, S., Datltzig, HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Aug.; Dordrecht, Loos, Bat., 1. v. Brouwcrsh. - Sif, Magnussen, Riga. - Wendelina, Rebels, Colding. BRIELLE, 9 Aug.; Waterloo, S-, Londen.- Zealous, S., Harwich.- Minos, S., Bremen. HAMBURG, 7 Aug ; Hendrika Sieberdina, Kraan, Amst. BR4KE, 26 Julij; Johanna Geerdina, Schoon, Petersburg. — 27 July ; Aukje, Teensma, id. — 28 Julij; Gebroeders Coerkamp, Hoeksma, id. — 2 Aug-; Aaltina Helena, Meijer, Antwerpen. EMDEN, 4 Aug.; Onrust, Mudder, Amst. i MEMEL, 5 Aug.; Alberdina, Boerhave, Grangemouth. KROONSTAD, 3 Aug.; Heerenveen, Prins, Liverpool. RUGENWALDE, 1 Aug.; Aukje Gepkelina, Duintjer, Bremen. STQCIvIIQLM, 4 Allg-i Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge, Hamburg. BOLDERA, 4 Aug.; Hendrik Jan Nassau, Roclfsema, Amst. - Claas Tholen, Geerdes, Dysart. NERVA, 1 Aug.; Titia Jaeobina, Klein, Liverpool, - Jonge Liofert, Bakker, Newc- Geertje, Hoveling, id.- Stad Steenwijk, Wijma, Harlingon.- Vriendsoliap, Visser, Dordrecht. - Nicssina Schuringa, Stroobos, Kopcuh. — 2 Mei; Herman, Doewes, Liverpool. . Gesina, Arnold, Newc. ELSENEUR, 7 Aug.; Eupatoria, Hutchinson, Amst.-Harmonie, Mulder, Catanzaro. - Gepasseerd: Leo Siunige, Kassies, IJetoi*sburg n. Engeland. - Sojan, Otterbeek, Amst. n. Gefflo. - Maria Paulina, Poulsen, Nieuwediep n. Hernos. - Hercules, Korter, Nerva n. Amst. - Gretina, Gortmaker, Libau n de Maas. LONDEN, 7 Aug.; Wicbergina Martcns, Balk, Groq, ABERDEEN, 5 Aug,; Eeudragt, Bos, Petersb. jjjij WEYMQUTH, 7 Aug.; Jantina Christina, Bekkering, Sunderland n. Óporto. FALMOUTH, 8 Aug.; Antilope, Fernström, Bat. NEWHAVEN, 4 Aug., Integrity, Hamden, Rott. QUEENSTOWN, 6 Aug.; Willem Jacobus, de Vries, Dcmerary. YARMOUTII, 7 Au;.; Nooit Gedacht, Naiming, Gotl.euburg. ALLOA, 5 Aug.; Lubbegina, Spithorst, Rott. SHIELDS,7 Aug.;EdH*ard,Miehelsen, Amst.-Oirados.Williams, Rott.- Franijois, van Eyk, Vlissingen. - Cailguano, Antila, Nieuwo D.ep. - Wandeier, Kluss, Zierikzee. - Jutter Zwanette, Pekcldcr, Havre. - Gei-iia Hendrika, Glim, Emden. - Mary, Lovell, Dordrecht. - Centour, Le:, id. - Patriot, Dixon, id. - Wilhelmin i. Puister, Grimsby. SUNDERLAND, 6 Aug.; Geo Smith, Marshall, Nieuwe Diep. —7Aug.; Jean, Batty, id. - De Weldaad, Pik, Wiabeaeji. MIDDLESBRO,7 Aug.; Olive.Mortimor, Amst. - J»hn Els.leth, Milburn, Rott. - Henrictte Catharina, Engcrson, id. DUBLIN, 9 Aug ; General Lee, S., Rott. MILFORD, 7 Aug. j Catherina Morgan, Joscs, Newport n. Doi drecht. ABERSOOH, 7 An &apos;,-&apos;■ Lucy, Jones, Port Madoc n. Rott, HARTLEPOOL, 7 Aug.; Ebenezor, Stephonscn, Amst. LIVORNO, 29 Julij; Cornelia Ijbuise, Casimier, Amst. KONSTANTINOPEL, 27 Julij;Nundeeps, Woodcock, Galatz n. Amst.- Hannah, Tadd, id. n. id- SINGAPORE, 27 Junij; do Hoop, van Duijn, Samarang. I * NEWSCHWANG, 5 Mei; Amazone, Kramer, Ningo (vertrok 29 Mei n. Swatow). AMOY, 1 Junij; Jaco&apos;j en Anna, Bongcr, Horg&apos;cong. — 3 Junij; MalvJna, HoogerwerfF. id. HONGKONG, 16 Junij; Ida Maria de Raath, d ■ Bctfr, Padang.-19 Junij; Admiraal P.et Hein, Priebee, Singapore. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 9 Aug.; Wildeman, Driest, Kaap de Goode Hoop. - Ironmastcr, S., Middlesbro. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Aug.; Irene, S.. Midd. Zee.- Levant, S., Havre.- Earl of Auckland, S., Londen. - Holyrood, S., Leith. - Scntinel, S., Newc. - Scahorse, S., Huil. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 9 Aug.; Island Quccn, S , Hartlepool. - John Wells.S., Goole. VLISSINGEN, 7 Aug.; Helleehina, Pik, Stokholm. - Zwaantina, Nieboer, Bergen. - Godelevus, de Boer, Kouingsb.. Cornelia Catharina, Hagedoorn, Avontuur. - Alida, Veen, id. MEMEL, 4 Aug.; Afien Smit, Boswijk, Zwolle. — 5 Aug.; Louiso Augustc, Noumann, Antwerpen. - Welgelegen, Nieting, Harlingen. BOLDERA, 3 Aug.; Helena Gesina, Schrender, Holland. - Sophia, Berg, Elsenour.- Anna Elise, Timmer, id.—4 Aug.; Soranus, Poelman.Dordrocht.- Margaretha, Kappen, Elseneur. NERVA, 27 Julij; Margaretha Hendrika, de Boer, Vegosack. — 2 Aug.; Aaltje Willemina, Jurrema, Lowestoft. BREMERHAVEN, 8 Aug.; Vijf Gezusters, de Vries, Amsterdam. LONDEN, 7 Aug.; zeilkl.: Helios, Winter, Avoxt. — 8 Aug.; Enjetta, Boswijk, id. - Bochina, Koster, id. DEAL, 8 Aug.; Wilhelmina en Elise, Wicrtsma, Londen n. Montevideo. FALMOUTH, 6 Aug.;Leonore, Jongebloed, Clyde. BONESS, 7 Aug ; William and John, Nunn, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 5 Aug.; zeilkl.: Themis, Buiten, Laguayra. GRIMSBY, 5 Aug.; Wilhelmina, Puister, Shields.-Alida, Nagel, Petersb. HARTLEPOOL, 6 Aug.; Herman, de Vries, Borgen. HOLYHEAD, 7 Aug.; Arm Davies, Davies, Liverpool n. Amst. NEWPORT, 5 Aug.; Naphtali, Jenes, Amst. - Nymph, Hughcs, Dordt DUINKERKEN, 7 Aug.; Catharina Regina, Wulf, Biga. PAIMBOEUF, 6 Aug.; Flambeau, Goupil, Amst. PORTO, 26 Jnlij; Harbcrdiua, Bakker, Leith. LISSABON, 1 Aug.; Amalia, Steen, Vlaardingen. HONGKONG, 22 Jnlij; zeilklaar: Generaal Michiels, Visser, Swatow. AMOY, 1 Junij; Argouaut, Drayer qq., Chcwfoo. SHANGHAE, 9 Junij; Petronella Catharina, v. d. Veen, Newschwang,</p>
</text>
