<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 27 Sept.; Margaretha Arendina, de Jonge, Livorno. - Emden, Jeffrey, New-Castle. - Volanteer, Clwls, Snnderland,</p>
	<p>24 Sept.; Etha Johanna, Gron. w old, Stettin. TERMUNTERZIJL, 21 Sept.; Geerdina, Wypkes, Noorwegen. -Jonge vrro1&apos; Hamburg. —23 Sept.; Hillechiena, Scherphuis, Noorwegen. VLIE, 26 Sopt.; Zeehond, Feninga, Petersburg. - Harmonie, Haver-ehmidt, Memel. - Fortuna, Andersen, Christiania. - Sicco, Douwes, Osternsoer. — 27 Sept.; Zuiderzee, de Jong, Havana. - 4 Gebroeders, Woudstra, New-Castle. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Sept.; Méde&apos;a, van Tentem, Bat. via Bronwerhaven. - Earl of Auckland.S., Londen. - Balmoral, S.Bristol.- Queen, S-, Dnndee. - Holyrood, S., Leith. - Seahorse, S., Hall. -John Wells,S., Goole. - Elisa, Zessin, Riga. - Anna, S., Bergen. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 27 Sept.; Wave, Adams, Middlesbro. - Parthenian, Jary, Newcastle. MAASSLUIS, 27 Sept.; Préciense, Monnier, Hartlepool. - Reform, Gabrielsen, Stavanger. BREMERHAVEN, 26 Sept.; Gezina, Deen, de Oostzee. - Najade, Sieh, Engeland. f EDDERWARDERSIEL, 26 Sept.; de Jonge Roelof, Douwes, Amst. LEER, 22 Sept.; Catharina Imkina, Hülsebos, Amst. - Thedina, Beerthuis, id. HAMBURG, 26 Sept.; Geznsters, van Duin, Amst. DANTZIG, 24 Sept.; Nina, S., Amst. MEMEL, 22 Sept.; Dirkje, Burghoudt, Harlingen. LIB AU, 16 Sept.; Carl Eudolph, Inge, de Maas. — 17 Sept.; Adolf, Kramer, Riga. BOLDER A, 21 Sept.; Pax, Mellema, Nederl. - Willem, Jansonius, Elseneur. — 22 Sept.; Twee Gebroeders, Bntter, de Weser. - Hillechina, Hooghoudt, Elseneur. - Flora, Jongebloedt, id. NERVA, 17 Sept.; Margrietha Hendrika, Datema, Harlingen. - Anrora, Brinkman, ... — 18 Sept.; Hendrika Frouwina, Muller, Huil. - Dankbaarheid, Wey, Liverpool. — 19 Sept.; zeilklaar: Twee Gebroeders, Hellenius, Amst. - Talma, Gullichsen, id. - Eendragt, Kok Houwink, id. - Adrianus, Paap, Schiedom. STOKHOLM, 21 Sept.; Zeilkl.: Rika. Puister, Christinestad. — 21 Sept.; Dolphin, Hazewinkel, Hamburg via Gefle. —22 Sept.; Cycloop S., Amst. GOTHENBURG, 20 Sept.; Annegina Elsina, Kmper, Nederland.-Jantje Doornbos, Addens, Engeland. — 22 Sept.; Amsterdam packet, Thiis, Nederland. RANDÖSUND, 15 Sept.; Catharina Hendrika, Fögen, Dantzig n Dokk ASSENS, 20 Sept.; Eendragt, Boer, België. LIVERPOOL, 25 Sept.; Ida, de la Hoyde, Rott. HARWICH, 25 Seat.; zeilkl.: Johanna, Wilmink, Elseneur. GRIMSBY, 23 Sept.; H. Vincentius van Paulo, Nagel, Dantzig. HULL, 25 Sept.; Hilkelina, Lupkcs, Koningsb. MIDDLESBRO, 25 Sept.; Janna, Struwing, Koningsb. CAEN, 23 Sept.; Louise Marie, Hawksworth, Schiedrm. PAIMBOEUF, 25 Sept.; Caroline Victoire, Lemelais, Rott. CADIX, 22 Sept.; Zeven Sterren, Hemmes, Montevideo. LISSABON, 18 Sept.; Vereeniging, van Duffelen, Vlaardingen</p>
</text>
