<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 30 Nov.; Zwerver, Hoster, Petersburg. - Elisabeth, Lollina, Visser, Gothenburg. — 1 Dec.; Henry Lawson, Benry, Newcastle. - Conro, S., Sunderland. - Neachus, Forster, id. - Alert, S., Huil.- Baron Sloet tot Oldhuis.Smit, Petersburg. - Norske Klippo, Heinricksen, Riga. - Médca, S., Dantzig. - Impérial, S., id. - Carolina, Christiaansen, Tonsberg. VLIE,29 Nov.; Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. —30 Nov.; Lion, S.,Londcn.- Argo, Koster, Riga. - 3 Gezusters, Boswijk,id.-Gebr. Fokkes, Fokkes, Memel. OSTMAHORN, 28 Nov.; Janna Meyer, Datema, Portsmonth. - 29 Nov.; Henderika, Vos, Engeland. - Gesina, Stenger, Gothenburg. DELFZIJL, 26 Nov.; 2 Gebroeders, Alberts, Bremen. • Bouwina, Heins, Ditzum. - Geertruida, Pronk, Leer. - Rensina Willemina, Kramer, id. — 27 Sept.; Imkina Catharina, Hulzebos, id. - Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Bremen.— 28 Nov.; Zwaantje, de Vries, id.-Roelfina Johanna, Drewes, id.- Maria, Minke, Rheine. - Pictronella, Kort, Leer. - Trientje Velikamp, Koopmans, Norden. —29 Nov.; Whisper, S., Londen. - Jonge Roelof, Douwos, Bremen. - Hendrika, Sterk, Leer. HELLEVOETSUIS, 1 Dcc; Maria Magdalena, Willenbrink, Samarang, l.v. Brouwersh., vertrok 30 Jnlij.-Feyenoord, S., Londen. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Progres, Jolly, Sunderland. - Admiral Cator, S., Hartlepool. Voor Pampus ten anker : Heimath, Lange, Bremen. BRIELLE, 1 Dcc; Leo, S., Londen. - Orion, S., id. - Avalon.S.,Harwich. ARENDAHL, 29 Nov.; Ora en Labora, Christensen, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 29 Nov; Edith Owen, S., Rott. n. Dantzig. ELSENEUR, 28 Nov.; gepasseerd: Cornelia Wilhelmina, Hoeksma, Stettin n. Bordeaux. - Hendrik Jan Nassau, Roelfsema, Riga n. Amst. - Goldhorn, Pott, id. n Antw. - Antonius, Gonningen, id. n. Gent. ABERDEEN, 28 Nov.; Roelfina, de Groot, Koningsbergen. NEWPORT, 26 Nov.; Elisabeth, Simmons, Bristol n. Dordt. LIVERPOOL, 29 Nov.: Harberdina, Bakker, Malaga. -In lading: Compact Goede Trouw, de Vries, St. Thomas. - Albatross, S., Rott. LEITH, 29 Nov ; Catharina, de Vries, Rostock. ALLOA, 28 Nov.; Hoogezand, van Driesten, Leith. SUNDERLAND, 27 Nov.; Messenger, Pani, Nieuwe Diep. SHIELDS, 29 Nov.; Juffer Zwanette, Pekelder, Amst. - Hondrina, van Breen, Rott.. - Amphitrite, Pritchard, id. ANTWERPEN, 1 Dcc; Hooste Wieher, Klazen, Palermo. - Afiena, Koops, Zante. ALICANTE,23Nov.; Aphradite, Roostee, Huil. -24 Nov.; Voorwaarts, Vink, Newc. LIVORNO, 19 Nov.; Bércnicc, S., Amst. NAPELS, 22 Nov.; Irene, S., Amst. NICOLAJEFSK, 10 Aug.; Elisabeth, de Boer, Hamburg (1. van Texel). BARBADOS, 3 Nov.; Soestdijk, (Nederl. Oorlogst.) Suriname. UITGEZEILD.</p>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Dcc; Nor, Sanne, Riga n.Gent. - Magnet, S., Londen.-Aurora, S., id. - Zoophite, Urguhart, id. OSTMAHORN, 28 Nov.; Alida Dijk, de Haas, Rochester. - Gebr. Visser, Faber, id. - Gesina Jantina, Bekkering, Londen.-Catharina v. Calcar, Koning, id.-Anna Metta, Ulrichs, Yarmouth. —29 Nov.; Jantina Alida, Texcr, Dover. - Ente, Reuter, id. - Froukina Hillechiena, Oosterhuis, Rochester. - Allegonda Magritha, Gort, id. - Karsina, Olvers, Londen. DELFZIJL, 27 Nov.; Delger, Helena, Bassclt. - Primo, Deters, Nordloh.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Dcc; St. Jan, Lommerse,Bataiia.-Macassar, van Bentveld, id. via Brouwershaven. - Silentium, Schagen van Leeuwen, Buenos Ayres. - Ida Willemina, Rotgans, Londen. -Cornelia Hendrika, Marcussen, Cardiif. - We.tley, Lecouteur, Jersey. - Marco, Laraman, id. - Tcnnant, Davies, Newcastle. - Storm Qneen, S., Hartlepool. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BROUWERSHAVEN, 1 Dcc; Johannes Anthonius, de Voogd van der Straten, Rotterdam n. Bat. - Otto, Stchman Tresling, id. n. id. - Almena, Swan, id. n. New-York, zijn allen bij Langendijke geankerd. LONDEN, 29 Nov.; zeilkl.: Domina Gcertina, Wolters, Elseneur. PLYMOUTH, 29 Nov.; de Hoop, Giezen, Nantes. • Mary Arm, Mathows, Rotterdam. FALMOUTH, 28 Nov.; Arendina, Boerhave, Rio Grande n. Londen.— 29 Nov.; Eppo Hendrik, Schut, Zante n. Hamburg. - Eensgezindheid, de Waal, Brazilië n. Hamburg. BONESS, 29 Nov.; Wiebergina Martens, Balk, Groningen.</p>
	<p>SHOREHAM, 29 Nov.; Wiebergina Martens, Balk, Groningen LIVERPOOL, 29 Nov.; Suffolk, Mc. Fic, Bat.</p>
	<p>EXMOUTH, 29 Nov.; Emilie, Jager, Newcastle. SHIELDS, 29 Nov.; zeilklaar: Amphitrite, Bekkering, Genua,</p>
</text>
