<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Mei; W. N. W., Troubadour, S., Londen. - Visscherij, Visser, fd.-XA.Jacks.rn, Elliott, Pentowan. Elisabeth, Ward, Sunderland. - Ada Florence, Mackleby, Middlesbro. - Rembrandt, S.. Stettin. - Croeso, Schröder, Drammen. VLIE, 14 Mei; Z.W.,Pieter, Oostervink, Oudsoen. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS.UMei; N.W-Ofcto, Stehman Tresling, Batavia I. v. Brouwershaven. - Libra, Dirksen, Manzanilla de Cubo. - Baobah, Levisage, Redon. - St. Malo, Chrétien. id. - Olga, S., Londen. - Amelia &amp; Arm, Holmes, id. - Tradesman, Press, Par. - Elisabeth, Timothy, Port Madoc. - Jane, March, Runcorn. - William. Jones. id. - Charles, Smith, Bridgewater. - Lord Raglan. S.. Newcastle, Planet, Campbell, id. BRIELLE, 14 Mei-, W.. Leo. S, Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 14 Mei; N. N. \.., John Fenwiek, S., Enos n. Rotterdam. „__, . ZIERIKZEE, 14 Mei; N. N. 0., County of Elgm, Mc&apos;Nicol, Samar. n. Rott.; vertr. 22 Dec. - Victoria, Kinian, Teignmouth n. Dordt. &apos;- „---.&apos; LONDEN, 13 Mei; Zeevaart, Engelsman, Groningen. - Twee Broeders. Stenders, Worcum. Bij DEAL, 12 Mei; Louwina, Heerrna, Harwich n. Southampton. - Jac. Johanna, v. d. Meulen, Liverpool n. Nerva. Bij DUNGENESS, 12 Mei; Mary Goddard, Nouhuys, Rott. n. ltTfK* _ _ _31* Bij DOVER, 12 Mei; Geert Herwig, Smit, Rott. n. 8.-Avres. PORTSMOUTH, 12 Mei; Bridesmaid, Dreland, Rott. GREENOCK. 12 Mei; Daniel Rankin, Hartwell.Amst. SCRABSTER, 11 Mei; Eendragt, Houwink, Liverpool naar Nerva. CARDIFF, 11 Mei; Venedy, Miller, Amst. LYNN. 12 Mei; Eliza, Ho ward, Rotterd. RUNCORN, 11 Mei; Grietje, Boer, Teignmouth. - Vriendschap. Lodewijks. id. SL&apos;NDERLAND, 11 Mei; Swan, Davison, Nieuwed. - Adele &amp; Marie. Guellic, Rott. - Joseph &amp; Marie, Selo, id. — 12 Mei; j Thomas k Mary, Shatton, Nieuwed. SHIELDS, Ï2 Mei; Alma &amp; Toni, de Vries, Rotterd. - Mars, j Patton. id. - Elizabeth. Annison, id. - William, Henberg, id. - i Harmony, Wilmut, id.-Trino, Cosalich, id.-Comet, Dudwich.id. Pallas, Bryant, Dordt. - Harmony, Lange, Yarmouth.— 14 Mei; Californie, de Wijn. Amst. TRIEST. 8 Mei; Hazard. Ketelaar Ancona. NEW-YORK, 30 April; Maria Elisabeth, v.d. Gevel, Padang.</p>
</text>
