<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 20 Oct.; Ned. oorl. stoomschip Adolf Hertog van Nassau kapt. Mossel, Middel! Zee. - Fosca Helena, Manje, Suriname.- Acora.&apos; Oelhoorn. Kust van Guinea. ¦ Sjonkina. do Jong, Ancona. - Alma, Banier&apos; NaDels. - Eendragt, Jelsma, Londen. - Bermuda. Hales, Newc. - Marsden&apos; Jaton, id. - Marchant, Dore. id. - J.insjen, Meijer, id. - Freilerika, Ijarks&apos; Engeland. - Carl Johan, Ivensen, Frederikstad. - Gebr. Jansen Andreassen, id. - Noordster, Tobiassen, id.-Emanuel, Hansen, id. -Flora Numan Drammen. - Haabet. Ulrichsen. Noorwegen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 20 Oct.; Pelican. S.. Liverpool. - Meteor, S„ Dublin. - Lonise, S., Grangemouth. - MariaStuart.S., Leith.-Lord Raglan. S., Newc. - Dunaborg. Meijer, id. - Diana. Thomassen, id. - Frederike Marie. Sprenger, Sunderland. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Hopewell, Kives, id. - Acalus, Albrecht, Oostzee. - Carl Gustav, Fieze. id. MAASSLUIS. 20 Oct.; Leo, S„Londen.- Samson.Friede.Sunderl.- Lyra, Strong, id. - Joh. Marie, Kappen, id. - Hermanus Wieher, Tan der Laan, Newc. - Jantje, de Groot, Hamb. - Gezina, Ei, ATontunr. - Joseph, Blnuw, Firth of Forth. De gisteren en heden vertrokken schepen zyn wel in zee. HAMBURG, 18 Oct; Ommelanden, Wieringa, Buenos-Ayres. - Anna Meta, Ulrichs. Belgien. - 4 Gebrüder, Kahloor, Holland. CUXHA VEN. 18 Oct; Geert Herwig, Smit, Kaap Haitï. -Hammonia S., Rott. - Willem I. S, Amst. THISTED, 11 Oct, Marie, Sabröe, Holland. STETTIN. 18 Oct; Vesta.S., Amst. KKOONSTAD, 14 Oct; Goldhoom, Pott, Plymonth. - Welvaart Ekamp, Findhern. • Geertruida Antina, de Weerd de Weser LONDEN, 19 Oct.; Anireas en Maria, Slik, Hamburg, -&apos;Sieuwert en Johan, Looze, Avontuur. LYNN, 17 Oct.;Charlotte,Teensma, Avontuur. HULL, 18 Oct; Martha. Topzant, Koningsb. FALMOUTH. 18 Oct; Result» Heuer, Amst. n. Swansea CARDIFF. 18Oct; Symbol.Dyble. Rott. &apos;n&apos;öwanBea&apos; LIVERPOOL, 17 Oct; Jane Kilgour, Williamson, Bat. -Zeilklaar: Yredelust Brouwer, Havana. RIO JANEIRO, ISSept.; Zeven Gebroedors, de Groot, St. Catharina.— 22 Sept; Cornelia en Geertruida, Wielema, New-Orleans. RIO GRANDE, 30 Aug.; Hendrika Huisman, Huisman,&apos; Fernarabuck. - Industrie. Mnller. id. MONTEVIDEO, 12 Sept.; Pleiaden, de Jonge, HaTana.</p>
</text>
