<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Maart, Z.W.; Hawk, S., Huil. -AlidaPronk, Scholtens, Avont.- 16Maart; Ella, Melly, Newc. -Blackness, Barnett, Sunderl. - Hawk, Morgan, id. - Emma, Peddon, id. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Scotia, Lorentzen, Krageroe. VLIE, 13 Maart, Z. Z. W.; Renskea, de Veen, Newc. -. Catharina, Strenge, Odensee. -Agina Undina, Pekelaar, Osterrisoer.--14 Maart; Hollandia, S., Londen. - Zenobia, Child, Yarmouth. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. - Catharina, v. d. Meulen, Kopenh. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 14 Maart, Z. W.; Rival, Doewes, Boston. A. - Oceaan, Post, Gibralt. - Olga, S., Londen. - Garibaldi, Bruno, Cardiff. - Ousei, S., Liverpool. - Lord Raglan, Si, Newc- Mary, Smith, id. - Dunnoter Castle, Vallode, id. - Marie Eugénie, Barbeduno, id. - Anna Geziena, Staal, id. - Diana, Fijn, id.- Jacob Sijnes, Nip, id. - Mettje Schönfeldt, van Dijk, id. - Louise Alofs, Korter, id.-Antje, Scholtens, Lynn. — 15 Maart; Concurrent, de Jong, Buenos-Ayres. - Teelkma Meiskina, de Haan. id. - Terpsichore, Pedersen, Philadelphia, A. - Lodewijk, Bax, Banana. - President Benson, Koning, id. - Tobina, Wortelboer, Bordeaux. - Sirene, Lorient, Nantes. - Père Lancelot, Bertot, id. - Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Wesley, Nuttall, Jersey. Ranfer, Ahier, id. - Rheidalvale, Thomas, Gloucester. - Truant, ones, Cardiff. - Antagonist, Pearce, id. - Eendragt, Kok Houwink, Newc. - Freerk Jan, Smit, id. - Planet, Campbell, id. - Marie Susanne, Roalet, id. BRIELLE, 14 Maart, W.; Leo, S., Londen. -Ravensbury, S., Harwich. — 15 Maart; Edith, S., Huil. MAASSLUIS, 14 Maart, Z.W.; Emilie, Niggebrugge,Newc- Johanna Maria, Fenenga,id.-HillechienaMargaretha, Joosten, id. - Alida, v. d. Veen, Avontuur. - Annacbiena, Jonker, id. - Johanna Petronella, Hillebrand, id.</p>
	<p>BROUWERSHAVEN, 15 Maart; Minister Fransen van de Putte, Bouwmeester, Rott. n. Bat. CUXHAVEN, 14 Maart; Willem I, S., Amsterdam. FREDERIKSTAD, 2 Maart; zeilkl.: Alexandra, Hanssen, Nederl. — 3 Maart; Olivia, Bredesen, id. - Haabets Anker, Hanssen, id. — 6 Maart; Axel, Grönwold, id. LONDEN, 13 Maart; Zeilklaar: Anna Gesina, de Vries, Harburg. — 14 Maart; Albertus Barend, de Boer, Santander. SEAHAM, 12 Maart; Arno, Harper, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 13 Maart; Otto, Sap, Laguayra. - Gerberdina en Jeannette Emilie, Vlaskamp, Kooperpolder. - Ida, S., Rott. RUNCORN, 13 Maart; Grimaldi, HUI, Zierikzee. LEITH, 12 Maart; Eendragt, Dorenbos, Boness. ST. NAZAIRE, 11 Maart; Gesina Dorothea, de Boer, Harl. - Cornelia, Nieboer, Rotterdam. TRIEST, 7 Maart; Entreprise, Mulder, Rotterdam. SAMARANG, 26 Jan., Juanita, v. John, Nederland. —18 Jan.; Ellen, Hunter, id. — 22 Jan.; Allegonda Jacoba, Mammes, id. PASSAROEANG, 15 Jan.; Zuleika, Riddell, Nederland.— 17 Jan.; Maria Adriana, Itz, id. - Willem Kroonprins der Nederlanden, de Bourgholles Zetteler, id. — 21 Jan.; Pieter, Hqogewerif, id. — 22 Jan.; Petronella, Leieher, id. BANJÓEWANGIE, 30 Dcc; Quartet, Mulder, Amst. - Whampoa, Janses, Rott. — 3 Jan.; J. C, Schotel, Chevalier, id. - Zeebloem, Gollards, Amst. — 12 Jan.; Henriette Elisabeth, Stenzel, Soerabaya. — 13 Jan.; Eastern Empire, Meiklejohn, Amst. - Generaal de Stuers, Viersma, Dordt. - Rotterdam, Janzen, Rott. - 2 Gezusters, Bemolt, id. — .14 Jan.; Cornelia Mathilde, Houtkooper, id. — 15 Jan.; Briston, Crombie, Amst.- Ferdinand &amp; Louis, Duinker, Padang, SINGAPORE, 21 Jan.; Julia, v. Loon, Bat. HONGKONG, 21 Jan.; Gloria, Puister, Nagasaki.</p>
</text>
