<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 28 April, Z. Z. O.; Alida, Borgman, Christiansand. VLIE, 27 April, Z. Z. O.—Z. W.; Boreas, Munneke, Leith. - Mercnrius, de Groot, Memel. - Aukje Gepkelina, Duintjer, Kiel. - Anje, Munning&apos;, Arendahl. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. - Gloria, Grapel, id. - Petronella Georgina, Krijnen, Helgoland. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 April; Z.Z.0.-N.0.; Fortuna, Hoogerwerff, Lissabon. - Isabella Sarah, Hall, Newc. - Emanuel, Beekman, Ystad. - Anna Catharina, Olsen, Malmoe.-Fortuna, Meyndert, Randers.- Broedertrouw, Woltman, Odensee. BRIELLE, 28 April, Z.0.-0.N.0.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Sheffield, S., Grimsby. - Avalon, S., Harwich&apos;. - Johanna, Kraeft, Stettin. BROUWERSHAVEN 28 April; O. N.0.; Notre Dame d&apos;Espcrance, Louwy, Licata n. Rott. - Jan van Galen, Braaf, Rott. n. Bat. BREMERHAVEN, 27 April, op de rivier: Cornelia en Susanna, Wijtsma, Seville. NORDEN, 22 April; Fennegina, Beerthuis, Bremerhaven. TRAVEMUNDE, 26 April; Heerenveen, Prins, Nantes. -SWINEMUNDE, 26 April; Rotterdam, S., Rott. DANTZIG, 25 April; Baron Sloet tot Oldhnis, Braam, Kampen. - Fockelina Emmelina, Folkerts, Rott. - Alida Margaretha, Eisses, Amst.</p>
	<p>Bij KOPENHAGEN, 25 April; Hoffnung, Sonne, Amst. n. Windau. KOPENHAGEN, 25 April; Titia Margaretha, Schaap, Amst.-Ter reede &gt; voor anker: Maria Christina, Balk, Rott.n. Koningsb. - Argo, Douwes, Kennetpans n. Petersburg. ELSENEÜR, 24 April, gepasseerd: Maria Christina, Balk, Rott. n. Koningsbergen. — 26 April; Maria, Sörensen, Schiedam n. Windau.-.Anna, Venema, Hamburg n. Riga. TONNINGEN, 24 April; Catharina Antina, Speelman, Hamburg. — 25 April, gepasseerd: Jantje.&apos;Rasker, Burnt Mand n. Rendsburg. - Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, Dordt n. Koningsbergen. - Geertruida, Rasker, Hamburg n. Aarhuus. -Zwaantje Klein, Drent, Bremen n. Dantzig.-Twee Gebroeders, Buss, id. n. Koningsbergen. LONDEN, 26 April; Anna, Schut, Ancona. — 27 April; Elisabeth Geertruida, Janknecht, Gron.- Nachina Lammechina, Rijnberg, Landscrona. Bij DEAL, 26 April; de Schelde, Hoffrnan, Bat. n. Amst. Bö LOWESTOFT, 24 April; Camperdown, Thoms, Nieuwediep n. Liverpool. Bü FOLKESTONE, 27 April; Generaal de Stuers, Yiersma, Rott. n. Cardiff. PL ÏMOUTH, 26 April; Balmoral, S., Rott. WARKWORTH, 25 April; Radiant, Pringle, Rott. ABERDEEN, 25 April-, Jonge Gerrit, Hazewinkel, Amst. INVEBKEITHING, 25 April; Margaretha Johanna, Meincrs, Bremerhaven. — 26 April; Maria, Pronk, id. LLANELLY, 25 April; Annechina, Smit, Cagliari. SHOREHAM, 26 April; Hermina, Gort, Groningen. GOOLE, 26 April; William, Johnson, Rott. HULL, 26 April; William, Greaves, Rott.-Hendrika, Holman, Zwolle.- MIDDLESBRO, 26 April;iElisabeth, Pekeler, Rott. - Vr. Martha, Koning, Vlissingen. SUNDERLAND, 25 April; Landrath von Strahlendorif, Lorenz, Rott. - NEW-CASTLE, 26 A pril; Johanna Wilhelmina, Faber, Amst. SHIELDS, 26 April; Arcturus, Richards, Rott. LEITH, 26 April; Concordia, Naatje, Brussel. GIBRALTAR, 18 April; Maria, Tieman, Livorno n. Hamburg. GENUA, 23 April-, Margaretha, Koster, Rott. LIVORNO, 22 April; Margaretha, Vos Peper, Amst. - 11. Florcntina id.</p>
</text>
