<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 15 Julij; Schuringa, Engelsman, Suriname.-EppoHendrik, Schut, Napels. - Lion, S., Londen. - Cornelia, de Jong, id. - 2 Broeders, van Kempema, id. - Stad Workum, Stenders, id. - Hartford, Coates, Newe. - Jabez, Lukas, id.-Marsden, Patow, id. - Jane,Scarfe,id.- ComeOn,Bolten, Sunderl. - Sultana, Buil, id. - Whim, King, Yarmóuth. - Minerva, Raven, Söderhamn. - Elisabeth, Cathrine, Olsen, Oostzee. - Amphitrite, Hansen, Frederikstad. - Fire Söskende, Agernp, id. - Elise, Hannevig, Drammen. - Aukator, Morck, id. - Mindes, Harrison, id. - Thetis, Hovgaard, id. - Deodata, Andèrsen, id. - Gebr. Janzen, Andreassen, id. - Fortnna, Kittelsen, Noorwegen. - Adeline, Ipsen, Avontuur. -Vigilantia, Jans,id.-StadEnschede, Niggebrugge, id. (Benevens de schepen per telegr. gemeld). VLIE, 14 Julij; Eendragt, Dorenbos, Newc. - Frithiof, Bjönness, Riga. - Stad Steenwijk, Wijma, id. - Harlingen, Hannema, Memel. - Concordia, van der Meyden, Koningsb. - Mercur, Roer, Christiania, - Jantina, Lohman, Noorwegen. &apos;- Elisabeth, Zeven, id. - Catharina, Thaden, id. - Jeltina, Wessels, Avontuur. — 15 Julij; Dorothea Elisabeth, Wied, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 15 Julij; Bezoekie, Reekers, Bat. via Brouwershaven. - Doelwijk, Hoefman, id. via id. - Oceanus, Dirksen, Singap. via Cardiff. - Arrow, Knowles, Napels. - Gitana, S., Antw. - Sara, S., Londen. - Zephyr, S., id. - Brother&apos;s Success, Hobarth, Rochester. - Therese, S., Grangemouth. - Holyrood, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newe. - Rhcidolvale, Thomas, id, - Saturno, Sehiaffino, id. - Azella, Peterson, id. - John Pearce, Furse, id. - Van, Thompson, id. - Thetis, Zeplien, Engeland. - Islander, Hegnander, Riga. - 2 Gebroeders, Waterborg, Koningsb. - Emanuel, Olsen, Stettin. - Heinrich, Jacobsen, Elseneur. - Johanna Margaretha, Ei, Dago Kertell. - Ingeborg Emelie, Henrichsen, Frederikstad. - Favorite, Back, Christiansand. MAASSLUIS, 15 Julij; Euphrasie, Hervé, Sunderiand. - Flimby, Moar, Middlesbro. - Eweretta, Annis, Shields. - Cornelia Elisabeth, Kramer, Koningsbergen. De gisteren vertrokken schepen wel in zee. EMDEN, 12 Julij; Margaretha, Mudder, Amst.- SophiaCatharina,Wiers, Engeland. - Maria Helena, Teerling, id. BREMERHAVEN, 14 Julij; Hillegina, Hassling, Avontuur. - Trientje, Feddcs, Schiedam. CUXHAVEN, 14 Julij ; Sicco, Potjer, Gibraltar. - Ceres, de Boer, Petersburg. WISMAR, 12 Jnlij; Twee Gezusters, Bakker, de Oostzee. DANTZIG, 12 Jnlij; Harmonie, Dik, de Oostzee. AARHUUS, 7 Juljj; Edel Catharina, ..., Schiedam. THISTED, 11 Julij; Eendragt, de Boer, Engeland. KOPENHAGEN, 10 Julij; Vriendschap. Elles, Bordeaux n. Lubeck. ARCHANGEL, 1 Julij; zeilkl.: Zorgvlied, Garnaat, de Maas. -Jan Smit, Boon, Kooger-Polder. - Lambertha, Karst, Amst. — 3 Julij; Hendrik Wester, Drent, id. - Fenna, Schmidt, id. LONDEN, 13 Jnlij; zeilklaar: Hendrik Pieter, Bakker, Elsenenr. - Pieter, Bekkering, id. — 14 Julij ; Koning Willem 111, Oort, Bat. FALMOUTH, 12 Julij; Mardochee, Repetto, Zwarte zee n. Amst. LIVERPOOL, 13 Julij; Gesina Hendrika, van Kampen, Galatz. HULL, 13 Julij; Alida Adriana, Kampen, Avontuur,</p>
	<p>CARDIF, 12 .ulij; Metje Schönfeld, van Dijk, Oldénburg. DARTMOUTH, 13 Julij; Carry Winch, Barret, Liverpool n. Harl. LEITH, 13 Julij; Jonge Gerrit, Hazcwinkel, Burnt Island. - Elisabeth, t. Wijk, Dysart. GENT, 13 Julij; Jantina, Boon, Avontuur. NANTES, 12 Julij; Alphonsine Jeanne, Lefèvre, Rott. - Capitaine Lassaigne, Leqnénel, Harl.</p>
	<p>LAGUARYRA, 11 Junij; Gerberdina en Jeannette Emila, Kuyper, Altona. — 21 Junij; Hermanus&apos;lsaac, van der Veen, Liverpool. PORT-AU-PRINCE, 8 Junij; Hsrstelling, Ligthart, Falmouth. ST. THOMAS, 16 Junij; Amisia, Sap, Maracaibo. CALL AO, 28 Mei; Elbans, (? Olbers) Deike, Nederland.</p>
</text>
