<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Oct.; Grange, Cuthbert, Newc. - Marsden, Paton, id. - Aurelia Gruno, Stuitje, id. - Margretha. de Vries, id. - Roza, Oelsen, Frederikstad. — 13 Oct.; Ivanhoe.&apos;S., Leith.- Hudgill, Breems. Newc. Mare.hant, Dove, id. - Vivid, Bedlingtield, Sunderl. - Fennechiena, Koetee, Petschora. - Wieka, Eelting, Petersb. - Nina, S.,Koningsb.-Columbia, Roed.Sundswall. (Benevens het schip per tel. gemeld.) VLIE. 12 Oct.; Olga, S., Londen. — 130ct.; Swauland, S., Huil. - Houkelina, Steur, Ystad. - Jansina, Buisman, Bandholm. - ..., Dunker, Neuharlingerzijl. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Oct.; Otto, Steltman Tresling Batavia, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Lydie, Gucriff, Nantes. - Aukeanor, Thorpe, Newc. - Laura, Jórgensen, Stubbekjü Mug. - Elve. S , Hamburg. BRIKLLE, 13 Oct.; Edith, S., Huil. ZIERIKZEE, 13 Oct.; Tonia, Haesloop Wernev Jr., Rangoen n. Rott. BREMERUAVEN, 11 Oct.; Meinsina, Klontje, Riga. ELVE, 12 Oct.; Urania, S., Havre. - Hammonia, S-, Antwerpen. LAUKVIG, 28 Sept.; Renske, Pott. Delfzijl. SARPSBORG, 3 Oct.; Ccres, Gabrielsen, Nieuwediep.- 6 Oct.; Bellona, Cornelinssen, id. GOTHENBURG. 8 Oct; Catharina. Thaden, Newcastle; - Oosterri*oer, Hansen, Nieuwediep. - Elisabeth, Trijsellus, Rott. KOPENHAGE S 10 Oct.-.Sif, Magnusseu, Petersburg n. de Maas. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 9 Oct.; Maria, Doyen,Schiedam n.Riga. DANTZIG, 10 Oct.; Ter reede: Saramadca, de Vries, Amst. PERNAU. 10Oct.;Engelina, Kouter, Amst. RENDSBURG, 9 Oct.; Gepasseerd: Jacoba Gesina,Heins,Stettinn. Rusterzijl, — 10 Oct.; Geertruida, Rasker, Horsens n. Amst. - Vier Gebroeders, Emmelkamp, Hamburg n. Stettin.— 11 Oct.; Lubbina, Hazelhoff. Ebeltoft n. de Zaan. - Fraukea, Meyor, Amst n. Stettin. HOLYHEAD, 11 Oct.; Heerenveen, Prins, Hamburg n. Liverpool.- Dorothea. de Boer, Amst. n. id. FALMOUTH. 11 Oct. -, Pietrouella, Wirtjes, Liverpool n. Riga. LIVERPOOL, 11 Oct.; Resolute, Hughes, Vlissingen. POOLE. 9 Oct; Albert Frederik, de Lange, öandarne. MIDDLESBRO, 11 Oct; Alecto, Mitchell, Rott. - Telegraph, Spence, Dordt.</p>
	<p>NDERLAND, loOct.-, Mag.lalena, ïuchsen, Dordt. - Elizahctii en \rn.., Zierii , Rott. NE VY«CASTLÊ, 8 Oct.; in lading: Jantiua, de Jonge, Triest. SHJELDS, 11 Oct.; Johanna, de Wit. Auist. - Helena.de Jonge, id.-/eeiueeuw, van der Meer, id, - Boreu, Munoeke, HArliogen, - Itordeacx, i &gt;uend*g, id. • Twee Gebroeders, Waterborg, Gron. - Jantins Catbarina, lijk, id.- liarbara Hendrika, i. - Hendrika,Smit, Emdcn. BOUOEAUX. 9 (jet.: Hollander, S., B NAPELS. 4ÜCti Atina, Koops. Var&gt;i DARHANELLEN, 27 Sent.; Berenico.Sk, Konstantiuopel. BATAVIA, &apos;.&apos;t; Au;: una, Singapore. - Hollands Trouw, de Vos.l 27 Aug.; Cornclia Hendrika, Marcussen, Singapore. - Jason, linsi STRAAT SONDA. II On weband, Sewo. naar Singapore. U 6 Aug.; Krimpen a/d. h&gt;k, lwitgaus. Kott, naar Hongkong. — 27 Aug.;lsis, Torley Duwell, Oardifi&apos;u. Singapore. - de Zwaan, Docksen, Bat. n. Cork.</p>
</text>
