<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 23 Maart; Manolo, Morua, Bilbao. - Parat, Gohrsen, Newc. -&apos; Urda, Melsen, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 23 Maart; Magnet, S., Londen. - Agma Undma, Brouwer, Hnll. - Elve, S„ Hamburg. BRIELLE, 23 Maart; Orion, S., Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 24 Maart; Arnold Böningcr, Stecnken, Eott. n. New-York. MAASSLUIS, 23 Maart; Wear, Cooper, Newc. - Elisabeth Arm, Strong, Sunderl. - Heldringen, Bjerk, id. - Jonge Wouter, Groenevelt, dc Noordzee. - Belina, Pot, Avontuur. BREMERHAVEN, 22 Maart; Margrieta, Gust, Amst. LONDEN, 22 Maart; Catharina, Drok, Elseneur. - Catharina, Duintjer &apos;Wiek. &apos; PORT MADOC, 21 Maart; Leonard Hollis, Roberts, Eott. CHARLESTON, 20 Maart; Oporto, Glanvil, Dordt. - Kiugaloch, 810- Yr.ey, Rott. IPSWI CH, 21 Maart; Christina, Oltmans, Nederland. SUNDERLAND, 21 Maart; Conqueror, Sanderson, Schiedam. - Hillechina, Hooghoudt, Caen. FALMOUTH, 21 Maart; P. Godeffroy, Meiier, Icmique n. Rott. - Cape Hom, Matzen, id. n. Amst. - Brilliant, Bacn, Callao n. Rott.-Zodiac, Dinnelow, Bat. n. Bremen. - Titia Susanna, Potjer, Rott. n. Belfast.- Zeilkl.: Charlotte Geddie, Forster, Matanzas n. Amst. ; NEWPORT, 20 Maart; Fortuna, Busch Keyzer, Brindisi. BRISTOL, 21 Maart; Cornelia, van der Velde, Goole. BRIDLINGTON, 20 Maart; Alida Sara, Mooi, Colchester n. Newc. CAEN, 20 Maart; Jeune Olvine, Gillard, Rott. PAIMBOEUF, 20 Maart; Pierre Raymond, Leboulicaut, Harlingen. - Dieverdina Alida Pot, Meycring, Rott. - Aline, Ordronneau, id. - Louise Desirée, Rivet, id. NANTES, 20 Maart; Ena Elisabeth, Smit, Rott. REDON, 14 Maart; Anna Agatha, Sloot, Rott. — 20 Maart; Gebroeders, Loodijzen, id. ROYAN&apos;, 21 Maart; Vier Gebroeders, Balkema, Antwerpen. GIBRALTAR, 8 Maart; Zeilkl.: Geerdina, Flik, Hamburg, ri. Triest. MONTEVIDEO, 1 Febr.; Carolina, Cupido, New-York. — 3 Febr.; d&apos;Ominelanden, Wieringa, Antwerpen. BAHIA, 12Febr.; Marehina, Nepperu.. Kanaal. RIO GRANDE. 31 Jan • Atalante, Looiier, Falmouth.</p>
</text>
