<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22Maart; Alpha,Jacobsen, Drammen.—23Maart;Friedrich, Fassmer, Bat.; vertr. 10 Nov. - 3 Broeders, Kaspersma, Londen. - Alert, S.,HuH. VLIE, 2 Maart; Colombo, Lamale, Nantes. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 22 Maart; Colletis, S., Goole. - 23 Maart; Eugénie, Couedelj Vannes. - Feycnoord, S., Londen. - Seagull, S., Huil. — Eagle, Hawkins, lpswich. - Faimy, Unger, Frederikstad. BRIELLE, 23 Maart; Avalon, S., Harwich. MAASSLUIS, 23 Maart; Maria, van Luyk, de Noordzee. LONDEN, 22 Maart; Lubbiija, Hazclhotf, Groningen. PORTSMOUTH, 21 Maart;Theodora Josina.Tjakkes, Curapaon.Amst. PORTLAND, 21 Maart; Mathilde, Kraeft, Odessa n. Rott. COLCHESTER, 21 Maart; Eendragt, Smit, Groningen. FOWEY, 21 Maart; Kingaloch, Blöway, Gharlestown n. Rott.- Oporto, Granville, id. n. Dordrecht. St. MAVVES, 21 Maart; Nelson, Jenkins, n. Dordt. ROCHÉSTER, 21 Maart; Brothers, Success, Hobart, Rott. JERSEY, 19 Maart; Seabird, Nuttall, Rott. CHARLESTOWN, 21 Maart; Fockelina Emmelina, FplkeiijiS, Plymouth. (ligt in lading n. Hamburg.) LIVERPOOL, 21 Maart; in lading: Cornelia, Voraikamp, Petersb. - Jacobus, Klaasen, id. - Alida Elisabeth, Potjewijd, Nerva. HARTLEPOOL, 21 Maart; Maria, Muller, Wolgast. SHIELDS, 21 Maart; Ebo, Lavagna, Amst. - Rieka, Puister, Dordt. - Concordia. Aden, Schiedam. - Johanna Jantina, Schoon, Harburg. - Drie Gebroeders,Letters,Londen.-Anna Elisabeth, Dik, id. -Jonge Gerrit, Hazewinkel, id. - Tetta Margaretha, Buss, id. TEIGNMOUTH, 21 Maart; Jacobina, Maathuis, Exeter. BORDEAUX, 19 Maart; Hendrik Wester, Drent, Petersburg CETTE, 19 Maart; Jantje Goossons, Leisier, Liverpool. - Wilhelmina, I do Groot, Londen. . GENUA, 20 Maart; Helen, Altraeppen, Amst. St. ÜBES, 14 Maart; Voorwaarts, Schouten, Lissabon. — 15Ma;rt; Wilhelmina, van der Weyden, Vlaardingen. i GIBRALTAR, 10 Maart; Geziena, Doekes, Bahia (vertr. 12 Maart n. &apos; Genua). — 13 Maart; Sophia, van Noord, Alicante n. Amst.- Annachiena, Jonker, Triest n. Hamburg.—l4Maart; Eden, Romano, Napels n. Eott.— 15 Maait; Mina, v. Keulen,Livorno n. id.-Morgenster,v. Dijk,Vlsiardiijgen. TARRAGONA, 16 Maart; Sophia, de Haan, Ncwport. NAPELS, 21 Maart; Verwisseling, Boon, Amst. (Alles wel aan boord.) MONTEVIDEO, 1 Febr.; Henriette, , Hamburg. - Meppel, Sukkel van Dam, Amst. - Hcrtha, Dusar, Cardiff. - Cornelia Maria, Timmer, Cadix. — 9 Febr. In lading: Cornelia Elisabeth, van Gijsel, Antwerpen. - Sirins, van Wijngaarden van Rees, id. - Alida, Visser, id. BAHIA, 21 Febr. Inlading: Ida,Hazewinkel,Kanaal.-Fcnnechina, Hotze, id. .</p>
</text>
