<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Jan., W. N. W. - Z. W.; Tagal, Stangebeye. Sundswail 1. v. Christiansand. VLIE, 20 Jan., W. N. W.; Nora, S„ Londen. ZOLTKAMP. 18 Jan.; Zwaantje Drost, Heijenga, Ramsgate. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Jan., W. Z. W.-, ïlebe, Kiehl, ÏSat. 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Laboramus, Ravmond. Newyork, Lv.id.- Presideht Benson. v. Duin, Kust v. Güinea, 1. v. id&apos;. - Oxidente, Fortunate, Taganrog, I. v. id. -Brigadier, S„ Londen. - Dragon, S., id. - Annie, S., Goole. - Weldaad, Voogd. Windau. -Père Meilleur, Luest, ~\ lissingen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 21 Jan., N. W.-. Almonde, Pijl, Bat. n. Rott., vertr. 26 Aug. - Helena en Anna, v. Waalberg, id. n. id., vertr. 5 Oct. DEAL, 19 Jan., O. N. O.: Kortenaer, Sehuchard, Bat.n. Rott. Bij DEAL, 20 Jan.; Cheribon, Reiniersen, Bat. n. Amst. RAMSGATE, 19 Jan.; Maria Elisabeth, Bonjer, Londen n. Aspinwall en Greytown. SHIELDS, 18 Jan.; Gesina. Kramer, Londen: LIVERPOOL, 18 Jan.; Gannet. S.. Rott. BORDEAUX, 16 Jan.: Mathilde, Westerberg, Gothenburg. St. HELENA,I9Dec-, Varuna, Clarke, Caleiittan. Londen — 24 Dcc; Pieter Adolf, Jaski, Bat. n. Nederl. Bij St. HELENA, 22 Dcc: Sliedrecht, Borchers, Samarang n. Amst,— 23 Dcc: Johanna Christina, le Clercq. Bat.n.Nederl. Bij ASCENSION, II Dcc,: Dionysia Catharina, Berkelbach van den Sprenckel. Bat. n. Amst, —!2Dee.; Souburg, Zwart. id. n. id. - Louise, Bonjer, id. n. id. —15 Dec.; Brouwershaven, Huizer. id. n. Nederl. RIO-.TANEIEO. 22 Dcc; Dankbaarheid, Kooy, P. Allegro. FERNAMBUCK, 23 Dcc; Adriana Johanna, Emerson.Montevideo. BUENOS-AYRES, 24 Nov.; Quatre Bras, Wêsterveld, Itapira. — 23 Nov.; Adelheid, Akkerman, Rott. - Johanna Maria, Post, New-York. —30 Nov.; Pleyaderi, de Jon ge, Amsterd. — 1 Dcc; Theresia. Huizing, Itapiru. — 5 Dcc; Hennes, Snerken, Amst, - Vrederust, Brouwer, id. BAHIA, 24 Dcc; Lida, Muller, Liverpool. UiTGEZEILD. TEXEL. 21 Jan.. W. N. W. - Z. W.; Minerva, S, Hamburg. Havre. - Palmen. Larsen, Tonsberg. BRIELLE, 21 Jan,; Ravensbury, S., Harwich. LONDEN, 18 Jan.; Zeemeeuw; van der Meer, Montevideo (via Cardiff.) — 20 Jan.-, zeilkl.: Admiraal de Winter, Dill, Bombay. Se. HELENA, 17 Dcc, Margaretha Simonetha, Hofhuami. Batavia n. Amst, NEW-YORK. 4 Jan.-. Zeilkl.: Duisburg, Heitjes, Baltim. HAVANA, 28 Dcc; Zeilkl.: Cuba Packet. Rapp, Bremen. RIO-JANEIRO, 14 Dcc: Presto, Eoelfsema, Marahe.</p>
</text>
