<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>Tï.&quot;&apos; Pada,&apos;. uI.&apos;UJ; JinKelina, de Uroot,Memel. — 4Jumi; Uncas, Mc&apos;ln-o„,orbecke,,orbecke, . \7- Ealmouth.-Bci-énico, S., Middell.__ee. - Minister Ti. ° . Sfi&apos;fl iHuII- _ Elisabeth Catharina, Hcegaard, Nerva.-Alice V^en rhamn- &quot; Rembrandt, S., Dantzig. - Protector, Mehre, \T°Srri\TATiIAnJ; Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. ciaSritha &lt; ,rN&gt; 31 Mci- Trientje Veldkamp, Koopman, Bremen.--n. a&gt; Wii,&apos;, &lt;.vina&apos;id- ¦ Trientje Kroder, Dijkstra, id. — 1 Junij- Hrlle&gt;ï ELltVfl-r &gt; &apos;a- i,i &apos;ay Mei;Aüm Wilhelmina, de Boer, Bremen. - Margrietha j&gt;, .. ei-&apos;i_ &quot;Catharina, Buisman, id. - Maria, Jungerhaus, Rheine. — B.?.ei-»&apos;Loo. Clln8e . Indewisch, Papenburg. - Uit Vriendschap, Bolw-Ki-r £&quot;*• — 31 Mei; Esperance, Schlüter,Oldenburg.-Catherine, Si&apos;eb, Paii^&apos;l ~~ l Junii-, Aldershof, Dijkstra, Laurvig. -de Hoop, IndehÓ|&apos;?«rs, &lt;&amp;** - 2 Gezusters, de Lange, Weener. - Taika Catharina, HÈ temunde- -de Hóóp, Drewes, Emden.-Engel_.Boek&apos;V öl&apos;ou .OT.h&apos;SLIIIS- 4 Jonij-, Minister Thorbecke, Kanncgictcr, Bat. tsn- - .Dankbaarheid, v. d. Eerg, Lissabon. - Minna, Kulise, Nantes. - Industrie, Garnier, id. -Sara.S.,Londen.-Batavier,S.,id.- Dubliu, S., id. - Wild Wave, Hoeken, Runcorn. - Queen, S., Dundce. - Leader, Davics, Workington. - Anna Sarah, Piekering, id. - Sarah Arm, Dickinson, id. - Storm Queen, S., Hartlepool. - Anna Augusta, Kuiper, Windau.. - Anna Molena, Anderson, Riga. - Cortgene, Wemmerus Pz., Amsterdam. BROUWERSHAVEN, 4 Junij; Adriana Petronclla, de Breuk, Bat. n. Rott.; vertr. 2 Febr. - Anna Eliza, Andrews, Jamaica n. id. VLISSINGEN, 4 Junij; Mathilde, Fekkes, Buenos-Ayres n.Antw.- ANTWERPEN, 2 Junij; Jantina, Eefting, Riga.— 3 Junij; Diana/Masdorp, Buenos Ayres. - Catharina, Stuven, Montevideo. — 4 Junij;Jennike Hendrika, Stoorvogel, Dantzig. - Arendina Jacoba, Menses, Riga. i UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 4 Junij; Albion, Todt, Newc. - Europa, Zielcke, Sunderland. - Vertrouwen, Kal, Archangel. - Richard Cobden, Stibolt, Riga. - Aurora, I Christensen, Drammen. - Folix, Walloe, id. - Mindet, Arvesen, id. - Vikingen, Sanne, id. OSTMAHORN, 31 Mei; Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, Ipswich. - Johan Gerard, Huges, Noorwegen. DELFZIJL, 28 Mei; 2 Gezusters, Geltes, Bremen. —29 Mei; Johanna Gesina, van Veen, Riga. - Catharina, Dijkema, Noorwegen. • Gesina, Niezen, Einden. - Hendrika, Vos, Avontuur. - Ida, Wolkamraer, id. — | O Mei; Broedertrouw, de Groot, Kroonstad. - Sophia, Bicze, Bremerhaven. - 3 Gebroeders, Klein, Varol. - Rcmgicna, Boerthuis, Leer. — . 31 Mei; Zeidina, Jansen, Engeland.- Pavadetta, Pott, Archangel. - Anno- i gina, Bul, Bremen. - Cathar. Imkiena, Hulzebos, Leer. - Yr. Grietje, Kuiper, Norden. - Margretha, Katt, Emdcn.</p>
</text>
