<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>fiutrgctrltjfcc Tan 2 tot en met 8 Nel 18G7. BEVALLEN : E. S. van Leeuwen , geb. van Heusden, I). —J. Rijke, geb. Hamaker, D. —J. Hensen , geb. van der Lof, Z. —H. van Wiereneen , geb. de Ouden, D. — J. E. van Noort, geb. Hoppenbrouwer, D.— A~. van den Bos.geb. Oudshoorn, D. — A. Wolfson.geb. Veegens, D. — J. van Leeuwen, geb. Arnoldus, Z. — S. W. Dirks, geb. Vlieland, D. — N. van Steenbergen, geb. Dingemans, Z. — C. M.Pleyte. geb.Templeman van der Hoeven , D. —G.van Rooyen, geb. Prins, D. — E.M.Gijsman, geb. Chardyn, Z. — M. A. M. F. Engelhart, geb. van Sloten, Z. — D. Sirach, geb. Slrijland, Z. — A. C. M. Sleeuw, geb. Raaphorst, D. — W. C. de Gunst, geb. Haneveld, Z. — M. F. Koppers, geb. Elshof, Z. — D. Laven, geb. Dozy, D. — W. J. Hakkaart, geb. Koenen, D. — E. van Maslrigt, geb. Goedraad ,D. — A. E. Kooyker, geb. Pelgrim, D. —C. F. Franchimon, geb. Coster, D. — .1. M. Aniba, geb. van Soest, D. —A. M. Verbrugge, geb Bernard, Z. — J. &apos;M. van Dalen, geb. Maaswijk, Z.— W. du Croix, geb. Retel. D. — B. Wagtendonk, geb. de Vroede, D. —M. van Weeren , geb. van der Reek ,D. —M. J. Singeling , geb. Labordus, D. —P. Loffler, geb. van Belle, D. — 11. Gerretsen, geb. Sipman, D. — C. J. Schenk, geb.Rietbergen ,Z. — 11. de Haan , geb. Keereweer. Z. GEHUWD: A. Tendeloo, jm. en J. S. Miog, jd. —W. F. Buys, jm. en C. CoPPy. jd. — J. N. van der Mark, jm. en M. S. Schouten, jd. — J. Kasteelen, jm.en J.C. van Vendelon, jd. — J. Pardon, jm. en L. Stekweg,jd. — M. Lindenhof, jm. en W. C. Dam, wede. —A. van Tienen, jm. en C. Welsink, jd. — 11. van Rosse, jm. en C. J. van Erkel, jd. — W. Oudshoorn ,jm. en L. Pillekers, jd. — F. Kikkert, jm. en C. A. Marks, jd. —T. van der Krogt, jm. en M. C. Vogels, jd. — J. A. de Does, wedI*, en J. H. f immers, jd.— A.C. Kuypers, jm: en J. M. Muusers, jd. —M. G. Ouwerkerk, jm. en D. van der Zee, jd. — G. Kroon .jm. en M.C. R. de Haas, jd. — R. W. de Jonge, jm. en C. Kasteele, jd. OVEIt LEDEN: &quot;Si&apos;, de Bolster, D., ruim 1 j. — C. J. van Hoeken ,60 j.— P. van Es, 77 j. — J.Colpa, Z.,4 w. —J. Wagemans,D.&apos;,9 w. —C. van Veen, D., 19 m. —W.F. dc Lange. Z., 16 d. —G. van Helden, D., ruim 7m.— W. F. Lambinon, Z., Im. —J.F. P. Peters, Z., 6d.— K. Kreft, Z., Im.—M. P. Erades, D., 7 w. —M. C. Janssen, wed. J. J. van der Lunr, 84 j. —C, Baars, D., 3m. — J. G. Coonacker, 91 j.</p>
</text>
