<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN. Scheepstijdingen.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 9 Julij; Hendrik, Hack, Santos, 1. v. Falm. - Johanna, Rötgers. Galatz. - J. Ruttersford, Chilvert, Newc- Hartford, Coatcs, id.- Jauc, Sc-uTid. - Times, Robinson, Seaham. - Joseph Hcnsley, Watson, id. - Cort Sc vertsen Adler, Hansen, Riga.-Ida Albertina, Brons, Dantzig.-Princes Gvd»* Chiistensen, Drammen. - Deodata, Audersen, id. VLlE,BJulij;Eendragt, Dorenbos, Newc- AlidaGiezen, Nieland,Rig*-&apos; ) 9 Julij; Arentina Jacoba, Menses, id - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Julij; Acadia, Boer, St.John&apos;s.Nfld.-HimalaV»- Schmidt, Syra. - Industry, Murray, Licata. - Catharina Louisa, v. Ml 3 &apos;•_ Villanova.- Marie, Coritson, Auray. - Willem &amp; Clara, S., Londen-&apos; Seahorsc, S., Huil. - Gesina, de Boer, Petersb. - Hiram, Roelfsema, Stot~o- - Amicitia, S., Bergen. _. &quot; BRIELLE, 9 Jnlij; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Cologne, S, L*»&apos; den. - Walter Stanhope, S., Goole. - Pacific, S., Harwich. BROUWEKSHAVEN, 8 Julij; India, Vonck, Banjocw. n. Rott.; vertr-26 Febr. ... HAMBURG, 7 Julij; Martha, Siemers, Amst. - Foskea, Janssen, M»**kum. - Elise fr Mary, Koster, Rott. - Lina, Albers, Malaga. — 8 Julij; SMf Geertruida, Mooi, Amst. - Zeemeeuw, van der Meer, Altona. - Alberd&apos;P&apos;1&apos; Loman, Operto. - Hammonia, S., Rotterdam. CUXHAVEN, 7 Julij; Hazard, Korter, Terranova. - Diana, KroO&apos; Cardiff. :. BREMERHAVEN, 7 Julij; Gezina Helena, Dost, Hooksicl. — 8 Jn-U&apos; Helena, Diepenbrock, Sevilla. : _ &apos; _» EMDEN, 4 Julij; de Hoop, Drcwes, Groning. — 5 Julij; Egberdina AW--&apos; Schuring, Stettin. STETTIN, 6 Julij; Louise, Hildebrandt, Hartlepool. . BOLDERA, 4 Julij;JDiana, Masdorp, Amst. - ElNathan,Knudsen, -CB*^ dam. - Kathinka, Niehaus, Termunterzijl. ARENDAL, 23 Junij; Herman, Boer, Nederland. -.., TVEDESTRAND, 17 Mei; Erstatningen, Jcnscn, Amst. — 10 JU**J&apos; Johns, Torjussen, Harlingen. . ELSENEÜR, 6 Julij, Gepasseerd: Magdalena, Buining, Schied. n. E.&apos; LONDEN, 8 Julij; Mentor, Toering, Worcum. —In lading: Voorw»*1 Lukkien, Koogerpolder. - Rosa, Tasker, Middelburg. . PLYMOUTH, 6 Julij; Anthonius, de Vries, Montevideo n. Antwerps Bij LIZARD, 7 Julij; Jacoba Helena, Zwart, Newcastlc n. Batavia. DUBLIN, 7 Julij; Zwan, Meal, Amsterdam. i LEITH, 7 Julij; George, Beekman, Petersburg. LITTLEHAMPTON, 5 Julij; Verwisseling, Scholtens, Groningen. , SHIELDS, 7 Julij; Anna, Meinerts, Amst. - Petite Paysannc, T«*j-r.. Rott. - Auxiliar, Frankland, id. - Christina Jacoba, de Groot, Koogerpo.o Zeemeeuw, Zwart, Memel.</p>
	<p>SUNDERLAND, 6 Julij; Tartar, Heap, Nieuwediep. CAMARET, 1 Julij; Trentemouzin, Ollive, Nantes n. Rott. MESSINA, 29 Junij; Alida Catharina, Jacobsen, Venitie. ANCONA, 28 Junij; Elsina, Geertruida, Mulder, Amsterdam. HAVANA, 18 Junij; Leda, Fortman, Rotterdam.</p>
</text>
