<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Oct; Ivanhoe, S„ Leith. - Tartar, Heap, Sunderland. - Herpp£s_ia Maria, Wegman, Bergen. - Alpha.Berner, Drammen. - Presto, Thojnas_£i, id. - Lympha, Allurn, id. - Drammen, Trost, id. VLlö, 30 Sept.; Eendragt, Dorenbos, Newc. - B.mdina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Sundswal. - Fortuna, Mcddes, Elbing. - Christine, Bolwin, Gothenburg. - Hendrika, Holman, Frederikstad. - Willem 1., S., Hamburg. — J Oct.; Ranger, Da vies, Londen. - Lubbcgiena, Spithorst, Malmoe. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Oct.; Gazelle, Seagers, Shorcham. - Phoenix, Jackson, Wiek. - Caciorn, Doughter, Workington. - Osborne. S., Leith.- Jenny, van Wijk, Riga. - Erlen, Salvesen, id. - Mentor, Nielscn, id. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 1 Oct.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken.- Leo, S., Londen. - Jntegrity, Hamden, Rye. - Avalon; S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 1 Oct.; Palladium, Neswarthy, Newc. n. Dordr. HAMBURG, 29 Sept.; Alida Margaretha, Meyer, Amsterdam. - Altina Helena, Meijer, Rott. - Hammonia, S., id. - Stoomvaart, S., Amsterdam. ;ïARBURG, 22/29 Sept.; Tbea, Thomsen, Rotterdam. CASOLINERZIJL, 26 Sept.; Frau Maria, Bonker, Amst. — 27 Sept.; (Beerdina, Ahrens; id. PILLAU, 28 Sept.; Urania, S., Amst. — 29 Sept.; Nijverheid, Kernper, Jïotter.&apos;am. BOLDERA, 25 Sept.; Twee Vrienden, Ebes, Amst. - 26 Sept.; Saphir, Aske, Nederland. - Stad Steenwijk, Wyma, Harlingen. KROONSTAD, 26 Sept.; Cycloop, S., Stokholm. GOTHENBURG, 27 Sept.; Nor, Lijderscn, Rotterdam. ELSENEUR, 23 Sept.; gepasseerd : Catharina, Oldcnburger, Petersburg p. Rott, •¦ Gesina Dorothea, de Boer, Riga n. Amsterdam. Bij DU£__ ENESS, 28 Sept; Alberdina; Scherpbier, Maroim n. Kopenhagen. — 29 Sept.; Zr. Ms. stoomschip den Briel, vati Mansfelt, Hellevoetsl. jn. Oost-Indie. - Zr, Ms. stoomschip Aert van Nes, Wichers, id n. id. Bij RAMSGATE, 28 Sept.; Zuiderzee, de Jong, Harlingen n. Havana. Bij het ZUID VOORLAND, 28 Sept; Hollander, Kruyt, Newc n. Cadix. Bij DOVER. 27 Sept.; Raphael, van de Velde Smit, Amst. n. Curacao. PÓRTSMOUTH, 29 Sept.; Twee Gezusters, Bakker, Groningen. SHIKLDS. 29 Sept.; Herstelling, Lukkien, Amst. - Domina Gsertina, Wolters, id. - Salem, Cafiero, id. - Voorwaarts, Vink, Vlaardingeh. FALMOUTH, 30 Sept.; Gesina, Mulder, Porto-Cabello n. Bremen. CLYDE ,28 Sept; Hendrika Huisman, Huisman, Fernambucq. MONTROSE, 23 Sept; Jan Frederik, Klazen, Petersburg. TLOILO, 20 Julij; Hellevoetsluis, Steifens, Manilla. MACASSAR, 25 Julij; in lading: Koerier, Carst, Macao. - Quatre Bras, Nieuwenhuvs, id. HONGKONG, 7 Aug.; Adnana Johanna, Nolles, Tientsin. — 11 Aug.; Gouverneur van Swieten, Singer, Singapore. SHANGHAE, 30 Julij; Bengalen, Hjelmstrom, Amoy. - Ter reede: Argonaut, Draijer. - Petronella Catharina, v. d. Veen. — Maria, de Jong. YOKOHAMxV, 19 Julij; Joan Melchior Kernper, de Vries, Nagasaki.— 23 Julij; Japan Packet, vau den Brink, id. - ter reede: Niphon, Carst. - Libra, Dirksen.</p>
</text>
