<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>üuvgerHjlic j&amp;fauD. » - Van 19 tot en met 35 September 1567. BEVALLEN: J. Mieremet, geb. van Gelderen, D. —I. M. Koene, geb. van der Meerschen, D. — M. A. H. Welvaars, geb. van der Wiere, Z. — J. C. van Velzen , geb. Langezaal, Z. — W. Langezaal, geb. Boot, 1. — _. van Veen, geb. Alberse, Z. —A.M. J. van Wijk, geb. van derTogl, Z. —L. J. Burgersdgk, geb. Blanken, Z. —E. W. van Oosten, geb. Waage, Z. —H. Choufoer, geb. vanden Heuvel, 1.— C. de Bruin, geb. Leget, D.—J. Florisson, geb. de Klerk, Z. — D. Plaizier, geb. Hanselaar, D. — C. M. Kooreman, geb. Smit, Z. — M. Teeuwen, geb. Brittyn, Z. —F. D. Overveld , geb. Linschooten ,Z. — J. M. de Matter, geb. Servaas, Z. — J. E. van Wijk, geb. van den Berg, Z. — A. VV. van Grasstek, geb. Veekmans, Z. —J. G. Loory, geb. Vermey, &apos;L.— T. E. Elshof, geb. Wanna. D. — VV. H. Bender, geb. Vergunst, Z. — J. Hols: wilder, geb. Privé, Z. —L. H. Korenhof, geb. Hoefsmit, D.—C.vanßerkel, geb. Bey, D. — J. Korenhof, geb. Singeling, ü. — A. M. F. Sommeling, geb. van der Drift, D. — L. J. Wittenaar. geb. de Vogel, D. — S.T. Leembroek, geb. Bccking, D. —E. Andrcson, geb. Stem, D. —M. J. Broekhof*&quot;, geb. van Troisenburg, Z. GEHUWD: J. Delfos, jm. en P. Vergunst, jd. — W. Jongbloed, jm. en M. R. Frankhuizen, jd. —P. van den Broek, wedl-, en A. Niesten, wede. —C. van j der Ben , jm. en M. C. Doornik, jd. OVERLEDEN: L. Wallaart, D. ,2 m. —J.D.A. de Nobel,Z., 22j. — H.C. Fles, Z., 14 d. — A. van Berkel, Z., 9 m.~ J. Arbouw, Z., 2m.—M. H. Weijer, D., 10 m. —J. M. Oudhof, D., 7j. —G. Ederzeel, D., bijna 1 in.— IM. Sleeuwagen, D., Ij.en4m.— C. J. G. de-Coningh , wed. S. J. Le Poole, 59 j. — P. van der Steen, D..3JJ. — W. F. H. Taverne, D., 36 j. —J. Kriek , Z., 16 j. en 9m.— W. Oudshoorn , Z.. 2m.—J. A. A. van Well. Z., Ij. — T. Sampion, Z. ,8&quot;. m. — A. Bink, D. ,4 m. — H. J. G. Monianus, Z., 2\ j. — M. A. Degon, 0., bijna Ij.— J. Dozy, Z.. ruim? m.</p>
</text>
