<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Nov., Z.;: __,via, lnazella, Taganrog, 1. v. Falm. - Anna Catharina W&apos;ühelmina, Grilk, Havre. - Swanland, S., Huil. — Gistercu nog: Glenclure, Baldwin, Probolingo. - Ge?«}&apos;?. I,Milniels, de Vries, Riga. — Gisteren nog: Orion,S., MiddoVi. Zee.</p>
	<p>\&quot;LIE, 20 Nov., Z.Z.0.; Hawk, S„ Huil. —21 Nov.; Ida, Wolkammer, Stockholm. - Petina, Groenewoud, Rostock. - Antina, Schoon, Nyekjöbing. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Nov., Z. 0.; City of Pertb, Lamont, Probol., 1. v. Plym. - Douane, Dudouet, St.Malo. - Levant, S., Havre.- Wild Wave, Hannon, Swansea. - Jane &amp; Arm, Hoeking, id. - Advance, S., Middlesbro. - Glencairn, S., id. - Fredericia, Christiausen, Nyborg. - Bloomer, Colberg, Sundswal, laatst v. Brouwershaven. — 22 Nov.; George Bell, Cann, Philad. A., 1. v. Brouwersh. - Jacques Paul, S., Nantes. - Estafette, Rio, Abbeville. - Favorit, Jemmeth, Granville. - Bèta, Chester, St. Valery. - Sylphide, Marshall, id. - Savcnir, Sanden, Runcorn. BRIELLE. 22 Nov.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. BROUWERSHAVEN, 21 Nov., O.; Georgo Bell, Cann, Philadelpia A., n.Rott. - Martinus&amp; Henriette, S., Dordrecht.n. Londen; heeft de reis voortgezet. — 22 Nov.; Lordßyron, S., Glasgow n. Rott. -Kesirel, S., Eott. n. Liverpool; heeft de reis voortgezet, Bij PLÏMOUTH, 20 Nov.; Eobertus Hendrikus, Mulder. Bat. n. Eott.</p>
	<p>LIVERPOOL.; Zuurdijk, Kwint, Maranham. _ HULL, 17 Nov.; Elise Marie, Goldman, Amst. —18 Nov.; Volga, ö.. Koningsbergen. SUNDERLAND, 19 Nov.; Baron Sloot tot Oldhuis, Braam, Stockholm.</p>
	<p>LEITn, 12 Nov.; Titia Susanna, Potjer, Koningsb. DUNDEE, 18 Nov.; Enjetta, Boswijk, Petersburg. FINDHORN, 13 Nov.; Geziena Jantina, Bekkenng,Petersb. BELFAST, 19 Nov.; Gondvisch, Teensma, Dordrecht. QüEENSTOWN, 18 Nov.; Hermina, de Vos, Gothenb. n. Ardrossan. — 12 Nov.; Elisabeth, Tryselius, Soerabaya. CLYDE, 18 Nov.-. County of Lanark, Andcrson, Eott. SWANSEA, 19 Nov.; Everhardus, Vos, Rott. CARDIFF, 19 Nov.; Agnes, Dinshaw, Rotr.- Emilio,Joha,id. SOUTHAMPTON, 19N0v.; Tinnoth, Seagull, Rott, Bij DUNGENESS,I9Nov.; Isabella Saunders, Scott, Nieuwe Diep n. Apple „ore. Bij DOVER, 19 Nov.; Christina Maria, de Veer, Amst.n. Soerabaya. HAVRE, 19 Nov.; Arend, Fijn, Petersburg. - Lambortha, Carst, id.</p>
	<p>St.UBES, 10Nov.; Agatha Catharina, de Weerd, Lissabon, TRIEST, 16 Nov.; Nicola Gesina, Hoeksema, Vadsoe. DARD ANELLEN, 5 Nov.; Assyrian, Jolly, Sulina n. Amst. KAAP PALM AS, vóór 23 Oct.; Apollonia, Steinhusen, Kust. St. GEORGE dELMINA, vóór 12 Oct.;Aiim, Lienoman, Kust.</p>
	<p>St. HELENA, 17 Oct.;Kosmopoliet 11, Bouten, Bat. n. Rott.- Waalstroom,Drijver, Padang n. Rott. - Dordrecht, Verhoeven, Bat. u. Dordt. — 21 Oct; Iduna, Dusar, Batavia n. Amsterd. — 24 Oct.; L. J. Enthoven, Gijzeler qq., Batavia n. Schiedam; hebben de reis voortgezet.— 27 Oct.; Stad Assen, Boer, Swatow. SAN FRANCISCO,I9Oct.-. Emma Maria &apos;</p>
</text>
