<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>Surgcrltjfïc Tan 16 tot en met 32 Mei 1867. BEVALLEN: K. de Haas. geb. Veere, Z. — ill.van Hoorn,geb.Rygersberg, D. — E. J. Hennik, geb. Schouten, Z. — S. Noyen, geb. van Egmond, Z. — S. vau Tongeren, geb. Segaar, D. — J. Hannaart, geb. Serdyn , Z. — J. Ansem, geb. Hakken, D. — W. van üs, geb. van der Heul, Ü. — J. W. Kok, geb. Jong, Z. — W. van der Velden , geb. Westhoeve, Z. — J. C. van Putten, geb. Swanenburg, Z. — A. J. Ouwerkerk, geb. Bakker, D. — E. J. Hensing, geb. van Btek , D. — A. H. van der Blij, geb. de Ruyter, Z. —P. M. Smit, geb. Legei, Z. — C. J.F. van Berkel. geb.Hannaart, Z. —C.P. de Graaf, geb. de Lange, D. — A. Bink, geb. l&apos;F.cluse, D. — M. D. Spoek, geb. Besems, Z. — A. Albert, geb. Devilee, D. — G. F. Roogers, geb. de Monnik, Z. — J. W. van Efveren, geb. Munnikhuizen, D. — M. Laman.geb. Overduin, D. — M. van der Rerg, geb. Smit, D. —J. C. Roodenburg, geb. Verhoog ,Z. ... GEHUWD: A. de Ridder, jm. en M. C. S. Bonte, jd. —P. Rohyn ,jm. en M. E. Frankhnizen, jd. — W. van Biemen, jm.en J. Regeer, jd. — B. van der Nat, jm. en K. Arbouw , jd. — R. van Keulen, jm. en J. Klok, jd. — J. E. Kikkert, jm. en J. M. 801, jd. — C. J. Dieben.jm.en W. van Cazant,jd. — T. Rruystens, jm. en E. C. Schuurman, jd. — P. Oostveen, jm.en CE. Ouwerkerk , jd. — E. J. van Rijkom, jm. en J. F. H.Mulié.jd. — E. G. Abspoel, jm. Eu F. J. P. Raartman, jd. OVERLEDEN: A. Vrploed, D., 3 m. — J. Delmeer, Z.,2od.—GiC. Dirkse, geb. Staats, 33 j. — J. de Leu, ruim 60 j.— H. Pel, geb. Hamel, 51 j.— B. van der Son, 66 j. — M C van Crimpen, wed. S. van Bel, 78 j. — W.F. P. Uitenhoul, I)., Ij. en 4 m. — E. de Klerk , D..67J. — A. van der Reyden.Z., ruim 7m.— H. Platteel. D., 3j. en 4m.— N. Libochant, 33j. —A. van Koningsbruggen , 54 j. — J. A. de Smit, geb. Koekoek, 70 j. — T. Hoogkamer, D., ruim 4 m. — H. J. Colpa,22j.— A.P. Scheels. D.,7m. — .1. 11. P. Stadhouder, 26 j. — D. van Latesieyn, Z., ruim 3 m — C. H. Koole, geb. Bonman, 65 j. —J. Remmers, 72j. —M. G. ten Sande, 73j. —J. M. Lut, D., 2i va. — W. G. Neiwold, D., bijna 3 tn. —J. A.W. Landesbergen, geb.Tiedorn ,44j.— P. Mulder, geb. Hogendoorn, 66 j. — L. C. Arends, D.. bijna 10 m. —J. du Mont, Z., 18.j. —A. C. Dool, Z., 3j.enlom.— J. C. A. Vinkeslein, geb. Carlon,2sj. — C. van Veen, D., 5 m.</p>
</text>
