<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>_jut-gcvHjf»c J»t«nnb. Tan 5 tot en met 11 Januarij 1865. BEVALLEN : S. M. Linschooien, geb. de Ridder, D. —E. Mieremet, geb. Bey, Z. — J. Overstap, geb. DisseUeld, D. — G. Frankhuizen, geb. van der Kwaak, Z. —P. van der Mark, geb. de Ridder, D. —A. Bogaards, geb. Francken, D. —S. B. Molet, geb. Ringels, D. —H. G. Doniier, geb. de Hoogh, Z. — C. H. Hoogkamer, geb. Fakkel, Z. —M. van Velzen, geb. Hasselbach ,Z. — L. Roos, geb. van Ees, Z. —C. H. Hoogkamer, geb. Fakkel, D. levenl. —M. van Lissenberg , geb. van Veen, D. —G. Boudewjjns, geb. van Egmond , D. —S. M. A. Meinlser, geb. van de Poel, Z. —M. 11. van der Drift, geb. Lamboo, Z. — A. J.Kleynhans, geb. van Poelgeest, D. levenl. — A. van der Voorden, geb. van Beek, Z. levenl. —M. Eikerbout, geb. Laman, D. — L. Hakkaart, geb. de Vrind, D. — M. J. Willenborg, geb. van Dieren , Z. — A. Bink, geb. PEcluse, Z. tweel. — K. de Water, geb. de Keyzer, D. — C. J. van den Berg, geb. Delfos, D. —A. van Ark, geb. Spaanderman, D. —E. Flanderhyn, geb. Reyk, D. — D. Plaizier, geb. Hanselaar, D. — S. M. Lepelaar, geb. Post, Z. — P. H.van der Voord, geb. Kuivenhoven, Z. — M. J. Blonk, geb. Nieuwenhnyzen , Z. — G. Reyners, geb. Fiege, Z. — J. Wallaard, geb. Singerling, Z. —A. M. Harleveld,geb,del&apos;Ecluse, D.—C. J.Gorree,geb. Maners, D. GEHUWD: A. van Schooien, wedr. en J. Verdouw, wed. — J.Terdu.jm. en F. van Wijk, jd. —P. Blaauw, wcdr. en C. M. Sablerolle, jd. OVERLEDEN: J. Voorzaad, 73 j. — A.C. Kouwenberg, Z., lij. —H. de Nobel, Z., 3 m. — C. A. E. Suringar, geb. Beckhaus, 86 j. -J.Smit, D., 2j. — E. Vijlbrief, D., 4d.—C. de Timmerman, geb. Voordvin, 80 j. — J. van der Laaken, D., ruim sm.—J. P. van der Burg, Z., 6m.—H. C. den Eezemer, geb. van Beek, 37 j. —J. D. Vinkestein, D., 3m.—T. A. C. Prevost, D.&apos;, 2 j. en 6 m. — J. J. Hanno, Z., Ij. en 2 m. — B. A. van Uiden, Z., Ij. en 3 m. — J.Selier, D., 6m. — A. Lepelaar, Z., 1 d. —MaSlokhuyzen,43j.— A. Smit, D., 3j: en 7 m. — A. Hoogervegt, 32 j. —A. N. van Grieken, Z., 1 j. _j. van den Ende,3oj. — J. van Zijp, Z., 9m. — Blarg&apos;vanden Heuvel, wede. Kums,Bsj. —L. G. van Dorp, Z.,9m.</p>
</text>
