<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 20 Febr.; Henriètta, Visser, Padang. - Elmina, v. Strijen, Kust van Guinea. - Fennechiena, Hotze, Newc. n. Triest. - Wildervank, Giezen, Messina. - Louisa Geerdiena, Wever, Napels. - Jacoba Johanna, v. d. Meulen, id. - Tubal Cain, Cann, id. ¦• Johannes, Kuper, Livorno. - Jan _r- Jacoh, Burghard, Newc. n. Cette. - Francisca, Ueker, id. n. Malaga. - Anton if Jacob, Bot, Lissabon. - Maria, van Duy venbooden, id. - do Hoop, Ouwehand,id.-Cito, Mooi, Nantes. - Diana, Schuit, id. - Gesina, Krook, Londen. - Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, id. - de Schelde, Hoefman, Newport. - Sumatra, Buyzer, Cardiff. - Anniver3ary, Parker, id. - Arrow, Hartley, Liverpool. - Weldaad, Pik, Dublin. - Brandon, Lamb, Newc. - Lodora, Howard, id. - Minerva, Hvidt, id. Agra, Evans, id. - Saturn, Lundström, id. • W_im, Smith, Yarmouth. - Norfolk Lass, Pile. id. (Benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld.) _ HELLEVOETSLUIS, 20 Febr.; Nagasaki, Hörner, Samarang. - Christina Maria, de Veer, Java.-Margaretha, Harnis,Buenos-Ayres.-Herstelling, Ligthart, id. - de Hoop.Boer, id. - Hendrika,v.Wattum,Triöst. - Zuid Laren, Drenth, id. - de Valk, Strijbos, Venetië. - Catharina, Oldenburger, Messina. - Gebroeders, Loodijzen, Rédon. - Leopard, S., Londen.- Rollo, Schep, Jersey. - Arm Margareth, Davies, Runcorn. [- Fop Smit, Mets, CardüF. - Harmonie, Doewes, Newry. - Nachina Lammegina, Eijnberg, id. • Jenne Nollen, de Goede, Newc. - Orphéline, Flambard, id. - Charles &amp; Jules, David, id. - Olive Branch, Brunyard, id. - Bon Pére, Maheo, id. - Marie Charlotte, Allain, id. - Arm, Dufheid, id. - Admiraal de Winter, Bunnemeijer, id. - Sknlda, Tönuesen, Flekkefiord. BRIELLE, 20 Febr.; de Maas, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 20 Febr.; Lammiena Elizabeth, Pott, Rott.n. Bat.- Maria Anna, Monnom_id.n.id. - Noord-Brabant, Loos, id.n.id.- Henriette Elisabeth Susanna, Meijboom, id. 11. Singapore. MAASSLUIS, 20 Febr.-, St. Francois, Rebours, St. Brieux. - Anna Agatha, Sloten, Redon. - Yenus, Meijer, Sandwich. - St. Jean.lngeau, Avontuur. - Victorine, Leveux, id. - Jeune Léoeadie, le Fruide, id. - Deux Louis, le Bérigot, id. STETTIN, 17 Febr.; Jantje, Zuidland, Flensburg. COWES, 18 Febr.; Cornelia Hendrika, Marcussen, Rott. n. Cardiff (na geëindigde reparatie). — 18 Febr.; Concordia, van der Meyden, Londen n. Swansea. DARTMOUTH, 18 Febr.; Baudina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Malaga. - Johanna Margaretha, Ei, Nantes. RAMSGATE, 17 Febr.; Goorreet, Huges, Hamburg n. Montevideo. PORTSMOUTH, 18 Febr.; Crest of the Wave, Woodburn, Bott. n. New-York. FALMOUTJI, 17Febr.; de Sperwer, Huisman, Cardiff n. St. Thomas. - Orion, Lindeboom, Troon n. Toulon. : - LIVERPOOL, 17 Febr.; Industrie, Mulder, Lissabon. - Harmonie, Boer, Civita Vecchia. — 18 Febr.; Hermanus Isaac. van der Veen, St. Thomas. - Mercurius, Both, Belire. - Fanny Sermes, Kramer, Galatz,- Wilhelmina Maria, Postma, Buenos-Ayres. - Alida, Nagel, Nanteß. NAPELS, 10 Febr.; Helen, Perrone, Amst. TRIEST, 14 Febr.; Wilhelmina, Knaak, Jalmo.nth. RIO-JANEIRO, 19 Dcc; Concordia, Wijgers, Maroim. BUFNOS AYRES, 4 Jan.; Louise, Mellema, Antwerpen.</p>
</text>
