<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10 Oet., Z. —O. N. O.; Carl von Döbeln, Stenman, Rangoon. - Christine, Pedersen, Napels. - Harmonie, Boer, Livorno. - Bérénice, S., Middell. Zee. - Soranus, Poelman, Nantes. - Lion, S., Londen. - Pearl, Barkett, Sunderl. - Boanerges3, Dunn, id. - Alpha, Thompson, id. - Albert Tholen, Mennen, Yarmouth. - Lyna, Knndsen, Drammen. —11 Oct.; Vice-Admiraal May, Lusink, Batavia. - Ferdinand &amp; Louis, Vogelsang, Samarang. - Margareth, Morck, Christiama. - Zeepaard, Tobiassen, Frederikstad. - Kong Sverre, Sundene, Noorw. - Frits, Christensen, id. - Vestalinden, Morck, id. Chelone, Frederiksen, id. VLIE, 9 Oct., Z.Z.W.;Laurentia, Johansen, Windau.- August, Amandsen, Stavanger. - Florida, Arnesen. Frederikstad. — 10 Oct; Herstelling, Ligthart, Stockholm. - Catharina Visser, de Vreeze, Arendahl. - Iwan, Johannesen, Avontuur. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Oct., Z. O.; Hollands Acera, Sabel, Liberia. - Sirius, Doewes, Triest.- Vertrouwen, Kal, Lissabon.- Troubadour, S., Londen. - Dolphyn, Robert, Swansea. - James Rankins, S., Glasgow. - Kinghorn, S., Leith.- Asperen, Southil, Berwick. - Lordßaglan, S.,Newcastle.-Friendship, Reberts, id. - Dunnoter Castle, Vallock, id. - Advance, S., Middlesbro. - Sarah King, Arnold, Ipswich. - Mary Arm, Mathisen, id. - John James, Tomlinson.id. - John, Inge, Libau. - Levant, S., Gothenburg. — 11 Oct.; Normandy, S., Banana.- Feijenoord, S.,Lond.- Waterwitch, Leadley, Newc. - Thomas Rusbridger, Burn, id. - Annie, S., Goole. - Niord, Schröder, Engeland. — Gisteren nog: Elize, Woodhead, Londen. - Seahorse, S., Huil. BRIELLE, 10 Oct., Z. O.; Leo, S., Londen. - Deborah, Scales, id. - Zealous, S., Harwich. - Moderatie. Scholten, Avont. BROUWERSHAVEN, 10 Oet., O. N. O.;Bezoekie, Reekers, Rott. n. Bat. - Macassar, Hörner, id. n. Bangoon. - Crest of the Wave, Jones, id. n. New-Torte. FALMOUÏH, 8 Oct.; Agatha, v. Wijk Jr.; (Uruguay) Plym.- Dolfijn. Hoekstra, (Rio Grande), Hamburg.</p>
</text>
