<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen.</title>
	<p>Gepraald, 3 Nov.; op 48&quot; 42&apos; N. Br. 8&quot; W. L.: Johanna Maria, Overgaauw, Rott. n. Melbourne. BINNENGEKOMEN. TEXEL, 8 Nov.; 2 Broeders, van Kempema, Londen. - Margaretha, ie Vries, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Nov.; Osborne, S., Leith.- Lordßaglan,S., Newc. - Ironmaster, S., Middiesbro. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. BROUWERSHAVEN, 8 Nov.; Noordstar, Hartogh, Petersb. n. Antw. als bijlegger. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 5 Nov.; Alma, Beek, Amst. n. Riga. - Emilie, S., Rott. n. Stettin. ELSENEUR, 5 Nov.; gepasseerd: Mantiira,Chapple,Petersb. n. Amst.- Wiebe Jacobs, Visser. Kopenh. n. Engelhohn. TONNINGEN, 2 Nov.; Maria, Bruhn. Nestved n. Antwerpen.-Tallina, Dekker. Londen n. Stettin. — 3 Nov.; Dieverdina, de Jonge.Hartlepool n. Suderstap. — 4 Nov.; Tjakina de Boer, Dost, Zwolle n. Sleeswijk. - Lena Catharina, Ewen, Workum n. Rostok.- Johanna, Brouwer, Dokkum n. Friedericia. LONDEN, 7 Nov.; Herstelling Archangel. SCILLY, 2 Nov.; Maria, v. Duivenbooden, Amst. n. Lissabon (heeft op 5 dito de reis voortgezet). ALLOA, 4 Nov.; Maria, Hansen, Amst. SHIELDS, 6 Nov.; Wilhelmina&amp; Elise.Wiersma, Amst. - Riga Mason, Dordrecht. - Marianne, Vlas, Londen. A NEW-CASTLEJS Nov.; in lading: Mercator, Huisman, Venetië. altje Maathuis, de Vries, Genua. O A DIX, 2» Oct.; Mathilda, Fekkes, Genua. VÊNÉTIE, 2 Nov.; Anna, Korf ker, Hamnierfest. VIGO, 18 Oct; Herman Albert, Potjewijd, Newc —20 Oct.; Niessina Jacoba, Barelds, Sunderland.— 24 Oct.; Goorrecht ca Oldambt.Rentema, Dundee. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 8 Nov.; Zephyr, S., Londen. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Hull. - Hawl;, S., id. - Hednig, Jörgensen, Frederikstad. - Aert Cornelia, Jórgensen, id. - Washington, Nielsen, Tonsberg. - Kinderdijk, Verdoes, Rott., is teruggekomen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Nov.; Wilhelmma, Willenbrink, New-York, via Brouwershaven. - Queen, S., Dundee. - Hammonia, S , Hamburg. BRIELLE, 8 Nov.; Zealous, S . Harwich. MAASSLUIS, 8 Nov.; Waterloa, S.. Londen. - Albert S., Hull. BOLDERA, 2 Nov.: Vier Gebroeders, Balkema, Enge.and. LONDEN. 7 Nov.; de Visscherij, Fortuin, Worcum. ABERDEEN, 5 Nov.; Zwaantina, de Boer. Helmsdale. GLASGOW, 6 Nov.; Antilope, Hubert, Rio Grande.</p>
</text>
