<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>Burgerlijke £taut&gt;. Van IC lolt en met 22 Jnlij 1868. BEVALLEN: J. C. van der Velden, geb. Paats, D. — A. Schaap, geb. Buddingh, D. — 11. de Just, geb. Nieuwenhuis, Z. — M. Rosier, geb. Breedevelt, D. - C. Goddijn, geb. Weylaart, Z. — J. M. Wijliug , geb. van Oosten , Z. — I B. P. de Hen, geb. Koole, D. —A. van Ouwerkerk, geb. Schullze, Z. —J. Jansen, geb. Brouwer, Z. — P. Plu, geb. Helfensiyn, Z. — C. van der Laan, geb. Klein, Z. — E. J. Noll, geb. Sluymer, Z. - J. Marujn.geb. van der Meel. Z.— J.A.Selicr. geb. Verra, D. — ffl. de Vries, geb. Visser, Z. — W. Singeling, geb. Dreef, Z. — JH. J. van der Wijngaard . geb. Galjaard, D. — M. J. Peyster, geb. Nielsen , Z. — A. M. Betgen, geb. Kaffijn , D. - C. van Wijk , geb. Laven , Z. — C. Wetselaar.geb. de Graaf, D. — G. van der Keur, geb. Bavelaar, Z. &apos;GEHUWD: S. Campeuhout, wedr. en A. Sieenbergen, jd. —Z. Hink, ja.&apos; «n B. Keubeek, jd. — J. J. Klinkhamer, jm.en C. Kruyk.jd. — M. Rebbers, jm.en A. van Paassen, jd. ■■■■&apos;&lt; -.- -t • - - ■-&apos; . . 11. E. L. Hoogenslraaten, D., 3m.— J. P. P. Bonten, D., 16 d. -K. M. Kosters, D., 4; m. -J. Bij, 79 j. — Jl. van Welzenis, D.,21 j. — i:&apos;an Driel, geb. Labee. 82 j. -P.J.de la Courl, D., 4m.— C. Sierat, Z.\ ij-enl m. —J. van den Ouweelen, 54j. —C. Ilouweling, wed. P. C. van Booren,7Bj. — H. van Es, D., ruim sm. — W. Mader, Zr, ruim sm. — W. Delmeer, Ü.. Ij. en 3 m. —F. P. Falder, 54j. -G. H. Roos, Z, 4m. - M. F. ynhler, D., 5 m. — J. Singerling, I)., 9 m. — C. Renné, D.,lj. en9m.— 0-Pieua, 1».,7m. — H. Knol, Z..3m. — S. Riebeek, D , 4 m. — C. IH.Starrenhurg .D . 15j. —J. van Bemmel. D.. sm.— S. van Groeningen, D., 18j. — AP. J. de Does, D., 9m.— J. van der Blij. 68 j. — J JL. van Dooren , Z., 3m. — J-M. Verpoorl, D., 3 ui. -L. S. Engers, Z.,1 m. —G. JH. Kempenaar, 69j — JL.deClercq, ü., 17 d. — M. van Houium, D., lOro. —C. Hoppenbrouwer, D., 2j en9m. —C. S. Kraneveld, D. ,3m. :• „ .-,. i</p>
</text>
