<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>lEALL, 27 Mei; Gerard Pieters Servatius, Beckering, Bat. - Niua, S , Bordeaux. - Endeavour, Taylor, Seaham. - Wieka, Wortel, Frederikst. - Scotia. Lorensen, Drammen.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Mei; Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Swallow S Huil. - Bradford, S.. Grimsby. MAASSLUIS, 26 Mei; Waterloo, S., Londen.-Christine, Hess, Newcastle. - ïre Vermer, Hansen, Hartlepool. - 27 Mei; Busy Bee, Ptidney Sunderland. - Maria Luitzia, Deters, Heppens. - Johanna, Ber» id &apos; BREMERHAVEN, 26 Mei; Hillechina, Wijnstok, Amst&apos;-Grietje Dijkstra, Venenga, Engeland. VAREL, 25 Mei; Elisabeth, Pekeler, Engeland. SWINEMUNDE, 24 Mei;HillechienWilkens, Karssies, Termunterzijl DANTZIG, 24 Mei; Catharina Hendrika, Feugen, Antwerpen BOLDERA, 20 Mei; Johannes, de Boer, Nederland. - Arme Malene Andersen, id. - Cort Adler, A.sbj örnsen, id. PILLAU, 23 Mei;Britannia, Valk, Burgsvick. LIVERPOOL, 24 Mei; Titia Susanna, Potjer, Nerva. NEWPORT, 23 Mei; Edouard en Marie, van der Kolff Hono-koner QUEENSTO WN, 25 Mei; Eliza Hunter, Moore, Amst. non&quot;Kong- ANTWERPEN, 26 Mei; Beerta Hendrika, Stuit, Dantzig. PORTO, 18 Mei; Maria Adolfina, Menldijk, Londen. &apos; LISSABON, 19 Mei; Valerius Lodewijk, de Jong, Maassluis. - Vlaardingen. Boeker, Vlaardingen. MALAGA, 10 Mei; zeilkl.: Godelevus Bernardus, Kral, Antwerpen. GENUA, 22 Mei; Amphitrite, Bekkering, Hamburg. BATAVIA, 1 April; Hoek van Holland, Bakker, Amst. — 2 April; Nor ner, Petersen, Nederland. — 3 April; Doesborgh, Spaanderman, Australië (den volgenden dag Straat Suuda gepasseerd). — 9 April- Ouderkerk a/d. Amstel, Dingemans, Nederland. — 14 April; Eva Johanna Hordiik Amsterdam. &apos; J</p>
	<p>o,W°wWf *vGffi&apos;K.W Zeelt, Golf van Persie,, 23 Maart; Hendrika, y d. Valk, Sydney. - 24 Maart; Graaf Dirk 111, Rotgans , Amst. — 27 Maart; Tweelingen, Bruin, Nederland. — 28 Maart; Rascot. Newton, Amst. .-pASOE_ROEAN, 24 Maart; Minister van Hall, de Haas, Nederland. — 26 Maart; Jan Daniel, van IJzendoorn, id. — 3 April; Cornelis Wemard Eduard, Swart, Nederland. SOERABAYA, 23 Maart; Petronella, Strootman, China. —30 Maart; A. R. Falck, van der Plas, Nederland. - Lonise, Buys Jr., id. — 31 Maart; Medea,v.Teutem,id.</p>
</text>
