<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Sept; Result, Hoyer, Maroïm. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Sept.; Foamskerriea, Mc. Donough, Lybster. - Waterloo, Wordingham, Newc. - Violet, Richardson.id.-Onnoco, Vince, id. - Waterwitch, Boy, id. — 2 Sept.; Bordeaux, S., Bordeaux. - Juno,Bell, Newc. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. BRIELLE. 2 Sept.; Zealous.S.; Harwich. „_..-, ¦_. _ MAASSLUIS, 2 Sept.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Orion, &amp;., &apos;BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Sept; Leonida,Breedenuurg, S&apos;mdswall n. Rotterdam. , _ • , VLISSINGEN, 1 Sept.; Willem van der Voort. Carst, Jacmel. HAMBURG, 31 Aug.; Industrie, Straatman, Makkum. CUXHAVEN, 1 Sept,; Hendrika, van Watturn, triest-Amphitnte, Kars, Genua. - Minerva, S., Amst. - Stoomvaart, S.,id. BREMERHAVEN, 31 Aug.; Vr. Aaltje, Voget, Harderwijk. - Folker- dina, Dijkstra, Rott. - Johanna Wilhelmina, Thïarnau, Baltimore. - Vft Sjouke, Voss, Amst. HUSUM, 29 Aug.; Elsina, Hansen, Newcastle. STETTIN, 30 Aug.; Hermann, Ruge, Amst. - Nina, S., id. DANTZIG, 30 Aug.; Alida Sarah, Mooi, Rugenwalde. WISMAR, 29 Aug.; Gouverneur van Ewyck, S., Amst., (vertr. 1 Sept. weder derwaarts). KRtJONSTAD, 21 Aug.; Maria Eiisabeth, Bonjer. Gioja. FREDERIKSHAMN, G Aug.;Skandia, Hutchinson.Nieuwediep. ELSE-iEUR,2.&apos;&gt; Aug.;gepasseerd: Constantia, Andersen, Frederikshamn n. Amst. - Victoria, Pedersen, Hernüsand n. Nieuwe Diep. — 29 Aug.; Annechina Harmina, Zuidema, Petersburg. - Oernen, Christensen, Wyburg n. Amst. - Synia, Berg, Riga n. Dordrecht. TONNINGEN, 28 Aug.; gepasseerd: Anna, Kuiper, Steenwijk n. Flens* burg. —29 Aug.; Alida ïkea, Pieper, Harlingen n. Wismar. — 30 Aug.; Alberdina Fokkelina, Schuur, Bremen n. Stettin. - Jantiua Alida, Texer, Franeker n. Wismar. - Frouwke, Heins, Memel n. Groningen. - Lena Catharina, Ewen, Stettin n. id. LONDEN, 1 Sept.;Zeemeeuw, ...., Petersburg. DEAL, 1 Sept.-, Baron van Heemstra, Nepperus, Shields n. Bombay. Baai van S WAN AGE, 31 Aug.; Margaretha Hendrika, Datema, .... CHARLESTOWN, 30 Aug.; Allegonda.de Vries, Leith. QÜEENSIÜWN, 1 Sept.; Anna Maria VeraCruz. , CARDIFF, 30 Aug.; Gesina, Lindeboom, Dungeness. LIVERPOOL, 31 Aug.; Maigaretha Arendina, Boerhave, Galipoli. SHIELDS, 31 Aug.; Truc Britou, Rogers, Derdt. NANTES, 30 Aug.; Deux Frères, Briand, Amst. LI V0RN0.29 Aug.; Jan van Eijk, van Groenendaal. New-Castle. PHILADELPHIA, 20 Aug.; Margaretha, Thesing, Rott. BALTIMORE, 19 Aug.; Baltimore, Meijer, Rott. BUENOS-AYRES, 15 Julij; Reinhardt, Muller, Montevideo.-21 Julij; Amisia, Sap, Fernambuck. SANTOS, 25 Julij; Leda, Muller, Liverpool. MONTEVIDEO, 17 Cornelis Pieter,sandu.</p>
</text>
