<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>t TEXEL, 12 Nov.; Perseverance, Elliott, Londen. - Hollander, S., Huil. - , Vesta, S., Stettin. i VLIE, 10 Nov.; Aurelia Gruao, Stuitje, Memel. - Frits fr Betsy, Stnut, ; Gothenburg. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. i HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Nov.; John Fraser, Galloway, Callao, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Willem en Clara, S., Londen. - Brother&apos;s Success, Hobart, Ro, chester. - Osprey, S., Liverpool. -6 n eral Lee, S., Dublin, i BRIELLE, 12 Nov.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Cologne, S., Londen. - Invicta, Hopkin, Rochester. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BREMERHAVEN, 11 Nov.; Bruno, Schoon, BRAKE, 11 Nov.; Arnoldus Willem Nanninga, Top, Petersburg. , LEER, 8 Nov.; Catharina Imkina, Hidzebos, Amst. — 9 Nov.; Helena, ¦ Gurseby, Groningen. —10 Nov.; Nijverheid, Kernper, Koningsbergen. KROONSTAÜ, 7 Nov.; Rubbens, S., Amsterdam. LONDEN, 9 Nov; Venns, Visser, Petersburg. - Karsina Harmina, Wai terborg, Stolpemu»de. —10 Nov.; Rival, Koning, Holmstrand. - Jcnne Nol. len, de Goede, Kouingsbergen. — 11 Nov.; Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, : Groningen. - Anna Elisabeth, Dik, id. —In lading: Rollo, Schep, Rott. Bij BEVEZIER, 9 Nov.; Speculant, Nyland, Rott. n. Bahia. RYE, 9 Nov.; Grietje, Scholtens, Gothenburg. PORTS MOUTH, 10 Nov.; Janna Meijer, Datema, Groningen. PEYMOUTH, 10 Nov.; Polly, Hirt, Liverpool n. Zierikzeé. . FALMOUTH, 10 Nov.; Gebroeders Smit, Smit, Buenos Ayres. NEATH, 10 Nov.; Princess Alexandra, Bovey, Rott. ALLOA, 9 Nov.; Margaretha, Wittenberg, Stettin. YARMOUTH, 10 Nov.; Wesselina Engelina, Koning, Bromen. SHIELDS, 10 Nov.; Eendragt, Doornbos, Harlingen. - Marsden, Paton, Nieuwe Diep. - Hudgill, Breem, id. SUNDERLAND, 9 Nov.; Shanghae, Sehultz, Amst. - Automate, Young, Nieuwe Diep. H ARTLEPOOL, 9 Nov.; Maria, Storm, Nieuwe Diep. L ABR li VACH, 6 Nov,; Paul et Marie, Lesindau, Vannes n. Schiedam. - Léoeadie, Bruère, Marans n. Amst. BORDEAUX, 10 Nov.; Seerdina Afina, Pomper, Stettin. TRIEST, 7 Nov.; in lading: Concordia, Goosscns, Rott. -deZwijger, Woltcrs, Groningen. MESSINA, 28 Oct.; Columbus, de Jong, Wadsoe. SINGAPORE, 30 Sept.; Kinderdijk, Verdoes, Bat. — 4 Oct.; Johanna aria, Kleynenberg, Newport. — 6 Oct.; ter reede : Honigbij, van der Valk, .... - Gebroeders van Beek, Walig, .... - Zeemanshoop, Reiniersen, .... BATAVIA, 29 Sept.; Quintet, Slijboom, Amst. HONGKONG, 13 Mept.; Ellina, Lammens, Newchwang. AMOY, 31 Aug.; Willem Daniel, Zeylstra, Samarang; 18 dagen reis, alles wel aan boord. SWATOW, 26 Aug.; Petronella Catharina, van der Veen, Shanghae. YOKOHAMA, 28 Aug.; Ida Maria d» Raath, de Boer, Hongkong. — 31 Aug.; Jan van Galen, Braat, Nagasaki. MANILLA, 4 Sept.; Adriana Petronella, de Breuk, ardiff. — 7 Sept.; Hollaudia, Ruige, Hongkong.— 11 Sept.; Guurtje en Maria, Flens, CardifF.— 17 Sept.; johannes Lodewijk, van Delft, id. - Vriendschap, Terbruggen, id. MELBOURNE,2 Sept.; Kanagawa, Ouwehand, Rott.</p>
</text>
