<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN. Scheepstijbingen.</title>
	<p>Maltha, Purvis, iri^EeSZ^^^^^^^^^- Hubertus, Nichols id - feron S,nß&apos;t tU?n,r ?nd&lt; \Aid, Smith, Seaham.-peror, Burger,, id. - AnnacWena Hnt -0t °vd^ls&apos; Braam&apos; Petewb. - Emfrutters, Vf indau. - Hermanoa ïïlTM&apos; Zuidema Nerva.- Maria Anna, 17 Mei, Knudaen, Krage.oe &apos;HaraUsen&gt; Sundswall. - Niels, Mörck, id.-temï SStf W&apos;! Smlt&apos; B°S Wijk&apos; Pet-burg. - JaCoba, Mun- HELLEVOETSLUIS, 26 Oei, Z. W.; Vermont ttÜtMJ. n*i , Brouwersh.-Flora, Roberts. Jamaica _T__AllSfc__l_^kk* delphia, - Aurore, Jollymore id. - Annie. Rover vfiova T V S_Wre.- Ville.de Ponterson, Rouel,Ponterson.-Forste,-,J™e_ Run&apos; corn. - Violet, Eichardson, Newcastle. - Skane, Cronberg, Petersbur&quot; Ocean Breeze, Wood, id. - Maria Elisabeth, Suwe, id. - Anna Christina&quot; Pedei.en,id.-Gepbina,Lohman, id.-Allegonda, Smit, id. -OldAmbt Schotema, Pitea. - Hoffnung, Sonne, Windau. - Die Loreley, Stohrmann, id.-Thor, Schmidt, Sundswall. - Wladimir, Heimberg, Eiga. - Nicolaas, Rijf, Dantzig. - John en Martha, Greaves, Australië. BRIELLE, 26 Oct., Z. W. — Z.; Avalon, S., Harwich. BREMEREAVEN, 23 Oct.; Marianne, Meijer, Amst. —25 Oct.; Harmina, v. d. Meulen, Menisl. HAMBURG, 25 Oct.; Amsterdam, S., Amst. ELSENKUR, 23 Oct.; Unie, Parrel, Schiedam n. Windau.-Golovna, Tonnesèn, Dordrecht n. Gefile. - Maria, Ammann, Amst. n. Koningsb.- Frits S&quot; Betsy, Stuut, id. n. Sundswal. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 23 Oct.; Jantina, Boon, Schiedam n. de Oostzee - Union, Hazewinkel, Brake n. id. SWINEMUNDE, 24 Oct.; Odin, S., Amst. STETTIN, 23 Oct.; Gesina, Mulder, Antw. Bij WIGHT, 22 Oct.; Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Bat. n. Rott. FALMOUTH, 24 Oct.; Mary &amp; Catherine, Crisp, Rott. - Verwisseling, Notmeijer, Hamburg n. Bilbao. MIDDLESBRO&apos;, 23 Oct.; Gesina, Lindeboom, Hamburg. NEW-CASTLE, 22 Oct.; In lading: Regina Maris, Ouwehand, Bat.- Wilhelmina, Hazevrinkel, Cadix, Rio Grande en Java. SHIELDS, 24 Oct.; Dunnoter Castle, Willock, Rott.-Caroline, Cilesta, id. - Ricardo, Maresca, id. - Sophia, de Groot, Schiedam. SURINAME, 30 Sept.; Albrecht Frederik, Bakker, Amsterdam (alles wel aan boord).</p>
</text>
