<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>lEXEL, 20 Maart; Omen, Hansen, Frederikstad. - Beurs van Amster¦ dam, Tofte, id. — 21 Maart; Grand Duc Alexis, S., Stettin. - Symmetry, Sörensen, Frederikstad. &apos; AMELAND, 16 Maart; Dirkjo, Poort, Bremen. - Seèhs Gebrüder, Siemers, id. OSTMAHORN, 10 Maart; Twee Gezusters; Meijer, Colchester. TERMUNTERZIJL, 15 Maart; Maria, Ebkes, Ape. - Hoffnung, Denekamp, id. — 19 Maart; Maria, Pasman, Basselt. VLIE, 20 Maart; Nora, S„ Londen. - Paul Fredrik, Naess, Frederikst. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Maart;Hendrikldo Ambacht, Bijl, Batavia 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Raoul, Lequillon, Caen. - Albatioss,«., Liverp. - Albert, S., Huil. BROUWERSHAVEN, 21 Maart; Pudsey Dawson, Baker, Rott. n. Liverpool, heeft de reis voortgezet. BREMERHAVEN, 20 Maart; Freerk Jan, Smit, Bordeaux. HAMBURG. 19 Maart; Hammonia, S., Rott. GOTHENBURG, 13 Maart; Margaretha Hcndrica, Datema, Flensb. RENDSBURG, 14Maart; gepasseerd: Geerdina Geertruida, Tonningen n. de Oostzee. LONDEN, 19 Maart; Sara, Stuit, Dordt. - Lion, S., Harlingen. — 20 Maart; Antina, de Vries, Greetsiel. - In lading: Sophia, Egberts, Emden. - Juliana .Antina, de Boer, Antwerpen. Bij BEVEZIER,.I9 Maart; Friedrich, Tasmer, Samarang n. Rott. Bij DOVER, 19 Maart; Louise, Jacobs, Requejada n. Antw. Bij PORTLAND, 19 Maart; Grietje,Legger,Londenn. Newport. Bij FOLKESTONE, 19 Maaart; Marie, Biesthorst, Bat. n. Amst. ROCHESTEB, 15 Maart; John and Charles, Carlton, Rott. CARDIFF, 17 Maart; Kortenaar, Schnchard, Rott. - Maria Adriana, Itz, Nieuwe Diep. DUBLIN, 19 Maart; in lading: Zorg en Vlijt, Mulder, Lissabon. HULL, 19 Maart; Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Amst. - Olinda, Teugh, Rott. HARTLEPOOL, 19 Maart; Johanna, Meyer, Rochester. MI DDLESBRO, 19Maart; Henriette, Weller, Rott.- Louwina, Heerma, Colchester. - Grietina, Gortmaker, Londen. NEWHAVEN. 19 Maart; Integrity, Hamden, Rott. BELFAST, 19 Maart; Trientjo Gesina, Bos, Riga. - Vartry, S., Rott. LEIÏH, 19 Maart; Gerhard, Steenken, Bremen. - Baudina, Pool, Harlingen. SHIELDS, 19 Maart; Hart, Cloak, Nieuwediep. - Zwaantje Elisabeth, de Jager, Groningen. - Auguste Mathilde, Groenlandt, Antwerpen.-Voor waarts, de Vries, Portsmouth.-Wilhelmina, Oortgiesse, Brake. -Martha, Martens, Bremen. -Karsina, Olfers, Dover. SUNDERLAND, 19 Maart; Geerdina, Jansen, Leer. STOCKTON, 18 Maart; Henriette, Wever, Rott. - Maria Josephine, Liveld, id. SWANSEA, 17 Maart; Maria Roelfina, de Groot, Londen. IPSWICH, 18 Maart; Gerharda Hendrika,&apos; Glim, Mistley. GOOLE, 19 Maart; Vlinder, de Jongh, Groningen. GLASGOW, 19 Maart; in lading: Aquarius, Altmaun, Bat. en Samarang. - Willem van der Voort, Carst, St. Thomas. GRANTON, 19 Maart; Pieter, Bekkering, Bremen n.Leith. - Sophia 1 Catharina, Weiss, Rott. n. id. NAPELS. 9 Maart; Jacoba Gesina, Kramer, Sunderland. Bij St. HELENA, 29 Jan.; Maria Agnes, Westenenk, Padang, 1. van de Kaap de Goede Hoop n. Amst. Si\ HELENA, 25 Jan.; Anthony van Hoboken, Hazewinkel, Banjoewangie n. Amst. - Temate, Cars Fzn., Bat. n. Rott. - 26 Jan.; Grootmeester Nationaal, Gie. sen, id. n. Amst. - Gieaner, Thompson, Pasoeroean u. id. ( hebben de reis TOoi.tg.__t).</p>
</text>
