<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 31 Julij; Pomona, Butchcr, Newcastle. — 1 Aug.; Nouvelle Eugénie, Anband, Nantes. - Swan, Annison, Newcastle. - Amazon, Norman, Archangel. - Seagull, Gullichsen, iii., (benevens de schepen per telegram gemeld). v YLIE, 31 Julij; Rembrandt, S.,Koningsbergen. - Willem I, S.,Hamb. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Aug.; Vincenzo Gianello, Capello, Rangoon. - Inyicta, Hopkins, Rochester. - Leo, Robiuson, Newc-Elizabeth, Tinemann, id. - Jane, Rowlan.ls, Sunderland. - Susanna, Middel, Riga. - Mathilda, Wiersma, Sundswall. BRIELLE, 1 Aug.-. Leo, S., Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 1 Aug.;Elize, Andrews, Rott. n. New-York. BREMERHAVEN, 31 Julij-, Vr. Grictj e, Schoon, Ncrva. HAMBURG, 30 Julij; Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Delfzijl. Bij KOPENHAGEN.27 Julij; Loiiisa Helena, Visser, Petersb. n.Amst.- Barteld Herman, Rasker, i^. n. id. - Margareth, Hamiucrs, Pmladèlphla n. Koningsbergen. SWINEMUNDE, 29 Julij; Blyham,Xuising, Rott. MEMEL, 27 Julij;Lucas Wildervank, de Groot, Brussel. STOCKHOLM, 24 Julij; Frecrk Jan, Smit, Petersburg. SUNDSWALL, 10 Julg-, Anna Colbjörnsen, Halstensen, N. Diep. —14 Julij: Shlvia. Smith, id. - Morr, Bugge, Antwerpen. EENDSBURG. 27 Julij; gepasseerd: Onrust, Mudder, Ystad mSchied.- Ebenezèr, Müdder, id. n. nl. - IWna, Kruisinsja, Dantzign. Maricnzjjl. — 29 Julü: Goerdina Geertruida, Kramer. Memel&apos;n. Scllfcdaih.-Fido, Engellandt, Ystad n. id. - Anna, Knliler, id. n. id. Bij DEAL. 30 Julij; Doelwijk, Hoefman, Rott. n. Bat. Bij BEAC H V HEAD, 27 Julij; Archipel, van der Gaauw, .... ROCHESTER. 30 Julij; John and Charles, Carlton, Rott. FALMOUTH, 31 Julij; Johanna, Meijer. Santos. CARDIFF. 28 Jnlij; Mercator, Rovers, Rott. ABERDEEN,3O Julij; Johannes, Kaper, Amst. ALLOA. 30 Julij; de Weldaad, Voogd, Nerva. DUNDEE, 28 Julij; Christina Jacoba. Plo.-g, Harlingen. LIVERPOOL, 29 Julij, William, Johnson, Amst. - Sarah Davies, Davies, id. — 30 Jnlij; Jacobus, Albers, Bahia. MIDDLESBRO, 30 Julij; Geertruida, Lindeboom, Hanover. -Jantje, Muller, Londen. SUNDERLAND, 30 Julij-, Sultana, Bell, Nieuwed. - Gez. Smith, Marshall, id. - Apollo, Mc. Donald, id.- Norway, Rawles,id.- Jupiter.Buch, id.- SHIELDS,3OJeIg-, Abel Tasman, Rgken, Amst. - Uncas, Mc. Intosh, id. - Germama, Möller, id. - Margaretha, de Vries, Zwolle. - Maid of Var, Vince. Dordt. - Crusader. Jones, id. - Mary, Hall, Rott. Baron v. Heemstra, Nepperus, Middelburg. - Tjakina |de Boer, Dost, Dantzig. - Dirk Hendrik, Prins, Antw. TRIEST, 27 Julij; Jacoba, Zwanenburg, Antwerpen. NAPELS. 25 Julij; Jacoba, Reinders, Cardiff. KONSTANTINOPEL, 11 Julij;ln quarantaine: Juffer Zwanette.Pekelder, Sulina. - Maria Sinna, Timmer, i.l. 24Fenna Ge/ma, Ymker,Liverpool.</p>
</text>
