<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10 Junij; Sagitta, Bakker, Tjilatjap. -Fosca Helena, Manje, Suriname. - Curacao Packet, de Ruiter, Curacao. - Dittatore Garibaldi, Rozetto, Messina 1. v. Falmouth. - De Hoop, Jelsma, Londen. - Sterling, Hutschinson, Sunderland.|- Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. Mehtta.Petersen, Riga. - Adieu, Buchholst, id. - Brodrene, Christcnsen, id. - Elise, Numann, ld. VLIE, 8 Junij; Willem I, S., Hamburg. —9 Jumj; Antje Visser, de Jonge, Riga. - Maria. Mcinsina, id. — 10 Junij; Lubbina, Hazelhoff, Gothenburg.&quot; Fenna. Woudsma, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Junij; Dash, Durrcll, Workington. - Osborne, S Lcith. - Grace, Frost, Newcastle. - Springflower, Daun, id. - Harriet, S ,&apos;Middlcsbro&apos;. - Seahorse, S., Huil.- Amelia, Kaiser, Riga - Cort Adler, Larsen, id. - St. Svitun, Jorsae, Libau. - Gothenburg, S., Gothenb. 1. v. Brouwershaven. . . &apos;_ . n . BRIELLE, 10 Junij; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Onon, fe., Londen. - Leeds. S., Grimsby. BREMERHAVEN, 8 Jumj; Capella, Timm, Rotterdam. HAMBURG, 8 Junij; Juliana Antina, de Boer, Brussel. CUXHAVEN, 8 Junij; Maroim. Kuypers, Liverpool. - Morgenster van Dijk Cadix. — 9 Jnnij; Annette, Poppen, Amsterdam. - Elve, _? Kott. NORDEN. 3 Junij. Grietje, Kuiper, Amsterdam. EMDEN, 5 Junij; Nooit Gedacht, Kroos, Amsterdam. STETTIN, 7 Junij; Eugenie Marie, Ris, Rotterdam. STOKHOLM, 2 Junij; Anneehina, Smit, Petersburg. GOTHENBURG, 4 Junij; Jonge Aukje, Balk, Middlesbro CHRISTIANIA, 30 Mei; Thor, Aubert, Nieuwed. - Geertruida, Dekker, Harlingen. ARENDAL, 25 Mei; B. D. Metcalf, Andersen, Rotterdam. GRANGEMOUTH, 7 Jumj; Eendragt, de Boer, Stettin.- Anna, Meijer, Koningsb. BELFAST, 8 Junij: Vartry, S., Rott. LYTHAM. 8 Junij; Zorgvliet, Garnaat, Kroonstad. LIVERPOOL, 8 Junij; Richard Warbrick, Dannison, Rott. LEITH, 6 Junij; Arendina/Sinit, Stettin. — 7 Junij; Allegonda Margaretha. Gort, Anclam. ABERDEEN, 6 Junij; Doggerboot, Gnodde, Dantzig. . WEST-HARTLEPOOL, 8 Junij; Nooit Gedacht, Bakker, lonningen. SUNDERLAND. 8 Junij; Margareth, Hall, Rott. SHIELDS, 8 Junij; Ridderkerk, Bunk, Antw. - Barend, Hoeksema, Rochestcr. - Ellcrsen, Schniidt, Dordt. _&apos;&apos;..„ -kt CADIX, 2 Junij; Otto, Sap, Cardiff. - 3 Jnnij; Jantina, Douwes, New- Castle. - Heilina Jacoba, Haverbult, id. ANCONA, 5 Junij-, Reyna. de Jonge, Amsterdam. NEW-YORK, &apos;l.Mei; Vrye handel, Lupkc, Rio-Grande. - Anna tSoc_-</p>
	<p>mann, Amst.</p>
</text>
