<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 25 Sept.; Preeiosa, Lond, Riga. - Médéa, S., Kopenh. - Erithiof, Torbiornsen, Frederikst. - Activ, Ulleberg, Persgrund. — 25 Sept.; Zr. Ms. , oorlog-stoomschip Watergeus, kapt.-luit. Geerling, New-York 1. v. Portsm. - Stad Enschedé, Niggebrugge, Dundee. - Hollander, S., Huil. - Cort Adler, Hansen, Riga. - Minerva, Rafcn, Södeiham. -Amphitrite, Hansen, Frederikstad. - Elisabeth Sophie, Svensen, id. - Thor, Buil, id. -Enigheden, Jacobsen, Drammen. - Foreningen, Seeberg, id. VLIE, 24 Sept.; Deltina, Wessels, Riga. - Etta, Willinga, Frederikstad. - de Flecken Jovwer, Mellema, id. - Elisabeth, Zeven, id. - 3 Gebroeders, Jassen, id. - Hercules, Koster, id. - Onderneming, Kooiman, id. - Geertruida Jaeoba, Bontekoe, Arendahl. - Grietje, Nieboer, Ostorisöer. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. — 25 Sept.; Zeelust, Kcun, Dantzig.-Vrouw Martha, Ebos Jr., Gothenburg. - Tro.Venner, Thorsen, Frederikstad. - Vrouw Helena, Kraan, id. - Johanna, Oldenburger, id. -Johanna Elisabeth, Helmers, id.- Geertruida, de Groot, id. - Jonkvrouw Elisabeth, de Boer, id. - Catharina Elisabeth, Pot, id. - Antje, Munning, Arendshl. - Creole, Pedersen, Drobach.- Castor, Ólsen, Aasgaardstrand. OSTMAHORN, 23 Sept.; Emanuel, de Jonge, Newcastle. - Hermanus Wieher, v. d. Laan, Dantzig. - Hilke Katt, de Vries, Bremen. - Jaeoba Cai tharina, Geltes, id. DELFZIJL, 21 Sept.; Jan Gijsbert, Smit, Dantzig. - Geerdiena, Jager, Frederikstad. - Johann Heinrich, de Jonge, id. - Geerdiena, Duintjer, Laurvig. - Vr. Geerdina, Speelman, Bremen. - Sophia, Bieze, Gcestemunde.-Vr. Janna, Oosterhuis, id. - Maria Geertruida, Mooi, Fedderwadderzyl. - Catharina Elisabeth, Gcertsema, Papcnborg. — 22 Sept.; Cornelia, Leeuw, Frederikstad. - Eendragt, de Witt, id. - Nooit Gedacht, Nanning, id. - Cathar. Imkiena, Hulzebos, Leer. - Susanna, Barghoorn, Emden. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 25 Sept.; Dankbaarheid, v. d. Wal, Bilbao. - Earl of Auckland, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. - Balinoral, S., Cardiff&apos;. - Louise, S., Grangemouth. - Holyrood, S., Leith. - Seahorse, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole. - Maria Coralie, Bakker, Frederikstad. BRIELLE, 25 Sept.; Jan Andreas, Doyen, Bergen. LONDEN, 25 Sopt.; Diana, S., Amst. Bij DUNGENESS, 21 Sept.; Clarovine, Jones, Galatz n. Amst. — 22 Sept.; Agatha, Zeilinga, Curacao n. id. — 25 Sept.; Nagasaki, Mos, Bat. n. Rott. (met een loods aan boord). SHIELDS, 20 Sept.; Elisabeth, Yallop, Rott. — 22 Sept.; de Spruit, Pott, &apos; Delfshaven. NANTES, 21 Sept,; Amphitrite, Calvé, Rott. PAIMBOEUF,22 Sept.; Harmonie, Boer, Stettin. LISSABON, 17 Sept.; Catharina Geerdina, de Greet, Amst. - Koophandel &amp; Zeevaart, Brouwer, Vlaai-dingen. PORTO, 18 Sept.; Maria, van Duijvenbooden, Amst. BANANA, 3 Julij; Möwe, Kuhn, Rott. NEW-CASTLE (N. Z. W.I, 7 JulijrElisabeth. Trvselius. Melbourne.</p>
</text>
