<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>u _ i&apos; 27 AnS-&apos; N,ï B«renice, S, Middell. Zee. - Stad Workum, van 4..r&apos; Eonden.- 3 Broeders, Bijkerk, id.- Vrouw Dieuwke, Feenstra,id.- VV ïlliam Hannah, Fullock, Newc. - Palladium, Nesworthey, id. - Cassandra, Laidler, Sunderland. - Rubin, Overland, Archangel. - Dannebrog, Nieism, id. - Sophie, Berg, id. - Heimdahl, 1 .ders.n, id. - Maria Catharina, Wessels, Nerva. - Brodrene, Christensen, Biga. - Omen, Bakker, id.- Waverley, ijoness, Sundswall. - Europa, Lerentsen, id. - Scandia, Hansen, Huaickswall. - Johns, ForgenseD, Osterrisoer. - Willem Csrel, Gudwunsen, Skeen. - Gisteren nog: Nor, Svensen, Sundswall. VLIE, 2H Am?., N.0.; Emauuel, Pedersen, Archang.- Jeantina, Eeftiug, Eiga. - Argo, Alta, id. - Haabet, Lorentzen, Sundswall. - Niord, Wilhelmeen, Drobach. —26 Aug.; Hendrik Jan Nassau, Roelfsenia, Biga. - Juße, Brunn, _ redenkstad. ZOLTKAMP, 24 Aug.; Heinrich, Koster, Riga. — 25 Aug.; Eendragt, van Hoorn, id. - Edel, Toft, Petersb. HELVOETSLUIS, 27 Aug., N.; Codan, Kirchsteiu, Akyab.l. v Brcuwersh. - Soefiwris, Mariach, Berdiansk 1. v. id. - Commerce, Cace Taganrog. -John &amp; Charles, Charlton, Rochester. - Robert Hannah, Wool . Poole. - Expert, Egert, Newc- Mary&apos;s, Ward, id. - Dugald Steward Bischop, bunde:rland. - Jane Spoors, Bruning, Seahara. - Hickman, Angleby, Middlesbro. - Albert, S., Huil.- Maria Jantina, de Boer, Archangel.- Equator, Huisman. Petersb.- Geertruida, Stuit, Nyberg. - Lina, Clarckscn, Libau. - Emilie, Steinorth, Dantz. - Caroüne Heimann, Boetius Wardoe.- De Vak, Stfijbos, Hamb. BRIELLE, 27 Aug., N.; Hiram, Mattson, Riga. - Heinrich, Brahm, Pernau. BREMERHAVEN, 27 Aug.; Harmina, Gort, Dantzig. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 26 Aug.; Johanna Maria, Fenenga, _&quot;eteisburg n. Gothenburg. KOPENHAGEN, 26 Ang.; Economie, Bossinga, Petersburg. - Maria, Pronk, id. - Renske, Nepperus, id. - J antina, Don wes id. - Meika Jacoba, Wielema, id. - Jonge Gerrit, Hazewinkel id.. (n. Antwerpen). LONDEN, 24 Ang.; Antje, Leeuw, Petersburg. — 25 Ang.; Eendragt, Jelsma , Workum.- Hersn Wilson, Rott. -Vriendschap, Kröger, Petersb.- Pax, Muller, id. - Aukjen, Wiebes, id. Bij PORTLAND, 24 Aug.; Jacoba, Rijken, Shields n. Bat. LO WESTO FT, 24 Aug.; Courier, Slotema, v n ALMWIJK, 25 Aug.; Daßh, üurrell, Rott. RYK, 25 Aug.; Carl Evans, Reynolds, Rott. SHIELDS, 23 Aug.; Flora Clinge, Oliver, Rott. — 24 Aug.-. Sikko, Jon» ker, Amst. - Metje Sehönfeld, v. Dijk, Schiedam. - Hennrika, Kramer, Bremen. - Margareth, Wilmink, Dordt. - Fortuva. Oncto, Delfzijl. SEAHAM, 23 Aug.; Elizabeth, Hartley, Dordrecht. MACDUFF, 21 Aug.; Stad Enschedé, Veldhuis, Amst. SUN DERLAND, 23 Ang.; Geo Sinith, Marshall, Nieuwe Diep. - Vivi.l, Bedingfield, id. - Waterhuizen, Heijenga,Holmstrand. — 24 Aug.; Excelsior, Buil, Koogerpolder GIBRALTAR, 20 Aug.; Oceaan, Post, VlaardiDgen. MARSEILLE, 23 Aug.; Irene, S., Napels. GENUA, 21 Aug.;Onon,S., Amst. NEW-YORK, 13 Aug-, Krimpen a/d. Lek, Rotgans, Havana. BATAVIA. 28 Junij; Herald of the Morning, Henderson, Soerabaya, 4 Juljj n. Nederl. vertr. — 29 Junij; Presto, Teekes, Amst., 2 Julij n. Samarang vertr. — 2 Jolij; Amazone, Dannberg, Panaroekan, 5 dito n. Ned. vertr. - _Egidia ..Paulina, Hoogland. Soerabaya, 5 diton. Dordt. vertr. enden 7den dito Straat Snnda gepasseerd.- Henri.tte Gerardina Susanna, Dam, Yokohama. — 5 Julij; Batavia, van Dolder, Inlramayoe. - Kaap Hoorn, Dik, id. — 6 Julij; Aluion le, Pijl, Liverpool. - 7 Julij; Maarten van Rossen, Wiebenga, Soerabaya, Il dito n. Nederland vertrokk.— 8 Julij; Nederland en Oranje, Möller. Soerabaya, 11 dito n.Nederland vertrokk. — 12 Julij; 6 Gezusters, Rutgers, Hongkong. - Argo, Ankringa, Pamanoekan. - Henriette Maria, Tjebbes, Samarang. - Minister Thorbecke, Kannegieter, Passaroeang. STRAAT SUNDA, 4 Julij; Alblasserdam, &apos;t Hoen, Cardiff n. Bat. SOERABAYA, 30 Junij; johanna Maria, Klennenberg, Bat — 1 Julij; Louise, Bonjer, Amst.</p>
</text>
