<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Oct., Z.0.-O; Diana, S.s Londen.-Heeg, Boontje, id. - Donor, Thompson, Sunderland. - Minister Thorbecke, SJ( HuU.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 110ct.&gt;O.ZsO.; Vrouw Clara, Bakker, Newc. - Else Johanna, Block, Petersburg. - Wodan, Meinders, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Oct., 0.N.0.; Ranger, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. - Egret, S., Liverpool. - St. Mathew, Watson, Newc. - Christina Hendrika, Bringman, Koningsbergen.—Gisteren nog.- Swanland, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole, BRIELLE, 12 Oct., N.0.; Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 12 Oct., N.0.; Leopold, Graaf van Limburg Stirura, Campbell, Rott. PILLAU, 9 Oct.; Anna, Kammenga, Huil. FREDERIKSTAD, 30 Sept.; Faïnilien, Aas, Nieuwe Diep. - EmanueJ, Christoffersen, id. - Marie, Johnsen, Rott. - Sylphide, Apeness, Nieuwe Diep. - Wubke Vellman, Krai, Harl. - Veendammer Courant, Zoutman, Kampen. - Martha, Krenier, Harl.- Onderneming, Kooiman, Stavaer. - Fortuna, Groot. Termunterzijl. - Jacob van Cleef, Nienhuis, Harl, - Geerdina, Wypkes, Termunterzijl. - Jantina, Jonge, Delfzijl. - Cath. Gerhardina. - Folgering, id. — 1 Oct.; Alida Giezen, Nieland, Termunterzijl.- Wilnelmine, Jansonius, id.- Nooit Gedacht, Ohlsen, Harlingeu.- Wilh. Catharina, Hesseling, id. - Theodor?, Lucretia, Grummels, Delfzijl. - Henderika, Holman, Kampen. - Castor, Samsing, Harlingen. - Nidaros, Pedersen, Amsterdam. - Laura, Wang, Nieuwe Diep. TONSBERG, 30 Sept.; TolvËrodre, Buil,Rott. - Nancy, Hansen, Amst. — 1 Oct.; Amerika, Dessen, Nieuwe Diep. - Verena, Jacobsen, Holland. - Fem Söstre, Knudsen, Dordrecht. - Bedalia, Klö.jö, Holland. - Emmanuel, Gjertsen, id. DRAMMEN, 28-30 Sept.; Jenny, Asby, Amst. - Gr. W. Jarlsberg, Bakker, Dordrecht. - Greven de Karen Wedel, Roed, Nieuwe Diep. - Mary, Andressen, id. - Activ, Uileberg, id. - Ogir, Lund, id. - Sylvanus, Schjaervig, id.- Judith, Stibolt, id.- Christiania, Halvorsen, id.-Petrus, Jahnsen, id.- Mindet, Han sen, id. - Enigheden, Mathiesen, Amst. - Phonix, Larsen, id. - Christiane, Haagensen, id. - Achilles, Wulf6berg, Purmerend. - Preciosa, Thomsen, id. - Marie Theresia, Dahlhof, Termunterzijl. - Alberdina, Wolkammer, Delfzijl.</p>
</text>
