<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 4 Aug., N.—N.O.; Sir John Bowes,Wright, Newcastle. — Gisteren nog; Amphitrite, Oelsen, Tonsberg. VLIE, 3 Aug., 0.N.0.; Isaac Sannes, de Jonge, Petersb. - Nüverheid, Bossinga, id. - Persa, Jansonius, Nerva. - Johanna Gesina, van der Veen, C hristiania. - Wubke Veltman, Kraai, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 4 Aug., N.—W.; Bang, S., Odessa. - Pride of the Wear, Nicholson, Kertch 1. v. Vlissingen. - Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Chevy Chase, S., Newc. - Norval, Nell, Sunderla nd.-Ironmaster, S., Middlesbro.- Seahorse, S., Huil. - Dina Adriana, Kwint, Dantzig.-Eureka, de Groot.id. BRIELLE,4 Aug., N—O.—W.;Prins van Oranje,S.,Duinkerken.- Waterloo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. - Sheffield, S., Grimsby, - Amicitia, S., Bergen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 4 Aug., N. W.; Kensington, Bakker, Rott. n. Newyork. ZIERIKZEE, 3 Aug., N.; Rovena, Palmer, Liverpool n. Dordrecht. BREMERHAVEN, 3 Aug.; Elisabeth, Peters, Namsos.- Aaltina, Hoekstra, Utrecht. - Sophia, Bieze, Delfzijl. BRAKE, 3 Aug.; de Hoop, Pott, Petersburg. HEPPENS, 29 Julij; Markthat, Drury, Rott,- John Piccard, Morris,id.- Elvira, Robinson, id. ,- «?. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 29 July; Antina, de Vries, Memel n. Amst. — 31 Julij; Hendrika Frouwina, Scholtens, Middlesbro n.Peterburg.— 2 Aug.; Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, de Eems n. de Oostzee. - Cornelia, Voogd, Petersburg n. Aberdcen. FLENSBURG, 2831 Julij; Geertruida, Easker, Amst. SARPSBORG, 23 Julij; Thetis, Lycke, Nieuwediep. WARNEMUNDE, 30 Julij; Alida Adriana, Kramer, Bremen. DANTZIG, 30 Julij; Antje, Kruisinga, Newcastle. — 31 Julij; Sophia, Vonk, Koningsbergen n. Buxtehude. MEMEL, 30 Julij; Eendragt, Boer, Fleusburg. KROONSTAD, 30 Julij; Louise Geerdina, Wever, Gioja.-Tjapko Schuringa, Drenth, Koningsbergen. ELSENEUR, 1 Aug.; gepasseerd: Johanna Hermina, Hoeksma, Aale- LONDEN, 1 Attg.jßulgersteyn, van Wijngaarden, Wiibnrg. — 2 Aug; Catharina, van der Meulen, Petersb. - Catharina, Bekkering, d, - Yeo, Wray, Rotterdam. __&apos;_&apos;&apos;._ Bij DEAL, 2 Aug.; Nieuw Beerta, Groen, Londen n. Montevideo. Bij DOVER, 2 Aug.; Anthony van Hoboken, Muntendam, Amst. n. Liverpool. - Herman de Ruyter, Ësink, Amst. n. Batavia. TEIGNMOUTH, 1 Ang.; Broedertrouw, Niezen, Memel. CLYDE, 1 Aug.; Egmont Hom, Frudden, Matanzas. Bij DUNGENESS, 2 Aug.; Lichtstraal, Jansen, Rott. n. Batavia. Bij BEACHY HEAD, 29 Julg; Maria Elise, van Deursen, Bat. ft Amst, SHIELDS, 2 Aug.; die Traube, Lange, Amst. - Waters, Payne, Dardt. Jane, Combers, Zierikzee. ,«,,_-.,. , _. *, MALTA, 23 Julij; Wilhelmina, van der Weyden, Vlaardingen (vertrol: 26 Julij n. Sicilië). . , &apos; , DARDANELLEN, 24 Julij; Brazilien, Jacobs, Odessa n. Amst. - An^ tonia, Paicurich, id. n. id. „,.._.. „ CARDENAS, 10 Julij; Sagua Packet, Slmsman, Havana n. Amst. Bg&apos; PHILADELPHIA, 23 Julg&apos;; Hertha , Rott. BOSTON, 20 Julij; de Komeet, Visser, Rott. NEW-YORK, 21 Julij; Garibaldi, Eldridge, Rott. SOERABAYA, 7 Junij; Minister Thorbeeke, Kannegieter, Samarang, BANANA, 3 Junij; President Lincoln. Bakker,... (alles wel aan bo«&gt;rd)__</p>
</text>
