<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 19 Oct., Compasrond; Diana, S., Londen. - Mentor, Toering, id. - Sharp, Bravey, Sunderl.- Alert, S., Hull.-Athalia, Pedersen, Sundswall. - Christiane, Buil, id. - Fortuna, Ravensbury, Söderhamn. - Frederikke Louise, Lercke, Jacobstad.- Minerva, Pedersen, Odensee. — Gisteren nog: Anna Maria Henriette, de Jong, Liverpool; alles wel aan boord. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. — 20 Oct.; Christina,Nieuwland qq., Bat. vertr. 21 Junij. - Vorwartz, Niemann. Taganrog, 1. v.Falm.- Irene, S., Middell. Zee. - Mary, Turling, Sunderl. - Daphne, Fredriksen, Hudickswall. - 2 Gebroeders, de Groot, Stockholm, VLIE, 19 Oct, N.N.W.; Nora, S., Londen. - Emilie, Jager. Newc. n. Gron., als bijlegger. - Anneta, Wenninga, Riga. — 20 Oct; Bordeaux, Ouendag Azn., Wasa. - Willem 1, S., Hamb. ZOLTJKAMP, 17 Oct; Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Newc— 18 Oct; Depositum, Nieveen, Antwerpen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 20 Oct, Compasrond; Mary Rellow, Mable, Par. - Ousel, S., Liverpool. - Harmonie, Bakker, Peters- Verdandi, Torgensen, Riga. -Terminus, Edmunds, Zierikzee. BROUWERSHAVEN, 20 Oct., W.; Burgemeester van Middelburg, Hoek, Rott. PILLAU, 18 Oct; Rubbens, S., Amst. - 4 Broeders, Ernmelkamp, Kiel. BOLDERA, 16 Oct.; Jan\isser, Boon, Amst. - Adelgunde, Lange, Nieuwediep. . „,.¦_.„ , „ LONDEN, 18 Oct; Louisa Sophia, Hollander, Duinkerken. - Margaretha, Duinker, Petersburg. FALMOUTH, 19 Oct.; Wildervank, Giezen, Rio Grande. DOVER.IB Oct.; PaulusMeintz,Venema,v. Savanilla n. Rott. RAMSGATE, 17 Oct.; Jantina, Vos, Newc. n. Alexandrie. STUDWALL ROADS, 17 Oct.; Sabrina, Pritchard, Portmadoc n. Rot. MACDUFF, 13 Oct; Hendrika Margaretha, Freie, Zweden. SWANSEA, 17 Oct; Dolnhin, Roberts, Rott. INVERKEITHING. 16 Oct; Niord, Anderson, Amst. NEW-CASTLE, 17 Oct.; Waterwitch, Leadley, Rott. LISSABON, 16 Oet; Lonrens, de Kromme, Newc. PORTIMAO, 9 Oct; Kleinkinderen, v. d. Wal, Lissabon. NEW-YORK, 5 Oct.; Sophia Maria, Teensma, Triest BOSTON, 6 Oct; J. Mildrcd, Harriman, Rott. BOMBAY, 22 Sept.; Californië, de Wijn, Newc.</p>
</text>
