<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 7 April;Bcrénice, S.,Midd.Zee. - Rubbcns, S., Kopenhagen. - Urania, S., id. - Nordstjernen, Christensen, Drammen. VLIE, 5 April; Nordstcrn, Niomann, Newcastle. - Gebroeders Cocrkamp, Hoekstra, Middlesbro. - Burgemeester van Setten, Holvast, Dantzig. - llillechina Vos, Lever, Avont. - Bouchina, Koster, id. — 6 April; Maria Beerta, Tap, Windau. - Helena Maria, Diependaal, id. OSTMAHORN, 5 April; Wiebergina Martens, Balk, Goole. - Magrietha Hendrika, de Boer, Engeland. - Drie Gebroeders, de Groot, Calmar. - Vier Gebroeders, Heida, Denemarken. - Marianne, Vlas, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 7 April; Ary Scheffer, S., Havre. BRIELLE, 6 April; Peace, Rhodes, Londen, n. Rott. - Excrtion, Elder, Boness n. id. - 7 April; Mary ie Catharina, Hayes, Londen n. Dordt. VLISSINGEN, 4 April; Titia Susanna, Potjer, Bremen. COWES, 5 April; Willem Frederik, Visser, Londen. DARTMOUTH, 5 April; Gesina Antina, van Klooster, Newc. FALMOUTH, 5 Aprl; A. 11. Gordon, Gordon, Kaap de Goede Hoop n. Amst.» Etjc, Mooi, Marseille n. Londen. -I _rsa, Drcnth, Ancona-n. id. LIVERPOOL, 5 April; zeilklaar: Marnix, Wassenaar, Amst. CARDIFF, 4 April; AVilhehnina Adriana, Bot, Lissabon. SUNDERLAND, 4 April; Leo, Robertson, Rott. BRISTOL, 5 April; Krommenie, Engelsman, Cardif. ANTWERPEN, 6 April; Gcertrnida Femina, Bakker, Lubeek. - Jantina Kobina, de Jonge, Memel. - Harmonie, Bakker, Rostock. - Enjetta, de Boor, Avontuur. CADIX, 24 Maart; Margaretha, Veen, Scvilia. NEW-YORK, 27 Maart; zeilklaar: Albert, Meijer, Bremen. RIO-JANEIRO, 7 Febr.; Riewcrtdina, Kieviet, het Kanaal. —11 Febr.; August, Rosenberger, Gibraltar. — 22 Febr.; Margaretha, Ilarms, het Kanaal. — 24 Febr.; Wellington, Mahy, Bat. - Jacoba Johanna, van der Meulen, Victoria. —25 Febr.; Johanna Adriana, Franken, Konstantinopel. RIO-GRANDE, 10 Maart; Compagnie, Donoma, Kanaal. - Hendrika, van der Veen, id. - Waalwijk, Schaafsma, id. MANZ ANILLA, 4 Maart; Ceres, Boog, Rott. BUENOS-AYRES, 9 Febr.; Deni, Knypcr, Montevid. - d&apos;Ommelanden, Wieringa, Gioja — 14 Febr.; Johanna Hendrika, v. Leeuwen, Uruguay. — 15 Febr.; Jacoba, Sprik, St. Catharina. - Antoinettc, Gnoddc, Paranagua. MONTEVIDEO, vo&apos;dr 28 Febr.; Margaretha , Antw. BAHIA, 13 Febr.; Anna Hendrika Carolina, Sijbrandi, Gibraltar. — 5 Maart; Gesina, de Jonge, Amst.</p>
</text>
