<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 19 Julij; Diana, S., Londen.-Cornet, Pedersen, Macdttff.- Hart, Cloak, Newc.-John Ruthersford, Shilvcrs, id. - Hudgill, Éreems, id.- Premium, Adamson, Seaham. - Agostina, Chcyno, Ivigtout. - Cilelenbcrg, Larsen, Avontuur. - Ceres, Remmers, iel. VLIE, 19 Julij; Gratitnde, Kolk, Avontuur. - Martha, Banting, id. - Almutb Catharina, Gewald, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 19 Julij; Admiraal Ver-lluell, S.. Havre. - Earl of Auckland, S., Lon len. - General Lee, S , Dublin.- - Queen, S., Dtiiidec. - Maria Stuart, S., Lcith. - Clievy Chase, S., Newc. - Fairey Queen, S,, Hart-, lepool. - Seahorse, S., llull. - John Wclls, S., Goole. - Anna, Sjam, Lïbai»/ - Catharina, Eekkcs, Frederikstad. - Ecm Söstrc, Kmidscn, id. - de Hoop, Sieger.-i, id. - Levant, S., Gothenburg. - Godt Haab, Torgcnsen. Holmstrand. MAASSLUIS, 1 ü Julij; Princess, Pa&apos;ker, Newcastle. - Margrietta, Paft. ncman,id.- Betsy, Patcr_on,Si_ndcrland.-Henry en Mariett, Symm.Shields.- Katc and Jane, Sewell, Middicsbro&apos;. -Noordstar, Brouwer, Riga. - lelun, Pedersen, id. BREMERHAVEN, 18 Julij; Alida Ikea, Pieper, Stokholm. - Twee Gezusters, Giltes, Groningen. HAMBURG, 17 Jnlij; Maria Gecrtruiela, Mooi, Nederland. — 18 Julij ; Al hortus, Wcgcncr, Porto Alegro, CAROLI-vERZYL, 13 Julij ; Anna, Hoekslra, Londen. ■ Aurora, Peters , id. STi (LPEMUNDE, 9 Julij, Bor.ua Roemeliiigh, Visser, Lonelcn. SWINEMUNDE; 15 Julij; Reina, Ktuisinga, Bremen. DANTZIG, 15 Julij; Vriendschap, Lodewijk, Amst. - Catharina Cornelia, Astuling, Harijrigcn, MEMEL,IS JulijjPax.Mcllcma,Harlingen. BOLDES.A, 12 Julij; Catharina, Gauthier, Nederland. — 14 Julij; Johanncs, dc Boer, Elscncur. NERVA, 4 Julij; Geertruida, Mandcma, Engeland. — 7 Julij; Activ, Erag, Nederland. A BERDEEN, 16 Julij; Texel, Hubert, Noorwegen. SHIELDS, 17 Julii; Catharina, ..., Nieuwe Diep. MIDDLESBRO, 16 Julij: Eraneois, van Evk, Vlissingen. ANTWERPEN, 18 Julij; Drie Gezusters, Breeland, Kopenhagen. MALTA, 7 Julij, Willielmina, v. d. Weyden, Sicilië.. St. HELENA, 26 Mei; d&apos;Elinina, Deinmcrs, Banjocwangie n. Rott. — 5 Junij; Catharina Maria, van Anicronge-n, iel. n. id. HONGKONG, 20 Mei; Ilebc, Kie_l,f watow. — 26 Mei; Jacob en Anna, Bojjger, Amoy. MELBOURNE, 13 Mei; zeilkl.: Susanna, Vonck Bat.</p>
</text>
