<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 19 Julij; Joseph Margareth, John_en, Sunderl. (benevens de schepen per telegr. gemeld). VLIE, 18 Julij; Niessina Jaeoba, Barelds, Dantzig. -de Flccken Jovwer, Mellema, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 19 Julij; Good Decision, Brereton, Lond. - John %■ Arm, Wray, Newc. - Heinrich, Egbsrts, Nerva. - Christina, Trost, Stolpmünde. BRIELLE, 19 Julij; Waterloo, S„ Lond. - Pacific, S., Harwich. - Albert, S., Huil. BROUWERSHAVEN, 18 Julij; WilliamWright,Wright, Callao n.Rott. BREMERHAVEN, 17 Julij; Jacoba Margiena, Kuil, Antw. - Meinsina, Klontje, Stettin. — 18 Julij; Aaltje, Bongers, Petersburg. HAMBURG, 17 Julij; Juffer Aaltje, Martens, Dokkum. STOLPEMUNDE, 11 Julij; Heidowika Rcgina, Pckelder, Pahlhuda (vertrok 15 dezer n. Londen). — 14 Julij; Jantina Alida, Texer, Rendsb. SWINEMUNDE, 17 Julij; Medea, S., Amst. - Cycloop, S., id. MEMEL, 13 Julij; Harmonie, Dik, Amst. - Afien Smit, Boswijk, Glouccster. - Wilhelmina Petronella, Bijl, id. — 14 Julij; Osiris, Warnekes, Antwerpen. — 15 Julij; Welgelegen, Nieting, Harlingen. BOLDERA, 12 Julij; Zeemeeuw, van Wijk, Schiedam. — 13 Julij; Sophia, Paulstm, Nieuwediep. - Magrietha, Kappen, Schiedam. - Lucretia, Bracht, Amst. - Aurora, Christensen, id. - Léontine, Auvray, Rott. — 15 Jnlij; Geertruida Jacoba, Potjcr, Lissabon. ÖTOKHOLM, 11 Jnlij; Concordia, Knijpenga, Rott. — 14 Julij; Wilhelmina, Ehlert, Amst. - Gouverneur van Ewijck, S., id. DALARÖ, 13 Jnlij; Jacoba Catharina, Nieveen, Cardiff. SANDHAMN, 13 Julij; Wilhclraine, Ehlcrt, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 16 Julij; Paradies, Bornholt, Pernau n. Lissabon. - Anna, Dottwes, Memel n. Duinkerken. - Catharina, Duitjer, Leba n. Dordt. ELSENEUR, 16 Julij; Tonsberg, Thrie, Suüdswalln, Nieuwe Diep.,- Jcannc, Kroon, Petersburg (om Order), — Gepasseerd: Eduard, Ahreas, Riga n. Nederl. - Twee Gebroeders, Hitman, Petersburg n. Anist. RENDSBURG, 15 Julij; gepasseerd: Roelfina Johanna, Drewes, Harlingen n. Wismar. - Vrouw Éiisabeth, Top, Bremen n. deOostzce. - Aurelia Gruno, Stuitjc, Ncstved n. Nederland. — 17 Julij; Catharina,Poppen, Dantzig n. Harlingen. - Lubbina, Hazclhoff, id. n. Bremen. • HEPPEN S, 17 Julij; Elisabeth, Schoon, Rott. VAREL, lö Julij; Andreas en Maria, Slik, Stettin. _ LON DEN, 17 J ulij; Jeltina, Scherpbier, Marathonisi. —18 Julij; Karsina, Waterborg, Groningen. - Anna, Veldkamp, id. Bij DEAL ,17 Julij; dc Zwaluw, Brongers, Groningen n. Grlemccster. Bij OXFORD , 17 Julij ; Eendragt, Martcns, Rugenwalde n. Londen. SHIELDS, 16 Julij; Ckarlotte Louise Wilhelmine, Eender, Schied. — 17 Julij ; Jantje Goossens, Leisier, St. Valery. HARTLEPOOL , 17 Julij ; Karen, Anderson, Rotterdam. DUINKERKEN, 17 Julij; Wilhelmina, Poelman, Riga. MALTA, 7 Julij; ele Zwerver, Schut, Newc. St. HELENA, 27 Mei; Maarten van Rossum, Gcrrebrands, Paelang n. Rott. — 30 Mei; Johanna Elisabeth, Duinker, Banjocw. n. Amst. — 31 Mei; Rudolf, Meinsina, id. n. Rott. — 6 Junij; Java Paeket, Crap Hellingman, id. n. Amst. — 10 Junij; Eva Johanna, Hordijk, id. n. Middelburg. — 16 Junij; Argo, Ankringa, Paelang n. Rott. — 18 Junij; Medea, van Teutem, Banj. n. Rott.- Jacob, Muller Drenth, id.n. iel.-Maria Anna, van Monnoin, id. n. id.— 19 Junij; Rcgina Maris, Ouwehand, Soerabaya n. Middelburg. - Ouderkerk a/d Amstel, Dingemans, Bat. n. Rott. - Johanncs Anthonius, van der Staten, Banjoew. n. Rott. —20 Junij; Theodora Machtilda, van der Wijck, Bat. n. Amst. — 2! Junij; Hollandia, Wap, id. n. Nederl. — 22 Junij; de Schelde, Hoefman, Tjilatjap n. Amst. TAFELBAAI, 20 Mei; Duivcland, Plnimer, Boston.</p>
</text>
