<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>m i* , TEXEL, 12Dec,Z.Z.W.- W.N. W.; Markland, Harding,Newyork, i» i-v, Queenstown. - Gezusters, Ridder, Havre. - Lion, S., Londen. — Gis-11 «ren nog: Laura, Willemsen, Baltimore. - Wilhelmina, Meijer, Dantzig. °? , HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Dcc, Z. W.; St. Bernard, Deetjen, Baltimore, \ ók&apos; Br°nwershaven.- Hull, S., Hull. - Proteus, Jörgensen, Petersburg. - p Wiristopher Hage, Block, Bandholm. - Catharina Geerdina, de Groot, M aorsoer. - Tbetis.de Zeeuw Bagges, Bergen. &apos;A .&quot;RIELLE, 12 Dcc, Z. W.; Waterloo, 8., Lond. - Ravensbury, S., Har, - Wardall, Gardner, Petersburg. A . BROUWERSHAVEN, 12 Dcc, Z.W.; Ary Scheffer, Kunst, Rott. n. «atavia. JF*__\ &quot;&apos; j^EER, 8 Dcc; Jantje, Forma, Amst. —10 Dcc; Jacobus Cornelius, Kchoon, Groningen. . i&apos; vBREMERHAVEN, 11 Dec&apos;; Onrust, Slankenberg, Hooksiel. - Venus, et&apos; &apos;isser, Koningbergen. , „HAMBURG, IO Dcc; SanNicolas,Larrazabal,Nièuwediep.-Pollux, * Mtott. f&quot; OSTERRISOER, 30 Nov.; Aukje, Wiebes, Petersb. n. Amst. 9 PILLAU, 9 Dcc; Phoenix, Giiin, Bergen. \ ELSENEUR, 9 Dec.; gepasseerd: Nina, S., Dantzig n. Amst. &apos;&lt;_ KENDSBURG, BDec.; gepasseerd: Geertruida, Mandema, Koningsb. V *• Harlingen. - Catharina Alida, Pronk, Memel n. Bremen. - Immanuel, «e Jonge, Petersb. n. Groningen. m , ;____\ &quot;&apos; m Bij DEAL, 10 Dcc; Geerdina Afina, Pomper, Amst. n. Buenos-Ayres. - 1.1&apos; AnjiaMargaretha, Oftmans, Londen n.Cardiff. i&quot; Bij PORTLAND, 10 Dec.; Excelsior, Date, Rott. n. St. Michacls. &apos;*&apos; KÈWiIA VEN, 9 Dcc; Integrity, Hamden, Rott. H&gt;&gt; MILFORD, 10 Dcc; Arm Williams, May, Rott. n. Liverpool. &lt;&quot; CARDIFF, 8 Dec.; Johanna Jacoba, Velt, Londen. i«&apos; jjSUNDERLAND, 9 Dcc; Leda, Richards, Rott. - Economie, Baxter, . i Hamburg. s* SHIELDS, 10 Dcc; Ilario Fleischer, Costa, Rott. 1, CADIX. 3 Dcc; Zeevaart, Ritzes, Swansea. J: GIBRALTAR, 2 Dcc; Speculation, van der Kooy, Bahia (vertrok den 4 eigenden dag n. Triest). — 4 Dcc; Helena Chnstina, During, Hani, lerlest. é 5Sikkes, Newc.</p>
</text>
