<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Oct; Anna, Hubert, Petersburg.- Cornelia Anna Christin», de Haan, Cliristiania. - Veendammer Courant, Zoutman, Frederikstad.— 2 Oot.; Fauna, Jorgeusen, Sundswall. - Sondswall, Buil, id.- Tbor.Su.ith id. - Tekla, Hansen, id. - Minerva, Rafen, id. - Rubens, Forbeck, id. - Maria, Berg, Frederikstad. - Dapline, Fredrikseu, id. - Presto, Tho&apos;inasson, Drimmen.-Wilhelm Tersmedc, Tofte, id. - Sara Margaretha Erichsen, Porsgrund. « • VLIE, 1 Oct.; Almuth Catharina, Vry, Archangel. - Gesina Jantina Bekkering, Petersburg. - Johanna, de Groot, Riga. - Hendrik Jan Nassau Roelfse.ua,id. - Harmonie, Uaverschmidt, id. - Valkyrien, Hansen Middelfahrt - Lina Monborg, Hoy, id. - Alida Ikina, Piepers, Kjerteu.inde. - Anna, Hansen, Anclam.-Agatha Ebelina, Hoekstra, Schulpcr/ijl. - Ai.nogina Bouw, Gotheub. - Frits _f- Betsy, Stuut.id.-Niord, Wilhelmsen, Frederikstad. - Harmonic, Kremer, id. - Argo, Koster, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Oct.; Anna, S., Grangemouth. — 2 Oct.; Gencral Lee, S., Whitehaven. - Active, Johnson, ijundcrl. -Grietje, Scholtens, Petersb. - Godolevus Bernardus, Kral, id.-Albertha Roemelingh de V nes, id. - Ales, Zimmermann, Pernau. -Dunabiirg, Meijer, Riga. -Rurik Madsen, id. - Joscph, de Bloom, id. - Maria, Jurgenseii, Lihau. - Emilie&apos; Löhnc, Koningsb. - Eendragt, Smit, Wismar. - Louise, S., Bergen.-Anna&apos; Marie, Halversen, Frederikst. - Mercurius, de Groot, id. - Jane Romnev Hölnisdale. &quot; MAASSLUIS, 1 Oct.; Seheveningen, Spaans, de Noordzee. BREMERHA VEN, 1 Oet.; Geertje, Panjer, Hamburg. • HAMBURG, 30 Sept.-, Hilke Alberdiuft, de Vries, Steltin. — 1 Oct • Trientjo, Terfehn, Makkum. NORDEN, 24 Sept.; vr. Elisabeth, Visser, Brake. EMDEN, 24Sept.; Hendrika, Smit, Dantzig. — 26Sept. ; Dankbaarheid. Scholtens, Steenwijk. - Vier Gebroeders, van der Horst Bremen BOLDERA, 22 Sept.-, Wicherdina, Dijken, Kopenhagen. KIFL, 29 Sept.; Catharina Cornelia, Astuling, Petersburg. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 28Sopt.; AnnaGcertruida, vanlugen, Peter.h. n.d. Zaan. - Jonge Albert, Kwint, id.u.d. Weser. - Frederika Tjarks Riga n. Nederland. - Theodor, Fick, Windau n. Dordrecht. ËLSENEUR, 28 Sept.; gepasseerd: Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Kroonstad n. Amst. - Gebroeders Fokkes, Fokkes, id. n. Nederland. —29 Sept.; Grietje Koens, Kuiper, id. n. Engeland. - Alice, Olsen, Soderhaiuu u.&apos; Nieuwe Diep. - Ellida, Hansen, Nieuwe Diep n. Nerva. HOLTENAU, 27 Sept.;gepasseerd: Concordia. Speelman, Dantzig n. Amst. - Harmina, van der Meulen, id. n. id. — 28 Sept.; Jonge Roelof, Douwes, Konmgsb. n. Gron. - Christii.e,oltmans, Dantzig u. Amst. - Hillechiua Margaretha, Joosten, Memel n. Vegesack. — 29 Sept.; Agatha Jacobina, Kramer id. u. id. - Vr. Grietje, Schoon, Koningsb.... Emden. - Anna, Knmnunga, Wismar n. Rolt. LONDEN, 29 Sept.; Sara, Stuit, Trouville. - 30 Sept.; Anna Gesina dc Vries, Petersbur*. - Sippe Visser, de Jong, Worcum. — 1 Oct.; Dina Adriana, Kwint, Amst. Bij DEAL, 30Sept.; Oceaan, van Slooten,Londen n.Montevideo Cornelis Wernard Eduard, Swart, .Cott n. Bat. Bg DOVER, 28 Sept.; Sagua Packet, Sluisman, Amst. n. Havana — 29 Sept.; Ellen Stewart, Shaw, Rott. u. Cardiff. Bg DUNGENESS, 30 Sept; Volant, Suow, Vlissingen n. New-York. - Alida, Vis3or, Amst. n. Soerabaya. Bg GOUDSTAART, 27 Sept.; Diana, Teengs, Shields n. Java. Bij WIGHT, 29 Sept.; Havana Packet, Harken, Amst n. Havana. WICK, 27 «Sept.; Hiilechina, Gruppelaar, Stettin. SUNDERLAND, 28 Sept.; Blackness, Hughes, Nieuwediep. -Belt Painter, id. - Vivid, Bedlinglield, id. - Bella, Straker.id.-Ouadiana, Scott, id. SHIELDS, 29 Sept,; Occan, Storm, Rotterdam. FRASKRBURGH, 29 Sept; Anna &apos;Elisabeth, Dik, Buckie. GIBRALTAR, 21 Sept; Jacoba, Reinders, Livorno, (vertrok den volgenden dag n. Liverpool.) FERN AMBUCK, 5 Sept; Hiilechina Reina, Muntendam, Rio Grande.--10 Sept.; Wendelina Jacoba, Schuur, Hamburg. BAHIA, 5 Sept.; de Valk, Strijbos, Triest MONTEVIDEO, 20 Aog.; Telemachus, Hazewinkel.St.Catalina.— 27 Aug.; Margaretha, de Jonge, Hamburg. — 28 Aug.; in lading: Pleiaden, de Jonge, Havana. • Twee Cornelissen, Potjer, Antw. -Gebroeders Smit, Smit, Rio Grande. BUENOS-AYRES, 13 Aug.; Baudina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Malaga. — 18 Aug.; dc Vrede, Nickus, Londeü. - Perseverance, Jonker, Cardiff. - Maria Anna. de Jong, Patagonié&apos;. RIO JANEIRO, 1 Sept; Cornelia,Wolkers, Londeii.-7 Sept; in lading: Amisa Manu, Peper, Montevideo. - Entreprise, Hut, id.</p>
</text>
