<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL. 2 Oct; Java, Ned. Oorl. Stoomsch., Modderman, Batavia. - Admiraal de Ruiiter, Wittiug, Soerabaija. - Jacoba Gesina, Kramer, Cagliari. - Vanda, Thompson, Leith. - Carl, Wiencke, Newcastle. - Elaitheria, Atrington, id. -Glenaln, Klles, id. - Catharina, Belchani, Sunderl (benevens het schip per tel. gemeld). VLltë. 2 Oct-, George. Rottgers, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Oct; Ary Scheller, S., Havre. - Batavier S. Londen. - Anna, Griend, Newcastle. - Gothenburi», S. Gothenburc BRIELLE, 2 Oct; Zealous, S., Harwich. uo_ucnour0. MAASSLUIS. 2 Oct; Orion, S.. Londen. - Isabella, Harley id. - Katrina de Boer, Waterbnr.,&apos;. Newc. - Isabella Wilson, Mitchell, id. BROUWERSHAVEN,2oct;Sun_ise,l&apos;orbes, Newcastle n Duinkerken HAMHURG,3OSept; Kppo Hendrik, Schut. Fernambuck. CUXHAVEN, 30 Sept; Vier Gebroeders, Emmelkanip.Stottiu.- Minerva, Doyen, Engeland. EMDEN, 27 Sept; Hilke de Vries, Kat, Rott STETTIN, 28 Sept; Karsina Harmina.Waterborg, Hanover. - 29 Sept; Anna Paulowna, S., Amst. BOLDERA, 23 Sept; Drie Gezusters, Boswijk, Aseneur. - Richard Cobden, Stibolt, id. — 24 Sept; Mcinsina, Klontje, de Wesor. - Geertjedina, de Bi er, Elsenenr.- Jantje, Niewoldt, Nederland. — 25 Sept; Oscar, Behrens, id. - Tobina, Wortelboer, Elseneur. LOWESTOFT, 29 Sept; Jane, Romney, Helmsdalen. Rott, (na het stoppen van een lek). HOLYHEAD, 30 Sept; Anna, Collings, Dordrecht FALMOUTH. 30 Sept; Gruno. Klunder, Gothenhurg. DÜNDEE, 30 Sept.; Baudina, Pool, Boness. RUNCORN, 29 Sept.: Diana, Brooks, Dordt CARDIFF, 25 Sept; de Zwaan, Riedijk, V igos. PLYMOUTH. 29 Sept; Bal.noral, S., Rott. n. Bristol. DEAL, 27 Sept; Baron van Heemstra, Nepperus, Newc. n. Bombay NANTES. 28 Sept; Jane Knor, Kerr, Rott. - Eugénie, Penau id LISSABON. 24 Sejit; De Hoop, Ouwehand, Portimao. KONSTANTINOPEL, 13 Sept.; Smart», S., Dordrecht. NEW-YORK, 17 Sept; Emilie, Meijer, Rott. via Baltimore —18 S &gt;i_ • Johanna, Oestmann, Rio Grande. * &apos; SANTOS, 5 Sept.-, Minerva, van Ommeren, &apos;t Kanaal SURINAME, 26 Aug.; Triton, Sandberg, Boston.</p>
</text>
