<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Febr.; Bessie, Murdy, Sunderland. VLIE, 19 Febr.; Magnet, S., Londen. - Themis, Bloos, Stokholm. - Equator, Huisman, Elseneur. - Jonge Evert, Duinker, Bremen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Febr.; Marie Joséphine, Leclercq, Caen.- Albert, S., Huil. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 21 Febr.; Ravcnsbury, S., Harwich. Op de ELVE, 1. Febr.;ldaMaria,Köhler,Rott.-Daniel,Feldmann,id KIEL, 16 Febr.; Petronella, de Vries, Neustadt. ELSENEUR, 15Febr.; gepasseerd: Neptunus, van Gorcnm,Landscrona n. de Noordzee. — 16 Febr.; Albert, Jaski, Riga n. lerland. - Trijntje Gezina, Bos, id. n. Belfast.</p>
	<p>LONDEN, 10 Febr.; Zwerver, Ates, Gron. -In lading.- Sirene, Hermans, Rott.</p>
	<p>Bij DEAL, 19 Febr.; Afien Smit, Boswijk, Delfzijl n. Gloucester. Bij het ZUIDVOORLAND, 19 Febr.; Cornelia Maria, de Joode, Newc. 11. Barcelona.</p>
	<p>Bij DUNGENESS, 18 Febr.; Paul Johan, Kooy, Shields n. Singapore. Bij YARMOUTH (Wight), 18 Febr.; Cornelia Hendrika, Marcussen, Rott. n. Cardiff.</p>
	<p>Bij HARWICH, 19 Febr.; Elisabeth, Weitinga, Petersb. n. Ipswich. LIVERPOOL, 19 Febr.; Pelican, S., Rott. BRISTOL, 19 Febr.; Balmoral, S., Rott. FALMOUTH, 20 Febr.; Roska, Sichtenberg, Antw. n. Rio Janeiro. POOLE, 19 Febr.; Janna Meijer, Datema, Groningen. FOLKESTONE, 19 Febr.; Provincie Drenthe,Westenberg, Groningen. YARMOUTH, 18Febr.;Domina Geertina.Wolters, Leeuwarden. SHIELDS, 19 Febr.; Caduceus, Holton, Nieuwediep. - Arendina, Boerhave, Londen. ANTWERPEN, 21 Febr.; Elisabeth, van Wijk, Riga. - Broedertrouw, de Groot, id. DUINKEEKEN, 19 Febr.; Charlotte, Teepsma, Petersb. HAVRE, 18 Febr.; Gothenburg, S., Rott. __•_._,_ __ LICATA, 28 Jan.-, Aduard, Aldershof, Napels (vertrok 1 Febr.n.Dordt). LISSABON 15 Febr.; Jantina Christina, Beckering, Londen. KONSTANTINOPEL, 3 Febr.; Euphrosyne, Creigh, Odessa n. Amst. BEYRUTH, 27 Jan.; Waterloo, van den Berg, Amst. BUENOS-AYRES, 5 Jan.; Cornelia, Teensma, Amst. — 6 Jan.; Concordia, Brandt, Fernambuck. BOMBAY, 26 Jan.; Machtilda en Simonetha, Maalsteed, Bushire,</p>
</text>
