<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 17 Oct., W. Z. W.; Raphaël, van de Velde Smit, Curacao. - Capella, Christoffer, Baltimore. - Cycloop, S., Middell. Zee. - Gorilla, Zemb, Drammen. — 18 Oct.; Eembrandt, S., Koningsbergen. - Médca, S., Dantzig. VLIE, 16 Oct., W. Z. W.; Eendragt, Dorenbos, Ne wc. - Hendrika, Nepperus, Petersburg. - Venus, Visser, Riga. - Pelikaan, de Jonge, Christiansand, HELLEVOETSLUIS, 17 Oct., W.Z.W.; Seine, S., Bordeaui.- Thomas, Rusher, St. Valéry. - Auspicious, Brown, id. - Wesley, Nuttall, Lond. - Balmoral, S., Bristol. - Brenda, Forcer, Newc- Jane, Mackenley, id. - John Arm, Trueman, id. - Bsther, Greenfield, id. - Expert, Usher, id. - Thomaszis, Mandel, id. - Nymph, Storm, id. - Sarah, Gibbs, Sunderl.—lB Oct.; Countess of Caihhtess, James, Fraserburgh. - Kinghorn, S., Leith.- Halcyon, Byes, Newc. - John Wells, S., Goole. . . BRIELLE, 18 Oct., N.0.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken.- Waterloo, S., Londen. - Sheffield, S., Grimsby. - Zealous, S., Harwieh. _.„_- „ ? „ BROUWERSHAVEN, 17 Oct., W.Z.W.; Cornelis Smit, Weidenaar, Bat. n. Rott.; vertr. 27 Junij. - Medea, v. Teutem, id. n. id.; vertr. 2 Julij. - Martinus &amp; Heiiriette, S., Dordt. n. Londen; heeft dc reis voortgezet. - Cornelis Wernard Eduard, Swart, Rotterdam. rT „ ZIERIKZEE, 16 Qct, W. Z. W.; Paragon, Frankland, Newcastle. — 17 Oct,; John Mijor, Burgess, Abbeville n. Rott. - Piel Castle, Iddon, Cardiff n. Dordt. VLISSINGEN, 17 Oct., Z. W.; Hertha, Warnaar.Bionos- A YT(?S. EMDEN, 14 Oct.; Gelie, Eeminersen, Delfzijl.— 15 Oct., Stad Emden, Katt, Amst. CHRISTIANIA, 16 Oct.; Hanna Christensen,Wathne,An st. FLENSBURG, 14 Oct.; Eta Johanna, Ulrichs, Amst. PILLAU,IS oct.;Rubbens,S.,Amst. _,_&apos;__ MEMEL, 13 Oct.; Meermin, Smith, Leba. — 14 Oct.; Astr. a, Janssen, Antwerpen. , _. SHIELDS, 15 Oct.; Waterwitch, Leadley, Eott. - o Sisters Lowther, Dordt-Oronoco.Vint, Zierikzee. , ALLO A, 15 Oct.; Zwilingen, Nielsen, Schiedam. CLYDE, 14 Oct; Zwerver, Visser, Bahia. CARDIFF, 15 Oct,; Redite, Stuit, Groningen. Bij LIZARD, 14 Oct; Crest of the Wave, Jones, Eott. naar New-York. „ , „ . DARTMOUTH, 15 Oct.; Southampton, fc., Amst.n, Genua, om steenkolen in te nemen»</p>
	<p>St. NAZAIRE, 14 Oct,; Titia Jacobina, Klem, Grangemouth&apos; GIBRALTAR, 4 Oct.;Wilhelmina. v.d.Weijden,Vlaardingen. DARDANELLEN, 5 Oct; Menno, Potjer.üalatzn.Engeland. KONSTANTINOPEL, 7 Oct.; Mary, \ oung, Galatz n. Amst. Northern Light, Oliohant, Sulina n. Rott St. THOMAS, 16 Sept; Curacao, Takes, Amst, 26 dito naar Curacao vertr. BATAVIA, 28 Aug.; Sophia Koningin der Nederlanden, Klein, Shields. — 29 Aug.; Maria Louise Antoinotte, Muysson, China. - Java, Tuk, Birkenhead. — 31 Aug.; Kandanghauer, Zeelt, Texel. —. 1 Sept.; Willemina en Clara, van Herwerden, Amst.&apos;— 3 Sept; Kosmopoliet I, de Groot, Rott. — 4 Sept.; Jason, Rusman.id. SOERABAYA, 27 Ang.; Cornelia Adolflna, de Roever, Shields. — 29 Aug.; Europa, Lupcke, Cardiff. SAMARANG, ... Aug.; Isaac da Costa, Klein, Macao. - St. Jan. Lommerse, Nederland.</p>
	<p>PADANG, 13 Aug.; Elmina, Piera, Amsterdam. AMOY, 12 Aug.; Wijk aan Zee, Mannoury, Singapore.— 23 Aug,; Wilhelmine, Willenbrink, Singapore.&apos; UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 17 Oct. JV.Z.W.; Lion, S., Londen. - Rotterdam, _? Petersb. - Ondine, S., Gothenburg. — 18 Oct.; Eos, Larsen, Livorno. - Hendrik Wergeland, Berkeland. - Genua. - Stad Workum, van &apos;t Veer, Londen. - Joseph Holmes, Groener, Cardiff. - Betsy &amp; Anna, Garrood, Newcastle. - Hawk, 8., Huil. - Whim, Smith, Yarmouth. - Rival, Koning, id. - Emanuel, Bang, Engeland. - Emma Marie, Anton, id. - Flora, Andersen, Fredcnkst- Bayard, Christensen, Tonsberg. - Haabets Anker, Eove, id.- Christian August, Movig, Noorwegen. VLIE, 16 Oct, W. Z. W.; Harmina, Emmelkamp, Norrköp. - Eagmar, Trampe, Christiania. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 17 Oct., W.Z.W.; Troubadour, S., Londen. - Windsor, S., Leith. - San Giovanni Baptiste, Salvatore, Newc, is teruggekomen. - Vlieland, Visser, id. - Lord Eaglan, S., id. - Catharina, Gauthier, id. - Hauchy, Feld, id. - Edward Stodard, Hughes, id. - Thames, Eichardson, Ipswich. - Antina, van Aswegen, Avontuur. — 18 Oct.; Admiraal Ver-Huel, S., Havre. - Feijenoord, S., Lond. - Glencaim, S., Grangemouth. - Albert, S., Énll. - Seahorse, S., id. - Annie, S., Goole. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. - Marie, Biesthorst, Brouwershaven. BRIELLE, 17 Oct, Z. — W.; Leo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwieh.</p>
	<p>CUXHAVEN, 15 Oct; Eendragt, de Boer, Riga. KOPENHAGEN, 14 Oct.; Bouchina, Koster, Oostzee. PILLAU, 14 Oct; Jacob Synes, Nip, Stockton. MEMEL, 13 Oct.; Broedertrouw, Niezen, Bremen. LIVERPOOL, 15 Oct,; Geertruida Janna, van Heijningen, Buenos-Ayres. - Jacoba, de Weerd, Nickerie. PLYMÓUTH, 15 Oct.; Vorwartz, Niemann,Taganr. n. Amst, RYE, 15 Oct.; Intcgrity, Hamden, Rott. LEWTS, 27 Sept.; Cor&apos;delia, Ring, Philadelphia (A) n. Rott. BATAVIA, 2 Sept; L. J. Enthoven, van Gijzelen, Nederl. — 3 Sept,; Kortenaer, Roovers, id. — 4 Sept.; Iduna, du Sar, id. — 5 Sept; Kosmopoliet 11, Bouten, id. SOERABAYA, 27 Aug.; Europa, Pickler, Nederland.</p>
</text>
