<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Mei, O.N. 0.; Malcolm, Partio, Newc. - Jane, Flemming, Sunderland.-Thetis, Nossit.r, Hartlepool.-Couiitess of Zetland, Barnes, Se. ham. - Endeavour. Taylor, id.- AginaUndina, Brouwer, Christiania.- Maria, Bryde, Groenland. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 14 Mei, N.0.; Schoonderloo, v. Leeuwen, Bat., 1. v. Brouwereh. - As.phitritè, Leroux, la Koche Bernard, 1. v. id. - John Snell, Carver, Liverpool. - Meglee, Tiun, Newcastle. - Francois, -. Hitrt, id. - Mars, C-iümings, il, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Maihews and Au», Wil__n, Sunderland.- Albert, S., Huil. - Julia Esche, P.ters.n, Libau, - Martha Theresia, Visser Ezn., Leba. - Bernsrl, Kun _-, Statu o. - Itengkya, de Veer. Col berg. - Anna Eli-abeth, M. =r .ensen, Randers. - Ki_i.t-berg, Larsen. Aarhuui.  L - &gt;n_&gt; BROUWERSHAVEN, 14 Mei;Light &amp; Sign, Robinson, Newc. n. Rott. Hollands Trouw, Brouwer, Eott, n. Bat. BEEMERHAVEN, 12 Mei; Vrouw Martha, Koning, Middlesbro. ■•HAMBURG, 11 Mci; Hilkoa-_ Buhr, Workum..—l2. Mei; Nadir, Kordes, Nederl. - Columbus, de Jong, Newc. —13 Mei; Uranus, Schumacher, Porto Cabello. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 10 Mei; Adelsar, Potje.wijd, Londen n.Petersb.- Reintje, Teensma, id. n. id. - 4 Gebroeders, Blok, Newcastle n. id.- Secundus, de Graaf, Bergenn.i-l. -ClasinaAidiaa, Wirtjes, Amst. n. Oostzee. WARN&apos;E-iUNI. h&apos;, 10 Mei; T.rmonie, de Boer, Dantzig, —11 Mci, Helena, Lafrenz, Antwerpen. SWINEMUNDF, 11 Mei; Rosalie, de Buhr, Amst. -Compact Goede Trouw.de Vries, Brussel. BOLDERA, 10 Mei; Hillecbiena, Gruppelaar, Newc. ELSENEUR, 10 Mei; gepasseerd: Ni-uwendam, de Jonge, Rott. n. id., is van ank r en ketting voorzien.-Fenna,Woudsuia, Beigen n.id. LOI. I &gt;EN, 13 Mei; ban cv, Amos, Dordrecht. Bij DEAL, .. Mei; San José, Goirom, ..., n. Amst. Bij DOVER. 11 Mei; Auua, Korf kor, Amst. n. Konstantinopel , M PORTLAN O, 10 Mei-, Scorell, Kaper, Harlingen n. Plyinouth. Bij RYE, 12 Mei; Elisabeth Austin, Barley, Liverpool n. Gron. Bij WIGHT, .. Mei; Brülant, Mauiice, Puiladelphian. Rott. , TÉIGNMOUi&apos;H, 1. Mei; -Tarinnno. Vl.is. Bradfort. ALLOA. i 0 Mci; Coucordia, Naatje, Leith. FALMOUTH, 12 Mei; Gebroeders-simt, bmit, Porto Allegro n. Amst. GLASGOW, 11 MeijCouutyof Argyle, Ediugton, Rott. CAJ-DIFF, 10 Mei; Heinrich Sorensen, Jacobsen, Rott. SUNDERLAND, il Mei; Jules &amp;Felix, Louis, liromngen.-Delight, Loulon, i&gt;l. — 12 Mei; Northuiüberland, Wilson, Nieuwediep. - Thor, Harsen, Schiedam. SHIELDS, 13 M i; Paul, Knuih, Eott. CAMAUET, 9 M ii; Boune Mère, Moyon, Bayonne n. Eott. NANTES, 11 Mei; Sophie, de Groot, Amst. - Cornelie, v. d. Velde, Liverpool. GIBRALTAR, 3Mei; Orion.S., Palermo-, vertrok n. Amst. — 4 Mei; Anna, Klein, Triest GENUA. 9 Mei: Berenice.S.. Rott. _ «v</p>
</text>
