<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>i^iH.. •■ &apos;j&apos; -Diana, S.» Londen. - Henriette, Wever, Peterhead. - \ &quot;&apos;iHeSfSgftröm, Bjorneborg. - Jeune Charles, Deveaulour, Gothenburg.- t Vljp7™me, Fattevin, id. - Jenny, van Wijk, Avontuur. &gt; ÜRT t&apos;_Mr&apos;Ivny&apos; J°han, Möller, Gothenburg. &apos;lv.ca -iVOETSLUIS,2I Junij; Earl of Auckland, S., Londen. -Nina, ! &apos; e&quot;&quot;1&quot;- i! V Queen&apos; s-&gt; Dundce. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Hebe, Storm, New- . SL&apos;Hsrtl&apos; an(* Shine, Robinson, id. - Van, Thompson, id. -Fairey Queen, J Nu.^01--Seahorse,S.,Hnll.- Walt er Stanhope, S., Goole. -Juno, ,?ncordia,Tan kanten, Archangel. - Friheden, Christopherscn, BlJlgJ- &quot;^nimanuel, Bjönness, Holmstrand. j *»ndofi j &gt;21 Junij; Agility, Knowles, Ncwcastle. - Elizabeth, Yallop, . MAAssr&quot;Caroline- Tilla7, Scarbro&apos;. * Sus &gt;j■ _|*UIS, 21 Jnnij; les Deux Reines, Soulas, Sundërland. - Assi- t,id- &quot;&quot;Vintage, Osborn, id. - MarieEulalie, Curet,id. - Zéno- \ : ?&apos;chi\lo_ ?r:&apos;•*.&apos; Thames, Longstaff, id. - Betsy, Paterson, id. - Harmony, . _*r, id i.l^- - Lyra, Nelson, Newc. - Rambler, Elsdon, id. - Princess, Par- &apos; &quot;&apos;Ktloi. &apos; March&gt; Shields. - William fr John, Nunn, Boness. -El Nat- ] jM,.^ üsen, Riga. - Gefion, Larsen, S&apos;avanger. - Saphir, Aske, Archan«ijï(.i ?&quot;• Uouwcs, Arendsburg. - Dankbaarheid, Dorland, de Noordzee. - V^iaè, Strijbos, id. -Anna, dc Weerd, Avontnur. - Omen, Lindtner,id. _TOT nGEN&gt; 18 Junij; Noord-Holland, Fijn, Buenos-Ayres. LO^EMUNDE, 16 Junij; Hilkelina, Lupke, Newc. &apos; i c&apos;fitia t &apos;19 JunÜ; zeilklaar: Jeannctto, Duiven, Aspinwall.—2o Junij; ] &apos;&quot;&quot;•f. ■ fi- °&apos;la,lna, Drewes, Amst. - Zwaantina Margrietha, de Vries, Avon- ] GRAIïSn^Ea,vcliff&apos;:Dordt- EM°UTH, 19 Junij; Anja Sietsia, Huisman, Koningsb. Ml_Jrj *&quot;EPOOL, 18 Junij; Titia Margaretha, Schaap, Brake. SBRO, 19 Junij; Francois, v. Eyk, Vlissingen. ,lkkien n TH&apos; 19 Jun&apos;Ji Favorite, Bach,Rio Janeiron.Rott. -Grietje, %Tit -&gt;a n- Petersbnrg. _ 9 &quot;funÜ; Jantina Alida, Texer, Charlestown. &quot;«tioi a F&apos;l7 JunÜ! Honigby, van der Valk, Singapore. - Alida, Visser, A)Vrryr es. | ïlbijg pA *7 Junij; Johanna Pctronella, Hildebrand, Elscneur.-Dageraad, Gtßlff ?Y&apos;l9 JnnÜ; Bordeaux, Harrison, Rott. a n TAR&apos;13 Jun&apos;J; zeilkl-: Wilhelmina, v. d. Weyden, Malta, ll.g_T_?A, 10 Junij; zeilkl.: Baudina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Hamburg. j ÜIO t\tPN&gt; 13 Junij; dc Zwaan, Riedijk, Konstantinopel. AIhqy^EIRO, 23 Mei; zeilklaar: Elisabeth, Metus, Kanaal. 1 &gt; -3 April; Cercs, Reiziger, Soerabaya.</p>
</text>
