<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>fiurgcrüjkc jètastö. Van 17 tot en met 33 December ISGS. ; BEVALLEN : S. Rtjueveld , geb. van Evert, D. — S de Bruin , geb. van Tongeren. D. — M. Chandron , geb. Jong , I). — C. de Goede, geb. van Houten . Z. — C. D.&apos;Fortanier, eeb. de Blank , Z. — J. Mensen, geb. vau der Lof. D. —&apos;M. W&quot; Straathof, geb. Velihuyzen , Z. — S. W. Dirks, geb. Vlieland , Z. — E. Ceder-, hout, geb Elkerboul, D. — A. S. F. Oostveen, geb. de Boer. &apos;L. — J C. van Eyk, geb. Canon , D. — E. Martin , geb. Eden, Z. —J.C. Dreef, geb. Fontein, . D. D. tweel. — M.C. Véefkind , geb. Reysl, D. — J.C. Voermans.geb Goddrjn, D. — M. E. Wendel, geb. Veilbriel, D — M.F. T. Kisicrmann , geb. Tethof, Z. — E. van Leeuwen , eeb Kriek . D. — E. Anneeze, geb. Selier, D. — E. Lul,&apos; geb. Kramer. 1). —M. Schols, geb. de Bruin , Z.— H. Azier. geb. van Leeuwen, D. — Jl: W. Sinteur , geb. Oostenbrug , &apos;L. — J.MI. P. Fontein , geb. Pen-&apos; nekamp, Z. — C. Sch&apos;iuien; geb. Dreef. Z. —A.W. M. Noordijk, geb. van Meurs, I). — M. C. Habraken , geb. van der Tuin , Z. — J. G. Verhoef., geb. van de Weer, Z. — M. den Uolder, geb. Veylbrief, Z. — N. «au Evert, geb. Mieremet, Z. —J. E de Nobel, geb. van Bnuren ,D. — J M. Larrewrjn . geb Beun, &apos;L.— H.G. üonner. geb. de Hoogh . D. — G. van Hoiiium . geb.de Haas, D. — C. C. Fontein, geb. Martyn, D. — E. Petiet&apos;,:geb. bourgeois. Z. — J. 11. Boon, geb. Cinjee, Z. — M. D. Mejjers, geb Zwaanenburg , Z. — S. M. Blote, geb. Vreiigdenburg, D. .:.;-.. -...:.; »:• GEHUWD: J. van Leenwpn, jm. en L. Loeps, wede. — C Dirkse, jm en J. Keereweer, jd. — J. J.van Henzen , jm. en E. W. Brnmmelkanip, jd. — A.F. S. van de Laar, welt. geseb. en M. A. Koppeschaar, jd. — P. J. Linschooien, jm. en A. C. Wendel, jd. ■■&gt; JSSI&apos; 1 OVERLEDEN: J. Wallaari, Z., 2} m. — A van den Bosch ,64j. — J. Turenhout, &apos;L., ruim 4m.—H. A. Groeneveld ,49j.— G. C. van der Wiele, Z., 4m. — H. J. Hensen, Z., 1} j — J. M. Piket, Z., 9 j—M.Colla, geb. Pieiers, 67 j. -C. Heeiman, 34 j.— H.A. M.Dercksen, Z. 6&apos;j. —S. M. Voerman, D., 2d. —S. Spierenburg, D., 2} m. — A. W. Vreem , Z., 11 m. —J. J Prevoo, 30j.</p>
</text>
