<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 17 Dcc, W.Z.W.; S. van Heel, van Munchen, Bat.; vertrokken 17 Aug. - fiakon Adelstein, Jensen, Galatz, laatst v. Ramsgate. - Mathias Evert, Andreis, id. -European, Wilson, Ibraila, laatst v. Falm. - Delta, S., Londen. — Gisteren nog: Tynemouth, Dunking, Galatz 1. v. Falm. VLIE, 16 Dcc, W.N. W.; Unie, Posta, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 17 Deo, W. Z. W.; Creswell, Meggison, Rangoon 1. v. Brouwersh. - Lodewijk, Bax, Kust van Afrika 1. v. id. - Traant, Jones, Sombrero. - Zwerver, Höster, Nantes. - Victor Emmeline, Èenouf, id. - Antje, Scholtens, id. - Alida, Nagel, id. - Gloire, Doucet, St. Malo. - Cornely, Bailles, Caen. - Alida Sara, Mooi, id. - Jantje, de Groot, id. - Emilie, Nighebrugge, Newc. - Jason, S., Stettin 1. v. Brouwersh. — Gisteren nog: May &amp; Catharine, Milis, Caen. - Ranger, S., Londen. - Gebroeders, Loodijzen, Petersburg. BROUWERSHAVEN, 17 Dcc, W.N.W.; Chieftain, Jacobsen, Triest n. Rotterdam.</p>
	<p>ZIHtiIKZEE, 15 Dcc, W.; John &amp; Arm, Trueraan, Newcastle. LONDEN, 16 Dcc; BarteldHerman, Meinders, Gron. - Voorwaarts, de Vriosj iii. PO UTLAND, 14 Dcc; Christina, Kamminga, Amst. n. Livorno. Bij DUNGENESS, 13 Dcc; Theod. Josina, Tjakkes, Carthagena naar Bremen</p>
	<p>Bij WIGHT, 14 Dcc; Fop Smit, Metz, Amst. n. Bat. - Verwisseling, Notmeijer, Eott. n. Triest. CO W K 8,15 Dcc; Jupiter, Kiewit, Amst. n. Bat. ÊLYMOUTH, 14 Dcc; Medea, v. Teuten, Rott. n. Bat. RYDE (E. W.), 15 Dcc; Otto, Sap, Schiedam. S HOEK HAM, 14 Dcc; 4 Gebroeders, Bols, Groningen. FALMOUTH, 13 Dcc; Tarquin, Huntley, Rangoon n. Vlaafdingen. - Arabia, Lord. Black River n. Rott.</p>
	<p>GRIMSBY, 14 Dcc; Doris, Hildebrandt, Petersburg. MALTA, 5 Dcc; Levant, Stam, Gibraltar. SIMONSBAAI, 20 Oct.; Elizabeth, Feenstra, Bat. n. Amst. —25 Oct; Hebe, Kiehl, Bat. n. Rott. ¦ TAFELBAAI, 27 Oct.; Wilhelmina #• Eliza, Wiersma, Bat. n. Amst.; heeft de reis voortgezet. St. HELENA, 30 Oct.; Ouderkerk a/d. Amstel, Dingemans, Batavia n. Amst. — 5 Oct.; Joharma Maria, Reid qq., voor wijlen Overgaauw, Bat. n. Rott.— 9 Oct.; Mary Goddard, van Nouhuys, Padang n. Rott.; hebben de reis voortgezet. i HAVANA, 23 Nov., Cuba Packet, Rapp, Amst.</p>
</text>
