<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 5 Mei; Lobelia, Holman, Londen. - Sarah Ellen, Samthill, Newcastle. - Lady Arm, Philips, id. - Libanon, Philips, Seaham.- Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil.- Alfen, Knudsen. Riga.- Christiania, Michielsen, id. - Canada, Abramsen, Sundswall. VLIE, 4 Mei-, Froukje, Koop., Petersburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Mei; Zephyr, S., Londen. - Therese, S., Grangemouth. - Maria Stuart, &amp;., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newcastle. - Jehn fiicks, Pille, id. - Grimaldi, Hill, id. -Lyra, Nelson, id. - Ossena, Hill,id.- Lucy en Paul. Sachs, id. - Geerdina, Nieboer, Petersburg. - Sircruse, James. Heppens. - Tradesman, Press, id. BRIELLE, 5 Mei; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Eavensbury, S., Harwich. CUXHA VEN, 4 Mei; Alida Adriana, Kramer, Aarhuus. - Vrouw Jauna, Oosterhuis, Leer. . FLENSBURG, 30 April: Froukina Hillechina, Oosterhuis, Rusland. SWINEMUNDE, 2 Mei; Stad Workum, Eisinga, Hartlepool. DANTZIG, 2 Mei; Ena, Looze, Termunterzijl. - Egberdina Anna, Schuring. Sonderburg. ._, _« MEMEL, 1 Mei; Anna Elisabeth, Koek, Amst. - Ernestine, Hansen, Nieuwediep. -&apos; Aurora, Schulte, Schiedam. - Urania, Pedersen, Rott. - Elisabeth, de Jonge, Bremer. - Welgelegen, Nieting, Harlingen. SUNDERLAND, 3Mei; Galileï, v. d. Mey, Bat. - Fagel, van Duyn, id DUNDEE, 2 Mei; Stad Enschedé, Veldhuis, Zwolle. LIVERPOOL, 3 Mei; Triton, Schmidt. Bat FALMOUTH 3 Mei; Henriette Elisabeth Susanna, Meijboom, Rott. n. Singapore. - Silentium, Schagen van Leeuwen, id. n Buenos-Ayres. (Beiden na volbragte reparatie). - Erndte. Kloek, New-York n. Amst. • PORTSMOUTH, 3 Mei; Zwijger, Wolthers, Zante n. Gron DOVER 3 Mei; Afien Smit, Èoswïik, Croonstad. - 3 Gezusters, Pluktje, Gron. - Catharina Ricardi, Meijer, id. NANTES, 3 Mei; Engelina Pietronella, Brouwer, Rott. AKYAB, 20 Maart; Honigbij, v. d. Valk, Falmouth. — 21 Maart; President Plate, Julius, id. — 22 Maart; Guurtje &amp; Maria, Flens Jhzn., id. — 26 Maart; Joséphine, Michiels, Coppenolle Jr., id. _K ivievberigten.</p>
</text>
