<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>___-T BINNENGEKOMEN. TEXEL, 6 Ang.; Halfard, Cappelen, Snndswall. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 7 Aug.^evada, Bartlett, Akyab 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Frey, Boe, Catanzaro 1. v. id. - Volunteer, Purvis Newc - Violet, Eichardson, id. - Betsy &amp; Jane, Nicholson, id. LEEE, 31 Julij; Catharina Imkina, Hulsebuss, Amst. — 1 Ang ¦ Heleua Guirsky, Gron. . &apos; BEEMEEHAVEN, 6 Aug.; Dankbaarheid, Scholma, Amst. HAMBUEG, 5 Aug.; Louise, Lamnicrs, Eie Janeiro. — 6 Aug.; Johanna, Meyer, Santos. Bii KOPENHAGEN, 3 Aug.; Geertina, Brouwer, Bergen. DANTZIG, 3 Aug.; Cernelia Jacoba, v. d. Meer, Montrose. BOLDEEA, 31 Julij; Maria, Heven, Antw. — 1 Aug.; Theodor.Marteiis, Duinkerken. - Elisabeth, Pott, Harlingen. HOLTENAU, 4 Aug.; gepasseerd: Dieverdina, de Jonge, Libau n. Schiedam. — 5 Aug.; Thelina, Dekker, Wismar n. Londen. LONDEN, 6 Aug.; Sara, Stuit, Trouville. - de Hoop, Teensma, Worc. DEAL, 5 Aug.; lda Elisabeth, Dooren, Shields n. Batavia, (heeft den loods aau wal gezet.) Bij ALDBOBOUGH, 4 Aug.; Amelia and Anu, Hollmes, Amsterdam n. Bristol. Bij LIZABD, 4 Ang.; Ellen Stewart, , Baltimore n. Botterdam. St. MAWES, 5 Aug.; Julius, Groenewoudt, (om order.) FALMOUTH, 5 Aug.; Sirius, Doewes, Eio Grande. - Elsina Geertruida, Mulder, Tonala n. Dublin. — 6 Aug.; Sara, Smit, Galatz. - Fanny Serines, Kramer, id. ABERDEEN, 3 Aug.; Hoogezand, van Driesten, Hamburg. HULL, 4 Aug.; De Zwerver, Hoster, Christiansand. - Twee Gebroeders, Waterborg, Nerva. HARTLEPOOL. 4 Aug.; Sieka, de Groot, Stockton. NEW-CASTLE, 4 Aug.; Cornelia, Voogd, Harling. - Eendragt, Doornbos, id. SHIELDS, 3 Aug.; Ceres, Boog, Bremerhaven. — 4 Aug.; Helen, Went, Eott. - Catharina, Slik, Groningen. - Orion, Buiten, Zwolle. - Johanna Margaretha, Jansen, Cuxhaven. CAETHAGENA, 2 Aug.; Geertruida, Stuit, Hull. (Vertrok naar Port Mahon, om 10 dagen quarantaine te houden.) GIBGENTI, 28 Julij; de Hnnze, Mulder, Messina. LISSABON, 30 Juin; Courier, Turner (?), Newc. BQSTON (A.), 24 Julij; Bezaleel, Watkius, Botterdam. MABOIM, 11 Junij; Barend, Hamstra, Bio Janeiro. —23 Jung; Thecla Marid. — 28id.</p>
</text>
