<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen. BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 5 Aug.,Z.O.—Ó.;Jan van Brakel, de Roever, Padang, vertr. 18 Maart. - Francina Willemina, van Winkel, Batavia; . vertr. 19 Maart. ¦¦ ChristinaMaria, de Veer, Panjoew., vertr. 11 M__rts - Rom_no C. Cosftlich, Nicol. j, - M&amp;rgareth, b_mbers, Snnderjan 1. - Brilliant, Sanderson, id. - Thomas &amp; Mary, Shntton, id. - Flinn, Young, Seaham. - Alert, S., Huil. - Aainhii trite, Ühlsen, Wyburg. - Frygeoe, Wilkensen, Sundswall. - Ju! dith, Stibolt, Drammen. - Jenny, Aabye, id. — Gisteren nog: i Rembraudt. S., Koningsb. j VLIE, 5 Aug., Z. Z. O; Willem, Kröger, Rostock.- Gertjelina, de Buhr, Kiel, - Q. eï truida, Dekker, Oudsoen. - Willem I, S., i Hamburg, _ï ABLINGEN, 3 Aug.; Niord, Bjornstad, Christiania. - Wil! heimina, Schuring, Frederikstad. - Aldershof, Dijkstra, id. - | Jacob van Cleef, Nienhuis, id. — 4 Aug.; Zenobia, Moss, Yari mouth. - Crescendo, Vos, Riga. HELLEVOEÏSLUIS, 5 Ang., Z,; Pride of Mestley, Man, Runcorn. - Pet, Gatenby, New castl. - Waters, Rayne, id.- Dunnoter Castle, Coorer, id. BRIELLE» 5 Ang.) Z.; Florence, S., Londen. - Avalon, $? Harwich LONDEN, 3 Aug.; John Howard, Crabtree, Rott. Bij DEAL, 3 Aug.; Concordia, Wijgers, Hammerfest n. Venetië. Bïj DUNGENE _ 5. _ Aug.; Meppel, Stikkel van Dam, Bat. n. Amst. ROCHESTER, 2 Aug.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rott. - Brothers Success, Wellard, id. KIRKALDY, 1 Ang.; Maria, Vis.er,Petersb. SUNDEELAND, 3 Aug.; Elisabeth, Wardoux, Nieuwe Diep.- Blackness, Dickinson, id. - Vixen, Crow, id. BHIELDS, 3 Aug.: Arab, Hawksfield, Rott.- Fleur de Marie, Brooks, Zierikzee. - Raven, Fleming, Harlingen. - Anna, jardes, Duinkerken. - Godelevus, de Boer, id, &apos; Dri. Ge_u_te_s, Herbert, id. - Albert Frederik, Rnperts, Huil. - Ceres,Rickless, RqtJ» . LülïH, 3 Aug.; Secundus, de Graaf, Petersburg. DUINKERKEN, 3 Aug.;Tobina, Wortelboer, Petersb. CADIX, 29 Julij; Nieuwe Beerta, Heimer, Vigo. GIBRALTAR,26 Julij; Hellenis,.S., Taganrog; verti&apos;ok n. Rott. - Pet, Reid, Ibraila• vertr; n. Amst;</p>
</text>
