<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>_ TEXEL, 22 Maart; Diana, S., Londen. - Ivanhoe, 8., Leith.- Tulma, Gulicbsen, Drammen. - Scandia, Hiitcbinson, id. - Charles Nordcote, Woldsen, Osterrisöer. - Atalante, Evensen, id. HELVOETSLUIS, 22 Maart; Magnet, S., Londen. - Cosmopolitan, S., d.- Theresc, S., Grangemoutli.- Rhonc, S., Leith 1. v. Brouwersh. - Prins Aliert, Svendsen, Osterrissöer. - Salus, Syvortsen, Lillesulid. - Aleida, Nieliof, Hamburg. BRIELLE, 22 Maart; Colletis, S., Goole. - Norfolk, S., id. - Pacific, S., Harwicb. BROUWERSHAVEN, 22 Maart; President v. Rijckevorsel, Vogelensang, Bat. n. Rott, vertr. 11 Dcc.-RobertusHendrikus, Mulder, Passaroean, B. id.; vertr. 23 Nov. - Johannes, Woltman, Hamburg n. Dordt. LONDEN, 19 Maart; Nooit gedacht, Bakker, Gron. - Hermina Maria, Vegter, id. - Harmina, van der Meulen, id. —20 Maart; Helena, Pieper, Greetzijl. - In lading : Maria, de Jonge,-Elseneur.-Leentjo Dost, Rasker, Amst. - Froukina Hülcchina, Oosterhuis-, id. - Johanna, Oosterkamp , Koningsbergen. ... DEAL, 19 Maart; Terug uit zeo St.George dc la Mina, Blackman, de Kust van Guinea n. Rott. - Bij DUNGENESS-, 17 Maart; Sophia Amalia, Lonrens, Java n. Rott. — 19 Maart; Arnold Banisger; Steenta, Rott.- n.New-York. Bij|SEAFORD, 17 Maart; Jacoba Cornelia, Jansen, Java n. Amst. PLYMOUTH, 19 Maart; Fortuna, Nicman, Ismaïl n. Amst. - Dolpbyn, Hazewinkel, Genua n. Macedonië. — 20 Maart; Onrust, Hoogendorp, Callao n. Rott. SHOREHAM, 19 Maart; Domina Geertina, Woltcrs, Gron. SUNDERLAND, 18 Maart; Alida Elisabeth, Potjewijd, Harlingen.— 19Maart; Sultana, Hollingsbead, Rott. WEYMOUTH, 18 Maart; Dina Adriana, Kwint, Gron. ïkkk^^kr? M,lart! Allegonda Margaretha, Gort, Gron. ™4An™ c®■ x 7 Ma;irt; Nundeep, Woodcock, Roti., met eenige schade. &gt; hHIKLDS, 18 Maart; Zwaluw, de Boer, Gend. - Sikko, Jonker, Harlingen. -^o*«^Ouendag, id; - Annechina Henriëtte, van der Meulen, Elsfleth. - Vier Gebroeders, Balkema, Delfzijl. - Hillechina, Pot, id. - Fernando Tito, Cavaso, Nieuwe Diep. - Ecliptica, Hoeksma, id. - Islander, Hirgsnander, id. - Wright, Buckham, id. - Susan Gray, Manson, id. —19 Maart; Euretta, Weoler, Dordt. - Jonge Albert, Kwint, Gron. - Alida, Valomstra, Londen. - Mary, Stehr, Nieuwe Diep. - Storm King, Mam, id. - Bonafide, Ford, Rott. - Asia, Dyble, id. - John &amp;Isabella,Younger,id. - Prudence, ..., Dordt n. Aberdeen. — 20 Maart; Fury, Denneer, Rott. - Washbum, White, id. - William &amp; Sarah, Calder, id. - Johann Herman, Bornhold, id. ABERDEEN, 17 Maart; Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Amst. BELFAST, 18Maart; Jantina,Doewes,Dordt.-Hydra,Munneke, Amst. CHARLESTON, 17 Maart; Hendrika, Margaretha.Freije, Schiedam. HÜLL, 18 Maart; Margaretha, de Vries, Zwolle. —20 Maart; Alert, S., Amst. - Anna Paulowna, S., Valeneia. - Clemens, de Kloe, Middelburg., LIVERPOOL, 18 Maart; inlading: Marnix, Wassenaar, Amst. LEITH, 19 Maart; Hilkelina, Lupkes, Amst. NEW-CASTLE, 17 &gt;laart; in lading: Voorwaarts, Vink, Lissabon. - Venus, Visser, Dantzig. FOWEY, 19 Maart; Freedom, Ley, Charlestown n. Dordt. SOUTHAMPTON, 20 Maart; Martin Schook, Schut, Groningen. . CLYDE, 20 Maart; Elise, Kooiman, Cuba. JERSEY, 19 Maart; Rollo, Schop, Rotterdam. - Irene, Wirt, id. HARTLEFOOL, 19 Maart; Condor, Bohn, Harlingen. - Leeutje, Hoedemaker, id. - Rheiderland , Brunhs, Vlaardingen. MIDDLESBRO, 20 Maart; Gesina Bernardina, Engelen, Varcl. - Perseverance, Greenock, Rott. HOLYHEAD, 18 Maart; Cbristine Jaequelina, van Noord, Liverpool n. Amst. — 20 Maart; Jantina Margaretha, Peper, Antw. n. Liverpool. DARTMOUTH, 19 Maart; YonngMarquis, Furseman, Amst. n. Ancona. HARWICH, 19 Maart; Visscherij, Fortuin, Londen n. Worcum. NAPELS, 11 Maart; Maria Elise, Hoeken, Cardiff. PALERMO, 6 Maart; Cycloop, S., Messina(ll d°. n. Amst vertrokken.)--10 Maart; Maria Johanna, Stam, Gibraltar. —13 Maart; Helena Jacoba, Bernardns, Cardiff. TRIEST,&apos;IB Maart; Anna, Hovener, Newc. VERA CRUZ, 3 Febr.; Fénélon, Arends, Antw. ST. J AGO DE CUBA, 1 Febr.; Gesina, Meyer, Bremen. M ANZANILLA DE CUBA, 8 Febr.; Elisabeth, Nolthenius, Bremen. Bij ASCENSION, 16 Februarij; Willemina en Clara, Abrahamsz Jr., Batavian. Amst.</p>
	<p>St&apos;. HELENA, 14 Fobr.; Sopbio, Colberg.Bat.n.Amst.-Philipsvan Marnix, van Ruyvcn, Banjoewangie n. Rott.—16 Febr.; Bernard &amp; Agnes, Ordeman, Bat. n. Amst. (hebben dc reis voortgezet). — 19 Febr.; Nordstern, Batjcr, n. AmsMt</p>
</text>
