<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 &amp;»g-, Z.0.-0.N.0.; Irene S., Koningsb.- JiéJes, S„ Dantzig. - 16 Aug.; Suecero, Bozzo, TaganrogTl v. Queeustown. - Zwerver, Bostor, Petersburg. - Bravo, Pagelsen. Kiga - Christiane Lull Svmuswall. - Christine, Abraha.nsen, Ström- &quot;nFwWW-&quot; orneil&apos; Han?en- frederikst. Tl «E,15 Aug., O.; Willem I, S., Hamburg. -16 Aug.; Tiiia I?;Petersb-&quot; Walborg, de Boer, Riga. iiSrr r\vnvrH uiß,s^waantinaHendrika,Vissenga, Riga. HELLEVOEISLUH 15 Aug.. 0.Z.0,, Koophandel Muller, Jiilatjap; l, v. örouwershav.; vertr. 13Maart. - Admiraal Verguel, &amp;, Havre. - Balinoral, S„ Bristol. - John &amp; Elisabeti». l^fTLT ew-,c;-.&quot; K&lt;™»ett, Brendal, Dautzig. - Alexander lil, S., btetbn.-Misschief, Amon. St. Vaierv. -ElisabetJi, Jcnes, Port Madoc-W hif.erav, Bodsou. Barrow.-Kinghoni, S., Leith.- S aanland, 8., Huil. - Venu». Visser, Riga. - Uïania, S., llamb. jjiUELLE, 15 Aug.. Z.; Prias van Oranje, S-. Diu&apos;Mïerlren. — 16 Aug.-. Waterloo. S .Londen.- Zealous, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 16 Aug., 0.Z.0.; Bastiaan Pot, Zetf eler, Passa.rceaag n. Dordrecht; vertrok J« Haart. - JfnensMp, Boherts. Newc. n. id. ? ? VEERE, 12 Aug.; Sarah Rebecca, Hbtb, ftewastle. PILLAU, 13 Aug.-, Vesta, S., Siindca-laiy. BOLDEEA,;; Aug.; Jautiua, de Groath, Antwerpen. KROONSïAD, 10 Aug.; AunaGezina, de Vries. Stettb.- A»na&apos;Hubert; Stetün, — il Aug.; Catliarina, Pik, Üvorao - Oiasiena, Dik, Maiaga. - Wiiheimina, de Groot, Boi&apos;deau», - Anna,Douwes,Eouaan.- Alida Sara, Mooi, Antwerp. - Maria, Pronk, Newc. - Alida, Nagel, Stockholm. AARHUUS, 8 Aug.; Geertruida, Rasker, Amst. BREMERHAVEN. 13 Aug.; Hilke, de Vries, Amst - 2 Vrienden, Kuiper, Hamburg. - Goede Verwachting, Mulder, id. - Pietronella de Boer, Kramer, Memel. SHIELDS, 12 Aug.; Brotherly Love, Moffith, Nieuwe Diep. • Robin Hool.Parrv, Hariingen. . DUNDEE, 12 Aug.; Domina Geertina, Wolters, Komngsb. HOLYHEAD, 13 Aug.; Kelso, Allen, Rott. n. Barrow. PLYMOUTH, 13 Aug.; Hoop, Lukkien, Petersb. FALMOUTH, 14 Aug.-. Haring, Boomgaard, Buenos-Ayres.</p>
</text>
