<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Julij; Magnot, S., Londen. / VLIE, 13 Julij; Ivanhoe, S., Leith. - Salamander, Trampe, Christian&apos;a. . Jonge Rieka, Klein, Fredcrikstad. - Johanna, Oldenburger, id. - Soeblocmsten, Pedersen, id. — 14 Julij; Vrouw Helene, Kraan, Arcndahl. HELVOETSLUIS, 14 Julij; Albatros, S., Liverpool. - Friends, Roberts, Newc. - Eagle, Hawkins, Ipswich. - Margaretha, Hecks, Koningsb. - Helcna, Jiincke, Avontuur. BRIELLE, 14 Julij; Amicitia, S., Bergen. MAASSLUIS, 14 Julij; Charlotte Louise Wilhelmina, Funder, Newc. - Billy Roberts, id. - Bordeaux, Harrison, id. - Ellida, Larsen, id. - Palladium, Gray, id. - J oseph &amp; Elizabeth, Milburn, id. - Karen, Andersen, id. - Dorothea, Brinck, id. - Fides, Nissen, Firth of Forth. - Pauline, Broek, id. - Balder, Istrig, Hartlepool. - Bellona, Lindemann, id. - Mariane, Niel-Ben, id. - Vixcn, Horsby, Sunderland. - Waterloo, Hovington, Whitby. - Caroline Marie, Rode, Schotland. - Fenna Johanna, Andresen, Avontuur. - Piemora, Codet, id. BREMERHAVEN, 13 Julij; Albert, Jaski, Petersb. - Wilhelmina, Oortgieze, Riga. - Amalia, Poppinga, Burnt Island. - Jantina, Veen, Amst. LONDEN, 12 Julij; zeilkl.: Weltevreden, Kieft, Petersb. — 13 Julij ; Sophia, de Haan, Hamburg. LIVERPOOL, 12 Julij; zeilkl.: Heeronveen, Prins, Petersburg. - Huis Garreweer, Vink, id. - Gebina, Loman, id. CARDIFF, 11 Julij; Johanna Maria Christina, Gorter, Kaap de Goede Hoop. YARMOUTH, 11 Julij; Dieverdina Alida Pot, Meijering, Elseneur, SUNDERLAND, 11 Julij; William, Scott,Nieuwediep. HARTLEPOOL, 12 Julij; Vredelust, Kok, Sleeswijk. FALMOUTH, 12 Julij; Jeltina, Scherpbier, Maratbonisi n. Londen. DEAL, 12 Julij; Jacoba, Reinders, Londen n. Montevideo. - Zeenymph, Schipper, id. n. Batavia. GENT, 12 Julij; Amicitia, Heyn, Avontuur. CAEN, 8 Julij; Cate and Jane, Sewel, Schiedam. PAIMBOEUF, 11 Julij; Sarcelle, Lancelot, Kott. REDON, 5 Julij; Aimable Prudence, Baron, Rott. — 9 Julij; Caroline, Liron, id. VENETIË, 8 Juiij; Jantina Alida, Pybes, Falmouth. NE V7-YOKK, 30 Junij. Zeilkl.: Don Jua&gt;i, Linda Rott.</p>
</text>
