<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN. Scheepstijdingen.</title>
	<p>vRIO GRANDE 15 Febr.}_éda, Muilen Fernambuek, 19 maxi a. Liv-rjwl rêrtr.</p>
	<p>SINGAPORE, 19 Maart; Stad Assen, Boer, Bombay. — 21 Maart; Jacob, Muller Drenth, Amst. — 27 Maart; Katharina Maria, Brandts, id.</p>
	<p>SAMARANG. 1 Maart-, Honingby, v. d. Valk, Newc. STRAAT SUNDA, 10Maart; Jacoba,Rijken, Bat. n. Nederl. 12 Maart; Clio, Kuardi Bek qq., Bat. n. Amst. — 21 Maart; Jupiter, Kiewit, Amst. n. Bat. UITGEZEILD.</p>
	<p>RANDERS, 25 April; Castor, Dik, doorwegen. KOPENHAGEN, 30 April; Mej.Pietronella Knijpenga, Klöfkorn, Castrup. HARTLEPOOL, 30 April; Annachiena Hannina, Stuitvoet, Hoekzijl. SHIELDS, 1 Mei; Goudvisch, Douwes, Triest.- Befje Pronk, Vos, Barcelona. - Lammechiena, Duit, Petersb. - Martha, Postema, Nerva. - Alberdina, Selierpbier, Memel. - Harberdina, Bakker, Kopenhagen. - Neptunus, Schuurman, Groningen. HAVRE, 1 Mei; Titia Jacobina, Klein, Petersburg. LISSABON, 27 April; de Hoop, Manneken, Faro. RIO-J AN EIRÜ, 31 Maart; Sqphia Constantia, Roorda, Ba-, hia. — 3 April; de Waarden, Agtien, id. MONTEVIDEO, 24 Maart; Regnera, Wortelboer, Itapiru. BUENOS-AYRES, 13 Maart; Columbus, Zomerdijk, Paysandu. — 16 Maart; jacoba, Eeinders, Engeland. — 17 Maart; Niphon, Vuyk, Montevileo. — 20 Maart; Anna Elisabeth, Schuur, Antw. — 21 Maart; Dirk Hendrik, Prins, id. - Jantina Maria, Ksijser, id. — 25 Maart; Adriana Johanna, de Vries, Antw. - Maria Cornelia, Roos, id. - Junior, Tunteler Jr., id. SINGAPORE, 23 Maart; Estafette, Oepkes, Hongkong. - Isaac da Costa, Klein, id. — 25Maart; Ellina, Lammerts, Bassein. — 27 Maart -, Fredrik Hendrik, van Ameyden van Duym, Maulmain. - Gijsbert Karel Graaf van Hoogendorp, Fabritius, Bremen.</p>
	<p>PROBOLINGO, 3 Maart; Imperator Alexander 11, Wahlroos, Nederland. PASSAROEANG, 12 Maart; Fagel, Smit, Nederland. — 16 Maart; Bastiaan Pot, Zetteler, id. SOERABAYA, 10 Maart; Sydpolen, Silversparre, Nederl. - Cornelia Hendrika, van IJsendoorn, id. — 14 Maart; Vice-Admiraal Mav. Outshoorn de Groot Stift, y, id. HONGKONG, 13Maart-, Widielmina,Tönjes, Chewf.o.</p>
</text>
