<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 30 Aug.; Geerdina Afina, Pomper, Galatz. - Maria, van Duyvenbooden, St. Übes, met gebroken zeilboom.- Lion, S., Londen- Dragon, S., Newc. - Hawk, S., Hull. - Gebr. Jansen, Andersen, Sundswall. - Caradoc, S., Dantzig. - Sophie, Sörensen, Sannesund. - Omen, Hansen, Frederikstad, (benevens de schepen per telegr. gemeld). VLIE, 29 Aug.; Neptun, de Haan, Frederikstad. - Maria N&quot;. 3(Haringbuis), Bootsman, Noordzee. - Janna Margaretha N°. 10, Visser, id.* Frith Jofna, ten Ham Dam, Groningen. — 30 Aug.; Maria, Pronk, Nerva. TERMUNTERZYL, 28 Aug.; Antina, Busscher, Hanover. - Cretin», Busscher, id., zijn 29 Augustus derwaarts teruggekeerd. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Aug.; Wilhelmina, Braver, Rangoon, 1. V- Brouwershaven. - Barend, Hoeksema, Lissabon. - Vereeniging, van Duffelen, St. Übes. - Aurora, S., Londen. - John &amp; Charles, Charltoii, Rochester. - Acadia, Boer, Rnncdrn. - Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Friends, Wells, id. - Leo, Benson, id. - Harriet, S., Middlesbro. * William Coleman, S., Goole. - Bradford, S., Grirasby. - Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg 1. v. Brouwershaven.</p>
	<p>ZIERIKZEE, 29 Aug.; Polly, Hirt, Liverpool. BROUWERSHAVEN, 30 Aug.; Elisabeth, Tryselius, Soerabaya n. Rott., vertr. 22 April, (benevens het schip per telegr. gemeld.) LEER, 23 Aug.-, Catharina Elisabeth, Geertsema, Termunterzijl. * HAMBURG, 28 Aug.; Waterhen,Coulson, New-York.—29 Ang.-,Oaterina, Claussen, Antwerpen. Albea.Weers, Makkum. - 2Gebrüder, Hieke», id. - Persia, Ahreus, Rott. - Ommelanden. Wieringa, Middlesbro. GOTHENBURG, 22 Aug.; Weldaad, Voogd, Alloa. - Vr. Clara, Post, Grangemouth. By KOPENHAGEN, 28 iug.; Gouv. van Ewy&apos;ck, S., Amst. n.Wismar. DANTZIG, 26 Aug.; Juliane Renate, S., Amst. ELSENEUR, 26 Aug.; gepasseerd : Medea, S., Petersb. naar Amst. — 27 Aug.; Caradoc, S., Dantzig n. id. - Urania, S., Amst. n. Petersb. - Verwisseling, Koster, id. n. Koningsb. TON NINGEN, 25 Aug.; gepasseerd: Andreas en Maria, Slik, Dantz. n. Londen. - Roelfina Johanna, Drewes, id. n. Amst. - S»eka,Venema, id. n. Emden. - 3 Schwestern, Klof kom, Straalsund n. Rott. - Eendragt, Boer, Leba n. Varel. - Tjakina de Boer. Dost, Newc. n. Rendsburg. — 26 Aug»; Christina, Brun, Dautzig. n. Amst. - Jacoba Margina, Kuil, Bremen naat Kopenh. - Margaretha Meijering, de Jonge, Hamb. n. Stettin. - Roellina, Prins, Bremen n. id.— 27 Aug.; 2 Gebrüder, Doyen, Kiel n. Amst..- HilK** de Vries, Katt, Wismar n. Rott. - Catharina Alida, Pronk, Dantzig naar Delfzijl. SWINEMUNDE, 27 Aug.Jßotterdam, S., Rott. LONDEN, 29 Aug.-, Anna Margaretha, Veldhuis, Gron. - Twee Broeders, Kempema, Worcum. - Comelia, de Jonge, id. By DEAL, 28 Aug.; Wildeman, Driest, Londen naar Buenos-Ayres. &apos; Eliza, Lange, Amst. n. Liverpool. FALMOUTH, 29 Aug.; Gooregt, Hughes, Buenos-Ayres. ABERDEEN, 27 Aug.; Phoenix, Veldhuis, Riga. STUDLANDBAY, 27 Aug.; Espérauce, Dik, Amst. n. Beyruth. FO WE V, 28 Aug.; Clown, Hill, Runcorn n. Zierikzee. PORTLAND, 28 Aug.; Johanna, Brouwer, Weymouth. SEAHAM, 27 Aug.; Robert Stride, Colun, Rott. SHOREHAM, 28 Aug.; Gazelle, Seagers, Rott. WICK, 23 Aug.; Seabell, Speed, Rott. HULL, 28 Aug.; Swanland, S., Amst. HARTLEPOUL, 27 Aug.; Helena, de Vries, Lynn. - Nooit Gedacht, Bakker, Dieppe. II&apos;SWICII, 28 Aug.; Engle, Hawkins, Rotterdam. SHIELDS, 28 Aug.; Alma, Gay, Rotterdam. - Francois, Hart, Dordt. CARDIFF, 24 Aug; de Zaan, Riedijk, Middelburg. NEWHAVEN, 28 Aug.; Integrity. Hamden, Rott. NEWCASTLE,2B Aug.; in lading: Diana,Teengs.Tagal en Pckalongon- St, N AZAIRE, 28 Aug.; Alexandre, Ezano, Amst. BORDEAUX, 28 Aug.; Louise, Hildebraudt, Stettin. GENUA, 25 Aug.; Irene, S., Amst. L AGUAYRA, 31 Julij; Caspar da Robles, van Slooten, Hamburg. WHAMPOA, 9 Elisabeth, de Boer,</p>
</text>
