<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Dec,Z.Z.O.-Z.Z.W.; Stad Appingadam, Kaiser, Nicolajeff.- Vriesland, Boontje, Londen. -Ranger, S., id. - I vanhoe, S., Leith.- FatLter Mathew, Adamson, Newc. 1. v. Cuxhaven. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. VLIE, 29 Nov., 0.Z.0.; Johanna. Oïdenburger, Christiania. —30 Nov.; Liou, S., Londen. —1 Dcc; Anna Tisiena, Kuipers, Neweastle.-European, S., Huil. - Jonge Pieter, Colle, Memel. - Eta Johanna, Groenewold, Randers. - Concordia, Speelman, Bremen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Dee. O. Z. O.; Violet, White, Cephalonia. - Martha &amp; Ellen, Crabtree, Boulogne. - Caroline, Henrichsen, id. - Meteor, S., Dublin. - Margaretha, Kappen, Libau. BRIELLE. 2 Dcc; Orion, S., Londen. MAASSLUIS, 2 Dec-, Orion, S., Londen. HAMBURG, 1 Dcc; Pollux, S.. Rott. BREMERHAVEN, 1 Dec.; Union, Hazewinkel, Petersburg. EMDEN, 27 Nov.; Petronella, Kort, Amst.- Hausina, Obes, Hoogezand.- Anna, Obes, id. - Hendrika, Jansen, Delfzijl. — 28 Nov.; Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge, Altona. - Sjouke, Voss, Amst. — 30 Nov.; Anna Hendrika, Dallinga, Hamburg. TONNINGEN,29Nov.; gepasseerd: Bona Römelingh, Visser, Horsens n. Amst. LONDEN, 1 Dcc; Jantje Tiddens, Hazewinkel, Nerva.-Cornelia, de Jong, Worcum. - Twee Broeders, Kempema, id.- Drie Broeders, v. &apos;t Veer, jd. - Celestine, Hill. Dordrecht. - Emma &amp; Èliza , Rott. BÜ NEWHAVEN, 30 Nov.; Nederland &amp; Oranje, Muller, Rott. n. Bat. R((CHESTER, 30 Nov.; John &amp; Charles, Carlton, Rott. SHOREHAM,3ONov-, Gazelle, Seagers,Rott. EXMOUTH. 29 Nov.; Margrietha Hendrika. de Boer, Harlingen. FALMOUTH, 1 Dec-, Harkaway, Wills, Rott, n. St. Michaels. IPSWICH. 30 Nov.; Eagle, Hawkins, Dordt. - Thames, Cracknell, id. HARWICH, 30 Nov.; Zwaantje, Groonendaal, Malmoe. SHIELDS. 30 Nov.; Riral, Koning. Grimsby. CARDIFF, 2 Dec;Zuid-Holland, Ureuning. Vlissingen. MALTA, 24 Nov.; Conrier, van Vliet, Vlaardingen. ANCONA, 24 Nov.; Confiance, Brongers, Amst. — 26 Nov.; Twee Goausters. Koning, id. - Cornelia, Vorenkainp, id. NEW-YORK 18Nov.-,Arnoldßöninger, Steenken, Rott. PHILAOELPHIA (A.), 26 Nov.; Sirene, Hermanns, Rott. NEW-ORLEANS, 22 Nov.; Cornelia en Geertrnida, Wielema, Rio- Janeiro.</p>
</text>
