<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 25 Sept., N.N.W.—N.; Zephyr, S., Londen. -Canadaigua, Eng. oorlog-stooraschip, comm. J.H. Strong, Kopenhagen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 25 Sept., W.; Neptun, Solfart, Nicolajeff 1. v. Brouwersh. - Derwent, Wnitho, Taganrog 1. v. id. - Elisabeth Brodie, Brodie, Marian, 1. v. id. - Thetis, Marck, Newcastle. BRIELLE, 25 Sept., N.W.; Ravensbury, S., Harwich. VLISSINGEN, 25 Sept., N.W.; Galileï, v.d.Meij, Bat., 1. v. de Tafel- Baai n. Amst., als bijlegger, met schade aan het galjoen enz. LEER, 19 Sept.; Geertina Kramer, Folkerts, Amst. HAMBURG, 23 Sept.; Weltevreden, Kieft, Christiania. - Amalina, Gauraud, Rott. — 24 Sept.; Willem I, S., Amst. - Willem, Króger, id. - Jantina Margaretha, Meijer, Livorno. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 22 Sept.; Valkyrien, Bang, Petersb. n. Amst. DANTZIG, 22 Sept; Sieka, Donwes, Dysart, MEMEL, 20 Sept.; Catharina, Bekkering, Koningsb.-Jantje, Rasker,id. KROONSTAD, 24 Sept.; Harlingen, Ploeg, Newc. ELSENEUR, 23 Sept.; Jacoba Cornelia, Fokkes, Petersb. n. de Maas. RENDSBURG, 20 Sept.; 4 Gebroeders, Muntendam, Petersburg n. Amst. —21 Sept; Ebeliena, Hoekstra, Amst. n. Aalborg. - Christina de Vries, v.d. Werp, Dantzig n. Groningen. — 22 Sept.; Anna, Kamminga, Hamburg n. Stettin. BAN ANA, 26 Julij; Machtilda S- Simonette, Remmers, Rott. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 25 Sept,, N.N.W.—N.; Willem de Derde, S., Middell. Zee. - Olga, S., Londeif. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. VLIE, 23 Sept., W.N.W.. Antje Visser, de Jonge, Riga. -Alku, Sjóberg, Borga. - Christina, Staal, Frederikst. - Ariel, Ihlen, id. - Oscar, Cornehssen. Drammen. - Christiane, Haagensen, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 25 Sept., W.; Citizen, S., Londen. - Queen, S., Dundee. - Windsor, S., Leith. - Chevy Chaso, S., Newc. - Seahorse, fe., John Wells, S„ Göole. - Lollige, S., Bergen.</p>
	<p>BRIELLE, 25 Sen.; N.W.;Waterloo, S„ Londen.- Sheffield, S.,Grimsby. BREMERHAVEN, 22 Sept.; Dirkje, Poort, Amst. - Johanna Carolina, deJßoer, Groningen. KOPENHAGEN, 21 Sept.; Jonge Andries, Steffens, Oostzee. - Margaretha, Kappen, id. PILLAU, 22 Sept.; Hendrika Margaretha, Freije, Peterhead. MEMEL, 20 Sept.; Catharina, de Vries, Schiedam. — 21 Sept.; Aikea, Dijk, Harlingen. - Herstelling, Panjer, Bremen. BOLDERA, 17 Sept.; Zwaluw, Visser, Nederland. — 20 Sept.-,lda, v. d. Molen, Elseneur. - Jacob, Freije, id. - Catharina Cornelia, Aikema, id. - Lucas Wildervank, Riks, id.</p>
</text>
