<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 16 Sept., W.—N.W.; European, S., Huil. - Kosmopoliet, Klein, Archangel. - Gezina, Ei, Petersburg. - Beurs v. Amsterdam, Toffee, Riga. - Amicitia, Brons, id. - Empress, Haraldsen, Sundswall. - Rea, Naess. id. - Orienten, Pedersen, Hudickswall. - Grevende Karen Wedel, Roed, id, - Wilhelniina, Svendsen. Nyekjöbing. - Symmetry, Larsen, Frederikstad. - Europa, Lorentsen, Drammen. — Gisteren nog: Christiana, Halforsen, Söderbamn. - Vesta, S., Dantzig. VLIE. 15 Sept., N.N.W.;Leentje, Hoedemaker, Riga.-Aurora, Heeren, id. - Vrouw Martha, Ebes Jr., Sundswall. - Soranus, Poelman, Dantzig. - Wilhelniina, Schuring, Frederikstad. - Jacob van Cleef, Nienhnis, id.- Concordia, Hendriksen, Oudsoen.--16 Sept.; Amsterdam, S-, Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Sept.; Lodewijk, Bax, Banana. - Brother&apos;s Success, Wellard, Rochester. - Balmoral, S., Bristol.- Swan, Annison, Newc, 1. v. Brouw. rsh. - Aurora, van Dijk, Petersburg. - Stella Maria, Harding, id.- Anna Elisabeth, Hansen, id. - Zwaantje Dost, Heijenga, id. - J. H. van Gent, Jensen. Liban. - Jacoba Alida, v. d. Laan, Pitea. - Hermina, de Vos, Tornea. - Proteus, Zeven, Sundswall. - Vlieland, Visser, Dantzig. - Maria, Kroon, Bergen. BRIELLE, 16 Sept., N. W.; Florence, S., Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 16 Sept., W.; Dawn, Harrison, Newcastle n. Dordrecht.</p>
	<p>SWlNEMUNDE,!OSept.;FennaScheltens,Drenth,Heppens. PILLAU, 14 Sept., Z. 0.; Azinga, Astra, Newc. LONDEN, 14 Sept.; Johanna, Wilkens, Archangel. - Anna Geertruida ,id. Bij LIZARD, 11 Sept.; Ellina, Lammerts, Bassein n. Bremen. Bij PORTLAND, .. Sept.; Geerdina, Nieboer, Marseille n. Wells.</p>
	<p>Bij SEAFORD, 12 Sept.; Elisabeth, Nepperus, Bordeaux n, Drontheim.</p>
	<p>PORTSMOUTH, 14 Sept.; Stad Apingedam, Kaiser, Rosario (1. v. Falmouth) n. Ipswicn. ROCHEBTER, 14 Sept.; Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Gron. LOWESTOFT, 13 Sept.;Raisbeck, Bernard, Rott. n. Newc. GLASGOW, 14 Sept.; County of Bute, Walker, Bott. HOLYHEAD, 14 Sept.; Bessie Whiraery, Hudgson, Rott. n. Barron.</p>
	<p>HARTLEPOOL, 13 Sept.; Anna, Knhlsen, Amst.-Hendrika, SUNDERLAND, 13 Sept.; Prince Alfred, Robinson, Amst. - Hero, Burlington, Nieuwediep. SHIELDS, 13 Sept.; Vittoria Alfieri, Castello, Amst.- Palladium, Stamp, Dordt. - Adriana Francisca, van Eyk, id. - Geertruida, Stuit, Hamburg. ANCONA, 31 Aug.; Oceaan, Post, Vlaardingen. LICATA, 11 Aug.; Reine Valois, Vonder, Venetië, (vertrok 13 dito n. Rotterdam). KONSTANTINOPEL, 14 Sept.; J. F. Gates, Parrot, Ibraila, (vertrok n. Amsterdam).</p>
</text>
