<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL,3 April,N.N. W. — W.N. W.; Hollandia, de Jong, Banjoewangie, vertr. 25 Nov. - Eendragt de Boer, Cette. - European, S., Huil.- Lympha, Allurn, Drammen. - Lyna, Knudsen, id. - Drammen, Frost, id. - Elisabeth Catharina, Heegaard, id. VLIE, 2 April, W. N. W-; Nidaros, Pedersen, Frederiksta,.. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 3 April, W. Z. W.; Johanna Hoydorn 11, Köller, Laguna. --Fortuna, Busch Keiser, New-York. - Antunma, Leo, Nowport. - Egret, 8., Liverpool. - Martha, Buss, Hartlepool. - Eaglo, Hawskins, lpswich. - Oandace, Michelsen, Genetehek 1. v. Brouwershaven. BRIELLE, 3 April, Z. W,: Ravensbury, S., Harwich. LEEK, 30 Maart; Jonge Maria, Boetje, Dokkum. — 31 Maart; Maria, ilelmers. Hartlepool. - Remgien, Beorthuis, Weener. BREMER HA VEN, 31 Maart; Anke, Bleeker, Amst. n. Rostock. HAMBURG, 1 April; Wilhelmina, Meijer, Amst. CUXHAVEN, 2 April-J. ieuwerdina, de Jonge, B. Eiland n. Rendsburg. GOTHENBURG, 30 Maart; Médéa, S„ Amst. SWINEMUNDE, 31 Maart; Citadel, S., Rott. ELSENEUR, 31 Maart; gepasseerd: Morgenster, van Dijk, LissaDon n. Petersb; - Anna Paulowna, S., Amst. n. Koningsb.-3 Gezusters,Pluktje, Gron. u. Koningsb. —1 April; Frits en Betsy, Stnut, Harlingen n. Memel. - Harmonie, de Weerd,id.n.Dantzig.-Hazard,Ketelaar,Gooien. ld.-Hermanna, Veling, Hnll. RENDSBURG, 23 Maart; gepasseerd: Jantina Alida, Texer, Hamburg n. Friedericia. - Froukje Dijkstra, Hamstra, id. n. Horsens. - Pietrondia, de &apos;V ries, Breinen n. Köpenliagen. - 2 Gebriider,Ulriclis, Amst. n. Stettin.- Margaretha Hillechiena, Pokeldcr, Harburg n. Oostzee. — 29 Maart; Elisabeth, Selioon, Amst. n. Flensburg.- Catharina Alida, Pronk, Bremen.ii. Kopenhagen. - Telina, Dekker, Firth of Forth. —30 Maart; Ülyrnpia, Eayen, Rott. n. Stettin. - Compagnie, Net, Memel n. Breinen. LONDEN, 2 April; Germania, Tielke, New-York. - Bij DEAL; 2 April; Cornelia eu Geertruida, Wiëlerna,&quot; New-Orleans n. Bremen. v Bij DÜNGENESS^I MaartjJohanna» Verduin.Newcastle n.Smgapore. HULL, I April; Lubbcgina, de Jonge, Leuven. SHIELDS, 1 April; Helena, Anderson, Rott. SEVILLE,2OMaart; Jaoobina, ...,Cadix. LISSABON, 27 Maart; Oostwolde, de Boer, Newcastle. — 23 Maart; Laure ns, van Noord, Newc. PIRAEÜS, 22 Maart; Britannia, Valk, Antwerpen. PORT LOUIS, 23 Maart; Myosolis, Cassard, Redon (vertrok 28 dito n.</p>
	<p>Amst.).</p>
</text>
