<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 4 Aug.; Eyr, Christensen, Frederikstad. — 5 Aug.; Java Packet, Crap Hellingman, Bat., vertr. 30 Maart. - Ange Gardien, Leven, Nantes. - Frans Picard, Alm, Vannes. - Kathloen, Chappel, Liverpool. - Hart, Cloak, Newc. - Kongs Verre, Walloe, Riga. - Resolute, S., Noordzee (benevens het schip per telegraaf gemeld). VLIE, 5 Aug.; Urania, S., Stettin. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Aug.; Argo, Ankringa, Padang, 1. v. Brouwersh., vertr. 6 April. - Médéa, v. Teuteni, Banjoew., 1. v. id., vertr.7 April.- Palma, Steenhagen, Akyab, 1. v. id. - Lonise Victorine, Bréhaut, JNantes. - John &amp; Charles, Gilbert, Rochester. - Balmoral, S., Cardiff. - Alarm, Vince, Boness. - Elizabeth, Yallop, Newc. - Waterwitch, Earl, id. - Thomarine, Mannall, id. BROUWERSHAVEN, 5 Aug.; Diana, Teengs, Akyab n. Rott. (Benevens de schepen per telegram gemeld.) EMDEN, 2 Aug.; de Hoop, Drewes, Groningen. HAMBURG, 3 Aug.; Annechina. Smit, Messina. - de Waarden, Agtien, Triest. — 4 Aug.; Gesina, Boeker, Makkum. - Siefer, Reents, Worcnm. CUXHAVEN,.4 Aug.; Amsterdam, S., Amst. - Hammonia, S , Rott. FLENSBURG, 1 Aug.; Alida Sara, Mooi, Faversham. DANTZIG, 2 Aug.; Vesta, S., Amst. STOCKHOLM, 31 Julij; Alliance, Haak, Triest. GOTHENBURG, 31 Julij; Twee Vrienden, Ruige, Dundee. • Carrie Winck, Barrett, Harlingen. TROMSOE, 16 Julij; Thetis, Buggus, Vlaardingen. KOPENHAGEN, 3 Aug.: Jonge Albert, Kwint, Newc. AARHUUS, 26 Julij; Twee Gebroeders,... , Kendsbnrg. - Margaretha Meijering, de Jonge, Doekum. ELSENEUR, 2 Aug.; gepasseerd: Thetis, Bakker, Petersburg n. Engeland. - Catharina, Slinger, id. n. de Weser. - Anna Paulowna, S., Kroonstad n. Bremen. RENDSBURG, 1 Aug.; gepasseerd: Jantina Alida, Texer, Stolpemunde n. Newcastle. — 3 Aug.; Catharina Ricardi, Meijer, Bandholm n. Amst. ARCHANGEL, 26 Julij; Susanna, Middel, Drontheim. LONDEN, 4 Aug.; Dina Adriana, Kwint, Helsingborg. - Vr. Anna, Croes, Worcitm. - Visscherij, Fortuin, id. MARYPORT, 3 Aug.; Egbertus, Schrik, Swansea. HARTLEPOOL, 3 Aug.; Reflect, Plumpet, Amst. DUNDEE, 2 Aug.; Johanna Maria, Fenenga, Petersb. SHJIELDS, 13 Aug.; Jacoba Johanna, van der Meulen, Londen. - Stad Goor, Veldhuis, id. - Lambertha, Hitman, Colchester. - Zwijger, Koens, Leith. - Adriana Francisca, van Eyk, Vlissingen. St. VALERY, 27 Aug.; Wilhelmina Catharina, Kiel, Nerva. PAIMBOEÜF, 2 Aug.; Cornelia, Boon, Stettin. CAMARET, 29 Julij; Eugène Felix, Cassand, Nantes n. Rott. - 31 Julij; Fleury, Thébaut, Roche Bernard n. Schiedam. GIBRALTAR, 25 Julij; Jacoba Gesina, Kramer, Alexandrie (vertrok n. Londen). RIO GRANDE, 10 Junij; Consul Voelkel, Bakker, Lissabon. —15 Junij; Marehina, Knijper, Triest. MONTEVIDEO, 19 Junij; Catharina, Visman, Amst. —23 Junij; Favor, Sannes, id. BUENOS AYRES, 26 Junij; In lading: Fortuna, de Groot, Antw. FERNAMBUCK, 6 Julij; Koster, Bohn, Hamburg. SANTOS, voor 4 Julij; Nannette, Kampen, Rio Janeiro. BUNDER ABBAS (golf van Perzie), 12 Junij; Hoek van Holland, Bakker, Soerabaya, (alles wel aan boord).</p>
</text>
