<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 28 Sopt.; Lion , S., Londen. - Vesta, S. Koningsbergen. - Rerabrandt, S., Kroonstad. VLIE, 27 Sept.; Familien, Thomsen, Osterrisoer. - Hvalen, Anderson id HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Sept; Lordßaglan, S„ Newcastle. — 28S.pt&apos;. Maria, Kilean, New York, 1. v. Zierikzee. - Zophyr, S., Lorden. BROUWERSHAVEN, 28 Sept.; Sara, S., Londen. - Médéa, v. Teutem Rott. n. Bat. &apos; HAMBURG, 2G Sept.; Jonge Barend, Prins, T.rmunterzijl. BERGEN, 9 Sept.; Grictina, Sprik, Petersb. - Concordia, S., Bilbao. SARPSBÖRG, 2 Sepfc; Henriëtte Susanna, van Wijngaarden, Dortlrecht, 11 dito weJer derwaarts uitgeklaard. — 7 Sept.; Emilie, Stangebye, Nederl.--8 Sept.; Maria, Bryde, Purmerende, 22 dito n. Nederland uitgeklaard, — 13 Sept., Freia, Uilen, Amst. -Lizza, Hanzen, Nieuwediep. — 16 Sept.; Odin Catharina, Movig, Dordt. —20 Sept.; Elida, Jacobsen, Nederland. STETTIN, 25 Sept.; Jan Hendrik, Slager, Dordrecht PILLAU, 25 Sept.; Pers-, Drenth, Huil. - Afiena, Goossens, Leer. SUNDSWALL, 9 S-pt.;Titania, Olsen, Amst. ELSENEUR,-&apos;25 Sept.; gepasseerd: Artemisia, Allan, Amst. n. de Oostzee. - Louise, Brandt, Gend n. id. - Engelina Pietronella, Brouwer, Schiedam n. do Oostzee. - Zwaantina Thelina, de Boer Sap, Sunderl. n. id. - Union, Hazewinkcl, St. Valery n. id.- Wilhelmina, Nagel,Bremen n. id.- Jantina, Lohman, Newc. „. Dantzig. - Nijverheid, Kernper, Rott. n. Koningsbergen. — 26 Sept.; Giionde, S , Petersb. n. Rott. - Urania, S., Amst. n. Koningsb. - Cornelia, S., id. n. Stettin. RENDSBURG, 22 Sept.; Gepasseerd: Anje, Meijer, Dantzig n. Gron. - Hendrika Margretha, Stel, Stettin n. Delfz. - Lubbegina, Spithorst, Malmoe n. Zaand. - Vriendenlust, Koops, Stolpemunde n. Dordrecht. —23 Sept.; V. Martha, 801, Carlshamn n. Londen.-Anke, Blceker, Rostok n. Bremsn.- Catharina Maria, de Roth, id. n. id. —24 Sept.; Eendragt, Kamminga, id. n. Londen. - Onrust, Slankonberg, Koningsb. n. Gent. - 3 Gebroeders, de Groot, Dantzig n. Bremen. - Grietje, Schoon, Memel n. id. - Alberdina Eokkelina, Schuur, id. n. Vegesack. - Catharina, Wcsterbiinck, Bremen n. Stettin. - Tjakina de Boer, Dost, Amersfoort n. Sleeswijk. TONNINGEN, 24 Sept.; Gepasseerd: 4 Gebroeders, Heida, Dantzig n. Dokkum. - Magrita Meijering, de Jonge, id. n. Groningen. STA VANGER, 5 Sopt.; Ziba, Pedersen, Schiedam. — 8 Sopt.; Anagarias, Jacobsen, id. ARENDAL, 12 Sept.; Ora et Labora, Christensen, Amst. CHRISTIANIA, 13 Sept.; Martha, Hansen, Amst. —15 Sept.; Vingolf Sörensen,id. LONDEN, 27 Sept.; de Hoop, Jelsma, Worcum. -In lading: Suriname, jifiddelberg, Suriname. Bij DUNGENESS, 25 Sept.; Pieter, Hoogerwerff, Soerabaya n. Rott.--26 Sept.; Angelina, Evans,Workington n. id. LIVERPOOL, 26 Sept. In lading: Caspar de Robles, van Slooten, Laguayra. LEITH, 26 Sept.; Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Koningsbergen. YARMOUTH, 26 Sept.; Zenobia, Child, Harlingen. SWANSEA, 26 Sept.; Maria Franeiseo, Longobardo, Rotterdam. CARDIFF, 25 Sept.; Johanna, Hubert, Bristol. v HULL, 26 Sopt.; O. P. Q., Lowery, Rott. &apos;NEW-CASTLE, 25 Sept. In lading: Jaeoba Gesina, Kramer, Genua.- Zwaantina, Gruppelaar, Kopenhagen.- de Spruit, Pot, id. -Catharina, Duintjer, Holmstad. - Oldambt, Scholtema, Malinoe. - Sojhia Maria, Teensma Cadix. &apos; SHIELDS, 26 Sept.; Remmini, Vissering, Amst. - Zeeploeg,Luders, id.. Sharon, Ford, Dordt. - Anna Margaretha, Lucas, Ilarbnrg. SUNDERLAND, 26 Sept.; Princess Royal, Riichi, Rott. - Vesper, White, Nieuwe Diep. - Zvvanette Jantina, Wegener, Groningen HARTLEPOOL, 25 Sept.; Gitana, Needham, Rott. PLYMOUTH, 26 Sopt.; Phoenix, lones, Ibrail n. Amst. FOWEY, 25 Sept.; Grimaldi, Hill,Whitehaven n. Rott. CAMARET, 26 Sept.; Heureux Retour, Couedel,Vannes n Amst NANTES, 25 Sopt.: Marie René, Finnean, Amst. GENUA, 24 Sopt.; Béréniee, S., Rott. LIVORNO, 20 Sept.; Béréniee, S., Amst.</p>
</text>
