<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen.</title>
	<p>Gepraaid, 3 Mei; op 3° 44&apos;N.8r.32° 16&apos; W.L.: Diana, Masdorp Dzn., Buenos Ayres n. Antwerpen. BINNENGEKOMEN. TEXEL, 6 Junij. W.Z.W.; Metalen Kruis, Ned. Oorl. Stoomschip, kapt. luit. J. de Vos, Kust van Guinea, I. v. Ascension. - 3 Broeders, Bijkerk, Londen.—7 Junij; Bellatrix, Haacke, Banjoewangie, vertr. BFebr. - Kongsverre, Marcussen, Newyork. - Prosper. Chalmers, Chester. -Stad Workum, Eisinga, Newc.- Johns, Torjusen, Osterriseer. — Gisteren nog: George Smith, Marshall. Sunderland. VLIE, 6 Junij, N. W.; Éendragt, Dorenbos, Bo&apos;ness. - Onderneming, Kooiman, Frederikstad. — 7 Junij; Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Jnnij. Z.W.; Normandy, S., Banana.- Upton, S., Taganrog. - Admiraal Ver-Huel, S„ Havre. - Margaretha Antina, Speelman, Londen. -Neva, 8., Petersb. — 7 Juuij-, Tasco, S., Taganrog, l.v. Brouwersh. - E. D.. Butley, Ruucorn. - S wanland, S., Huil. - Éendragt, de Boer, Harwich. j BRIELLE, 7 Junij, N.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - j Waterloo, S., Londen. - Sheffield, S., Grimsby. - Zealous, S., j Harwich. ! BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Junij; Mary Monarch, Urn, Rott. n. Newc, heeft 7 dito de reis voortgezet. — 7 Junij; Indian Queen, Marris, Callao n. Rott.-Hugo Grotius, Leversteïn, Liverp. n. id, ZIERIKZEE, 6 Junij. N.; Dash, Durrell, Liverpool. EMDEN, 3 Juuij; Coop Roelf Sikkens. Schaaf, Newc. BREMERHAVEN, 4 Junij; Henderika, Bakker, Heppens.</p>
	<p>HEPPENS, l Junij; Coneordia, Kaatje, Dantzig. BOLDÊRAA, 31 Mei; Oostwolde, ten Kate, Amst. - Hermanna, Pyors, Antw. - Tjakiena, van Sluis, Gloucester. - Cornelia Anna Christina, de Haan, Hamburg. — 1 Junij; Minerva, Jans, Harlingen. - Trijntje, Egberts, Gloucester. KROONSTAD, 2 Junij; Elisabeth, Wiersma, Bordeaux.- Alberdina, Lontan. Boulogne. - Jantina, de Jonge, Antwerpen. - Gepbina, Lohman, Newport. - Zwerver, Höster, Liverpool. - Maria Christina, Balk. Hamburg. — 3 Junij; Cornelia Jantina, Kwint, Gloucester. - Alida Hendrika, Nieuwenhuijs id. - Alida, Brouwer, Liverpool. - Enjetta, Boswijk, id. - Meika Jacoba, Wielema, Newcastle. - AnnaPaulown&apos;a, S., Kiel.-HendrikJan Nassau, Lukui, Bergen. Bij WIGHT, 4 Junij: Willemina &amp; Clara, van Herwerden, Amst. n. Bat, - Jason, Rnsman, Rott. n. id. Bij SALCOMBE, 3 Juni); E. D. Barter,..., Liverp. n. Dordr. BRIS l OL, 4 Jnnij; Rival, Koning, Straalsund. FINDHORN, .. &apos;...; Eutreprise, Watt, Rott. LEITH, 4 Junij; Emelie, Steinorth, Amst. SHIELDS, 4 Junij; Charlotte,Temperley, Amst. - Gerda, Niel, Rott. - Hsirmony, Humprey, id. - Friends, Wells, Dordr. - 2 Gebroeders, Persoon, Vlissingen. SUNDERLAND. 4 Junij; Germania, Behrend, Dordrecht. - Alida, dc Vries, Duinkerken. HARTLEPOOL, 4 Junij; Gesina Mensinga, Nielsen, Dordrecht. - Alida Pronk, Scholtens.Norrköping. HARWICH-, S.Junij; i&apos;aragon, Frankland, Rott. Si. VALERY. 23 Mei; 4 Gebroeders. 81-&apos;s, Groningen. DARDANELLEN, 27 Mei; Mont Carmel, Bravey, ïaganrog n. Amst. NEW-YORK, 23 Mei; Bessie North, Fove, Rott. — 25 Mei; Helios, Rickmers, id. PHILADELPHIA, A., 24 Mei; Germania, Uhlbruck, Rott. l/TGEZEILD. TEXEL, 6 Junij, W.Z.W.: Troubadour, S., Londen. - Setubal, S.. id. - Agias Dimitios, Pasos, Newc. - Waterloo, Patterson, id. - Douglas. S., Sunderland. - Elisabeth, Wart, id. - Garrison, S., Hartßpool. - Bulgerstein, v. Wijngaarden, Sundsw. - Wingolf, Sörensen, Harnösand. - Johanna&apos;Petronella, Hillebrandt, Avontuur. — Gisteren nog: Sippe Visser, de Jong, Londen. — 7 Junij; Éendragt, Feenstra, Londen. - Vrouw Anna, de Jong, id. - Carbon, S.. Newcastle. - Médéa. S.. Dantzig. VLIE, 6 Junij, W. Z. W.; Niord, Bjornstedt, Drobach. - Willem 1, 8.. Hamburg. - Cella, Olsen, Archangel.- Oscar, Evensen, Pifea. - Jacoba Lucretia, Maas, Windau. - Lykkens Prove, Lindahl, id. - Argo, Alta, Dantzig. - Roelfina Johanna, Drewes, Stettin. - Anna Luitzia, Jager, Frederikstad. - Geertruida, Dekker, Oudsoen. - Vrouw Helena, Kraan, Christiansand. - Niord, Bjornstedt. Drobach. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Junij,Z.W.;olga,S„Londen. - Mary Maria, Heard, Newport. -Louise,S., Grangemouth.-Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan. S., Newc. - Violet, Richardson, id.- Aleiandra, S., id. - Mary Monarch, Urn, Brouwersh. — 7 Jnnij; Gironde, S., Bordeaux. - Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Seahorse. S., Huil. - Albert, S., id. - Willi&apos;am Coleman, S., Goole. - Bradford, S.. Grimsby. BI.IELLE, 6 Junij, W. Z. W.; Leo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich.</p>
	<p>BROUWERSHAVEN, 7 Junij, N.j Cameronian, Sherman, Rott. n. Cardiff. PILLAU, 4 Junij; Odin, S., Antwerpen, - Farailietrouw, de Boer. Heppens. - Gesina, Bontekoe, id. BOLDÊRAA, 3!) Mei; Protens, Zeven, Nederl. - Chnstine, Kassens, Duinkerken. - Wilhelmine, Meijer, Engeland. —31 Mei; Elsje, Tap, id. - Wieka, Wortel, Nederl. - Gesina, Gorteniaker, Antwerpen. KROONSTAD, 3 Junij; Handel, Westerling, Schiedam. -</p>
	<p>Zwaluw, Visser, Harlingen. FALMOUTH. 4 Jnnij; Wvnvard, Beckett, Ibraïla,n. Amst. KONSTANTINOPEL, 20 Mei; E. Covacevich, Crelich, Amst.</p>
</text>
