<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>&apos;TEXEL, 1 Nov., Z.W.—N.N.W.; Mary &amp; Arm, Richardson, Liverpool. - Hawk, S., Huil. - Catharina de Boer, Waterborg, Ipswicb. — Terug mt j zee: Curacao Packet.de Ruiter, n. Curacao. — bisteren nog: Auguste, Grosz-Herzogin v. Mecklênburg, Roggensack, Wismar. VLIE, 31 Oct., W-; Tjapco Schuringa, Drent, Petersburg. , . HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Nov., Z.W.; President v. Rijckevorssel, Vogelenzang, Bat. 1. v. Brouwershaven.-TeresaCarmelo,Lagana,Odessa, 1. v. | id. - Theresa, Marchazano, Berdianski, U v. id - Result Petiuan, Zante. - Mary Helen, Tadd, Cephalonia. - Wesley, Le Couteur, St. Malo. - Mana, de Laner, Caen. - Alexandrina, de Sunnai, id. - Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Pilot, S., id. - Expert, Allan, Montrose. - Cornelia, van Hengelaar, Newc- Hercules, Calder, id. - de Burger, Bartelse id. - Seagull S., Huil. - Middlesbro*, S., Middlesbro&apos;. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. - Harberdina, Bakker, Petersburg. - Albertha Roenielingh, deVries, id.- Geertruida Anna, Schrikkema, id. - Anna Hendrika, Ebliug, id. - Demetrius, Storey, id. - Germa- BIBRÖU WERSHAVEN, 1 Nov. Z.Z.W.; Emilia Mignano, Meglio, Odessa nVILLAUf3O Oct., W.N.W.; Familietrouw, Jonker, Schiedam, - Ulrika, LONDEN, 30 Oct.; Anton , Scbröder, Gron. - Catharina Ricarci Bij DEAL, 30 Oct.; Cornelia, Teensma, Amst. n. Bueuos-Ayres. DEAL, 31 Oct., ten anker gekomen; Johanna, Ouwehaud,Amst.n. ST IC 3.S S 3,1* Bij WIGHT,3O oet.;Ternate,Oars,Rott n.Bat. _&apos;__.&apos;&apos; Bij LOWESTOFT, 30 Oct.; Septmius, Shil ing, Portsoyn. Rott. LAMLASH, 26 Oct.; Pavadetta, Pott, de Clyde n. Berbice.- Elsje, Boer, id. n. Buenos-Ayres. . PLYMOÜTH, 30 Oct.; Balmoral, S., Rott. n.Bnstol SHIELDS, 30 Oct,; Sif, Magnussen, Schiedam. - Fnede, Wachtel, il. Cherubin. Thelberg, Harl. CADIX, 25 Oct.; Sirius, van Rees, Vigo. GIBRALTAR, 22 Oct.; Elisabet Barker, Leslie, Ibraüa, vert. n. Aimd. NAPELS, 25 Oct.; Dido, van Wijk Amst. , PALERMO, 21 Oct.; Orion, S.jAmst. — 23Oct,ManaKemna, ac</p>
</text>
