<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Oct.; Diana, S., Londen. — 2 Oct.; Frouwina, Duit, Maroim. - Theodora Josina, Tjakkes, Curasao. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Mcdéa S., Petersb. - Norske Küppe, Henriksen, Riga. - Preden, Morck, Drammen.- Princesse Gyda, Christensen, id. OSTMAHORN, 30 Sept.; Debiteur, Koning, Southampton.-Jacob Synes, Nip, Gothenburg. — 1 Oct.; Alida Dijk, de Haas, Roehester. - Zwaantje Elisabeth, Jager, Gothenburg. DELFZIJL, 28 Sept.; Aldershof, Dijkstra, Noorwegen. - Grietje Huis- man, Kuipers, id. - Catharina Luitgardina, Bos, id. - Goessien Schreuder, Albers, id. - Maria Edina, Hegerman, id. - Johann Heinrich, de Jonge, id. - 2 Gezusters, Geltes, Bremen. - Fennegien, Beerthuis, Hoekzijl. - Ettina, Heiten, Oldersum. - Antina, Buisker, id. - Ida, Lubbers, Ditzum. - Kleine Julia, Burman, Emden. — 30 Sept.; Cornelia, Jentzema, Noorwegen. - Jantje, Forma, Leer. - 2 Gezusters, de Lange, Pruis. Pold. TERMUNTERZIJL, 25 Sept.; 2 Gebroeders, Bolt, Noorw. — 26 Sept.; Aaltje, Koning, id. - Geertje Pott, Tap, id. — 27 Sept; Antiena, Kettwich, id. — 29 Sept.; Christina Jantina, Dood, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Oct.; Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Batavia via Brouwershaven. - Vectis, Parrei, Newc. - Marie Coralie, Bakker, Frederikstad. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Oct.; Diana, Teengs, Rott. n. Bat. MAASSLUIS, 2 Oct.; Albion, Elles, Hartlepool. - John fr Charles, Hopkins, Roehester. - Catharina, Gewalt, Avontuur. S WINEMUNDE, 28 Sopt.; Geerdina, Nieboer, Livorno.-Jaeoba Gesina, van der Meulen, Rendsburg. BOLDERA, 25 Sept.; Speculant, Hustede, Elseneur. - Gesina, Riks, id. QUEENSTOWN, 28 Sept.; Voorzorg, Huisman, Montevideo n. Liverp. GLOUCESTER, 29 Sopt.; Jantje Berg, van Driesten, Cardif. SHIELDS, 29 Sept.; Boreas, Munneke, Harlingen. ROUA AN, 28 Sept.; John and James, Balmforth, Harlingen. PAIMBOEUF, 29 Sept.; Caroline Victoire, Lemetais, Rott. LISSABON, 24 Sept.; Kleinkinderen, de Jong, Faro. - Koophandel en Zeevaart, Brouwer, Villa Nova. AMOY, 5 Aug.; Solide, den Breems, Takao. BATAVIA, 14 Ang.; Zeilkl. Drie Gezusters, Fischer, Nederland.</p>
</text>
