<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 April, N. N. W.; Alert, S., Hull, (benevens de schepen per tcleg. gemeld). VLIE, 11 April, N.N. W.; Hollandia, S., Londen.- Terra Nova, Abel, Frederikstad. - Maria, Meinsma, id. - Pieter, Oostcrvink, Osterrisoer. - Concordia, Hendriksen,.Noorwegen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Aprïl.N.; Jannetje, van Striemen qq.,Batavia I. v. Brouwershaven. - Luconia, Admiraal Jzn., id. 1. v. Zierikzee.-Veritas, Nyman, Oallao, 1. v. id. - Ary Scheffer, S., Havre. - Feijenoord,S.,Londen. BRIELLE; 12 April, W. fl. W.; Soagull, S., Hull. - Ravcnsbury, S., Harwich.</p>
	<p>BROUWERSHAVEN, 12 April, N.; Nercus, Planten, Passer, n. Rott.; vertr. 3 Dec. - Jacobus Martinus, Meppèlder, Bat.; 1. v. de Simons-Baai n. id. - Catharina Maria, van Amerongen, Rott. n. Bat. HAMBUP.Ü, 10 April; Nooit Gedacht. Bakker, Itzehoo. ALTONA, 10 April; Cornelia Jantina, Kwint, Hamburg.</p>
	<p>BREMERHAVEN, 10 Aprü; Twee Gezusters, Geltes, Groningen.- Jantina Margrieta, de Winter, id. - Engelina Fransen, Dost, id.-Pietertje, Dost, id. SWINEMUNDE, 10 April; Olympia, Hayn, Rott. - Fortuna, de Groot, Londen.</p>
	<p>DANTZIG, 8 April; Twee Gebroeders, Borgers, New-Castle. AREND AL, 2-5 Maart; Amicitia, Visser, Nieuwediep. BERGEN, 26 Maart; Herstelling, Ligthart, Antwerpen. —28 Maart; Anna, S., Altona. — 29 Maart; Jonge Lieffert, Bakker, Harlingen.- Catharina Uornelia, Borst, Antwerpen. —30 Maart; Ida, van der Molen, Newc. KORSOER, 6 April; Arnoldus Willem Nanninga, Top, Engeland. HORSENS, vóór 3 April; Frauke Dijkstra, Hamstra, Hamburg. HOLTENAU, 5 April: Gepasseerd&quot;: Herstelling, Banjer, Rugénwalde n. Londen. - Aukje Gepkelina, Duintjer, Kiel n. Amst. TRIEST, 6 April; Jan Hendrik, Slager, Antwerpen. HONGKONG. 19 Febr.; Amazone, Kramer, Saigon. — 24 Febr.; Albatros, ..., Bangkok. —25 Febr.; in lading: St. Helena, Pille, Tamsui. - Vesia, van der Eyk, Saigon. MACAO, 25 Febr.; in lading: Krimpen a/d. Lek, Rotgans, Havana. - Onrust, Weissenbruch, id. AMOY, 21 Febr.; in lading, Constance, Mulder, Saigon. - Sophia Koningin der Nederlanden, Klein, Singapore en Java.</p>
</text>
