<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 27 Julij; Favorite, Withelield, Galatz. - Irwcll, S., Huil. - Gode Hen-iigt, Berg, Sóderhamn. - Harmonie, Stangebye, Frederikstad. - Enigheden, Torkelsen, Tonsberg. — 28 Julij; Raphael, v. d. Velde Smit, Curaipao. - Coop Roelfs Sikkens, Schaaf, Londen. - Dawson, Prouton, Newc. - Betsy &amp; Jane, Torp, id. - Leo, Robertson, Sunderland - Zephyrus, Elliot, id. - Victor, Time, Hudickswall. - Freya, Gjersoe, Frederikstad. - Embla, Dahn, Drammen. - Friheden, Christophersen, id. - Josephine, Thiin, id. (Benevens de schepen per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 27 Julij; Catharina Cornelia, Astuling, Dantzig.-Elizabeth, Kjo_&apos;n~r„ Frederikstad. - Vrouw Helena, Kraan, Arendahl. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 Julij; Elise, Briere ,Nantes. - Orchidee, Rivet, id. - Nymph, Storm, Newc. - Admiral Cator, S., Hartlepool.-Eduard, Gorth, Memel. - Freya, Sönnichsen, Randers. - Familien, Knud3cn, Gothenburg. BRIELLE, 28 Julij; Leo, S., Londen. - Feijenoord, S. id. - De Maas, S., id. - Swallow, S., Huil. - Colletis, S., Goole. - Pacifie, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 28 Julij; Eleanor, Adams, Newc. n. Rott. BREMERHAVEN, 27 Julij; Aukje, Teensma, Petersb. - Elise, Voogt, Sannesiind. LONDEN, 27 Julij; Helena $• Anna, Jansen, Thisted.-Vr. Dieuwke, Foenstra, Won-urn. - In lading: Wietska, Bos, Petersb. Bij DEAL, 25 Julij; Bantam, Claassen, Amst. n. Japan. Bij DOVER, 25 Julij; Jan van S&lt;-hanelaar, van Duyn, Java n. Amst. Bij DUNGENESS, 25 Julij; Don Juan, Lindo, New-York n. Rott. - Julius, Schuurman, Amst. n. Liverpool. Bij FOLKESTONE, 26 Julij; Gerberdina&amp; JeannetteEmilie, Kuyper, Laguavra n. Altona. Bij SOUTHWOLD, 26 Julij; Enjetta, de Boer, Libau n. Londen. DUNDKE, 26 Julij; Louise, Kaspersma, Petersb. FRASERBURGH, 26 Julij; Lambert, Kramer, Dantzig. BEKWICK, 25 Julij; Alpha, Puister, Petersb. - de Hoop, Pot, id. BONESS, 26 Julij; Ulrika, Dik, Gothenburg. GRIMSBY, 26 Julij; Hydra, Munneke, Stettin. HULL, 20 Julij; Jacoba Margaret&apos; a, Rozenveld, Christiaansand. NEW-CASTLE, 24 Julij; In lading: Concordia, Goossens, Malta. - Leentjo, Hoedemaker, Memel. - Catharina, van der Meulen, Roeskilde. Verwisseling, Scholtens, Rostok. - Anna Catharina, Huges, Stettin. SHIELDS, 25 Julij; Utility, Walker, Amst. - Fortune Teller, Weleh, Dordt. -Zwaluw, de Vries, Ipswich. — 26 Julij; Henriette, Johnson, Rott. - East Cornwall, Dyev, id. - Oernen, Hansen, Zaandam - Diadem, Butchard, Dordrecht. SUNDERLAND, 25 Julij; Clyde, Granger, Dordtr. Sainte Marie, Cori*/i,-n, Sch&apos;i dam. &apos; HARTLEPOOL, 25 Julij; Vertrouwen, Boldt, Riga.-Petronella, Pluktje, Loc (len. &apos; MACDUFF, 25 Julij; Cornet, Pedersen, Amst. P&apos;LYAÏOIJTII, 25 Julij; B-lmora!, S., Rott. (vertrok n. Bristol). MARSEILLE, 25 Julij; Fortuna, Hoogerwerff, Lissabon. &apos;PAIMBOEUF, 25 Julij; Bon Père, Lemerh-, Harlingen. LIVORNO, 21 Julij; Bére&apos;nice, 3, Antwerpen. &quot;BALTIMORE, 13 Julij; Zr. Ms. Stoomschip Watergeus, comm. Geerling, A-trika;. HAVANA, 7 Julij; in lading: Zuiderzee, de Jong, Amst.</p>
</text>
