<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 Mei; Undine, Bonde, Frederikstad. — 9 Mei; Espérance, Hazewinkel, Cette. - Vcracity, Hardy, Newc. - Sultana, Bell, id. - Hart, Cloak, id. - Minister Thorbccke, S., Huil. — 10 Mei; Delft, van Geelkerken, Soerabaya, vertr. 7 Jan.; Johanncs Hermanus, Hoekstra, Cette. - Eur&apos;opean,S., Huil.- Argo,Schwartz, Drammen. VLIB. 8 Mei; Stella Matutina, Beekman, Leba. — 9 Mei; Concordia, van der Meyden, St. Übcs. - Neptunus, van Gorkum, Newc. - Joham;a G _ sina, v. d. Veen, Gothenburg. - Enigheden, Torkeldsen, Holmstrand.— 10 Mei; Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Mei; Zeenimph, Sikkcma, Triest. - Anna Margaretha, Olthoff, Livorno. - Meridian, Francis, Whitehavcn. -Osprey, Simpson, Charlestown. - Melby, Edwards, Newc. - Francois, &apos;t Hart, id. - Adriana Francisca, van Eyk, id. - Karel August, Meermans, id.- Oceanos, Thorpe, id. - Sterling, Hutcnirison, Sunderland. BLTELLE, 0 Mei;&apos; Anna Gezina, de Vries, La Roche Bernard. BROUWERS ÜA VEN, 9 Mei; Nathaniel, Jwnes, Livonio n.Dordrecht.- Mary&apos;s Peacock, Newc. n. id. - Betsy Jane, Nicholson, id. n. id. - Dageraad, Duinker, Rott. n. Bat. — 10 Mei; K. aiagawa, Ouwehand, Banjuew. n. Rott., vertr. 15 Jan. - Adelina, Giacamo, Licat. 11. id. CUXI_AVEN,BMei; Grietje van Bolhuis, Jansen, Bremerhaven. — i) Mei; Eltica Mcczenbrock, Vegter, Nizza. BREMERHAVEN, 8 Mei; Jonge Georg, Pieper, Dclfzyl. STETTIN, 7 Mei; Rotterdam, S., Rott. DANTZIG, 7 Mei; Jantina Roelfina, Broekoma, Hamburg. - Triton, Munnix, Newc. CHRISTIANIA, 29 April; Johanna Catharina, van Veen, Newc. — 30 April; Stad Steenwijk, Wyma, Harlingen. - Jonje Rieka, Klein. Newc. ELSENEUR, 7 Mei; gepasseerd: Hoffnung, Sonne, Amst. n. Windau. FOWEY, 7 Mei; Lydia, Dobson, Charlestown n. Dordt. CARDIFF, 5 Mei; Argo, Dartels, Amst LIVERPOOL, 7 Mei; Isaac Sannes, de Jonge, Antw. - Juffer Esse Mcusinga, Eofting, Livorno. - Elisabeth Helena, Coerkamp , Rio SIIIELDS, 7 Moi; Truc Briton, Rogcrs, Dordt. LEITH. 7 Mei; Raven, Wright, Rott. ?&apos;.., . „ , ANTWERPEN, 8 Mei; Ondine, S., Bordeaux. -- 9 Mei; Maria, Beekman, Buenns-Ayres. _..._-¦,, _ „ r&gt; *. CHBRBURG, 2 Mei; Amphitrite, Calve, Redon n. Rott. SANTANDER, 4 Mei; Alberdina, Loman, Ferro. ¦ROSTON, 24 April; Suriname, Middelbcrgh, Falmouth. TJITGEZEILD. , T TEXEL, 9 Mei; Diana, 8, Londen. - Sippe.Vtóser, de Jong id. VLIE, 8 Mei; Neptmras, Scholtens, Péteretorg. - MattlieW &amp; FanTVr Johannesen, Riga. - Schlun.p zu Lulle, Strack, Stockholm.-Adelheid, Hanson, Söderhamn. - Olaf Kyrre, Jorgensen Hernosand. - bortuna All dersen, Christiania. - 3 Gebroeders, Jansen, id. - Wilhelmina, Schuurling, Frederikstad. - CatharinaVisser, do Vreeze Chnstiansand -Chnstma Ja eóba Rloes Noorw. - Catharina Elisabeth Pot, Avontuur. •=- 9 Meh fmoSk^^raXtK- •G«*iena Antlcll!l-vanKloos^&apos; -&apos; Annacniêna.&apos;BlQnw.Falkenbevg.</p>
</text>
