<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 16 0ct.,Z.Z.0.-Z.W.; Engel, Appel, Bat.,vertr. 16 Mei.-Shields Newall, New-York, 1. v. Falmouth. - Clara &amp; Carl, Sachs, Odessa. - Lion S., Londen. - Perseverance, Elliot id. - Lydia, Dobson, Liverpool. - Margaret, Chambers, Newc- European, S., Hull.-Piet Hein, Meijer, Petersb.- Neptun, Meislaw, Riga. - Najaden, Edwardsen, Sundswall.-Mercur, Czernichow, id.- Elisabeth Catharina, Heegaard, id.-Nathael, Jobson, Swartvick. - Rubbens, S., Koningsb. - Oriënt, S., Dantzig. — Gisteren nog: Eensgezindheid, de Waal, Samarang. VLIE, 15 Oct., Z. O.; Hanna, Warness, Petersb. - Haabet, Lorentzen, Sundswall. — 16 Oct.; Zwaluw, Visser, Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Oct., Z.; Ingeborg, Petersen, Rangoon.-Little Dorritt, Stephens, Zante. - Laurens, de Kromme, St. Übes. - Anton &amp; Jacob, Bot, Faro. - Hannah Booth, Andrews, Par. -Star of the West, Searle, id. - Speedwell, Readings, Cardiff. - Gannett, S., Liverpool. - William, Johns, Dublin. - Albert, S., Huil. - Eva, Crosby, Stettin.— Gisteren nog: Mary Arm, Krenkel, Newyork I. v. Brouwershaven. BRIELLE, 16 Oct., Z.;Leo, S., Londen. - Ravensbury, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 16 Oct.,Z.; Nederland en Oranje, Moller, Bat. n. Rott.; vertr. 11 Julij. - Morning Star, Key, Rangoon n. Vlaardingen.- Georg Emily, Brown, Taganr. n. Rott. • BREMERHAVEN, 15 Oct.; Vr. Geerdina, Speelmann, Hamburg. - Grietje, Siebel, id. ,&apos; Bij KOPENHAGEN, 14 Oct.; Tjakiena.v. Sluis, Petersb. n. de Maas. - Wilhelmina Petronella, Bijl, id. n. Schiedam. BOLDERA, 11 Oct.; Lambertha, Carst, Nantes.-12 Oct.; Wilhelmine, Dreetmann, Antwerpen. - Catharina Regina, Wulff, St. Übes. ELSENEUR, 13 Oct., O. Z. O.; Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Petersb. n. Amst.- Jantje Wilkens, Hotze, id. n. id., is van anker en ketting voorzien.— 14 Oct.; Lubbegiena, Spiihorst, id. n. id. - Henriette, Aslachsen, Sundsw. n. Antwerp. - Bulgerstein, v. Wijngaarden, id. n. de Noordzee. - Reintje, Teensma, Petersburg, met schade aan tuigage. Bij DOVER, 13 Oct.; Kosmopoliet, Mulder, Groningn. Cardiff. Dunrobin Castle, Campbell, Rott. n. Swansea. Bij DUNGENESS, 13 Oct.; Triest, S., Odessa n. Rotterdam. HARWICH, 14 Oct.; Anna, Hoekstra, Groningen n. Ipswich. - Domina Geertina, Wolters, id. n. id.</p>
	<p>HULL, 14 Oet.; Adriana Wilhelmina, v. Eyk, Narva. WEST-HARTLEPOOL, 14 Oct.; De Hoop, Pott. Christiania. MIDDLESBRO, 14 Oct.; Gustave, Nehls, Amst.- Francisco, Hellius,id. POOLE, 14 Oct.; Margaretha Geziena, de Groot, Kroonstad. &apos; SUNDERLAND, 140ct.-, Watermillock, Ernskine,Harlingen.-Elisabeth, Ward, Nieuwediep. SHIELDS, 14Oct.;Messenger, Pomery, Amst.-Star, Kinley,Vlaardingen. - Annette Sophia, Aste, Nieuwediep. - Catherina Elisabeth, Lever, Narva. PHILADELPHIA, 2 Oct.; Cynthia Palmer, Milner, Rott. via Boston. SWATOW, 8 Aug.; Jacobus, v. d. Tas, Newschwang.</p>
</text>
