<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL. 28 Dcc, N.N.W.-N.W.: Ondine, S.. Bordeaux. V LIE, 28 Dcc, N.N.W.; Nora, S.&apos;, Londen. - Hollandia. S., id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 Dcc, O.; Hoek van Holland, Bakker, Bat. 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Alcyon, Bouviré, Éédon. - Pilot, S., Londen. - Aurora, S., id. - Cosarine, Blanchet, Falmonth. - Caspina, Etherington, Sunderl. - Baron Hambro, S., Middlesbro&apos;. - Albert, S., Huil. - Orion, Braamhorst, Eiga. - Sirius, Doowes, id. - Diana, Fijn, Dantzig. BRIELLE, 28 Dcc, O.; Maas, S., Londen. - Gisteren nog: Anna Gesina, Garrels, Dantzig. BROUWERSHAVEN, 28 Dcc, Z. 0.; Unio, Parrei, Windau n.Schiedam. DELFZIJL, 26 Dcc; Nestor, Kneppe, Riga. - Alberdina, Lohman, Laurvig. VLISSINGEN, 28 Dcc; Zeemeeuw, v. Wijck, Riga. - Fenna Hendrika, Duit, id. AEENDAHL, 18 Dcc; Helios, Sievertsen, Sundswal n. Amst. LONDEN, 27 Dcc; Douwina Timmer, Seiveling, Gron. PLYMOÜTH, 26 Dec.; Astrea, S., Eott. n. Bristol. St. MAWES, 25 Dcc; Hend. Frouwina, Scholtens, v. Gron. n. Nantes. LOOE, 24Dec; J. F. Bulier, Scapcott, Amst.; FOWEY, 26 Dcc; Isabella, Tippet, v. Eott. n. Gloucestcr. GRANGEMOUTH, 24 Dcc; Bronghty Castle, Pringle, Rott. GBEAT YARMOUTH, 26 Dcc; Karsina, Olfers, Leeuwarden. HABTLEPOOL, 24 Dcc; Bover, Anderson, Schiedam. — 25 Dcc; Bon Père, Mahoo, id. MIDDLESBRO, 26 Dcc; Charies, Beranger, Bott. NEW-CASTLE, 24 Dcc; In lading: Minister Thorbecke, Kannogieter, Onrust. - Nederland en Oranje, Haasnoot, Soerabaya. - Maria, Slnyk, id. SHIELDS, 25 Dcc; Triumphant, Dorrit, Schiedam. - E. T. K., Organ, Dordrecht. . TT _ LEITH, 26 Dcc; Nouvelle Union, Conseil, Harlingen. - H. Jens MonbergMinden,..., Eott. OSTENDE, 24 Dcc; Drie Gezusters, Broeland, Biga. CAMARET, 23 Dcc; Amélie, Lebeau, Eédon n. Eott. BILBAO, 24 Dcc; Vertrouwen, Kal, Eott. NAPELS, 17 Dcc; Zwerver, Visser, Amst.— 18 Dcc; Andrea, Ladanza, Amst. . __» _ ? SINGAPORE, 10 Nov.; Nereus, Planten, Newport. - Maria Diedenka, van Marion, Cardiff. - Concurrent, Singer, id. - Neptunus, Lodowijks, Newc. — 13 Nov.; Leopold! Graaf van Limburg Stirum, Keuker, id.— 14 Nov.; Geessina Maria, Rolff, id. — 16 Nov.; Schelde, Hoffmann, Newport, laden voor Batavia.</p>
</text>
