<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 6 Julij; Reina Dethmers, Mulder, Galatz. - Ready Rhir.e, Strike, W, 1. v. Falmouth. - Franco, Oxiglia, Nicolajef, 1. v. Galipoli. - Lion, S., Londen. - City of Rotterdam, Earnshaw, id. - Hendrika, Beekonkamp, id. - Eendracht, Bijkerk, id. - Oliver, Mortimer, id. - Sultania, Buil, Sunderl. - Solon, Otterbeek, Nerva. VLIE, 5 Julij; Tjapko Schuringa, Drenth, Petersb. — 6 Julij; Familietrouw, Jonker, Petersb. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Julij; Brother&apos;s Ruccess, Hobart, Roehestcr. - Rheidal Vale, Thomas, Newport. — 6 Julij; Jeannette &amp; Cornelia, Romijn, Banjoew., 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Tonia, Haesloop Werncr Jr., Tjilatjap.l. v. id.; vertr. 13 Maart. - Zephvr, S., Londen. - Advance, S., Burnt-Eiland. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Colletis, S„ Goole. HEPPENS,2 Julij; Catharina, Meijer,de Weser.- Gesina, ele Vries, Leer - Dorothea, de Vries, id. - Catharina, de Boer, id. - Agatha, Wortel, Rott. HAMBURG, 4 Julij ; Amsterdam, S., Amsterdam. - Catharina Groeneftold, Velvis , Leer. WARNEMUNDE, 3 Julij; Neptunus, van Goikum, Harlin--en STETTIN, 3 Julij; Triest, S., Rotterdam. RUGENWALDE, 28 Junij; Margaretha, Koch, Flensburg STOLPEMUNDE, 27 Junij; Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Amst! ABO, 23 Junij; Dankbaarheid, Wey, Bergen. GOTHENBURG, 29 Junij; Isaac Sannes, de Jonge, Newc. ELSENEUR, IJ ulij; Gepasseerd: Ambrosia, Buil, Söderhamn n. Rott. — •i Jnlij; Willem, de Boer, Riga n. Amst. - Gloria, Puister, Dantzig n. Hartlepool. . Alida, Feiken, id. n. de Eems. TONNINGEN, 1 Julij; Gepasseerd: Geerdina, Visser, Bremen n.Haderslebcn. — 2 Julij; Jantina Catharina, van Dijk, Dordrecht n. Stettin. - Jonge •Jan et Margaretha, Jelies, Bremen n. Stokholm. LONDEN, 5 Junij; Herman, de Boer, Rugenwalde. - Gebr. Visser, Faber, &quot;dessee. Bij GOUDSTAART, 3 Julij; Lodc-wijk, Bax, Congo-rivier n. Rott. Bij LIZARD, 3 Julij; Isaac da Costa, Klein, Padang n. Amst. - Catharina, ■Hakker, Amst. n. Triest. TORB AY, 3 Julij; Welcome, Cohen, Rott. n. Bari. » 5._ BEVEZIER, 3 Julij; Jacoba Helena, Swart, Newc. n. Bat. Bij DOVER, 3 Julij; Geertruida Femina, Bakker, ..., n Plymouth Bij PORTSMOUTH, 4 Julij • Hillegonda, Hcikamp, Rio Grande n. ■Antwerpen. GRANGEMOUTH, 3 Julij; Commerce, Konning, Drammen. HULL, 4 Julij; Alida Atlriana. Kramer, Nyckjobing. POOLE, 4 Julij; Dieverdiena, do Jonge, Groningen. A BEK DEEN, 4 Julij; Johanna, Veldhuis, Petersburg. CHARLESTOWN, 3 Julij; Voorwaarts, Douwes, Bremen. - Amaiia, ö|niuge, Jansen, Hamburg. - Jantina, Douwes, id. LEITH, 4 Julij; Zwaantje Dost, de Jonge, Koningsbergen. - Jon-re Ger*&apos;t, Hazewinkel, Rostok. SHIELDS, 4 Julij; Aurora, de Jonge, Schiedam. - Catharina Johanna, «&apos;■^.^e.-Patriot, Dixon&apos; Dordrecht.-J.H. Meijer, Wilms, Schiedam. P A ™R?™ AND&apos; 4 Ju,&apos;J; Mol,y&apos; Westhoff* Amst. - Dolly, Mentz, Rott. *f- iH &apos; 3 Jul&apos;J&apos; s&apos;r*ns&gt; van Wijngaarden van Rees, Antw. - Mietje Sehonfeldt, van Dijk, Watchet. J -{r?SS?^ïEB *4 Jn,« ■ Flora&gt; Goyken, Groningen. 7»ISHPSBKO&apos; 3 JnlÜ ; Harmonie; Lever, Geile. LLYDE, 5 Julij ; County of Lanark, Battesby , Amsterdam. ANTWERPEN, 5 Julij; Godelevus, dc Boer, Saxkjöbine. £?£££ ££5T&apos;27 Juni&apos;; nillo«l»en Scholtens, Scholtens, Amst. CIENFÜGOS, 5 Junij; Loïs, Lewis, Amst. HAVANA, 10 Junij; Cuba Packet, Rapp, Amst. ii.7.éVIA&apos; 29 -A-P-&quot;l** Cornelia en Geertruida, Wielcma, Londen. — •*■« Mei, Friesland, Sipkes, Kio Janeiro. STRAAT SÜNDA, 10 Mei; Dordrecht, Loos, Bat. n. Rott. — 15Mei; «a Maria de Raath, de Boer, Padang n —18 Mei; Japan Packet, den gxter van den Brink, Rott. n. Nagasaki. — 21 Mei; Adelaide, Wijbrands, £_L. &quot;&apos; ShttnShae- —22 Mei; Celebes, Reuvckamp Gille, Samaran* n. o ~25 Mei&apos; Helen Baird, Harris. Soerabaya n. id. SAMARANG, 7 Mei; Dorothea Henriëtte, Ort, Rott. T UITGEZEILD. IEXEL, 6 Julij; Cornelia, Vorenkamp, Messina - de Hoop, Ouwehand - Birgitte Melehior, Harboe, Londen. - 3 Gebroeders, Kaspersma&apos; _«■ - Sippe Visser, de Jong, id. - Brotherlcy Love, Mofiet, Sunderl. - Sophiel »ulsen, Riga. ■ Rampachc, Jahn, Norrküping. - Neptunus, Danielsen, Zwe- Vt Margaretha, Olthof, Avontuur. A-n E&apos; 3 Jll&apos;&apos;J! Boreas, Mnuneke, Newc. - Cathalina van Calcar, Meijer, A\ S -t*ncretia* Bracht, Avontuur. j AMELAND, 4 Julij ; Hillechina, Joostcn, Kopenhagen. - Immanucl, dc &quot;ge, Aalborg. - Gesina, Bökcr. Hamburg. - Catharina, Eivcn, id. - Vrouw m. ï&apos;-7oss&apos;Altona*&quot; Drei Gebriitler, Katt, Hennen. - Byka, Gort, id. ULLLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Julij; Sophia Amaiia, v. Overklift, Singapore. - Aümiraal Ver-Hnell, S., Havre. - Balmoral, S., Plymouth. -Elizabeth, taml&apos;™a&quot;e&quot; Albcrt&apos; S*&apos; Hull* ■ Hammonia, S., Hamburg. «KILLLE, 6 Julij; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S., Skudenacss °&apos; S&quot; Harwich&apos; &quot; Arma&apos; S*&apos; Bergen. - Mazeppa, Olsen, K™AyENf5 Julij; Dclphin, Hoeksma, Amst. Hoffm,™ „ ,&apos; tr i ,J; Imi?e!ina Gooren, Menholt, Dokkum. - 5 Julij; mx.^raak&apos; Makkum- - Helena, Albers, Amst. vah J, _*IG, 2 Julij; Aurora, Brinkmann, Bergen.</p>
	<p>FALMOUTH, 4.Tulij; Amicitia, Viacava, Amst.-Industry,Murray, Rott.i Adelaide, Koch, Java n. Hamburg. COWES, 4 Julij; Maria Cornelia, Brinkerink, Stokholm. SHIELDS, 4 Julij; zeilkl.: St. Maartenshoek, Schut, Riga. GRAVESEND, 4 Julij; Hendrika, Bekenkamp, Zaandam. BORDEAUX, 3 Jnlij; Bordeaux, S., Rott. NEW-YORK, 22 Junij; zeilkl.: Fosca Helena, Ridder, Amst. — 23 Junij; Enterprise, Westerdagh, Savannah en la Mar.</p>
	<p>BATAVIA, 11 Mei; Willem Daniel, Zeylstra, Amst. — 13Mei; Holland, Auffmortb, Nederland. — 16 Mei; Celebes, Reuvckamp Gille, id. — 21 Mei; Juno, Nuss, id.</p>
	<p>SOERABAYA, 10 Mei; Solide, denßreems, China.-Helenßaird,Harris* Nederland. — 11 Mei; Nederland, van Steendcren, id. —16 Mei; Aeolus, de Vries, id. — 18 Mei; Japara, Zweede, id. - Soerabaya Packet, Olivier id. via Batavia. — 21 Mei; Nieuwe Waterweg, von Lindern.id. via Pasoeroean. BANJOEWAN GIE, 30 April; Henriëtte Elisabeth Suzanna, Meyboom, Schiedam. — 2 Mei; Cornelia Hendrika, van Straten, Amst. PANAROEKAN, 28 April; Otto, Stheeman Trosling, Nederland. - de Vrede, van Duyvenboden, id. TAGAL, 15 Mei; Fop Smit, Leverstein, Nederland.</p>
</text>
