<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 24 April, Z. W.; Adrien, Chauvelon, Nantes. - Comodore, Franks, Newc- European, S., Huil. (benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld.) VLIE, 24 April, Z.W.; Willem I, S., Hambnrg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 April, Z. W.; Italio, Scurich, Triest, l.v. Brouwersh. - Dankbaarheid,- v. d. Berg, Lissabon. - Vlaardingen, v. d. Boogert, St. Übes. - John Harriet, Joy, Newcastle. - Elisabeth &amp; Mary, Arno, id. - Merrimac, Patterson, id. n. Middelburg, als bijlegger. - Star, Lawrence, Hartlepool. - Mathilda Catharina, O verberg, Tstad. BBIELLE. 24 April, W.-, Avalon, S., Harwich. HAMBUEG, 22 April; Familietrouw, de Boer, Amst. - Hilke de Vries, Katt, id. — 23 April; Harmina, Emmelkamp, Brussel. Op de ELVE, 22 April; Johanna Heydorn 11, Köln, Rott. — 23 April; Amsterdam, S., Amsterdam. CÜXHAVEN, 23 April; Sylvanus, Hassing, Drammen n. Harlingen, met verlies van boegspriet, stengen, enz. CHRISTIANIA, 13 April; Neptun, de Haan, Harlingen. MALMÜ, 17 April; 2 Gebroeders, Butter, Amst. - — 18 April; Stad Workum, Eisenga, Huil. ELSENEUR, 21 April; Union, Hazewinkel, Praesto n. Kooger-Polder.- Rembrandt, S., Amst. n. Koningsb. - Astrea, S., id. n. id. — 22 April; N°. 1, Albrecht, Rugenwalde n. Amst.; met schade binnengesleept, na op&apos; strand gezeten te nebben. BREMERHAVEN, 23 April; Hanke de Boer, Schnrdt, Groningen. FALMOUTH, 22 April; Hendrika, Walvius, Zante n. Hamburg. MILFORD, 22 Apnl; Tonia, Haesloop Wemer* Newport n. Hongkong. Bii MUMBLES, 22 April: Sharon, Mitchell, Newport n. Dordt. . BB.IDLINGTON, 22 April; Hubertus. Nichols, Nieuwediep n. Seaham. ABEEDEEN, 22 April; Eoyal Dove, Urquhart, Amst. HULL, 22 April; Alberdina, van den Bos, Dordt. HABTLEPOOL, 21 April; Emma, Brandt, Schiedam. \ MIDDLESBEO, 22 April; Marie Prancoise, Donic, Amst. - Melbourne, ! ..., id. - Garibaldi, Nielsen, Schiedam. SHIELDS, 22 April; Columbus, de Jonge, Eott. - Triton, de Jonge, id. - 1 Jack Tarr, Quicq, Dordt. - Karsina, Oifers, Duinkerken. - Siewert en Johan, Looze, Eu. BOEDEAUX, 19 April; Girondo, S., Eott. POETO, 16 April; Elisabeth, Metns, Newc. St. ÜBES, 13 April; Lanrens, Noordhoek, Lissabon. St. HELENA, 15 Maart; Balisama (Ned. bark), Java n. Eott., 53 d. reis. Bij St. HELENA, 20 Maart; Nydia, Mc.lKerlie, Pasoeroean n. Amst.)</p>
</text>
