<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>Ri_ r &apos; i 24 Juny; Ml-nister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Omen, Christensen, , &apos;ga.-Jacobus Anthonie, Mellema, Dantzig. - Janus, Sörensen, Fredriksvt V&quot; Immanuel, Bjertness, Holrastrand. ___H?&apos; 23 JuniJ&apos;&apos; Piet Hein,Meijer,Petersb.-AlidaElisabeth,Potje- W&apos;.Nerva. - 2 Gebroeders, Hillenius, Windau. -Hendrik Jan Nassau, weitsema, Riga. - Anje, Munning, Christiania. - Geertruida, Dekker, wnstiansand. - Mmerva, Schuurman, Krageroe. - Christina Elisabeth, Arendahl. — 24 Junij; Will. Carel, Gudmundsen, Klostefiorden. - * r«deni_ Hendrik, Mulder, Frederikstad. #-&gt;LTKAMP, 18 Junij; Fokkelina Emmelina, Folkerts, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 Junij; Leeds, S., Grimsby.&apos;-Christel, Frietil?? Bremen-&quot; Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg. jjiiRIELLE, 24 Junij; Zealous, S., Harwich. - Bonna Römelingh, Visser, _, MAASSLUIS, 24 Junjj; Orion.S., Londen. - Prins van Oranje, S., u«inkerken. VLISSINGEN, 24 Junij; Frouwina Elisabeth, dc Jonge, Riga. BREMERHAVEN, 23 Junij-, Wilhelminc, Meijer, Anfst. „KOPENHAGEN, 20 Junij; St.Petersburg, Hoven,Petersb.— 21 Junij; Hofland, Hazewinkel, id. - Anja Sietsia, Huisman, Newc. , HAMBURG. 22 Junij; Petronella, Wirtjes, Altona. - Elve, S., Rott. — «-Junij; Hillechina, Wijnstok, Amst. WJXIIAVEN, 22 Junij; Jonge Barend, Prins, Termunterzijl. MREL, 18 Juuij; Voorwaarts, Ukstra, Dordt. - Aaltina, Lycken, id. HEMEL, 20 Junij; Wilhelmine, Schuring. Harlingen. n 16 Junij; Twee Vrienden, Ruige, Groningen. — 18 Junij; ptnahna van Calcar, Meijer, Amst. - Alpha, Jacobsen, Nederl. - Frithio&apos;f, £*uritzen, id. - Otto, Christensen, Nieuwe Diep.-Hendrik Westcr, Drent, &quot;Wdeaux. — 19 Junij; Urda, Nielsen, Amst. - Suzannah, Middel, Lon&quot;«J. - Catharina, Martens, Delfzijl. CIIRISTINESTAD, 2 Junij; Medea, S., Zweden n. Amst. öIOCKHOLM, 18 Junij; Diana, Fijn, Charlestown. ILLAU, 21 Jnnij; Frouwkje, Faber, Randers. , JVROONSTAD, 18 Junij; ïjakina, van Sluis, Bordeaux.— 19 JunijjZee&quot;°nu, Fencnga, Amst. -Lambértha, Karst, id. - Louise Helena, Visser,id.-*anana Wilhelmina, van Eyk, Dordt.-Hooite Wigher, Klazen, Galliër !i&quot; Sophie, Louws, Palermo. - Conflance, Brongers, Bordeaux. - Broeertrouw, de Groot, Antwerpen. NORRKÖPING, 21 Junij; Willem, Jansonius, Amst. pi/LSENEUR, 18Junij. Gepasseerd: Thor,Smith,Rigan.Amsterdam.-jrovidentia, Agerup, Dordt. n. Sundswall. — 20 Junij; Sooblomsten, Pe¦ji^cn, Hudikswall n. Amst. — 21 Junij; Dagny, Hemmers, Hernösand n. . edcrl. - Isaac Sannes, de Jonge, Liverpool n. Koningsberg. - Geertruida £&quot;a&apos; Schrikkema, Petersb. n. Londen. g!j DOVER, 22 Junij; de Vrede, van Rijn, Newc. n V*&apos;l DUNGENESS, 22 Junij;Estafette,Oepkes, Amst.n. Soerabaija.--1 °°Phandel, Verseeff, Sunderland n. Bat. - Jacobus, van der Tas, Sunder«nan.Amboina. FALMOUTH, 22 Junij; Bérénice S., Amsterdam n. de Midd. Zee. w) DEAL, 22 Junij; Vesta, van der Eyk, Rott. n. Singapore. fS,i HOLYHEAD, 22 Junij; Stel la, Gibson, Runcorn n. Rott. p 21 Junij; Ceres, de Boer, Nerva. — 22 Junij; Allegonda, Smit, petersburg. ÏARMOUTH, 22 Junij; Zenobia, Child, Harlingen. HONTREAL, 6 Junü; Raven, Harrison, Rott. A-WEST, 19 Junij; Maria, Tanteier, Antwerpen.</p>
</text>
