<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>Ui ,»•*•=-&apos; h*** &apos; •■-&apos;■■■&apos; •&apos; ••• ~ n 7;/&apos; &gt; Eut-gcr Hjkc j Stanb. Van 19 tot en met 25 Maart 1808. &apos;v BEVALLEN: L. Biebeek.geb. Heymans, D. ü. iweel. —K. F. Gestman, eeb. flarms, Z. —M. C. van der Vlisi. geb. Broekhnyzen, D. —J. Olivier, geb _e Graaf, Z. — L. li uilenbeek, geb. de Haas, D. —G. van der Plank , geb. de Graaff. Z. — J. C. Meijer, geb. Kleinen, D. -- A. Slikkelorum, geb. de Wit, D —M.Cerdyn, geb. Smit, D. — E. Blommesiein &apos;geb. Heins, D. —M. J. Lege!, geb. Korswagen.Z. — J. Perriti, geb. Plalleel. Z. — M. 1. Boogkamer, geb Brugman, Ü. — J. Elkerbout, geb. van der Vliet ,D —J. Warmerdam, geb&apos;van der Bosch . D.&apos;—J. H. Chimaer van Oudendorp.geb.Scheuer; I). —M. Monleba, geb. Vilders, D. —i U.&apos;J.&apos;M. Fontein, geb. »an Niehoff, Z. — J.C. Waasdorp, geb. Makko, D. — J. Smit, geb. de Vrind, D. — M. van der Erf, geb. vanden Berg, Z. — J. Pauw, geb. van Leeuwen, Z. — VV. D. Cailin, geb. van der Klugt, Z. — E. van der Blom, geb. Neuieboom, D. — A. H. Lens, geb. Schuller, Z.,-7 C.Milders, geb. Kranenburg, Z. — A. M. Bavelaar, geb. Biegstraaten, D.&apos; — A. Hanwijk, geb. Meurs, D. — P. Erades, geb. Neuleboom.D.— Jl E. Cornet, geb. Slar, Z. — M. Louwrier, geb. Slavleu, D. GEHUWD: J. D. Bobbers, wedr. en J. van der Nat, jd. —B. Dekker,jm. en N. Singerling, jd. — W.F. Neuteboom ijm. en M.Langezaal. jd. — G. van Evert, wed.en N. Mieremei, wede. —J. H. Buytenbeek, jm.en J. Bouter, jd. —. •W. F. vaii dêr Stad. wed.en J. S. Moelet, wede. ~, ~,. ;,.„,, ÓVEBLEDEN: K. van Proosdy,s7j. —S. A. Sprock, 53jl — H.Oostveen, D. 7 d. - ll.J.Üljee,s2j. —D. Visser.27j. —J.W. Filippo, Z.,2_ m.— V.&apos;.Loozen, D.,23j. —S. Frankhuizen, D.,2 m.en 16d. —H. van der Sleen, wed. J..W. van Wijngaarden, 75j. —H. Blommesiein, D., Id.—- J. Bausen, Z. 3m. —P. Hartevelt. geb. Cucler, 56 j. — M.Sloeke, D., _j.— C. Diemei, eeb van der Hert, 52 j. —S. Hirschig, 70j. —L. Moncouri, 49 j. —H. Bietkerk , wed. N. Fakkel.B6j. , , ~ . .</p>
</text>
