<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL,9Sept.,O.N.O.; 2Zusters,Feenstra, Londen.-Eva Maria, Nichols, Newc, - Enstace, Taylor, Snnderland. - Whina, Smith, Yarmouth. - Rotterdam, S., Pitea. - Memskiena, Oldenbarger, Osterrisoer. - Phoenix, Larsen, Drammen. VLIE,BSept, 0.N.0.; Grietje, Nieboer, Frederikshald. — 9 Sept.; Ecliptica, v. Heukelen, Öndsoen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Sept., N.0.; Maas, S,; Londen. - Ravensbury, S.. Harwiph. - Jtferwestroom, de Groot, Bergen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 9 Sept., N.0.; Staffa, S., Hnll n. Rott. PLYMOÜTH, 9 Sept.; Vooruit, Logger, Bat. n. Rott. Bij LIZ ARD, 3 Sept.; Helios, Sanders, New-York n. Rott. SHIELDS, 6 Sept.; Nieuwe Waterweg 11, Zwart, Rotterd. - Grondwet, Kamminga, Zierikzee.— 7 Sept.; Anna, Kraig, Koogerpolder. - Warwick, Brown, Nieuwe Diep. - Oronoco, Vint, id. - Hart, Milburn, id. - Pero, Wilson, id. - Nina, Earl, id.- Sisters, Partis, id. - Hawk, Morgan, id. - Planet, Campbell, Rott. - Waterwitch, Learlley, id. - Kjerteminde, Olsen, Dordr. - Avab.iHawksgejd, id. - Friendship, Roberts, id.- Meika Jaeoba, Wielen^, Amst &apos; &apos; _ , Bij BEACHÏ&quot;HEAD, 6 Sept.; Rotterdam, Jansen, Rott. naar Bat., alles wel aan boord. . LElTfl, 7 Sept.; Allegonda, de Vries, Stettin. - Maartje Boswijk, de Jonge, ui, Bij BRIGHTÜN, 5 Sept.; Havana Packet, de Boer, Antw. n. Havana, alles wel aan boord. MILFORDHAVEN, 7 Sept.; Columbia, Evans, Liverpool n. Dordrecht, ABERDEEN, 4 Sept.; Broedertrouw, Woltman, Stettin. GREAT YARMOUTH, 7 Sept.; Maryland, Tucker, Amst. - Isis, Smith, Rott. SEAHAM, 7 Sept; Flinn, Yonng, Nieuwediep. QUEENSTOWN, 6 Sept; Wilhelmina, Hazewinkd, Rio Qr^nde, SCILLY, 6 Sept.; Bato, Rotgans, Bat. n. Amst. LIVERPOOL, 7 Sept; Geertruida Janna, v. Heyningen, Bahia.</p>
	<p>HULL, 7 Sept.; Maria, Tunteler, Riga. IPSWICH, 5 Sept; Index, Long, Rott-John and Harriet, ¥oy, ici, HARWICH, 7 Sept.; Eagle, Hawkins, Rott. - Samaritan, Bradley, id. §UNDERLAND, 6 Sept.; Brilhant. Sanderson, Nieu-vediep.- Savah, Gibbs, id. - Wm, and John, Stafford, id. - Rover, Consittid. - Mary, Furlong, id. — V Sept., Ejisabeth, Ward, id. - Swan Davison.&apos;id. - Elisabeth, Jai-vis, id. TRIEST, 1 Sept.-. Libra, Dirksen, Newc. HALIFAX, 20 Aug.; Lèda, Muller, Liverpoql. NEWGASTLE (N.Z. W.), 23 Ju_j; Jaeobus, v. d, Tas, Udfy (nsl-trok 7 Ju}ij n. Jay&gt;,)</p>
</text>
