<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 9 Junij; Ivanhoe. S., Leith. VLIE, 8 Junij; Willeml, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Junij; Bczoekie, Reekers. 1 _naroeka.ii, 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Anc, Storm, Riga. - Henriette Susanna, v. Wijngaarden, id. - Anna Catharina, Eusen, Aalesund. CUXHAVEN, 8 Junij-, Ahvinc,Hertzer, Amsterdam. DANTZIG, 5 Junij; Alberdina, Schuur,Harl.- Meermin, Smit, Bremen. CHRISÏTNESTAO, 16 Mei; Kleinkinderen, van der Wal, Nederland. CHRISTANU, 25 Mei; 11,-.!lum, Bienks, Dokkum.- Argo.Alta, Harl.— 27 Mei; Argo, Schwarts, Amst.i— 28 Mei; Auje„Munning, Lenuner. RIISOER. 24 Mei: Jenny, Zachnriassen. Amst. n. Riga. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 5 Jnnij; Belina, Pott, Riga n. de Eems. — 6 Junij; Agnes. Mentz. id. n. Amst. KOPENHAGEN, 5 Junij; Maria Anna, Rutters, Riga. NAPELS, 31 Mei; Persa, Drenth, Rott. - Margaretha Arendma, de Jonge. Hamburg. SUNDEELAND,7 Junij: Maassluis, Kttcliler. Schiedam. LYNN.7 Junij: Harmiiia, Enhnelkainp. Koningsb. HULL, 6 Junij: Caroline Henriette,Klcist, Riga. HARTLEPOOL, 7 Junij; Zeedina, Jansen, Delfzijl. - Jonge Albert, Kwint, Putbus.</p>
	<p>SHIELDS, 6 Junij; Albion, Todd, Amst. — _ Junij; Anja Sietsia, Huisman, Harlingen. EYEMOUTH, 5 Junij; Jonge Eicka, Klein, Christiania. LEITH. 6 Junij; Helena, de Jonge, Drontheim. CHARLESTOWN, 6 Junij; Princc of Sa„e Coburg, Storm. Rott. Bij DEAL, 4 Junij; Jetskalina Everts, de Jonge, Triest n. Rott. CADIX. 2 Junij; Otto, Sap. Cardiff. &apos; CARTHAGEN A, 4 Junij; Befje Pronk, Vos, Malaga. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 9 Junij; Constantia, Brinkerink, Soerabaya. - Estafette, Oepkes.id. VLIE, 8 Junij; Julie, Bruuu, Frederikstad. - Josephine, Jahnsen, Drobach.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS. 9 Junij; Margaretha, Thesing. Philadelphia, A. - Zephyr, S., Londen. - Pelican, S.&apos;, Liverpool. - Louise, S.. Grangemouth. - Lord Raglan, S.. Newc. - Pcre Lcgal. Cadet. id. - Anna Maria, v. d. Kooy, Archangel., - Marie Coralie, Bakker. Gcffie. - Sophie, Pedcrsen. Riga. - Sophie, Asken, Oostzee. - Amazon, Norman, id.-Venator, Reinertsen, Sta vanger. - Niels Herzberg, Utne, id. - Alpha, Jacobscn, Erederikstad. BRIELLE. 9 Junij; Ravensbury, S., Harwich. ÏRAVEMUNDE, 7 Junij; Hendrika Alida. Keppel, de Oostzee. SWINEMUNDE, B Junii; Dina Adriana, Kwint, Engeland. DANTZIG, 6 Juny; Alida Sara, Mooi, Newc- De Spruit, Pott, Gr imsby Johannes Antonie, Mellcma, Amst. HARTLEPOOL, 7 Junij; Boreas, Munneke, Harlingen. - Zeeploeg, Ludêling. Kroonstad. LI VERPOOL, 7 Junij; Catharina, Visman. Bat, FALMOUTH, 7 Junij; Lord Collingwood, Dodds, Rang. n. Schiedam. - Concordia. Wijgers. Maroïm n Clyde. VERA-CRUZ, 10 Mei; Elsicna &quot;Geertruida, Mulder, Tonala. HAÏTI, 11 Mei; Concordia, Klein, Hamburg. —13 Mei; Sperwer, Huis, man. Falmouth.</p>
</text>
