<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Oct., 0.N.0.; Choice, Hardcastle, Newc Tallula, Davies,_id. - ürace, Carr, id. - Ophir, Hean.id.-Friends, Well&apos;s id - Bervvick, b., id. - Archimedes, Fretwurst, id. - Mate, Gialich id - Mari&apos;i Terragello id. - Ersilia Nabro, id. - Port Wallace, Sayers, Sunderland. - Albert, S., Huil. - Greath Yarmouth, S., Harwich. - Eagle, Hawkins Ipswich. - Emily, Wright, id. - Industry, Dickenson.id. - Thames, Cracknell id. - John, Higgs, id. - Albion, Mawen, Koningsb. - Thetis, Morck id - Dorothea, Bamck, id.-10 Junij, Wittenhagen. id. - Ebenhaezer, Osoütsèn id. - Anno Harboe, Hansen, id. - Morris, Hutleston, id. - Callona, Ton essen, id. - Maria, Hansen, id. - Zeevaart, Mulder, id. - Mercur, Malebien id.-Guilette, Goldrig.id.-Courier, Hansen, id. - Amalia, Thorsen Stavanger. - Margareth Mime, Morck, Ohristian.- Amazone, Petersen Noorwegen. - Nordstern, Rofer, Heppens. &apos; MAASSLUIS. 9 Oct., Compasr.; Brother&apos;s Succes, Wellard Rochester - Colonel Evans, Reynolds, Rye.— 10 Oct; Leo. S., Londen. -Elsie Maxwell, Leith. - Elisakth, Pigott, Newc. r Carl Milberg, Schmidt id Ronaldus, Green, id. - Grace, Roxberry, id.- John Isabella, Younger id - Pride, Cowley, id. - Graye August v. Rantzen, Svarrer, id. - Maria SÖrvnesen, id. - Harmony Richmond, id. -Paul, Knuth, id. - Matthëw £ Arm pson Sunderl.-P^oeniï,Jacksonid..Caesar.Rehbock.id.-Elirabeth Brodie, Brodie, id.- Catharina, Limschen, id. - Albert Dienis id Viomm Walkea, Middlesbro - Hendrika Glinnnenga Avont&apos;e^tSX- Jonge Rieka, Klein, id. - Jacoba. Boerhave, id. e&apos; BROUWERSHAVEN, 10 Oct., 0.Z.0.; Batavia, Zwanenburg Rott n Batavia. B&apos; &quot;¦u&apos; WASA, 26 Sept. Zeilklaar: Catharina, Drok, Lubeck. HELSINGBORG, 28 Sept.; Zeilklaar: Catharina, v.d. Meulen Engel . A Gebroeders, Woudstra, id. &apos; g STETTIN, 8 Oct.; Johanna Margaretha, Ei, Nantes. BESGEN, 23 Sept.; Annaehiena Henriette, v. d. Meulen Pruisen — 25 Sept; Gesina Alida, Meijer, Kopenh. &apos; STAVANGER, 27 Sept.; Hendrika Ebelina, Jonker, Nerva.</p>
</text>
