<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 23 Mei; Z&apos; W.; Albert Tholen, Mennen, Porto. - Vri-sland, Jelsma, Londen. - Mentor, Toering, id. - Carbon, S., ïfewe, - Alert, S.,Hull. - de Haan, Dekker, Wmdau. - Christine, Ateahamsen, Stromstad. - Wilhelmina Magdalena, Jansen, Gothenburg. — 24 Mei; Capella, Christoffer, Baltimore. - Johanna Petronella, Hillebrandt, St. Übes. - Diana, S., Londen. VLIE, 22 Mei, W.Z.W.; Willem I, S., Amsterdam. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 23 Mei, Z. W.; Svenborg, Rasmussen, Bahia. - Laertess, Witt, Banana. - Hopewell,Pearson, Londen.- Wesley, Nuttall, Jersey. - Sterling, Hutchinson, Newc. -Vixen, Crewe, id. - Violet, Richardson, id. - Elise, Frank, id. - Light &amp; J-_n, Robinson, id. - Effort, Miller, Sunderland. - Martlet, S., JI»_L - Elve, S., Hamburg. — 24 Mei; Urania, S., Antw. - Mar«»reih£ Allan, Butler, Liverpool. - Angelina, Evans, Whiteh. - üieaner, Besford, St. Davids. - Levant, S., Gothenb. BRIELLE, 34 Mei, Z. W.; Admiraal Ver-Huell, S., Havre. - Prins van Oranje, S,, Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwieh. LEER, 19 Mei; Geertruid», Pronk, Harl. PILLAU, 22 Mei; Orion, Buiten, Cette. - Gesina, Bontekoe, o&lt;Je»see.. Familietrouw, de Boer, Sleeswijk. KROONSTAD, 18 Mei; Maria Reifina, de Groot, Rott. Areo, Brouwer, C«tte, - Alida, Sprik, Newc. - Hydra, Munneke, id. - Jantina Christin», Bekkering, id. —19 Mei; Orion, Braamhorst, id. - Cornelia, Drenth, id. Bi- U9J£&amp; 22 Joachim, Hettmeijer, Bat. n. Amst. HARWICH, 21 Mei; Eendragt, de Boer, Nyekiöbing. HULL, 21 Mei; WUhelmina, v. d.Weyden, Cadix. SHIELDS, 21 Mei; Lion, Chisholm, Harlingen. - Comforter, Halversen, Schiedam. CARDIFF, 21 Mej; Noord-Brabant, Overklift, Rott. - Ida, Knippe, id. - Enrifle, Evans, id. NEWPORT, 20 Mei; Hendrika, Dik, Gloucester. TEIGNMOUTH, 21 Mei; Diana, Lnder, Amst. Bij DEAL, 21 Mei; Fortuna, Hoogewerf, Rott. n. New-York. DEAL, 21 Mei; Rio de la Plata, Horner, Antw. n. Cardifl. St. VALERY, 19 Mei; Anna, Huisman, Groningen. DUINKERKEN, 18 Mei; Granvilaise, Lebourgeois, Eott. HEEL VA, 16 Mei; Maria, de Jonge, Tarragona. GIBRALTAR, 16 Mei; Rotterdam, S., Lissabon, vertr.&apos;naar Napels.</p>
</text>
