<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 23 April; Verwisseling, Boon, Konstantinopcl. - Diana, S., Londen.-2 Zusters, Feenstra, id. - Arm, Raddler, Newc. - Mathilda Arm, Au-, gard, Sundcrland. - Alert, S. Huil. - Sophia, Hansen, Avontuur. VLIE, 22 April; Minerva, Schuurman, Christiansand. - Catharina Visser, de Vreede, id. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. — 23 April; Zcnobia, Child, Yarmonth. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 23 April; Huydecoper, Reinders, Bat. via Brouwershaven. - Minister Thorbecke, Kannegieter, id. via id. MAASSLUIS, 22 April; Thomas &amp; Isabella, Nicholson, Newc. - Leo, Robertson, Sunderland. - Sarcelle, Lancelot, id. - Ange Gardieu, Vince, id.--23 April; Thames, Cracknell, Ipswich. - Elisabeth &amp; Jane.Esson, Newc. - Hart, Cloack, id. - Emile &amp; Marie, Leclerc, Middlesbro, - Bcute, Johnson, Hartlepool. - Thames, Longstaff, Sunderland. ZIERIKZEE,22 April; Choice, Grant, Blakeney. HAMBURG, 22 April; Gécrdina Geertruida, Kramer, Fridericia. ALTONA, 22 April; Jaeomina, Kuipers, Hamburg. . CUXHAVEN, 20 April; Maria Hinrichs, Hes, Portugal. - Elzina, Nanninga, Petersb. EMDEN, 19 April; Margatka, Mudder, Amst. - Jenske, Smit, Leith.- Hansina, Obes, Hoogezand. - Johannês, Obes, id. — 20 April; Hilke Alberdina, de Vries, Londen. - Suzaua, Barghoorn, Gron. • Antje, Muikau, Hoogezand. BRAKE, 12 April; Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge, Rustringersiel. NORDEN, 19 April; Catharina,Brandt, Gron. STETTIN, 19April; Vesta, S., Amst. DANTZIG, 19 April; Louise, Reetzke, Amst. —20 April; Friedericke Louise, Lcrcke, Schiedam. FREDERIKSTAD, 4 April; Minerva, Rafen, Nederland. ODENSE, 10 April; Dorothea.Anthonsen, Nederland. LONDEN, 22 April; Zeilklaar: Jacobus Begeman, Reyer, Elseneur - Battruida, Kladder, Kiel. - Jautina Alida, Texer, Wolgast. SHIELDS, 20 April; Louis Meijsr, Holtgreve, Bat. — Zeilklaar: Assiduous, Nisbitt, Nieuwe Diep. HARTLEPOOL, 20 April; Alida, v. d. Veen, Koningsbergen. SUN DERLAND, 21 April; Robert and Mary, Morgan, N ieuwo Diep. - Maxwell, Dyer, Schiedam. LIVERPOOL, 20 April; Jantina Margaretha, Peper, Riga. - Catharina Geerdina, de Groot, Petersburg. BELFAST, 17 April; Hennctte Susanna, van Wijngaarden, Liverpool. ANTWERPEN, 22 April; Willem van den Bey, Lutje, Avontuur. - Nicolaas Albert, de Jonge, id. HAVRE, 21 April.; Levant, S., Rott. TRIEST, 15 April; Zeilkl.: Otto, Sap, Hamburg. ALGOABAAI, 13 Maart; Kaapstad Packet, Niewold, Falmouth. HAVANA, 30 Maart; zeilkl.: Napoleon, Arriola, Amst.</p>
</text>
