<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>B _,f. TEXEL, 25 Junij; Hilga &amp; Elconora, Aabye, Drammen. —• -&apos; « Brtftheftelius, Groote, Banjoewangie, vertr. 12 Febr. - Diana, S., Lpndc óesp,id.&apos; ley Love, Maffel, Sunderland. - Vivid, Betlingfield, id. - TBJr,;,7ODhe«e|1&apos; Hollander, S., Huil. - Sophia, Paulsen, Riga. - Amphitnte, l/Mis .f . Söderhamn. - Meinskina, Oldenburger, Memel. - Gustaaf, deoouy Agostine, Cheyne, Ivictue. . . ctaal, V^ VLIE, 25 Junij; Concurrent, Teensma, Petersb. - Christina, o _ w&lt; dau. - Grietje, Nieboer, Riga. - Jonge Andrics, Stellens, id. &apos;„.^„burg* Pettersen, Stockholm. - Mathilda, Johnsson, id. - Johanna, upaDtï.- Memel. - Herstelling, Lukkien, Koningsbergen. - Nautilus, Gut) - Sicka, Douwes, Arendahl. -naai - J&quot;*&quot;1 HELLEVOETSLUIS, 26 Junij; Candace, Plaas, Alg&lt;»-^Agatbi&gt;. Pearce, Furse, Barcelona.-Trois Soeurs, Chauvelon, Nantes. -•» ,batros, S-&gt; Sloot, Rédon. - Nora, S., Londen. - Berly, Jones, Port Madoc -j* Jleerj, Liverpool. - Therese, S., Grangemouth. - Osbornc, S., Leith. - A &apos;jiartle- Newc- Billy, Roberts, id.- Waterwitch, Bilby, id.- Fairey Q&quot;«enircéms, pool. - Mina, v. Keulen, Ranea.- Koophandel en Zeevaart, dea &quot; y/n* bau. - Ellida, Larssen, Malmö. - Helene, Jaencke, Ystad. - Lnar jj^,,, Wilhelmina, Funder, Hobroe. - Abelona, Ohle, Randers. - U»&quot; Bode, Odensee.  BRIELLE, 26 Junij; de Maas, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., w- terngg«&apos; GOTHENBURG, 18 Junij; Levant, S., Rott. (22 dito denvaai keerd). - Brittannia, Valk, Warkworth.  pstavi»- By GOUDSTAART, .. Junij; Cortgene, Wemmerus, Rot* PAR, 22 Junij; Voorwaarts, de Vries, Penrhyn. Hormanll&apos; &amp; LIVERPOOL, 23 Junij; Hirundo, Towning, Amst. - »er Groningen. —24 Junij; in lading: Argo, Brouwer, ~PeUT3°&apos;xf-Mtia, G&apos;bs . I SHIELDS, 23 Junij; Eendragt, Dorenbos, Harlingen. - &quot; - &amp;»_?_, Dordrecht. - Jantina, Blaak, Rugenwalde. - Battruida, J°&quot;K&apos; b„rg.-W Louise Sophia, Hollander, Yarmouth. - Vertrouwen, Kal, n lenshoek, Schut, Sandwich. TRIEST. 23 Junij; Hermanna, Pybes, Newc. .</p>
</text>
