<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>xJi am-,,2. April; Diana, S., Londen. — 3 April; Australië, Lucas, Bat. - Catharina, Drok Nantes. - Gesina Alida, Meijer, Liverpool. - Ocean, Sandstrom, Newc, - Nordstar, Tobiassen, Predrikshald.- Eme lic, Riehelsen, Preari_«t»d. . Mmd«t, Ar?«sen,.CariBtiania. - Unie, Parrel, Avontuur. - Adelhoid, Kramer, id. - Vriendschap, Elles, id. - 2 Gebroeders, Prins, id. - Jan Hendrik, Slager, id. - Grietje de Weerd, Pothuis, id. OSTMAHORN, 29 Maart; Anna, Hoekstra, Sandwich. — 1 April; Verwisseling, Scholten, Newport. - Burgemeester Danneberg, Visker, Bristol. - de Haring, Boomgaard, Gloucester. - Alida, Star, Southampton. - Coneordia, Oosterveld, id. - Maria Beerta, Roosjes, Londen. - Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, id. - Zwaantje Groenendaal, Dekker, id. - vr. Geertruida, Heijinga, Ipswich. - Zwaantje Elisabeth, Jager, Newc. - Trijntje Meijer, Tonkens, Kopenh. - Byka, Gort, Aalborg. - Froukje, Faber, Denemarken. - Renskea, de Veen, id. - Hillegonda Maria, van der Me uien, Noorwegen. - Johan Gerard, Huges, id. - Jonge Roelof, Donwes, Bremen. DELFZIJL, 30 Maart; Geerdina, Wijpkes, Noorwegen.-Helena, Dclger, Leer. - Margaretha, Dclger, id. - Anna Maria, Engels, id. - Susanna, Hostcr, Einden. — 31 Maart; E va, Bakker, Noorwegen. - Gesina, Siemers, Norden. - Helena, Gurski, Leer. - Goede Verwachting, van der Ley, id. - Dc Hoop, Drewcs, Emden. - Martha, Siemers, id. - Herstelling, Lukkien, Avontuur.— 1 April; Catharina Hofland, Uazcwinkel, Newc. - Grietje Huisman, Kuipers, Noorwegen. - Trientje Veldkamp, Koopmans, Elmsharn. - Maria, Pronk, Avontuur. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 3 April; Hendrika Margaretha, Bakker, Bari. - Noordstar, Brouwer, Dysart. - Vesta, Tobbens, Newc. - Zwaan, Riedijk, id.- Van, Thompson, id. - Cornelia, Voogd, id. - Maria Reifina, de Groot, id. - Crescendo, Vos, id. - Castle Eden, Huiiter, id. - Victoria, Fredberg, id. - Christiane, Muller, id. - Bermuda, Chappel, Sunderland. - Aleida, Eeckhoff, Middlesbro. - Thetis, Butterill, id. - Thames, Crackuoll, Ipswich. - Dankbaarheid, Boon, IJsland. - Harmonie, Doewcs, Windau. - Magdalena, Buining, Liban. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 April; Sara, S., Londen.—3 April; Henderika Bus, Rott. n. Bat. MAASSLUIS, 3 April; Thames, Longstof, Sunderland. - Bcssies, Mordev, id. - Vigilantia, Janssen, id. - Pheil, Wel, id. - Cappellc, Weilkers, Middlêsbro. - Princess, Parker, Newc. - Houthandel, v. d. Stolk, Fredcrikshaven. - Salus, Sylvertsen, Seclcsung. VLISSINGEN, 30 Maart; Familietrouw/Woortman, Lissabon.— 1 April; Julius, Schuurman, Sunderl. - Jant. Catharina, Dijk, Rostock. - Marg. Gesina, de Groot, Bergen. - Eendragt.de Boer, Kopenh. - Annechien en Jantje, Vencma, id. - HUI. Scholten, Scholten, Dantz. - Aikea, Dijk, Avontuur. VEERE, 1 April; Canellc, Steward, Middolb. n. Sunderland. LONDEN, 1 April; zeilkl.: Gebroeders Visser, Faber, Amst.</p>
</text>
