<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 Aug.; Hoop, Jelsma, Londen. (Benevens de schepen per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 7 Aug.; Pax, Mellema, Memel. - Ida, Wolkammer, Dantzig. - Drie Gezusters, Pluktje, Wis mar. • Maria, Meinsma, Frederikstad. - Geertruida Speelman, Speelmaö, id. - Jonge Jacob, Herman, id. - Sylvia, Smith, Drammen. - Sieka, Douwes, Arendahl. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 8 Aug.; Brothers&apos; Succes, Hobart, Rochester. • Balmoral, S., Cardiff. BRIELLE, 8 Aug.; Batavier, S., Londen. - Cologne, S , id. - de Maas, S., id. - Pacific, &apos;S., Harwich. *H &lt; BOLDERA, 1 Aug.; Mercur, Cassens, Amerika.-Burgemeester v. Settan, Holvast, Zaandam. - Johanna Paulina, We93cls, Schiedam. - OldAmbt, Sehotema, id. - Jcannette, Ehrenfried, Nederland. - ConstantiH, Zeiss, Elseneur. - Zeemeeuw, van Wijk, id. - Spr uyt, Pott, id. BRAKE, 7 Aug.; Elsina, Nanninga, Avontuur. HAMBURG, 5 Aug.,* Zeemeeuw, van der Meer, Petersburg. — 6 Aug.; Anna Catharina, Henning, Londen. — 7 Aug.; Trijntje Gesina, Bos, Noorwegen. ALTONA, 7 Aug.; Heinrich, Lücken, Asist. VAREL, 2 Aug.; Elisabeth, Pekelder, Marieasiel. DANTZIG, 5 Aug.; Vesta.S., Amst. . L, . ABO, 27 Julij; zeilkl.: Celeritas, van der Leest, de Noordzee. LONDEN, 5 Aug.; zeilkl.: Grietje Teisman, Rasker, Falkenburg.-Anno, Veldkamp, Zwolle. - Lubbegina, de Jonge, Zaandam. — 7 Aug.; Willemina, de Jong, Koogerpolder. - Renske, Nepperus, DOVER, 6 Aug.; Jantje Doornbos, Addens, Newcastle. DÜNDEE, 5 Aug.; Alberdina, Lever, Helmsdale. ABERDEEN, 4 Aug.; Hillechina, Scherpbier, Leith. FRASERBURGH, 4 Aug.; Lambert, Kramer, Dantzig. SUNDERL AND.S Aug., William, Scot, Rott.-Pieter,Bekkenng,Sevilla. MIDDLESBRO, 5 Aug.; Secundus, Rozema, Koningsbergen. CARDIFF, 4 Aug.; Cornelia, Voogd, Horsens. NANTES, 5 Aug.; Bonne Esther, Calve, Amst. - Marie Alexandnne, Lecarré, id. . , BORDEAUX, 5 Ang.; Martha, Postema, Koningsbergen. BATAVIA, 14 Jnnij; Fanny,Wuift&apos;,Nederland. —23Junij;zeilklaar: Nederland, van der Eb, id. - Paul Johan, ICooy, id. (via Samarang). - Maria Diederika, v. Marion, id. (via Soerabaya). - Whampoa, Metz, id. (viaSamarang). - Wilhelmina, Braver, id. (via Pekalongan). - Jacoba, Schaap, id. (via id.) SWATOW, 25 Mei; Malvina, ..., Newchwang. NAGASAKI, 11 Junij; Minister van Hall, de Haas, Taku CbuFoo.</p>
</text>
