<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Sopt.; 3 Gebroeders, Bijkerk; Londen.- Dawson, Alwel, Newc.-Hawk,S., Hull. J VLIE, 20 Sept.; Lion. S., Londen. - Zorgvliet, Garnaat, Archangel. - Elisabeth, van Wijk, Petersburg.- Emerutia, Christensen, Cliristinastad.- Emil, Meijer, Bergen. - Grietje, Nieboor, Frederikstad. - Catharina Cornelia, v. d. Stolk, id. - Alida Giezen, Nieland, Osterisoer. - Nyssiena Prak, Arendahl. - Creole, Larsen, Drobach. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Sept.; Lilly, Ambroose, Philadelphia A.- Ceres, Meul dijk, St. Übes. - Feyenoord, S., Londen. - Seagull S., Hull. - William Coleman, S., Goole. BRIELLE, 21 Sept.; Ravensbury, S., Harwich. LEER, 14 Sept.; Dorothea, Brahins, Koningsbergen. - 15 Sept.; Helena Johanna, Rozebooin, Harlingen. - Uit Vriendschap, Bolmeyer, Groning EL VE, 20 Sept.; St. Philip, Sehwanenberg, Rott. - Johanna Mathilda Toosbuy, Zwijndrecht. STA VANGER, 2 Sept.-, Venus, Holm, Schiedam. -Frigga Thorsen id WISMAR, 18 Sept.;Geerdiiia Geertruida, Kramer Frauekcr SWINEMUNDE, 19 Sept; Jacoba, Muntcndam, Rott. ELSENEUR, 17 Scpt.; gepasseerd: Harmonie, Doewes, Petersburgn Dordrecht. — 19 Sept.; Artizan, Lucas, Amst. n. Dantzig. - Pieter Visser Nieuwediep n. Sund.all. HOLTENAU, 15 Scpt.; gepasseerd: Jantina Petronella, de Boer, Kiel n. Amst. Bij DEAL, 18Sept.;Boreas, de Jongo, Vlaardingen n. Gibraltar. Sirius, van Rees, Amst. n. Batavia. RAMSü ATE, 19 Sept.; Zeeplocg, Lndeling, Londen n. Swansea. ABEBDI EN, 18 Sept.; Hermine Olberdinc Archangel By ISRIXiIAM, 19 Sept,; S.ibina, Martin, Rott, n. 1 .yinouth FALMOUTH, 19 Sept.; Ee_ta,Leinminga,Maroi_i. - Espcrance, Dik, Amst. n. Beyruth. HOL V HEAD, 19 Sept.; Anna, Collings, Liverpool n. Dordt. - Conqueror, Herdby, id. n.id. SWANSEA, 19 Sept.; Gesina, van Veen, Havre. SHIELDS, 19 Sept,-, Orinoco, Vint, Dordt.- Nevada.Bartlet, Schiedam. - Dorens, Munnck. Hiirliugen. NEWPOKT, 17 Sept.; Rosinante, Zomerdijk.Bristol. GENT, 20 Scpt.; BarbaraHendrika, Meijer, Riga. BORDEAUX, 16 Sept.; Catharina, de Wall, Avontuur. TRIEST, 16 Sept.; Zeemeeuw, Sikkema, Ancona. MALTA, 14 Sept,; Oceaan, Post, Vlaardingen. HAVANA, 18 Aug.; De Hoop, Zeegers, Montevideo. — 29 Aug.; Frcia, Carls, Vlissingen.—3o Aug.;ouba packet. Rapp, Amst., (in quarantaine).</p>
</text>
