<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>Tan 7 tot en met 13 November 1867. BEVALLEN: A. E. Buitendijk, geb. Provoo, Z. — M. W. Jasperse.geb.van Zomerveld, Z. — C. Brouwer, geb. van der Reyden , D. —M. van der Linden, geb. Webbers, D. — M. J. Epskamp, geb. Bezier, D. — S. M. Veldhuyzen , geb. van Iperen, Z. — J. M. Cosler , geb. Vreeburg, Z. — M. C. Bodry, geb. Disseveld, D. —S. A. Voorhuyzen, geb. van Wel, Z. —C. E. Bruning, geb. Zijdenbos, Z. — M. van Egmond, geb. Dieben, Z. —C. den Hoed, geb. de Fey, D. — S. Chrisliaanse, geb. van den Bosch, Z. — C. Bey, geb. Broekhof, D. — S. J. Cuper, geb. van Noord, D. —A. van Thiel, geb. van der Kwast, Z. —J. P. Bekooy , geb. de Cler, Z. —E.C. C. Vergnnst, geb. van der Klugt, Z. —T. Schenkeveld, geb. van Leyden, D. — C. H. Hoogkamer, geb. Fakkel, Z. — 11. S. Uilenhout, geb. Milders, D. — J. C. P. Schneider, geb. — C. Regeer, geb. Lasschuit, D. —J. C. Konmann, geb. Speet, D. —J. M. Kallenberg, geb. de Beer, Z. GEHUWD: A. deMan.jm. en E. van Dorsten, jd. — IJ. Schouten .jm.en A. J. C. Duchatlel.jd. — 11. van Ulde.jm. en M. C. de Haas.jd.— W. de Vos, wedr. en W. van Laare, jd. —J. Molenaar, jm. Eu P. Sieval, jd.— P.Meijer, jm.en C. J. C. Schreuder, jd. — J.Smittenaar, wedr. en SI. Onderwater,jd. — F. Eikerbout, jm. en P. Privé&apos;, jd. — A. van der Henst, jm. en J. D. A. van Gysel, wed. OVERLEDEN: P. 0. van der Chijs, 65 j. - A. W. Suringar, geb. ten Cate, 58 j. —J. Oostveen, Z., 18jj. —J. Raaphorst, D., 3m. — A.S. Aldenhoven, D., 4m.—A. de Heyder, D., 14 d. —P. van Veen, 25j. —P. Overdijk, geb. Tijssen, 51 j. — G. Korenman, wed. A. van Biemen, 68 j. —N. 11. J. Z., 5 m. —W. van Deursen,soj. —J. C. Epskamp, D., 2d. —H. Tuinhof de Moed , D., 14 d. —J. Vielen, 61 j. —J. B. Samsom, Z., 4d.—S. M. Anakker, geb. Witmans,3sj. —J. W. van Gent, D., 4 j.en 9m.— A. Verstraaten, D., 9j. en 3m. — J. Klok, Z.,4m. — A. Starre, Z.. 3 m. — P. Mazurel,B2 j.— G. de lluu, 38 j. — M. J. F. C. Moltzer ,-83 j. —D. van der Mark, Z., Ij.</p>
</text>
