<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 26 Julij; Clémentine, Mnlet, Havana 1. v. Falmonth. - Eensgezindheid, de Waal, New-York. - Ranger, Andrews, Newc. - Swanland, S., Huil. - Richard Cobden. Stibolt, Riga. - 6Söstre, Erichsen, Sundswall. - Jorgen Lorentscn, Kjonning, Drammen. - Lympha, Allurn, id. VLIE, 26 Julij; Lubbiena, Hazelhoff, Gothenburg. OOSTMAHORN, 22 Julij; Freukje, Faber, Koningsbergen. DELFZIJL, 22 Julij; Anna -f-Elise, Fimmen, Frederikstad. - Helena Johanua, Rozeboom, Leer. - Anna, Obes, Emden. — 23 Julij». Celeritas, van der Leest, Gotheuburg. - Engeliua Fransen, Dost, Leer. - Vr.Helena, Giursky, id. ? TERMUNTERZIJL, 20 Julij; Antina, Bohlen, Leer. - Dorothea, de Vries. id. - Antina, de Vries, id.. (zijn op 22 Julij derw. teruggekeerd). HELLEVOETSLUIS, 26 Julij; Otto, Gronnobeck, Akyab.-Hebe.Kiehl, id., 1. v. Brouwersh. - Aurora, S., Londen. - Osborne, S., Leith. - William Coleman. S., Goole. - Gironde, S., Petersburg. BRIELLE, 26 Julg; Bradford, S., Grimsby. -Thamcs, Cracknell, Ipswieh.-Ea»le, Hawkins. id. ; MAASSLUIS, 26 Juiij», -Seagnll, S., Huil. HAMBURG, 25 Julij; Eire&apos; S., Rott. L AURVIG, 11 Julij; Jan Gijsbert, Smit, Termuiiterzg&apos;l» BERGEN. 11 Julij; Ettii*a,oldeHbnrgcr, Charlestown. RANDEKS, 12 Julij», Jantina Catharina, v. Dijk, Newc. WOLGAST, 21 Julij; 4 (ieznsters, Wagenmaker, Kopenhagen. DANTZIG, 22 Julg; Roelfina Johanna, Drewcs, Breinen. BOLDERA, 18 Julij; Enigheden, Larsen, Amst. — 20 Julg; Aeatha, Schnur id. - Inimanuel, Bartncss, Nieuwe Diep. - Johan Gerard, liuges, Zoltkamp - Jonge Ricka, Klein, Warkworth. - Margaretha Antiena, de Boer, Kopenhagen. - -Margaretha, Branibcrpcn, Arendahl. NER\*A vóór 20 Julg; Brodrene, Ohnstensen,Nieuwediep.-Ariel, Ihlen. Terschelling. -Maria, Pronk, Liverpool ,_-&quot;_, i vi s!i,*viriTß whlHi c*epass.:Z\va-intina ihelina, de Boer Sap, Dantz. n Ant„-AnaMetta Ulrichs, Gothland n. Newc. HEPPÊNS _3Julü- Fronkè Dijkstra, Hamstra, Londen. I LON DEN 21 jüliji&apos; Catharina, Boon, Petersburg. -25 Julg; Margaretha Hendrika, Dateuw, Wismar.</p>
	<p>Bg LIZARD, 20 Julij; de Hoop, Boer, Bat. n. Rotterdam. COLCHESTER. 24 Julij;Catharina, de Tries, Dantzig. CHARLESTOWN, 23 Julij; Neptnnus, van Gorkum, Leith. ROCHESTER, 24 Julg; Invicta, Hopkins, Rotterdam. STOCKTON, 23 Julg&apos;; Geerdioa, Nieboer, Petersburg. HULL. 24 Julij; Catharina, Lucht, Petersburg. BRIDLINGTON, 24 Julij. In de baai ten anker: Cordelia, Hoskins, Dordt n. Shields. NEW-CASTLE, 21 Julij. In lading: Jennike Hendrika, Stoorvogel, Lissabon. DUNDEE, 24 Julij; Alida, Nagel, Nerva. DIEPPE. 23 Julij; Eendragt, Vuursteen, Stolpemunde. GIRGENTI, 14 Julg; Adelaide, de Haan, Messina. GENUA, 22 Julg; Willem 111, S., Amst, ,</p>
</text>
