<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Mei; Coop Roclfs Sikkens, Schaaf, Londen- 2lsroc^ ;(1, Newc. - Zephyrus, Elliot, id. - Elisabeth, Pigot, id. —; 3 *»»_ JoDS*^*. &lt; Kempema, Londen. - Bona Roëmeling, Visser, id. - E*sw&gt; &gt; jje»dl VLIE, 2 Mei; Josephine, Hanscn, Drobach. - Concoi p, Oudsoen. - Catharina Elisabeth, Pot.id. _  paler°&apos; °&apos;-tfi&apos; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Mei; Thetis, de Zeeuw sabeth Austin, Finley, Runcorn. - John James, Clayton, pj^po.&apos; il) 3lj. &apos; liam &amp; John, Nunn, Boness. — 3 Mei; Kate &amp; Janß, SeWe», sc„, lf Nichols, Londen. - Cosmopolitan, S., id. - J. H. van Gcnw Gothenbnrg, S., Gothenburg, 1. v. Brouwersh. ...ich. flott6* &apos; BRIELLE, 3 Mei; Albert, S., Huil. - Pacifie, S.,W^2h_^lh »&quot; BROUWERSHAVEN, 3 Mei; General Lee, S, W»&quot;* (benevens dc schepen per telegram gemeld). Vork- VLISSINGEN, 3 Mei; Maria Louisa, Brandt, New* STETTIN, 29 April; Anke, Bleeker, Hamb. retif/ SWINEMUNDE, 30 April; RhOnc, S., Rott, April;» DANTZIG, 29 April; Agatha, Schuur; Amst. — pjgsi.&quot; Bracht, Newc. - Wieka, Wortel, Delf. Ijl. [ . Vries, Ai»9f&apos; T,cft&apos;• ELSENEUR, 28 April; gepasseerd: Jacobus, de vr .^yw^fop* Sperwer, Schaap, Bergen n. Rusland. —29 April; iro. Dantzi|&apos; jJ. »&apos; Dantzig n. Nederl. - Anna Margaretha, Olthoff, New£»^ £._-, S., Amst. n. id. - Triest, S., Rott. n. Konmgsb. - Jong gc,,,e Triest. - Agatha, Valom, Bergen n. Riga. **____«. Odense bc. / RENDSBURG, 28 April; gepasseerd: Rema, W»1 sdeo - * dam. — 30 April; Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Anibt. .„,, Schoon, Grcnae n. Nederl, Wnvcum. - Ment___s, 110 LONDEN, 2 Mei; Sippe Visser dc Jong,Snn,HoU»eS&apos; id. - Eendragt, Bijkerk, id. - In lading :A^* Rosa Alba, Arnold, id. - Phemie, Arnold, Middelburg _ Bij DEAL. 1 Mei; India Packet, idrTos-Ayi&apos;^ «■ **?•&amp;!&gt;* FALMOUTH, 2 Mei; Visser, id. n. Antvv. - Junior, TuntelerSminia Cardltt. Jacoba, Reindcrs, Alcxandrie. - Z.rcon, ft «at»* aiu»</p>
	<p>B .S?LA.}?&apos; Apri,; St!entJê Eoemeling, Bruins, Rio-Janeiro naar &apos; G__d„ g&apos; »&apos; Rlewertdina. Kieviet, id. n. Altona.- Courier, Claassen, Rio wuiae n, Antwerpen. niT^S_frESTOFT&gt;29 APrili Petronella, Leieher, Newc. n. Bat. IrvTO EY&apos;27 APril; Koll°&apos; ScheP&apos;RottdeT™ « 00L&apos; l Me&apos;i Hermanna, Veling, Nantes. - Nicolaas Albert, CW„f&apos; ntw&gt; &quot; Osprey, S., Rott. — 2 Mei; Frouwina Elisabeth, de Jong, T* -In lading: Helena, de Jonge, Dantzig. b ao » v?&apos;* Mei; Hortense Sidonie, Gautier, Harlingen. «KANTON, 29 April; Johanna Charlotte, v.Veen, Bcrwick. pt _&quot;_&amp;0W&gt;l Mci:Jolul &amp; Harriet, Joy, Amst. Sttv £E&apos;2 Me!; Cherokec&gt; Torrance, Rott. Buroi fRLAND&apos; 1 Me&apos;i Amaranth, Hall, Amst.- George _Elisaboth, Usr|?s&apos;. Schiedam. - Thomas, Longstaff, id. Ateip -PS&apos; ï Mei; Janna MoiJer&apos; Datema, Amst. - Reine des Angcs, Thnm &quot; Glom&apos; Buister, id. - Eleanor, Adams, Nieuwediep. - Elisabeth, Co_.hP!!(r&gt;n&apos; ld&apos; &quot; McS Leo&apos; Brown. id. - Emily,Mitchell,id. - Constance, uott. - Melby, Houlsby, id. - Van, Thompson, id. - Elisabeth Jane, jT&quot;n&gt; id - Hart, Cloack, id. - Rosina, Daniel, id.-Waterwich, Bilby, Dordt. - Olsen «&apos; f .nt.chard&apos;id-&apos; Graces, Coward, id.-Deo, Mallet, id. - Twa Systrar, «__&gt;«&apos; bc™cdam-&quot;JuHo eu Sophie, Rasmussen, id. - Courier, Meuldijk, Zietoout h &quot; Utharma&gt;dc Vries, Southampton - Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Yartham t &quot; Annechma Henriette, v. d. Mculen, Rochester. - Alida, Star, Sou- EenT &quot; r 6ebr°eders, Woudstra, Londen.-Maria Beerta, Roosjes, id.- Hrvrv DoornDOS&gt; Exeter. - Martha Theresia, Visser, Antwerpen. r_ir„ HEAD, 1 Mei; Symmetry, Davis, Liverpool n. Dordrecht. TÏ&gt;7_;EY&apos; 3° APril: Wesley, le Couteur, Rott. T Vm?N&apos;3o APril! Thomas Campbell, Green, Rott. MttuV &apos; l Mei; Justus- Strackholder, Groningen, wóld id BSB]Ro&apos;&apos;l Me&apos;i Béontine, Gruselier, Rott. - Immanucl, Groene- Joh_IwTLEPOOI&quot;28APr; 1; Thelina, Dekker, Aberdeen. — 30 April; inEldeib Barsen, Schiedam. r t^WERPEN, 2 Mei; Holyrood, S., Eotterdam. MARSEILLE, 1 Mei; Bérénice, S., Amst. St m»X&apos;2G April; Irénc&apos; S- MiddeU- Zee. TAi) _ES&apos; 19 1&apos; Vertrouwen, Teensma, Lissabon. JAHRAGOSA, 23 April; Speculation, v. d. Kooy, Barcelona. Nffw v 9&gt;A&apos;23 April; Kogina, Peper, Sevilla. *- W-VORK, 19 April; iv lading: van Sehack Retschcndorf, Bruss, Amst.</p>
</text>
