<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 24 Julij; Beurs van Amsterdam, Tofte, Sunderl. - Pravidentla, Sorensen,, Umea. - de Vrede, Naess, Riga. - Richard Cobden, Stibolt, id. - Tartar, Heap , Sundswall. - Soeskummeren , Lorensen, Frederikstad. — 25 Julij; Wilson, Rich, Sulina. - Vriesland, Boontje, Londen. - Christina Vos, Riga. - Willem Frederik, Visser, id. - Neêrlands Vlag, Meeter, id.- Scotia, Lorensen, Sundswall. - Tre Vermer, Hansen, Bogensee. - Lympha Allurn, Drammen. - Foreningen, Seeberg, id. - Presto, Thomassen, id. - Judith, Stibolt, id. - Ogir, Pehrson, id. (benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld.) VLIE,|24 Julij; Nora, S., Lond. - B.reas, Munncke, Newc. -Anna Luitsia, Jager,J Riga. - Jantje, Nicuwold, id. - Johanna Elisabeth, Helmers, Meinel.- Alyda Anthonia, Visser, Dantz. - Wiebo Jacobs, Visser, Leba. - Concordia Haut, Straalsund. - Terra Nova, Abel, Frederikstad. -Freyer, Pederscn, id. - Hendrika, Kolman, Osterriisoer. - Grietje, Nieboer.id. ■ Anuechiena, Blouw, Christiansand. - Niord, Andersen, Drobach. - Minerva, Boe, Holmstand. —• 25 Julij; Frits &amp; Betsy, Stunt, Riga. - Minna, Heeren, Dantzig. - Concordia, Thomsen, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 Julij; Cornelia Hendrika, Swart, Banjoew., 1. v. Brouwershaven. BRIELLE, 25 Julij; Albert, S., Huil. - Rcbecea Abrahamsen, Norbey, Pernan. BROUWERSHAVEN, 25 Julij; W. D. Sarah, Clarke, Pcntowan n. Dordt. - Een schip in het gezigt. ZIERIKZEE, 25 Julij; Luconia, Admiraal Jz., Banjoewangie n. Rott., vertr. 21 Febr. GEESTEMUNDE, 24 Julij; de Goede Verwachting, Muller, Hamburg. HEPPENS, 20 Julij; Catharina, Ulrich, Rott. LIBAU, 14 Julij; Grttina, Gortmaker, Newc. ELSENEUR, 20 Julij; gepasseerd: Bordeaux, Ouendag, Petersb. n. Newburgh. — 21 Julij ; Jacob Synes, Schut. - Triest, Buys. — 22 Julij ; Triton, Bnrghout. - Jantina, Eofting. - Alida, Sprik..- Anna Augusta, Kuiper.- Wiarda Hendrika, Meezcnbroek. - Johannes, de Boer. - Gebroeders Visser, Faber. HOLTENAU, 19 Julij; Gepasseerd: Èlschlea, Albers, Praestoe n. Nederland. — 22 Julij; Hendrika, van der Mcnlen, Randers n. de Maas. TONNINGEN, 18 Julij; Gepasseerd: Vriondenlust, Koops, Hartlepool n. Steenwijk. —20 Julij; Tjakkina de Boer, Post, Dokkum n. Aarhuus. — 21 Julij; Aurclina Gruno, Stuitje, Nestved n. Nederland. Johanna Christina, Heida, Dantzig n. Dokkum.-Frau Foskea, Jansen, Friedrichstadt n. Nederl. LONDEN, 24 Julij; Lizzie, Earnshaw, Rott.- Wilhelmina, de Jonge, Groningen. - Lubbegina, de Jonge, id. - Rosé, Tasker, Middelburg. - In lading: Maria Hendriks, Hes, Koningsb. Bij DUNGÈNESS, 21 Julij; Archipel, van der Gaauw, Triest n. Hamb. F ALMOUTH, 23 Julij; Gerberdina &amp; Jeannette Emilie, Kuiper, Laguayra n. Hamburg. - Didalo, Havanna, Galatz n. Amst. Bij FALMOUTH, 22 Julij; Occanus, Dirksen, Rott. n. Cardifl. Bij AVIGHT, 22 Julij; Catharina Jaeoba Henriette, Tonjes, Rotterdam n. Cardiff.</p>
	<p>Bij PORTLAND, 21 Julij; Senior, Bakker, Amst. n. Bat. DUNDEE, 21 Julij; Queen, Steel, Rott. ABERDEEN,2I Julij Hillechina, Scherphuis, Petersb. BONESS, 22 Julij;Eendragt, Doornbos, Leith. SHIELDS, 22 Julij; Gratitude Kolk, Amst. - Ceres. Remmers, id. - John Rnthenford, Chilvers, id. - Elisabeth, Yallop, Rott.-Hart, Cloak, Nieuwed.-de Hoop, Zegers, Dordt. — 23 Julij; Hugell, den Breems, Nieuwediep. HARTLEPOOL, 21 Julij; Martha, Banting, Amst. SUNDERLAND, 22 Julij; Pieter, Bekkering, Londen. WISBEACH, 21 .ulij; de Weldaad, Pik, Trilleborg. GIBRALTAR, 14 Julij; Jacobns, Wegener, Napels. GIRGENTI, 14 Julij; Jacobus, Wegener, Napels. LISSABON, 18 Julij; Hesperus, Muller, Rio Janeiro. St. ÜBES, 14 Julij; Verwisseling, Hetmeijer, Gibraltar. ____ NEW-YORK. 9 Julii; Catharina, Schultz, Rott.</p>
</text>
