<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Julij; Médéa, S., Stettin. - Cycloop, S., id. — 13 Julij; Advena, Hales, Newc. - Express, Lybeck, Wasa. VLIE, 12 Julij; Leentje Dost, Rasker, Yarmouth. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg. — 13 Julij; Herstelling, Lukkien, Newc. - Skulda, Tonnesen, Eisen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Jnlij; Oceanßride, Harrison, Londen.-John &amp; &apos;,Charles, Hopkins, Rochester. - Gazelle, Seagers, Shoreham. - Auspicious, Longmund, Newc. - Jules &amp; Charles, David, id. Thomas Varcoe, Conth, id. - Torn Rosé, Gilden, id. - Aneyo, Dickson, id. - Mary Ogle, Jones, id. - Romp, Mc&apos;Kenzie, id. - Caledonian, Newson, id. - Anna, Collins, id. - Elisabeth, Hurd, id. - Eliza, Thomas, id. - Alice, Meers, id. - Mary Arm, Matthew, id. - Leo, Robertson, Sunderland. - Albert, S., Huil.- 3 Soeurs, Chauvelon, Middlesbro. - 2 Systre, Ohlsen, id. - Jenny Liud, Eckles, Lynn.-Odin &amp; Catharina, Movig, Golf van Bothnie. - Mathilda, Jörgensen, Frederikstad. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 13 Julij; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S-, Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich. - Elisabeth, Schoon, Heppens. MAASSLUIS, 13 Julij; Houthandel, v. d. Stolk, Frederikshaven. ELSENEUR, 10 Julij; Johanna Petronella, Hillebrand, Petersburg. STOLPEMUNDE , 7 Julij ; Elsina, Mulder, Londen. LEBA, 8 Julij; Catharina, Duintjer, Dordt. DANTZIG , 10 Julij ; Ida, Wolkammer, Leeuwarden. LONDEN, 12 Julij; zeilkl.: Catharina, van der Meulen, Elseneur. DEAL, 11 Julij; zeilkl.: Elise, Nieboer, Brazilië n. Aberdeen. YARMOUTH, 10 Julij; Whim, Smith, Nieuwediep. MIDDLESBRO, 10 Julij; Adriana Francisca, van Eijk, Vlissingen. CH ARLESTOWN , 10 Julij ; Jantina, Douwes, Hammerfeit. SHOREHAM ,11 Julij ; Afina, Goossens, Avontuur. IPSWICH, 11 Julij; Maria Beerta, Roosjes, Avontuur. -Jonge Albert, Kwint, id. HULL ,11 Julij , Anna, S., Bergen. NANTES, 10 Julij; Orchidee, Rivet, Amst. - Deux Associés, Coriton, Rott. - Jonge 801, Kolk, id. - Elise, Briève, id.</p>
</text>
