<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 6 Aug.; Dankbaarheid, Kooi, Havana. - Revenna, Hanssen, Newcastle. - Dawson, Olouston, Sunderl. - Alert, S., Huil. - Anna, Korf ker, Malaga n. Petersb. - Elio, Baeke, Drammen. VLIE, 5 Aug.; Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELVOETSLUIS, 6 Aug.; Levant, den Breems, Napels.- Ai y Scheffar, S., Havre. - Feijenosrd, S., Londen. - Three Brothers, Charlton, Rochester. - Wesley, Lecouteur, Jersey.-Maria, Brooks, Swausea. - Gencral Lee, S., Dub&apos;in. - M. D. Sarah, Clark, Newc. - Sunbeom.Wrcck, id..- Ellen Neyerfield, Thompson, Sunderland. - Swallow, S., Huil. - Eagle, Hawkins, Ipswich. - Jan &amp; Jacob, Burghard., Riga. - Merwestroom, de Goede, Bergen. - Immanuel, Bjerdness, Holmstrand. - Greven Wedel Jarlsberg, Bakker, id. - Dio Palme, Gallas, Avontuur. - Mathilde, de Jong, id. BRIELLE, 6 Aug; Colletis, S., Goole. BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Aug.; Boni, Möller, Rott. n. Bat. MAASSLUIS, 6 Aug.; Eersteling, Wiersma, Newc. - Abelone, Clemmensen, id. - Aurora, Kuiper, Sunderl. - Aenie, Ankern, Kopenh. BREMERHAVEN, 3 Aug.; Rensina Willemina, Kramer, Kopenhagen. HAMBURG, 5 Aug.; Hillechina Margrietha, Blaauw, Amst. - Alida Margrietha, Meijer, Tonningen. STETTIN, 4 Aug ; Ida, Lukje, Fisherow. DANTZIG, 3 Aug.; Geerdina, Visser, Bremen. - Afina, Goossens, Leer.- Concordina, Naatje, Dordt. MEMEL, 1 Aug.; Harmonie, Dijk, Amst.- WilhelminaPetronella, Bijl, Rotterdam. KOPENHAGEN, 3 Aug.; Alida Dijk, de Haas, Dantzig. ELSENEUR, 3 Aug.; Margaretha, Brambergen, .. - Ago, Doewes .. - Iris, Roueour, Bordeaux n. Petersburg. LONDEN, 5 Aug., zeilkl.: Barbara Jonker, Oltmans, Newcastle. POOL E, 4 Aug,; Anna Gesina, de Vries, Newcastle. CARDIFF, 3 Aug.; Anna Maria, van der Kooy, Brazilië. GRANGEMOU TH, 3 Aug.; Grietje Koens, Kuiper, Faro. YARMOUTH, 3 Ang ; Zenobia, Child, Harlingen. SUNDERLAND, 4 Aug.; Come on, Routell, Amst. CHARLESTOWN, 3 Aug.; Elisabeth, Bijl, Hammerfest. ANTWERPEN, 6 Aug.; Alida, Veen, Avontuur. - Cornelia Catharina, Hage Joorn, id. PORT LOUIS, 27 Julij; EugèneFélix, Cassard, Rott. NANTES, 3 Aug.; Prudent, Baudry, Schiedam. NAPELS, 29 Julij; Courrier, van Vliet, Catania. St. HELENA, 22 Junij; Ouderkerk aan de Amstel, Dingemans, Java n. Rott. - Theodora Mechtelda, van Wijk, id. n. Amst. — 23 Junij; de Schelde, Hoefman, id. n. id. — 25 Junij; Hollandia, Wap, id. n. Rott. BATAVIA, 3 Junij; Soerabaya Packet, Olivier, Nederland. — 4 Junij; Nederland, van Steenderen, id. (6 dito Straat Snnda gepasseerd;.^ 14 Junij; Lammina Elisabeth, Pot, id. - Zeilkl.: Fanny, Wuift&apos;, id. - Nederland, van der Eb, id. CHERIBON, 29 Mei; Aeolus, de Vries, Nederland, (via Indramayoe). SOERABAYA, 26 Mei; Prins Carl, Hartzel, Nederland.— 28 Mei; Glencaple, Crowder, id. —30 Mei; Albert, Wegens, id.—4 Junij; Laura &amp; Adèle, Lund, id.</p>
	<p>PADANG, 23 April; Solid, Andersson, Amst. — 10 Mei; Ida Maria de Raath, de Boer, Bat. —27 Mei; Aleyone, Kruisinga, Nederland.</p>
</text>
