<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 29 Mei; Suriname, Middelberg, Boston, 1. v. Falmouth. - Wu stelling, van&apos;t Voer, Londen. - Brothcrley Love, Moffeth, Newc. - WW» Diana, S., Londen. - 2 Zusters, Feenstra, id. - Cornelia, de Jong,ia&apos; European, S., Huil. - Prins Oscar, Rood, Christiania. &lt;* VLIE, 29 Mei; Jacoba Lucretia, Maas, Riga. — 30 Mei; Union, HeiÊB sen, Drammen. ? OSTMAHORN, 25 Mei; Maria Henrichs, Hes, Stettin. -Johan Gerat&quot;* Huges, Noorwegen. DELFZIJL, 26 Mei; Zeedina, Jansen, Dantzig. ,roi; HELLEVOETSLUIS, 29 Mei;Margareth, Hall, Sunderland. - 30 4 Broeders, Emmelkamp, Londen. - Harriet^- Eliza, Gostelow, id. -&quot;%; truida, Rasker, Rochester. - Osprey, S., Liverpool. - Jane Ellen, Richa&apos; Whitehaven. - Hertha, Melson, Pernau. EMDEN, 21 Mei; Clio, Roskamp, Rotterdam. u;s, BREMERHAVEN, 29 Mei; Hilke Katt, de Vries, Amst. - Frau A»ra Voget.id. . „rj DANTZIG, 27 Mei; Ecliptica, Hoeksma, Antw.- Anna Tedora, W%t Varel. - Compagnie, Net, Fricdericia. - Alida Sara, Mooi, Randers. - reede: Sieka, de Groot, Lubek. MEMEL, 25 Mei; Bonna Roemeling, Visser, Koningsbergen. BOLDERA, 21 Mei; Clasina Aidina, Wirtjes, Amst. ALTONA, 28 Mei; Pietronella, Kort, Stavoren. nrCa, BERGEN, 16 Mei; Cornelia, van de Velde, Goole. -18 Mei; Saram»&quot; de Vries, Amst. - Arme et Marie, Legal, Rotterdam. LANDSCRONA, 21 Mei; Sieka, Venema, Dokkum. NED STADT, 20 Mei; Atticna Hendrika, Meyer, Stettin. ,u n. ELSENEUR, 25 Mei; Gepasseerd: Anna Augnsta, Kuiper, Dordrecht. -Johann, Tiddens, Memel n. Delfzijl. - Walhalla, £$¦$!), Nieuwe Diep n. de Oostzee. - Meteoi-, Andysijn, Rott. n. id. - j^&apos;Vjg-&apos; Hazewiukel.Hamburgn.Riga.-Jacobina,Maathuis Methein..Dg $, 27 Mei; Johannes, de Boer, Riga n. Nederl. - Arme Malene, Ander»t., . n. id. - 28 Mei; Anna Paulowna, S, Stettin n. Amst - Remeliaue«Jk Katoen. Hartlep. n. Nerva, •MathiWe,W»«ismaJDoïdre«htn.S«ndsn</p>
	<p>- - RENDSBURG, 27 Mei; Neptunu», van Gorkura, Harlingen. —27 Mei; Margaretha Antina, Speelman, Antw. n. Rostock. LuNDEN, 28 Mei; Anna Eüaabeth, Dik, Malmoe. • Sara, Stuit, Dordrecht. - Aurora, Badrock, Harlingen. Bij DUNGENESS, 26 Mei; Consul, Hallis, Liverpool n. Rott. FÜWEY, 27 Mei; Capella, Bate, Liverpool n. Harlingen. DROGHEDA, 21 Mei; Niessina Jacoba, Barelds, Passages. GOOLE, 28 Mei; Anna Margaretha, Hoeksma, Nerva. WESr HARTLEPOOL, 27 Mei; Neptunus, de Boer, Bremerhaven. LEITH,2IMei; Helen Bell, Smith,Rott. - Vriendschap, Lodewijks, Randers. - Alida Dijk, de Haas, Anclam. SHIELDS, 28 Mei; Evangelista, Califano, Dordrecht.- de jonge Gerrit, Hazewinkel, Stettin. - Nijverheid, Kernper, Koningsbergen. SUNDERLAND, 27 Mei; Koophandel, Verseeff, Amst. CADIX, 23 Mei; Bérénice, S., Genua. BORDEAUX, 28 Mei; Zephir, Zuyderduin, Rott. - Hydra, Rockwald, ¦ id. - Alfredo, Mendietta, Amst. — 30 Mei; Nina, S., Amst. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 30 Mei; Nora, S., Londen. - Vivid, Bedlingfield, Sunderland. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil (benevens het schip per tel. gemeld). VLIE, 29 Mei; Thekla, Odmann, Straalsund. - Castor, Olsen, Aasgaardstrand. OSTMAHORN, 25 Mei; Jacob Synes, Nip, Havre. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Mei; Trieste, S., Triest. - Eva, S., Londen. - Gazelle, Seagers, Shoreham. - Vartry, S., Dublin. - Clievy Chase, S., Newc. - Seahorse, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole. BRIELLE, 30 Mei; Leeds, S., Grimsby. BROUWERSHAVEN, 30 Mei; Hendrik Ido Ambacht, Bijl, Rott. n, Samarang. MAASSLUIS, 30 Mei; Middlesborough, S., Middlesbro&apos;. LEER, Jantje, Forma Jr., Amsterdam. HAMBURG, 26 Mei; Helios, Winters, Rio Grande. - 27 Mei; Hendrika Sicberlina, Kraan. Bremerhaven. TRAVEMUNDE, 28 Mei; Wijbrandus Udo, Kiers, Archangel. WISMAR, 26 Mei; Jacoba Catharina, Geltes, de Oostzee. SWINEMUNDE, 26 Mei; Alida, Borgman, Termunterzyl. - Eendragt Boer, Leith. - Roelfina, Prins, Bremen. DANTZIG, 26 Mei; Christina, Vos, Londen. — 27 Mei; Leonora, Jongebloed, Amst. - Zaanstroom, Visser, Huil. MEMEL, 25 Mei; Osiris, Warnekes, Brussel. — 26 Mei; Jacoba, Muntendam, Hamburg. BOLDERA, 23 Mei; Agatha. Schuur, Amst. - Melitta, Petersen, id. ¦ Dorette, Lenk, id. - Prithioff,Bjoness,id. - Antje Visser, de Jonge, ISte derland. - Familienshaab, Kruge, id. - Theodor,Tobbens,Maas. - Mar ffietha Alida, Duin, Elseneur. - Johanna, Witt, id. - AnnaWimann &apos;le\n, id. - Cornelia, Dekker, id. - Martha Theresia, Visser, id. - Constantia, Zeiss, id. - Maria, Meinsma, id. - Elisabeth, Arends, id. — 25 Mei Reform, Gabrielsen, Nederland. - Brödrene, Christenson, id. - Henriette Susanna, v. Wyngaarden, id. DOVER, 28 Mei; Anna Margaretha, Veldkamp, Groningen. CORK, 26 Mei; Eliza Hunter, Moore, Amst. LIVERPOOL, 27 Mei; Elisabeth Helena, Coerkamp. Harlingen. MIDDLESBRO, 28 Mei; Jonge Aukj e, Balk, Gothenburg. LOWESTOFT, 28 Mei; Helen, Reynolds, Rott. n. de Noordknst. PLYMOUTH, 28 Mei; Havelock, Taw, Liverpool n. Zierikzee. HULL, 28 Mei; Amicitia, S., Bergen. BORDEAUX, 26 Mei; Cornelia Wilhelmina, Hoeksma, Petersburg.</p>
</text>
