<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10 Dec.; Nora, S., Londen. - Alert, S., Huil. - Jacoba Cornelia, Fokkes, Grimsby. - Tubal Cain, Cann, Petersb. - Caroline Louise, Söderström, Windau. VLIE, 7 Dcc; Cornelia, Dekker, Frederikstad. — 8 Deo.; Bordeaux, Ouendag Azn., Dantzig. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Dec.; Justitia, Damman, Venetië. - Maria Stuart, S., Leith. - Admiral Cator, S., Hartlepool. - Burgemeester v. Setten, Holvast, Dantzig. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 9 Dcc; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Raveasbnry, S., Harwich; beiden 10 dito derwaarts teruggekeerd. — 10 Dcc; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Cologne, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 10 Dcc ; Staffa, S., Leith n. Rott. BREMERHAVEN, 8 Dcc; Martha, Topzant, Antwerpen. CUXHAVEN, 8 Dcc; Eppo Hendrik, Schut, Zante. - Eensgezindheid, de Waal, Buenos-Ayres. SWINEMÜNDE, 8 Dcc; Cycloop S., Amsterdam. FREDRIKSVAERN, 27 Nov.; Gebroeders, Loodijzen, IJstad, n.Schied LONDEN, 9 Dcc; in lading: Petronella Johanna, Warnaar, Batavia. DEAL, 8 Dcc; Lodewijk, Bax, Rott. n. Banana. Bij DEAL, 8 Dcc; Margaretha Jantina, de Boer, Dordt n. Nantes FALMOUTH, 8 Dcc; Elisabeth Maria, Smoor, Londen n. Brazilië LIVERPOOL, 8 Dcc; Ena Elisabeth, Smit, Koningsbergen CARDIFI^ 7 Dcc; George Cafiero, Rogers, Dordrecht. FINDHORN, 7 Dcc; Jonge 8011, Kolk, Petersburg. DARTMOUTH, 8 Dcc; Macassar, van Bentveld, Rott. n. Japan. SCARBOROUGH, 8 Dec. Allegonda, de Vries, Malmoe. WHITBY, 8 Dcc; Brillant, Goodsir, Rott. NEWCASTLE, 6Dec; In lading: Susanna, Middel, Lissabon.-Vr. Clara, Po3t, Oporto. SHIELDS, 7 Dcc; Margaretha Hendrika, de Boer, Colchester. BORDEAUX, 5 Dcc; Elisabeth, Botje, Triest. BARCELONA, 4 Dcc; Aaltje, Hoedemaker, Swansea. LIVORNO, 1 Dcc; Mina, Hansen, Vlaardingen. MADERA, 15 Nov.; Sunda, van den Bolk, Glasgow, 1. v. Plymouth (verok 17 dito n. Batavia). St. HELENA,24 Oct.; Queen of the South, Wilkin, Algoaßaai n. Londen. — 25 Oct.; Almelo, Tjebbes, Bat. n. Amst. — 27 Oct.; Arrow, Hartley, id. n. id. —29 Oct.; Maria Adolflna, Blom, id. n. id, hebben de reizen voortgezet. gAvf NA, 11 Nov.; Zuider. .e, de Jong, Amst. x- N^f^MA, 6 Sept,; D. T. Visser, v. d. Linden, Yokohama. —18 Sept.,- Jingel, Appel, id.. Japan Packet, van den Brink, id. / i ITTrrPT*17&apos;KTT D HELLEVOETSLUIS, 9 Dcc; Prins Carl, Hartzell, Brouwersh. - 10Dec; Levant, S., Havre.- Feyenoord, S., Londen.- Zephyr, S., id. - Lucy, Cleary, Newc. - Seagull, S., Huil. - CoUetis, S., Goole. - Alpha, Frocken, Herwegen.</p>
	<p>BRIELLE, 10 Dec.; Orion, S., Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 10 Dcc; Sara, S., Londen. BREMERHAVEN, 8 Dcc; Maria Gezina, Mooi, Groningen. HAR BURG, 1/8 Deo.; Ida Gesina, Egberts, Groningen. TRAVEMUNDE, 8 Dcc; Jantje, Zuidland, Avontuur. DANTZIG, 7 Dec.; Rimini, Vissering, Hartlepool. - Gebroeders Coerkamp, Hoeksema, Antwerpen. LONDEN, 9 Dcc; zeilkl.: Domina Geertina, Wolters, Amst. GRIMSBr, 6 Dec.; Sophia, van Neord, Alicante. - Jacoba Cornelia, Fokkes, Amst. LEITH, 8 Dcc; Catharina, de Vries, Methel. PAIMBOEUF, 7 Dcc; Charles et Jules, David, Rott. GENUA, 5 Dcc; Voorwaarts, Doewes, Messina. HAVANA, 13 Nov.; Havana Packet, Harken, Antwerpen.</p>
</text>
