<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Nov.; Maria, van Duyvenbooden, Villanova, 1. v. Lissabon. VLIE, 20 Nov.; Paquobot, Coriton, Vanne3. 1 HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Nov.; Dankbaarheid, van der Wal, Bilbao. -, ] Rollo, Schep, Londen. - Louise, S., Grangemouth. OOSTMAHORN, 16 Nov.; Johanna, Brouwer, Bremen n. Antw. — : 17 Nov.; Anna Elize, Lukje, Carlscrana n. Rott. BREMERHAVEN, 20 Nov.; Drie Gebroeders, Klein, Amst. - Catharina Margaretha, Beek, Antwerpen. - Vr. Wiegertje, Luikinga, ... KIEL, 18 Nov.; Geerdina, Visser, Stettin. KANSÖ, 13 Nov.; Sophia, de Haan, Gothenburg 11. Londen. KOPENHAGEN, 10 Nov.; Heyo en Dieke, Doyon, Petersburg, (vertrok n. Bremen.) PREDERIKSHAVEN, 13 Nov.; Renske, Nepperu . Eanders n. Engel. ELSENEUR, 17 Nov.; gepasseerd: Jonge Rieka, Klein, Windau n. Rotterdam. — 18 Nov.; Agatha, Bloos.- Lambenha, Karst. TONNINGEN, 15 Nov.; gepasseerd : Elise, Lukje, Carlserona n. Rott.- Sieka, Venema, Landscrona n. Schiedam. - Fraukea, Watjes, Lubeck n. Groningen. - Twee Gezusters, Meijer, Stettin n. id. — 17 Nov.; Vr. Charlotta, Noordenbos, Nerva n. Amst. ROCHESTER, 19 Nov.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rott. RAMSGATE, 19 Nov.; Hillechina Reina, Muntendam, Nieuwpoort n. Cardiff. FALMOUTH, 18 Nov.; Johanna Christina, Leclerq, Rott. n, Melbourne.- Arendina, Bocrhave, Rio-Grande. LIVERPOOL, 17 Nov.; Thecla Maria, Muller, Minatitlan. — 20 Nov.; Tjetska, Doewes, Bordeaux -In lading: Mentor, Schuring, Aspinwall. HARWICH, 19 Nov.; Agatha Ebelina, Hoekstra, Groningen. IPSWICH, 19 Nov.; Alberdina Ed-ina, Uchtman, Groningen. SHIELDS, 19 Nov.; Wilson, Bieb, Amst. - Èlisabeth, Yallop, Rott.- Albion, Montgomery, id. - Gesina, de Jonge, Schiedam. - Mcg Leo, Brown, Dordt. - Hillechina, Gruppelaar, Hardwich. - Dariington, Raby, Dolfshaven. SUNDERL AN D, 19 Nov.; Jabez, Brody, Rott. - Rover, HUI, Nieuwed. HOLYHEAD, 19 Nov.; Valencia, Matheson, Gla*gow n. Zierikzee. CARDIFF, 17 Nov.; Anna, Keyser, Duinkerken. PLYMOUTH, 18 Nov.; Balmoral, S., Rott. n. Bristol. St. NAZAIRE, 19 Nov.; Fcnna Gesina, Jonker, Riga. CADIX, 12 Nov.; Maria Johanna, van Gelderen Sr., Rott. GIBRALTAR, 13 Nov.;Zuidlaren, Drent, Triest.(vert. n. Rott.) PHILADELPHIA (A.), 7 Nov.; Sirene, Hermans, Rott.</p>
</text>
