<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>¦ TEXEL, 17 Oct,; Börénice, S., Nicolajeff. - Victoria, Couland, Girgenti. - M. J. Enthoven, Stomp, Londen. - 2 Zusters, Feenstra, id. - Emelie, Pearson, Newc. - Hart, Mann, id. - Margareth, Johannsen, Sund3-wall. - Ogir, Pehrson, Drammen. - Enigheden, Mathisen, id. - Pilen, Andersen, Osterrisoer. - Christiua Elisabeth, Takes, Arendahl. VLIE, 15 Oct; Baudiua,Pool, Boness.-Gesiua Alida, Botje, Petersb. - Cecilie, Grönerup, Randers.- Maria, Hansen, Karebecksminde.- Johannes, de Boer, Frederikstad. - Argo, Alta, id. - Elisabeth, Zeven, id. — 16 Oct; Zephyr, S., Londen. HELLE VOETSLUIS, 17 Oct.; Europa, Lupcke, Bat. n. Rott, l.v. Brouwershaven. - John &amp; Charles, Charlton, Rocnester. - Pclican, S., Liverp.- Bill Point, Joknson, Newc. 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Hillechiena, Hooghoudt, Petersburg. - Haabet, Knudsen, Drammen. - Friesland, S., Amst. BRIELLE, 17 Oct; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 17 Oct.-. Catharine, Hunter, Newc. n. Rott- Duisburg, Holljes, Rott. n. New- Vork. - Argocy, Swift, Callao n. Rott. MEMEL, 12 Oct.; Johanna Maria, Schummelketel, Sunderland. SWINEMUNDE, 14 Oct; Henriette, Kuiper, Bergen. BOLDERA, 12 Oct.; Pax, Mellema, Schiedam. - Heinrich, Rotgers, Rott. - Maria Catharina, Wessels, Delfzijl. — 13 Oct; Catharina Regina, Wulf, Delfzijl. - Annechina, Velt, Gent. - Renskea, Voogd, Aalb. - Trientje Gesina, Bos, Harl. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 12 Oct; Sedig, Jacobsen, Umea n. Harl. ELSENEUR, 15 Oct. Gepasseerd: Rieka, Puister, Petersburg naar do Noordzee. - Aüen Smit, Boswijk, Riga n. Amst RENDSHURG, 12Oct Gepasseerd: Amanda, Lutjens, Rott.n.Stettin. — 13 Oct.; Jacoba, Muutendam.Malmoe n. Gron. — 14 Oct; Familietrouw, de Boer, Aarhuus naarAinst. — 15 Oct; Lena Catharina, Ewen, Ustad n. id. LONDEN, 16 Oct.; Stad Worcum, van &apos;t Veer, Worcum. Bij DOVER, 13 Oct; Arendina, Boerhave,Nrw-York u. Rotterdam. Bij NE WH AVEN. 15 Oct; Souburg, Swart, Newc. n. Java. STOCKTON, 14 Oct; Ellen Kerr, Mc Laren, Rott —15 Oct; Electra, Mitchell, id. ROCHESTER, 15 Oct; Invicta, Hopkins, Rotterdam. FALMOUTH, 14 Oct; Grietje, Legger, Cardiff n. Rott. — 16 Oct; Resul t, Petterson, Amst. n. Swansea. CARDIFF. 13 Oct.-, Conference, Cook, Rotterdam. LIVERPOOL, 14Oct; Heoreiivoen,Prins, Hambtirg.-GesinaDorothea, de Uoer, Amst, — 15 Oct; Vision, Hasselmau, Rotterdam. HARTLEPOOL, 14 Oct; Nautilus, Steffens, Rotterdam. SHIELDS, 15 Oct; Persevurance, Scott, Rott. -Drie Gebroeders, Koog, Petersburg. GIBRALTAR, 5 Oct; Willem lU, S., Amst. n. Ancona. - - 6 Oct; Jeannette, Duiven, St D#mingo n. Genua. MESSINA,2 Oct; Cornelia, S., Napels. NE 3Maria, Mulder, Tasko.</p>
</text>
