<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10Aug.; AukjeGepkelina,Duintjer, Neweastle.- Brilliant Mc Grehsry, Ivichtout. VLIE, 9 Aug.; Lion. S., Londen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Aug,; Aoadla, Huyser van Reenen, Bat. 1 v Brouwershaven. - Ellen Stewart, Shaw, Baltimore 1. v. id. - Dankbaarheid, v. d. Berg, Lissabon. - Feijenoord, S., Londen. - William Coleman, S., Goole, - Anncitia, S., Bergen, B RIELLE, 10 Aug.; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich MAASSLUIS, 10 Aug.; Admiraal Verheull, S., Havre. - Edith S Huil. &apos; &apos;</p>
	<p>CAROLINERZIJL, 6 Aug.; Vrouw Maria, Bonker, Harlingen. HAMBURG, 8 Aug.; Jantina Potrouella, de Boor, Amersfoort. - Hen» drika. Pijbes, Tarragona. CHIUSTIANU, 1 Aug.; Martha, Topzaud, Antwerpen. DANTZIG, 7 Aug.; Roelfina Johauna, Drewes, Amst. STOKHOLM, 7 Aug.-.Médóa, S., Amst. SANDHAMN, 5 Aug.; 2 Gebroeders, de Groot, Amst. KROONSTAD, 10 Aug.; Piet Hein, Meijer, Amst. VAREL, 8 Aug,; Hennanna, Veling, Dantzig. ALTONA, 8 Aug,; Johanua, Meijer, Santos. ODENSE, 28 Julij; Anna, Hoekstra, Newc,. ELSÊNEUR, 5 Aug.; Boris, LewerdowVtz, Schiedam n. Libau. - Vrede, Aacss, Nieuwediep n. Sundswall. - Yalkyrien, Bjonnes.id.n. de Oostzee - Skogman, Johusen, Amst. n. id,. Geertje Elisabeth, Borg, Delfzijl n. id. - Albertha Koenielnigh, de, Vries, Methei n. id. - Isaak Sannes, de Jonge, n^l^8!,&apos;&quot;,11- I V^&quot;,&quot; &quot;^&quot;laSletria, Huisman, id.n. Macduff. - Ulricitn. Dik, Stettfo ii. •Junderl.- Gnetie, Scholtens, Newc. n. Petersb.- Gesina.de £ocr, Harlingen n. id,» Bordeaux,Ouendag,id.n.Memel.-Joh.Christianc, Jorgenseii, Amst. n, Riga.-Euighedeu, Foyn, Nieuwed. n. Sniidsw.- Venskabctl!. Abrahamseii, id. n. id. - Anna Geertruida, van Ingen Newhaven. ii.de Oostzee. - de Vlijt, Engelsman, Alloa u. id. - Alpba, Jacobsen. Nieuwediep n, id, Stjemen, Torstensen, Rott. n. id. — 7 Aug.; Alfen Knudseu, Nieuwediep n. id. Bij SOUTHWOLD, 6 Aug,; Herman Albert, Potjewijd, Petersburg o. Londen. BEI.FAST, 8 Aug.; Goneral Lee, S., Rott. DUBLIN, 8 Aug,-, Meindina, ..., Livomo. GIUMSUY, 8 Aug.; de Hoop, Pott, Bremen. SUN DERLAND, 8 Aug.; Union, Zealand, Nieuwediep. SHIELDS, 8 Aug.; Friends, Wclls, Dordrecht. - Tiialia, Downiug, id. - Exertion, Elder, Vlisiduaen. STOCKTON, 8 Aug.; Libra, Klein, Petersburg. MESSINA, 30 Julij-, Sophia, van Noord, Amst. NAPELS, 2 Aug.; Willem de Derde, S., Amst. BOSTON, 27 Ju[ij; Sappemeer, Rosenberg, Barbados. SINGAPORE, 25 Junij; Holland, Gronbeck, Neweastle. HONGKONG, |4 Junij; Excelsior, Wytenherst, Ba*„. — 15 Junij-, Frederik Hendrik, van Ameydeu van Duyn, Soerabaya. - H. Liduina van Blind. Bangkok.— 16 Junij; Salatiga, Kettler, Singapore.— 18 Junii- Oceanus, Dirksen. id.</p>
</text>
