<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 26 Mei; Friesland, Boontje, Londen. VLIE,26Mei,W.Z.W.—O.Z.O.; Johanna, Mathisen, Fanoe. ZOLTKAMP, 23 Mei; Hensina, Meeter, Memel. - Zwaantina Hendrika, Vissenga, Lanrvig. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 26 Mei, O. Z. O.; Gannet, S., Liverpool. BEIELLE, 26 Mei, O.Z.O.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Trompson, Condensen, Hobroe. - Avalon, S., Harwich. - Pacific, S., id. HAMBURG, 24 Mei; Willem I, S., Amst. — 25 Mei; Jonge Barend Prins, Termunterzijl. - Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Fedderwarden. BuSÜM, 20 Mei; gepasseerd: Ora etLabora,Latje,Bremenn.Wöhrdfiii. TEAVEMUNDE, 24 Mei; Ettina, Oldenburger, Dantzig. PEENAU, 12 Mei; Afina, MeUema, Newc. — 13 Mel; Ettina, Gortc- BOLDEEAA, 19 Mei; Antjo Visser, de Jonge, Amst. - De Flecken Jouwer, Mellcma, id. — 20 Mei; Elisabeth, Bijl, id. - Jacobus Antome,MeJlema, id. - Vlieland, Visser, Harl. - Helena Gesina, Schreuder, Delfzijl. - Anna Augusta, Kuiper, id. - Amicitia, do Groot, Antw. - Speculaüen, Björke, Dordrecht. - Charlotte, Wille, id. - Alberdina, Scherpbior, Gron.- Constantia, Andersen, Schiedam.-21 Mei; Drammen, Frost, Amst.- Argo, Koster, Harl. - Hillechina, Brakke, Delfzijl. - Broedertrouw, de Groot, Londen. _ . _. BALT1SHP0ET, tot 15 Mei; Phoenix, Veldhuis, Newc. - Domma Geertina, Wolters, Grimsby. SÏOKHOLM, 21 Mei; Dageraad, van Wijk, Amsterdam. ; Bij KOPENHAGEN, 23 Mei; Ales, Ohlson, Pernau n. Schiedam. LAUEVIG, 17 Mei; Bouwina, Middel, Delfzijl. LONDEN, 24 Mei; Diewerdina, de Jonge, Bugcnwalde. ■ Bij GOUDSTAABT, 23 Mei; Gooregt, Huges, Bahia n. Bremen. - Wilheimina, de Groot, Gallipoli n. id. . Bij DEAL, 24 Mei; Providence, Toft, Carthagena n. Shields. Bij FOLKESTONE, 24 Mei; Alida Pronk, Scholtens, Cette n. Amst. FOWEY, 24 Mei; Forester, Johns, Nowport n. Dordrecht. CHAELESTOWN, 23 Mei; Elisabeth Catharina, Hansen, Amsterd. - Marens Minde, Jensen, Schiedam. HAEWICB, 24 Mei; Vr. Anna, Hospes, Londen n. Worcum.- Twee Zusters, Feenstra, id. n. id. SHIELDS, 24 Mei; Vertrouwen, Kamman, Falkenberg. . LEITH, 24 Mei; Catharina Luitgardina, Bos, Dantzig. - Wilhelmina, Koppelgaard, Kiel. OPOETO,20Mei;deHoop,Ouwehand,Amst. LISSABON, 20 Mei; Irene, S., Livorno. - Alphard, Puister, Amst. - Courier, v. Vliet, Vlaardingen. TEIEST, 21 Mei; Cycloop, S., Amst. BATAVIA, 7 April; Elisabeth, Feenstra, Eotterd. - Telanak, Popken Amsterdam. - Caroline, Limd, Liverpool. - 9 April; Nederland en Oranje, Mulder, Eott. - Maria, Stuit, id. - Maarten van Bossen, Gorrebrands, id. - Jupiter, Kiewit, Amst. - Krimpencrwaard, Kluit, Melbourne. — 11 April; Yokohama, Comfurius, Macao. — 12 April; Batavia, van Dolder, Japan. PASOEBOEAN, 1 April; Niphon, Vuyk, Sydney. STBAAT SUNDA, 5 April; gepasseerd: Onrust, Weisenbrock, Macao n. Havana.</p>
</text>
