<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>BINNENGEKOMEN. TEXEL, 23 Scpt.; Arm, Bell, Newc. HKLLEVOETSLUIS, 23 Sept.; Stad Middelburg, Ouwéhand, Akyab I. v. Zierikzee. - Queen, S., Dundee. - Maria Stuart, S., Leith. - Seahorse, S., Hull. - Hamniouia, S., Hamburg. VLIE, 22 Sept.; de Fleckeu Jovwcr, Mellema, Riga. - Hanna Christen- Sen, Wathne, Christiansand. - Amsterdam, S., Hambur&quot; BRIELLE, 23 Sept.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Ravensbury, S., Harwich. &apos;1 MAASSLUIS, 23 Sept.; Prins vau Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Orion, S., Londen. - Leeds, S., Grimsby. HAMBURG, 21 Sept.; Johanna Mathilde, Toosbuy, Zwijiisdrecht - Catharina, de Vries, Londen. CUXHA VEN, 22 Sept.; Willem I, S., Amsterdam. BOLDERA, 15 Sept.; Antje Visser, de Jonge, Amsterdam. - Regnera, Wortelboer, Montrose. — 16 Sept.; Valerins Lodewijk, de Jong, Newc. — 17 Sept; Marie Pauline, Broous, Dordt.-Jacoba Alida, ran der Laan, Amst. - Margaretha Marchiua, Beckering, Londen. — 18 Sept.; Frouwiua Elisabeth, de JoDge, Newc. SARPSBORG, 17 Sept.; Helene, Halvorsen, Nederland. KOPENHAGKN, 20Sept.; Wilbelmina, Neuman, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 20 Sept.; Margaretha, Schoon, Papenburg n. Dantzig. - Louise Helene, Visser, Amst. n. Petersb. SVENDBORG, 17 Sept;Elschlea, Albers, Amst. KANSOE, 17 Sept; Albatros, Thesen, Nederl. n. Riga. ELSENEUR, 20 Sept.; gepasseerd: Vlinder, de Jong, Grimsby n.Dantzig. - Gerharda Hendrika,Glim,Grimsby.-Anna,deWecrd,Nederl.n. de Oostzee. - Jeltina, Wessels, Londen n. id. TONNINGEN, 19 Sept; Eendragt, Smit, Wismar n. Dordrecht Bij LIZARD, 20 Sept; Jupiter, Kiewit, Bat. n. Amst. DUINS, 21 Sept; Abeona, ..., Lissabon n. Vlaardingen. PLYMOUTH, 20 Sept: Sabiua, Martin, Dordrecht. CARDIFF, 20 Sept.; Elsina Geertruida, Mulder, Dublin. SUNDERLAND,2O Sept; John Ritson, Gihson, Rotterdam. NEWCASTLE, 21 Sept; Boreas, Munneke, Harlingen. SHIELDS, 21 Sept; Anna, Himter, Hellevoetsluis. - Waterloo, Wordingham, Rotterdam. - Light and Sign,Robinson,Dordt - Frieuds, ..., id. - Triester, Johns, Harlingen. MESSINA, 10 Sept; Irene, S., Napels (vertrok den volgenden dag naar Patras.) —11 Sept; Zwaluw, Brougers, Watsoe. VIGO, 6 Sept; Wildervank,Giesen,Cardiff(vertr. 12Scpt. n. Wick.)--9</p>
</text>
