<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 11 Aug.; Dc Hoop, Ouwehand, Lissabon. - Lion, S., Londen. - Magnet, S., id. - Stentor, Toering.id. -Pilot, Cawthorn, Itusterzyl naar •Sandwich. - Alianoo, Arnold, Bristol. - Advauce, Taylor.Liverpool.- Pomona, Butcber, Newc. - Dral&apos;ua, Nicholsen, Fredenkstad. - Nidelvun, 1! je rtness, Avontuur. !&apos;-.&apos;&apos;. „ .... HELLE VUETSLUIS. 11 Aug.; Eurora, S., Londen. - Hopewell, Pearson, id. - Crestoftbe Wave, Woodburn, Cardiff. - Thereae, S., Grangemouth. - Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Star, Nock, id. - (jogstadt, Sundene, Ncrva. MAASSLUIS, 11 Aug.; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Colonel Evans Rev nolds, Bye. &apos; J &apos; BRKJIERHAVEN, 10 Ang.; Harmonie, van der Meulen Iladerslohen HAMBURG, 8 Aug.; Eltfca Meezenbroek ftSffi «h&quot; grietha, Niessen, Nederland. &apos; n&lt;lzcwinkel. ™°le- -Ma- TRAVFM{iNnpllc!jiAHJe^lunni,nS&apos;Ne(ïerland. lm DFR w i™ &apos;t &quot;&apos;T WeIte^artier, Dijk, Oostzee. Mm,ve77 £&apos;t autlura. de Jonge, Maas. -Jantina, Eefting.Amst.- Idun, Haosen, id. - i ortuna, LüUlein, fieltzyl. - Arentina Jacoba, Menzes, Elsêneur. » Ida Cornelia, Schenk, id. - Phönix, Veldhuis, Aberdeen. — 6 Aug.; Joseph, de Bloom, Maas. - Zeeploeg, Luder, Nederland. - Carl, Wieueke, id. - Eersteling, Wiersma, Engehnd. - Hillechiena Catharina, Hesseling. Elsêneur. PILLAU, 9 Aug.; Helcna, de Jonge, Koogerpolder. - Anna Elisabeth, Mmitendam Dik, Aberdeen. LONDEN,9 Aug.; Zeilkl.: Grietje,Lukkien,Petersb.— lOAng.; Alberdina. van den Bos, id. QUEENSTOWN, 9 Aug.;&apos;Gesina, Lindeboom, Friesland n.Durgarvan. COWES, 9 Aug.-, de Zwerver, Visser, Bahia n. Breinen. INVERKEITHING, 8 Ang.; Catharina Geerdiva, de Groot, Kroonstad. — :) Aug,; Hendrika Margaretha id. HULL, 9 Aug.; Antina, de Vries, Wiek. IPSWICH, 9 Aug.; Eagle, Hawkins, Rotterdam. SE AH AM, 8 Aug.; Premium, Adamson, Nienwediep. NANTES. 7 Aug.; Rover, Marshall, Rotterdam. TENERIFFE, 24 Julij; Doris, Lolling, Bremen.</p>
</text>
