<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>il»r. ke&gt; Snnrt ! ; Tllsmas Mitchell, Mc&apos;Keehnic, Glasgow. - Louise, S&apos;lll«. - B]e., and- - Helvotia, Christenscn, Nerva. - Familien, Holst, Sö- Ilt?&apos;&quot;■ Önds &quot;rcterius, Gothenburg. - Fortuna, Andersen, Christiania.-fl JEVni?SOn&apos; brammen. - Elisabeth Catharina, Oelsen, Porsgrund. t)anm&quot;&apos;ttal V. r urSLUIS, 24 Mei; Idea, Dalahavde, Middlesbro. — 25 Mci; 2if,-?&apos;e- LeV U&apos; S-&gt; Havre-&quot; Cosmopolitan, S., Londen. - Bordeaux, S., hl2-&quot;S.],,.&quot;]&apos; S-&gt; Gothenburg.— 26 Mei; Tcrnatc, Cars Tz., Batavia via %^*LLK os °&quot;enbrugge, Boston (A).- lronmaster, S., Middlesbro jgu. -, ■.c&quot; Z~, Mei; Albert, S., Huil. - Zealous, S., Harwich. - Anna, S., Kt • ASgf rr/^&apos;i Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. »nC&apos;? Cutlicj. 4 Mcii Collegie Voorzorg, Hubert, Avontuur. —26 Mei; I&apos;lr &apos; De&apos; Brand&gt; Sunderland&apos;. (De Collegie Voorzorg is buiten ge-6t&apos;iiin v 4 ¥ei; A- E-Vidal&gt; Rehse- Java n- Hamburg, hit&apos;;-., r , e&apos;! Willem vau den Bey, Lutje, Barcelona. - Vriend. «Ui, 23 ïï1 •&apos; llermanna Hendrika, Datema, Nerva. **■ Norfolk Tar, Bunting, Amst. - Neptunus, van der Mey*^J^fif Z?p_lyr&gt; Pekelder&gt; Mcthel. Lt\rï?ain fn, &apos; T?Me&apos;; Christine Jacqueline, ran Noord, Liverpool naar CNa^POOlfo?d^doreParati«)- SfïiT~.~~ 23 mL-&quot;T, Me&apos; &gt; Hcrraanna, Veling, Dantzig. - Thora, Jansen , C^AMfe. a?ley- Co°P^ Dordt. S(T\_oïf,2l M • ?&apos; 4 Meiï Aurelia Gruno, Stuitjc, Elseneur. Glft^Alß^ïn ™e , le Gnilloux, Rott. ïfil^ENTT in1.;¥ei Titia Jacobina, Klein, Liverpool. C 0&amp;Sï. 20 IU ; Hazard- Koster, Herberg. ■ , C/K* fe dc Wa»rden, Agtie_n, Hamburg. W* WAVU 2&apos; fan.f redcrik, Klazen, Petersburg. Padan_- P-Ti NaSa3aki, Mos, Nederland. - Ida Maria de Raath, i SAlw _Kr«isin„, r&gt;_Tpril i Maria Anna, van Mermom, Rott. — 8 April; ** MaTAItANG80/wdane- -11 April; Jacob, Mulder Drenth, Rott. .„SOvï.; Johann&apos;t  M; Admiraal de Ruiter, Mollinger, Golf van Persie. %p ii^BAYA ik £nius&apos; de Vo°gd d°r Straaten, Nederland. h°»ntv / ReBiniCTb Maart; Pietcr, Hoogerwerf, Nederland. -Hollandia, 11 Kt? »«nèew Man«&apos;onwehand, id. -Celebes, Reuvekamp Gille, id, - faaoeroean{ w%N.ICOUd. — 30 Maart; de Vrede, v.Duyvenbooden, • - April; van der Palm, van Katwijk, id. — 3 April; Marinus Willem, Buyser, id. - Stad Enschedé, Kretschmer, id. (via Bat.) - 8 April; Nederland, van Stcenderen, id. ?,4SOEiIOEAN&apos; 24 Maart; Emilie, Lundstrom, Nederland. — 30 Maart; Meden, v. Icuteni, id. — 4 April; Emma Broberc id BANJOEWANGIE, 24 Maart; L. A. Bang, Fallenius, Amst. - 27 Mrt. Johanna Maria, Wilhelmie, Rott. INDRAMAYOE, 24 Maart; Nagasaki, Mos, Nederland. TAGAL 2o Maarr; Cornelia Hendrika, v. Straten, Nederland. PADANG, 28 Febr.; Isaac da Costa, Klein, Nederland. — 3 Maart; Padang Packet, Huidekoper, id. —10 Maart; Lammina Elisabeth,Pot, Bat. — 19 Maart; Maarten van Rossem, Gerrebrands, Nederland. —20 Maart; Zaanstroorn, Schaap, id.</p>
</text>
