<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>liim. tif -i ° üct-; Graf von Crassow, Luhmann, Odessa. - Neanthes, WiluZ&apos; o &apos;l van Plymouth. - Argo, Gesterkamp, Newc. - Crance, CuthtMson, bnndcrland. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Alpha, Pilage, Archanfcw. Üortuaa, Raben, Nerva.- Sophio, Paulsen, Riga. -Titania, Olsen, Sundswail. - Rong Sverre, Walloe, Nyland. - Theresa Lina, Bendsen, Skelskior. - &quot;grim, Erichsen, Sannesund. - Erstatning, Hassing, Bergen. - Wilhelinine •&quot;&apos;eisen, Drammen. - Haabet, Ulrichson, Holmstrand. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Oet.; Lammiena Elizabeth.Pott.Bat. l.v. Brouwershaven. - Celebes, Reuvekamp Gille,id.l. v. id.-Earlof Auckland, S Londen. - Hopewell, Pearson, id. - 3 Brothers, Charlton, Roehester. - Janet, Jones, Workington. - Hope, Marshall, Peterhead.- Pelican, S., Liverpool. - Therese, S., Grangemouth. - Holyrood, S, Leith. - Rosé, Champlin, Newc- Springflower, Dunn, id. - Perseveranec, Mallen, id. - Sir Robert Calder, &quot; r&apos;ght, Arendsburg. - Martha, Scherpbier, Riga. - Ambrosia, Buil, Sunds- Wall. - Tre Kroner, Olsen, Fredrikshavn. - Vlaardingcn. Goudswaard, Bergen. - Solid, Mörck, Frederikstad. - Nordstjernen, Hansen, Holmstrand. BRIELLE, 16 Oct.; Leo, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. BROUWERSHAVEN, 16 Oct.; het schip per telegr. gemeld. VLISSINGEN, 16 Oct.; Louise, Lammors, Buenos-Ayres. KROONSTAD, 15 Oct.; Zeehond, Feninga, Amst. LONDEN, 15 Oct.; Diana, S., Amst. BORDEAUX. 13 Oct.; Clasina Aidina, Wirtjes, Triest. - Martha Alida, Karst, id. - Tjetska, Doewes, id. LIVORNO, 11 Oct.; Margaretha, Boerhave, Rott. LISSABON, 9 Oct.; Anton en Jacob, Ouwehand, ... SINGAPORE, vóo&apos;r 7 Sept.; Anna, Bok, Amst. - Gebroeders van der Beek, Walig, Cardif. (Beiden laden voor Batavia.) — 7 Sept. In lading : Albrecht Beijling, van der Burg, Hongkong. HONGKONG, 11 Aug.; Gouverneur van Swieten,Singer,Singapore. SHANGHAE, 11 Aug.; ter reede: Bengalen, Hjelmstrom. - Maria, ue Jong. MELBOURNE, 14 Aug.; Emilie, Bruynseels, Manilla. —24 Aug.; Prof. &lt; n?l?or Boos Mesch, van Santen, Rott. — 1 Sèpt.; Nercus, Planten, Guam. • „b°iJS-ï Hendrik Ido Ambacht- Sljl, Batavia. SïDNEY, 9 Aug.; Aegidia en Paulino, Hoogland, Dordrecht.</p>
</text>
