<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>i3urqct Itjfïc Stattb. Van 33 tot en niet 29 Maart 18G5. BEVALLEN: M Koene, geb. Kok. I). — J. Spaanderman . geb. Hoek . D.— J. Galjaard, geb. van llooven , Z. — G. Lamatt, geb. Steensiraien ,Z. — G. van llemmelen , geb. Serrurier, D. — -M. A. Prooi, geb. Schrellen , Z — W. A Bekker. geb. de Bruyn , Z. — A. van der Linden . geb. van der Mark , D. — C. Klynee. geb. Dirkzwager. Z. — J. Hoog kamer, geh Lepelaar, Z. — J. Duyvcrman, geb van der Wielen, D. —A. de Vroede, geh. Iloogenorst, Z.— M.H. van Egmond, geb. .Ilicben,&apos;ZJeveul. — S. Boogers,geb. Christiaansc, Z. levenl.— H. Faes, geh. Hakkenberg, D. levenl. — Ë. de Noliel. geb. Steyger, I). — J. Schoeree. geb. Greveii, 1. — J. M. de Jley,. Geb la Lan, D. — J. &apos;M. de Vrind, geb. vau Beek, D. — J. Noest, geb. Monieba,D — W. van Leeuwen, geb. Sierat, Z.&apos;— E. Nonien&apos;, geb. Lau, ü. — M. C. Lul. Geb Koster, D. — N. Korcneef&quot;, geb. van der Knyff. I. — M. van Ees, geb. Florisson . Z. — S. van Kam-pen, geb. Kwakkenbos, D. •— .1. Carton, gtb. Piket. D. — E. de Kier, geb. Dinnet, D —G. VVallaart, geb. Mazurel, 1). Iweel. —C. J. van Bemmelen , geb. Linschoirn . Z. — E Spierenburg . geb. Loeber, D. GEHUWD: G. J. A. de Meere. jm. en J. M. van Daalen.jd. — J. VV. van der Beyden . jm. en A. 11. de Geus. jd. OVERLEDEN: Hel» van Hooidonk, 27 j. — 11. Karstens, Z ,ruim3m.— D &apos;Regeer, Z., 17 d. — H. van Geldden, Z., 7m. —J. Mulder, 54 j. —J. Stallen. &apos;L.. ruim 3 m — A. Verhoef!&apos;, Z., 4,j. en 3m.— J. Fallaux, 84 j.— Joh» Ma Calh» VAillemson, 18 j. — E. VV inteikamp. geb. Dool. 42 j. —G. J. liorsboö.n , Z.. 6 j en 7m. — S P. van Kampen , Z., ruim Ij. — l. Zimmer, D., bijna 3m. — W Kersbergen .79j. — Mr. C. F. van Goi kont. 23 j. —J. Regeer, &apos;L. ,2m — F. Giezen, &apos;L , 6 w. — .1. Spaanderman, geb. Hoek , 42 j. — I). Weiselaar, Z.\ ruim 2 m. — H. Lely.eld, Z. 4j. Eu 5 m. — T. van Geldtreu, Z. , 8 j. — D. de Bruyn, 36 j. — J. Korswagen, geb. Kreugcr,s3j. — J. Elswilder, &apos;t.., 2 in.;..</p>
</text>
