<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Sept., Z.Z.0.—Z.0.; 2 Zusters, Feenstra, Londen. - J. A. Jackson, EUiot, Newc. - El wine, Eschricht, Archangel. - Louis, Philips, id. - Ondine, S., Dantzig. - Veendammer Courant, Zoutman, — Gisteren nog: Hero, Hayward, Sunderland. - Anno Otto, Boonsack, Archangel. - Niord, Pederseh, id. - Johanna Adriana, Sikkes, Riga. VLIE, 2 Sept., Z. O.; Olga, S., Londen. - Jantje, Knol, Archangel. - 2 Vrienden, Ruige, Dantzig. -Anna Luitzia, Jager, Frederikstad.- Gesina Jantina, Pott, id. - Oscar, Oomelissen, Drammen. - Pilen, Olsen, Osterrisoer. Catharina Visser, de Vreese, Drobach.- 2 Gebroeders, Butter, Riga. ZOLTKAMP, 2 Sept.; Karsina Harmina, Waterborg, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 3 Sept., Z. O.; Gannet, S, LiveFpool. - De Jonge Rieka, Klein, Archangel. BROUWERSHAVEN, 3 Sept., Z. 0.; Louise, Kroonprinsesv. Zweden, Mèppelder, Dordrecht. ZIERIKZEE, 2 Sept., N.; Rnvits, Mattersen, Spanje n. Antw. HAMBURG, 3 Sept.; Hendrik Pieter, Bakker, Buenos-Ayres. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 2 Sept.; Confiance, Brongers, Londen n. Petersb.- Secundus, de Graaf, Doekum, n. id. - Barend, Hoeksema, Galipolo n. id. - Hiilechina, Grnppelaar, Aarhuus n. de Oostzee. KROONSTAD, 2 Sept.; Baron Sloet totDldhuis, Braams, Zwolle.--2 Broeders, Prins, Schiedam. LONDEN, 31 Aug.; Ida, Hazewinkel. Petersb.—l Sept.; Jan Freeseman, de Jonge, Buenos-Ayres. - Hillechina, Pot, Petersb. - Jeltina, Wessels, id. - Vertrouwen, Moesker, id. - Diana, Kraan, id. Bij DOVER, 1 Sept; Wilhelmina, Tonjes, Rott. n. Cardiff. Bij WIGHT, 1 Sept.; Schuringa, Brandt, ... n. Rio-Janeiro. Bij LIZARD, 29 Aug.; Duisburg, Holjes, Baltimore n. Rott—3o Ang.; W. H. M00dy,..., Philadelphia, n. id. Bfi DEAL, 31 Aug.; Anna Sophia, Witt, Soderham n. Póole. Bij PLYMOUTH, 30 Aug.; Raphael, v. d.VeldeSmit, Amst n. Curacao. Bij GOUDSTAART, 30 Aug.; Samarang, de Groot, Shields n. Soerab. In de GULL STREAM, 3U Aug.; ten anker: Eendragt, Boer, Stokholm n-Napels (28 d. reis). CHARLESTOWN, 31 Ang.; Zeemeeuw, Swart, Lossiemouth. - Anna, dartels, Gothenburg. LIVERPOOL, 31 Aug.; In lading: Zeemanshoop, Dekker, St. Thomas. LITTLEHAMPTON, 31 Aug.; Weldaad, Pik, Riga. YARMOUTH, 31 Aug.; Whim, Smith, Nieuwediep. HULL, 31 Aug.; Jantina Alida, Bakker, Stokholm. SHIELDS, 31 Aug.; Vesper, Ermitage, Amst. - Libra, Klein, Schied. - &quot;anepe, Drewe, Dordt. — 1 Sept. Rosslare, English, Rott. CADIX, 23 Aug.; Carolina Cornelia, Peters, Cardiff. RIO JANEIRO, 24 Julij; 7 Gebroeders, de Groot, Paysandu.— 30 Julij; Géertruida Janna, v. Heijningen, Itahapoana. BUENOS-AYRES, 12 Julij; Junior, Tunteler, Paranagua. —14 Julij; Vertrouwen, Middel, Londen. — 16 Julij; Kosmopoliet, flayes Klein, Paranagua. - Catharina, Stuven, Rott. MONTEVIDEO, 27 Julij; Anna Maria Henriette, de Jong, Cardiff.-ffl Boerhave, Rott. — 28 Julij-, Maria, Deuze, id.</p>
</text>
