<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 12 Sect., Z. Z. O.; Rembrandt, S., Bordeaux. - Mentor, Toering,. Londen. - Caroline, Cupido, Sundswall. - Olivia, Quisling, id. - Josephine, Them, Drammen; benevens het schip per tel. gemeld.) VLIE, 11 Sept., Z.Z.0.; Oscar, Storm, Petersb. - Jacoba Alida, van der Laan, Nerva. - Alida Elisabeth, Potjewijd,_ Christiania. - Concordia, Naatje, Frederikst. - 3 Gebroeders, Jansen, id. - Wilhelmina, Schuring, id. - Creole, Larsen, Drobach. -12 Sept.; Hollandia, S., Londen. - Aoteterdam, S., Hamburg., HELLEVOETSLUIS, 12 Sept, Z. W.; Andromeda, Rudin, Panarokan, L v. Brouwershaven.- ZephjT, S., Londen. - Acadia.Boer,Runcorn.- Dharwar, Hulshof!&apos;, Liverpeol, 1. v. Zierikzee. - Vartry, S., Belfast. Windsor, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Seanymph, Crosby, id. - Seagull, S., Huil. - Eliza, de Boer, Archangel. - Alexandra, Rasmussen, id. - Tonningen, Jacobsen, Drammen. - BRIELLE, 12 Sept., Z. 0.; Bradford, S., Grimsby. BROUWERSHAVEN, 12 Sept., Z.W.; New-Brunswick, Tirie, Dordtr. n. Newc, heeft de reis voortgezet. BREMERHAVEN, 11 Sept.; Margiena Catharina, Koops, Hamburg. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 11 Sept.; Sikko, Jonker, Newc. n. Petersburg. - Maria, Hansen, Petersburg n. Dordt. - Adolf Rantzow, Swarrer, id. n. ¦Rott. HAMBURG, 11 Sept.; Drie Gebroeders, Klein, Amst. - Catharina, Buismann,Dokkum. — 12 Sept.; Hummonia, S., Rott. DANTZIG, 10 Sept. Uit zee terug: Reina, Kmisinga en Agatha Jacobina, Kramer. SUNDSWALL, 31 Aug.; Alfa, Hagemann, Rott. - Canada, Abrahamsen, Nederland. - Scandmavien, Aagensen, id. GOTHENBURG; 9 Sept.; Kronprmses Louise, Meppeldër, Dordrecht. CHRISTIANSAND, 3 Sept.; Arnoldus Willem Nanninga, Top, Nykjö- J&gt;ing. LONDEN, 10 Sept.; Geertje Dijkstra, Veninga, Petersb. - Afiua, Mellema, Kroonstad.</p>
	<p>ROCHESTER, 10 Sept.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rotterdam. INVERKEITHING, 9 Sept.; Enigheden, Clausen, Schiedam. CARDIFF, 10 Sept.; Glasgow, Rap, Retterdam. YARMOUTH, 10 Sept.; Whim, Smitb, Alkmaar. HARTLEPOOL, 10 Sept.; Vertrouwen, Boldt, Dantzig. SUNDERLAND, 10 Sept.; Alberdina, Meijer, Nieuwediep. NEW-CASTLE, 7 Sept.; In lading: Sumatra, Buyser, Point de Galle en Columbia rivier. KONSTANTINOPEL, 28 Aug.; F. Ferrara, Montanï, Taganrog, (vertr. n. Rott.)—Triest, S., Cardiff. __. SINGAPORE, 1 AHg.; Johanna, Verdnyn, Newcastle. MACAO, 26 Julij; Neêrlands Vlag, van den Broek Humfrey, Macassar. HONGKONG, 12 Julij; Amazene, Kramer, Saigon (laadt voor Nagasaki). — 23 Julö; Pieter, Hoogcrwerffid. — 24 Julij; Johanna Antonia, Withoff.SÏBgapore.</p>
	<p>AMOY, 15 Julij; in lading: St. Helena, Pille, Shanghae. YOKOHAMA, 13 July; in lading; China, Tofield, Batavia. - Telanak, Popken, Nagasaki.</p>
</text>
