<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXL, 23 Julij; Urania, S., Oostzee. VLIE, 22 Julij; Cort Sivertsen Adler, Hansen, Riga. - Martha, Ebes Jr., Gothenburg. - Hermanus Gerhardus, Baumé, Bergen. - Tvende Brödre, Winsnes, Drammen. - Amsterdam, S., Hamb.-Alida, Borgman, Avontuur., P HELLEVOETSLUIS, 23 Julij; Afrika, Dekker, Qnisembo. - Bordeaux, S., Bordeaux. - Eeijenoord, S., Londen. - Swallow, S., Huil. BRIELLE, 22 Julij; Leo, S., Londen.- Lubbegiena, Spithorst,lnverness.- Sir Henry Havelock, Ma\e, Scarbro. - Colletis, S., Goole. - Zealous, S., Harwich. MAASSLUIS, 23 Julij; William &amp; John, Nunn, Boness.-Elizabeth, Normandall, Newc. - Springtiower, Vaught, id. - Patriot, Nordoe, Skudenes. - Maria, Jorgensen, Avontuur. HAMBURG, 21 Julij; Vr. Sjouke, Voss, Nederland. CUXHAVEN, 21 Julij; Louise Helene, Aggen, Archangel. BREMERHAVEN, 22 Julij; Elisabeth, Schoon, Erederikstad. EMDEN, 20 Jalij; Louise Sophie, Hollander, Londen. WARNEMUNDE, 20 Julij; Houkelina, Stuer, Dantzig. STRAALSUND, 13 Julij: Albert, Wiese, Nederland. — 17 Julij; Anna Maria. Kernper, id. STETTIN, 20 Julij; De Weldaad, Lnkkien, Bremen. SWINEMUNDE, 20 Julij; Louise, Hildebrand, Söderhamn. - Henriette, Kuiper, Bremen. BOLDERA, 18 Julij; Baron Sloet tot Oldhuis, Schmidt, Nederland.- Cornelia Anna Christina.de Haan, Elsetieur.-Frouwina Elisabeth, de Jonge, Antwerpen. - Krageroe, Nielsen, Nederland.— 19 Julij; Catharina, Dijkema, - Gesina Alida, Meijer, de Maas. - Simon Martina, Oldenburger, Elseneur. PILLAU, 20 Julij; Harmina, Emmelkamp, Engeland. - Nachina Lammechina, Hijnberg, Rusland. KROOi-JSTAD, 17 Julij; Equator, Huisman, Amst. - Elisabeth,. Stefïens, de Weser. KOPEN HAGEN, 19 Julij; Niessina Schuringa, Stroobos, do Oostzee. ELSENEUR, 20 Julij; Java, Tuk, Swartwick n. Australië. BRAKE, 22 Jiüij; Jaeoba Margiena, Kuil, Antw. - Elise, Boye, Dantzig. COWES, 21 Julij; Barteld-HermaE, Rasker, Groningen. LIVERPOOL, 21 Julij;Dirkjc, Thaden, Stettin. — Zeilkl.: Syne Jacobs, Blaupot, Nerva. CHARLESTOWN, 20 Julij; Margaretha Gesina, de Groot, Straalsund.</p>
</text>
