<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 5 Oct.; Gebr. Fokkes, Fokkes, Petersb.- Jaxiob Synes,Nip, Cliristiania. - Penelope. Helgesen, Drammen. — 6 Oet.; Premium, Adam - son, Seaham. - Jantje, Smit. Archangel.- Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Pel Ella Const.-.nce, S., Pillau.- Dorette, Fyrian, Dantzig.- Heinrich Thcedor, Voss, id. - Seraph, Westendorfl&apos;, Landscrona.-jFrcderika, Johnson, Christiania. - Elisabeth Sophie, Svensen, Frederikstad. - Carl Johan, Iverscu, id. - Scotia, Lorcnsen, Drammen. VLIE, 5 Oct.; Christir.a, Oltmans, Dantzig. - Hendrika Ebeliena, Jonker, id. - Alida,Borgman,Gothenburg-3Gebroeders, Jansen,Frederikstad. - Catharina Elisabeth, Pott, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Oct.; Thomas Scddou, Parr, Rangooii 1. v. Zierikzee. - Ida, S., Liverpool. - Lyra, Strong, Newc. - Waterwitch, Boog id. - Middlesbro&apos;, S., Middlesbro&apos;. - Swanland, S., Huil. - Berthold, Voss,&apos; Riga. - Sylyestcr, Sprenger, id. - Borussia, Niemann, id. - Theodor, Fick, id. - Lucretia, Bracht, id. - Adler, Patkamp, Koningsbergen.- Hammoni.i, S., Hamburg. BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Oct.; Swan, Annison.Newc. n. Rott.-Gogstad, Sundene, Drammen n. id. BREMERHAVEN, 4 Oct.; Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Memel. - Jongo Albert, Kwint, Petersburg. - Hiilechina Margrieta, Jooston, Memel.- Trientje, Veldkamp, Hamburg. HAMBURG, 4 Oct.; Willem I, S.. Amst. - Stoomvaart, S., id. KOPENHAGEN. 2Oct.; 2 Söstre, Willarsen, Pillau n.Gron. — 3Oct.; Enjetta, de Boer, Petersb. n. Londen. - Aurora, de Jonge, id. 11. Antw. STOKÜOLM, 1 Oct.; Nina, S.. Amst. ELSENEUR, 2 Oct.; Christina Jacoba, de Groot, Petersburg naar Londen. -Wieka,Eeftin_,id. n. deZaan. — 3 Oct.; Alert, Paulsen, Söderhamn n. Nieuwe Diep. - Flora, Ncnmann, Sundswall n. id. - Enigheden, Foyen, id. n. id. - Sesostris, Ericssen,id. n. Holland. - Heinrich, Krull, Riga naar id - Julie Moses, Museviech, iel. n. 4e Noordzee. - Broederschap, Bakker, Pc e-sburgn.Schiedam. - Gesina Alida, Botje,id. 11. Amst.- Jonge BolJ, h olk, id. n. Leith. - Stad Enschede, Niggebrugge, Wyburb n. Rott. sabeih, Kraeft, Dantzig n. Delfzijl. - Hercules, Nielsen,Geflen. Amst.- Ellen Constance, S., Pillau n. id. - Rubbens, S., Amst. n. Koningsb. RENDSBURG, 1 Oct,; Junge Heinrich, Kofahl, Memel n. Zaandam. - Anna. Kamminga, Wismar n. Rott. — 2 Oct.; Elsiena, Vlieger, Riga naar Schiedam. - Jacoba Margina, Kuil, Eckersund n. Antw. — 3 Oct.; Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge, Odense n. Amst. - 3 Gezusters, Pluktje, Grcnac n. Koogerp. Karsiua Harmina, Waterborg, Stettin n. Norden. M&apos;einsina. Klontje, Riga n. Wcser. LONDEN, 5 Oct.; Renske, Nepperas, Petersburg. YARMOUTH, 4 Oct.; Maria Hiurichs, Hes, Koningsb. MIDDLESBRO, 4 Oct; Elisabeth Geertruida, Janknecht, Groniugen.- Eansfórd, Duckrow, Dordt. SUNDERLAND, 4 Oct; Catherine.Belcham, Amst, SHIELDS, 4 Oct.-, Margaretha Hendrika, de Boer, Groningen. - Alida Dijk, de Haas. id. - Vier Gebroeders, Woudstra, id. - Jane, Scarfe, Brouwershaven - Hebe, Storm, Dordt. - Burger, Bartels. id.-Mathilde, de Jonge, id. - Argo, Brouwer, Amst. - Crescendo, Vos, id.- Everhardns, Vos, id. - Haimah. Gihbs. Middelb. GRANGEMOUTH, 3 Oct.; Mary Jane, M&apos;Pherson, Rott. G KANTON, 2 Oet.; Ida Engelsman, Duintjer, Cremenes. Bij FALMOUTH. 3 Oct.; Sirene, Hermanus, Rott. n. Phlladelphi. 4 Oct.; Cnmbrian, Simpson, Bassein n. Amst. DEAL, 4 Oct,.; Alice, Harding, Pentowan n. Dordt. JERSEY, 2 Oct.; Seabird, Nuttall, Rott. NAPELS. 29 Sept.-, Cornelia, S., Rott. enz. «5 DARDANELLEN, 22 Sept; Maria, Hillebrandt, lbrailan. Rott, MAC A SSAK, 3 Aug.; Constance, Mulder, Amst. PADANG, 4 Aug.; Whampoa. Jansen, Sunderland. YOKOHAMA, 3 Aug.; Macassar, van Bentveld, Nagasaki (in ladii.g n. Bat.) - Duodecima, Euvves, id. — 7 Aug.; Niphon, Carst, Slianghae.</p>
</text>
