<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>iiiAfcL,, -28 jumj; Matthew&amp; Arm, Wilson, Newc. VLIE, 27 Junij; Martine, Enochsen, Wvburg. - Vertrouwen, Kamman, iredenkstad. - Catharina, Hansen, id.-Mentor, Schjottelrig, Drammen - Josephine, Jahnsen, Drobach. - Meinskina, Oldenburger, id. AMELAND, 25 Junij; Dirkje, Poort, Bremen. -Petina, Groencwold,i«L- Ida Christina, de Vries qq., Elmshorn.— 26 Junij; Lyna Catharina.Ewen, Hamburg. DELFZIJL, 24 Junij; Aldershoff, Dijkstra, Laurvig.-Johanna Helena, Rozeboom, Leer. - Anna, Obes, Einden. — 25 Junij; Geerdina, Duintjer, Laurvig, (is 27 Jmiij derwaarts teruggekeerd). - lmelina Gooren, Menholst, Papenburg. - Vr. Trijntje, Spel, id. - Elisabeth, Schoite, Oldenburg. - De Hoop. Drewes, Emden. — 26 Junij; Jantina, de Jonge, Laurvig. — 27 Junij; Cornelia, Leeuwe, id. - Concordia, Zeven, id. -Ida i Lubbers, id. ZOLTEAMP, 26 Junij; JohaE Gerard, Huges, Laurvig. ! HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 Junij; Zephyr, S., Lenden. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Wilfiam Coleman, S., Goole. - Jacob Freie, Riga. - F. G. Schmahl, Glies, Libau, (heeft op strand gezeten). BRIELLE. 28 Junij; Bradford, S., Grimsby. MAASSLUIS, 28 Junij; Seagull, S., Huil. BROUWERSHAVEN, 28 Junij; Marie, Biesthorst, Rott, n. Bat BOLDERA.2I Junij; Maria Anna, Rutters, Kopenhagen. ELSENEUR, 24 Junij, gepasseerd: Eendragt, Bos, Petersburg n.Newburg. - Agina Undina, Brouwer, Nerva n. Grimsby. — 26 Junij-, Rotterdam, S., Rott, n. Stettin. i RENDSBURG, 22 Jnnij. gepasseerd :Trientje Meijer, Tonkens.Bre- I menn. Malmoe. — 24 lunij; Jacoba, Muntendam, Hamburg n. de Oostzee. — 25 Junij; Anna Thedora, Kuipers, Dantzig n. Dokknm. j TONNINGEN, 24 Junij; Johanna, Brouwer, Jönköping 11. Hambunr. VEGESACK, 27 Junij; Heidewika Regina, Pekelder, Riga. ! LONDEN, 26 Junij; Wietska, Bos, Petersb. -27 Junij; Frouke Dijkstra Hamstra, Bremen. - Amelia and Arm, Holmes, Gronii gen. Bij DUNGENESS, 25 Junij; Nijverheid, Schaap, Rott. n. Cardiff. - Co; abri, Riedijk, id. n. Liverpool, NEW-CASTLE, 26 Junij; Jantina Catharina, van Dijk, Randers. POOLE, 26 Junij; Drie Gebroeders, de Groot, Groningen. 1 SHIELDS, 26 Junij; Laura, Chew, Amst.-Batavia, Zwanenburg, Rott.- Loms Meyer, Holtgreve, id. - Helen, Went, id. I SUNDERLAND, 26 Junij; Gesina Jantina, Alberts, Ipswich. - Raisbeck, Barnard, Nieuwediep. i YARMOUTH, 26 Junij; Gesina, Meijerdierk, Bremen. HULL, 26 Junij; Sisters, Tamlin. Rott. Charles, Jones, id. LEIIH, 28 Junij; Boreas, Munneke, Harlingen. HAVRE, 24 Junij; Henriette, Wever, Norrköping. BALTIMORE, 13 Junij; Arnold Böninger, Steenken, New-York. BOSTON, (A) 12 Junij; Tjetska, Doewes, Matanzas. Bij PHILADELPHIA, (A) 15 Junij; Sirene, Hermanns, Rott. St. THOMAS, 2 Junij; Zeester, Zoetelief, Amst. LAGUAYRA, 30 Mei; Theresia, Wekenborg, New-Yoik.-Raphael, van de Velde Smit, Amst. PORTO CABELLO, 6 Junij; Dankbaarheid, Kooi, Amst. CURACAO, 9 Mei; Columbus, Wolkiug, Amst. (30 id. derwaarts teruggekeerd). —17 Mei; Maria, Witt, Hamburg. —28 Mei; Posseidon.Dedaes, id.</p>
</text>
