<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>VLIE, 5 April; Wendelina, Rebels, Petersb.-Weldaad, Voogd, Bergen. - Zwaantma Hendrika, Vissinga, id. - Josephine, Hansen, Drobach.- Antje, Hoeksma, Osterrisöer. - Alida, Borgman, Avont. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 April; Frei, Gallas, Philadelphia, A. - Wieka, Eefting, Napels. - Boreas, van Dijk.Gibraltar. - Gazelle, Seagers, Shoreham. - Balmoral, S., Bristol. - H. Vincentius v. Paulo, Nagel, Swansea.- John Snell, Carver, Newc. - Bread Maid, Dealing, id. -Fan_y,Unger, Frederikstad. - Herman Wedel, Bühr.id, - Elve, S., Hamburg. MAASSLUIS, 6 April; Autumna, Lee, Newc. - Conqueror, Sanderson, Sunderland. - Stag, Carr, Londen. - Aurora, Pieper, Stockton. - Eugénie, Couëdel, Gothenb. - Minerve, Lebot, Avontuur. - Dankbaarheid, Schouten, de Noordzee. -Alida, Schouten, id.-Zeemanshoop, Manneken, id.- Noordpool, Penning, id. - Vaarwel, Berkhout, id. BREMERHAVEN, 5 April; de Hoop, Pott, Havre. GRANGEMOUTH, 4 April; Catharina Elisabeth, Lever, Petersburg. SOUTHAMPTON, 4 April; Jantje, Smid, Groningen. TEIGNMOUTH, 3 April; Elsiena, Vlieger, Dordt. NEWPORT, 3 April; de Schelde, Hoffman, Singapore. - Mary Jane, Ashburner, Dordt.</p>
	<p>PARR, 3 April; Mary, Hadgraft, Dordt. CARDIFF, 3 April; Laura &amp;Adèle, Lund, Singapore. - Passaroeang, Hollander, id. CHARLESTOWN, 3 April: Westerkwartier, Dijk, Lubeck. SUNDERLAND, 3 April; Catharina, Drok. Londen. S WANSEA, 3 April; Anna Agatha, Sloot, Nantes. WHITEHAVEN, 4 April; Rosina, Daniels, Dordt. CALAIS, 3 April; Hermann Wieher, van der Laan, Haylc. CEAR A, 23 Febr.; zeilkl.: Maria, van der Plas, Hamburg. NAPELS, 29 Maart; Ringleader, Quick, Amst. BUENOS-AYRES, 11 Febr.; Sirius, Douwes, Rio-Grande. — 22 Febr/, Telemachus, Hazewinkel, Rio-Janeiro. — 24 Febr.; zeilkl.: Johanna Hendrika, Lieuwen, Rio-Grande en New-York. MONTEVIDEO, 10 Febr.; Cornelia Maria, Timmer, Frayßentos.- Twee Cornelissen, Potjer, Corrientes. AKYAB, 24 Febr.; zeilkl.: Hebe, Kiel, Falmouth.</p>
</text>
