<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>lEAEL, 31 Aug.-. .losiah L. Hale, Nowell, Maulmaiii 1. v. Falmouth. - Dawson, Allwell, Newcastle. - Miranda, Smith, id. - Mclona , Ne.il, baaliam.-Die Erndte,Kloek, Riga.- Frederika, Jansen, Sundswall. - ündine, Bonde,Frederikstad. - Noordster, Tobiassen.id. • Drammen, Trost, Drammen. - Arga,Sohwartz,id. — 1 Sept.; V.inda.Thoinpson.Raug., 1. v.yueenst, - Elisabeth, Rode, Santos, 1. v. Falmonth. - Ansion, Bloni&lt;l wst, Baltimore. - Sultana, Bell, Newcastle- Esk, Bennet, id. Premeuin, Adamson, Seaham. - Wnim, Smith, Yarmouth. - Willem v. d. Beij.Lntje, Archangel. - Bedalia, Kje-loe. Frederikstad. -Lympha, Allum.Dramuich.- Fiiigheden, Mathüsen, ld. - Preciosa, Thomson, id. VLIE, 31 Aug.; Martha. Bauting. Petersburg. -Zeeploeg, Luder, Kiga.-(.hnstisa, Zachrisson, Holbeck. — 1 Sept.; Symon en Martina, Uldenburger, Archangel. - Pieter, Oostervink, Riga. - Frankliu, liohman. Stockh.- Willeml, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Sept.-, Brother&apos;s Success, Hobart, Rochester. - Spnngflower, Pritchard. Newcastle.- Thomas en Isabella. Nicholson.id,- Eweretta, Annes, id. - Elizabeth en Jane, Easson. id. - Zeevaart, Ritzes, Arendsburg. HAMBURG,30 Aug.; Vr. Geerdina, Speelman, Gron. -31 Aug.; Voerman. Lukkien, Amst, CUXHAVEN, 30 Aug.; Grietje Woltovs, Alberts, Zwolle. WISMAR, 29 Aug.; Gouverneur van Ewijck, S., Amst. SARPSBORG, 21 Aug.; Kebekka. Dahm, Nieuwed. STAVANGER, 16 Julij; Martine, Enoksen, Amst. — 18 Julij; Caprice, Larsen, Schiedam. — 20,1 ulij; Ertzager, Edstrüm, id. - Marie Sophic, Taraldsen. id. — 30 Julij; Oemen. Lindtner, id. BEBtiEN, 4 Aug.; Gesina Alida, Meijer, Petersb. BREMERHAVEN. 30 Aug.; Poseidon. Deddes, Santa Martha. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 29 Aug.; Anna Gesini, de Vries, Petersburg n. Londen. - Weltevreden, Kiel&apos;, iel. n, Amst. - Clasina Aidina,Wirt,jes, Rott. ». d. Oostzee. - Margaretha.Wilniink, Stettin n. Belfast. KOPENHAGEN, 29 Aug.». Ifenriette.Weber,Newc- Alplnrd,Puister Petersb. - Hoop, Cort, Livorno. * hr. DAVID&apos;S, 29 Aug.; Julies• Sopbi?,Rasmussen, Amst.- Try,Durrant, Dordrecht.</p>
	<p>RIO JANEIRO, 4 Aug.; Cornelia &amp; Geertruida, Wiolema, Newcastle. BUENOS-AYRES, 11 Julij; Jeltina, Scherpbier, Londen. FKRNAMBUC, 13 Aug.; Krommenie, Engelsman, Triest. MARANHAM, 24 Aug.; Zuid-Laren, Triest.</p>
</text>
