<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 15 Aug.; Zeemanshoop, Dekker, Curacao. - Reina, Munneke, Londen. - Naphtali, Johns, Newport. - Azores Packet, Stevens, Liverpool. - Frithjhof, Torbjornsen, Frederikstad (benevens de schepen per tel. gemeld). VLIE, 14 Aug.; Nora, S., Londen. - Jantina, Lohman, Sandefiord. - Nyssiona, Prak, Frederikstad. - Alida Hendrika, Bicze, id. - Egberdina Anna, Schuring, id.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 14 Aug; Ouderkerk a/d. Amstel,Dingemans, Bat., 1. v. Brouwersh. — 15 Aug.; Maria Anna, Monnom, Banjoewangie, l.v. Brouwersh. -Ida Willemina, Rotgans, id. l.v. id.-Amphitrite, Calvé, Rédon. - Osprey, S., Liverpool. - Retriever,Wynack, Liverp. - Gesina Alida, Meijer, Riga. - Rotterdam, S., Dantiig. - Henriette Susanna, van Wijngaarden, Frederikstad. BROUWERSHAVEN, 15 Aug.; Mathilde, Jörgensen, Frederikstad n. Dordrecht (benevens het schip per tel. gemeld). ZIERIKZEE, 15 Aug.; de schepen per tel. gemeld. BREMERHAVEN, 14 Aug.; Voorwaarts, de Vries, Frederikshald.- Agatha, Tonkes, Hamburg. - Gebroeders, Loodijzen, Petersburg. - Sophia Maria, Feenstra - Espérance, Brandt, Porto Cabollo. SWINEMUNDE, 11 Aug.; Geerdina Geertruida, Kramer, Leer.-Jacoba, Muntendam, id. STETTIN, 11 Aug.; Nina, S., Amst.. (vertrok n. Dantzig). - Georg,Mulder, Burntisland. DANTZIG, 11 Aug.; Johanna Petronella, Hillebrandt, Petersburg. REVAL. 4 Aug.; Stad Appingedam, Olsen, Newcastle. HELSINGBORG, 1 Aug.; Maria, Jacobs, Newcastle. ELSENEUR, 9 Aug.; gepasseerd: Sirius, Hansen, Lulea n. Antw.- Peru, de Jonge, Gene n. Australië.- Families, Aas, Suudswalln. Nederl. -Wester- Kwartier, Dijk, Bjorneborg n. Malaga.- Beurs van Amsterdam.Tofte, Amst. n. Riga. - Sophie&apos; Cöwan, Riga n. het Nieuwe Diep. - Rauma, Nielsen, id. n. Amst. - Engelina Pietrónella, Brouwer, Arer.dsb. n. de Maas. - Egelie, Basberg, Sundswall n. het Nieuwe Diep. - Margaretha Antina, de Boer, Petersb. n. Dundee. - Concordia, Naatje, Dantzig n. Dordt. - Atalante, Evensen, Hörncfoi-3 n. Nederland. - Jacoba Alida, v. d. Laan, Riga n. Schiedam. - Welgelegen, Nieting, Memel n. Harlingen. - Sprayt, Pott, Riga n. de Maas. - Marie Coralie, Bakker, id. n. Dordt. - 2 Gezusters, Bakker.Windau n. Newcastle. - Soranus, Poelman, Riga n. Dordt. - Elisabeth Lolliua, Karst, Petersburg n. Amst. - Sieka, de Groot, id. n. Christiania.- Trygve, Ulleberg, Nieuwe Diep n. Nerva. -Emely, Bülow, Stockholm n. Amst. — 11 Aug.; Tonsberg.Thue, Nieuwe Diep. - Niord, Thorsen, Antw. n. Hernüsand. - Lucretia, Bracht&apos; Riga n. Londen. ■ Trouw, Bosker, id. n. Gend. - Collegie Voorzorg, Hubert, id. n. Antwerpen.</p>
	<p>LONDEN, 13 Aug.; Tw?e Zusters, Feenstra, Worcum. — 14 Aug.; De Hoop, Jelsma, id. - Zwaluw, Blomberg, Rio Grande. FALMOUTH, 11 Aug.; Carlo, Martes, Brazilië n. Amst. - Catharina, Albers,Rio Granden.Bremershavcn.-14Aug;Elisabeth,_Hetus,Rio Janeiro. Bij BEVEZIEB, 12 Aug.; Wildeman, Driest, Amst.n. de.Kaap de Goede Hoop; alles wel aan boord. Bij DUNGENESS, .. Aug.; Zeemeeuw Sikkema, Terra Nova n.Dordt. BLYTH, 12 Aug.; Alfrcd, Meriel, Rott.&apos; CARDIFF, 11 Aug.; Zeven Sterren, Hemmes, Sshiedam. HULL, 11 Aug.; Elisabeth Davy, Dav y, Rott. LEITH, 12 Aug.; Cornelia Catharina, Hagedoorn, Antwerpen. JERSEY, 11 Aug.; Wesley, Lecouteur, Rott. SHIELDS, 13 Aug.; Palladium, |Johnson, Rott- - Mars, Cunningham, id. - Grace, Howard, id. —14 Aug.; Columbine, Malbranc, id. - von Schack Retschendorf, Bross, id. - Margareth Arm, Wilüams, Dordt. - Barbara Jonker, Oltman, Londen. SUNDERLAND, 12 Ang.; Marchodeo, Ripctto, Amst -Auckland, Allen, id. - Perle, Tamke, Rott. - Moslem, Tukker, id. - Aurora, Kuiper, Schiedam.- Thompson, Richardson, id. - Sultana, Bell, id. - Zcié Pierre, Poireau, id. - Thames, Longstaff, id. LAGUAYRA, 11 Julij; Gezusters, van D«yn, Hamburg. — 19 Julij ; Gesina, Mulder, Liv erpool. PORTO CABELLO, 7 Julij; Nicolaas Albert, de Jonge, Liverpool. — 17 Julij; Regina, Peper, Malaga.</p>
	<p>VALPARAISO,22 Junij; Agnes, Semcker, Amst. tja £HOMAS&apos; 15 Jnbj; Santa Rosa, Buykes, Amst. BATAVIA, 29 Junij; Concurrent, van der Harst, Kust van Guinea.</p>
</text>
