<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>... Fenna, Woudsma, Frederikstad.. Catb»KM, jy^ Drammen - Johanna Hansen, Oudsoen - 13 Aug• Jo&apos; Old.nburgêr, Frederik&apos;st^l Gee.&apos; s,na,R,ksd - Jonkvrouw elisabeth, de Boer, id. - AberdTnaMkdL&apos;&quot; SC«^«;T&apos;^Ge.2;,S-ter&apos;&apos; Christiania. okkelma&apos; CUXHAVPI f .fJg-; Helena Catharina Knndsen, Porto (fctello. Tide, cIJJ „&apos; 144uS-ilouiseSophie,Hollander, Ipswiëh. -15 Aug; __iaes,^_a»sen3(portor;c9i &quot;&quot;fa-t NSxtVA, 3 Ang.; Allegonda, de Vries, Bergen. — 4 Aug ■ FrfrVa thtph w,lm&apos;tAnsi Hef3teUing&apos; Lükkién Newcait,B-:- &amp;&amp;*xkSS PILLAU, 13 Aug.; Vrouw Gri .Stje, Schoon, Bremen LONDEN, 12 Aug.; Silctns, Davidson, Whampoa. DEAL, 13 Aug,; ..., China h. Londen. SHIELDS, 12 Ang.; Mina, Heeren, Amst; - Britton, Foreman Schic f\~ «^A«g-ï Jessie Craig, Jitrvis, Amst. - Anrelïano Dodero id Zephyrus, EUiot, Nieuwediep. - Marsden, Paton, id. - Helen Adams llntt Ellen Owen, DaVis, id. - Sarah Arm, Rayne, id,-Good^^n BJeretÖn &apos;v™ *$°^^&lt;™i&amp; ■ Sarah a?d id : Van , Thompson, Schiedam. -. Gesina Jantina, v. Klooster, id. - Princes* Part ,d. - Harmony, Richmond, Dordt. - William and Henry, Johnsonid LIVERPOOL, 13 Aug.; Dirk Hendrik, Prins, Buenos Ayres CLYDE. 12 Aug;Leonoïe, Jotlgebloftd,Havana, LEITH, 13 Aug.; Baudina, Pool, Harlingen. DUNDEE, 12 Ang.; Fortuna, Zwa 1, Petersburg. MONTROSE, 12 Ang^ Thetis, Bakker, Petersburg. GIRGENTI, 4 Aug.; Thcresia, Wekenborg Jzn., Napels. NEW-YORK, SI Julij; Magdalena, Henkerßott. ££mv a^?!^^&apos;* C^par de Robles&apos;r- SlooteD&apos; A&quot;»st. SURINAME, 18 Julij; Palöa, Tiktak, Unvuay. _ UITGEZEILD? HARLINGEN 15 Aug.;Bon Père, Lemerle, Engeland. .„°™AMr&apos; 14 Aug.; Battruida, Jonkhoff, Rochester. - Margaretha Hillechiena, Pekclder, Glouccster. - Aurelia Gruno, Stuitje, Avontuur • HAMBURG, 14 Aug.; Jantina Pietronella, de Boer, Nederland - Drie Gebroeders, Alberts, id. — 15 Aug.; Amstel, S., Cuxhaven. NERVA, 3 Aug.; Annechina Hermina, Zuidema, Hartlepool. — 6 Ave • Broedertronw, Vos, Amst. - Goldhorn, Pott, Duinkerken. BOLDERA A, 10Aug.; zeilkl: 2 Vrienden, Ebes, Amst. LONDEN, 14 Aug.; zeilkl : Maria, Beekman, Buems-Ayres. DUINKERKEN, 11 Aug.; Hermanna Hendrika, Slstema, Middlesbro&apos;.</p>
</text>
