<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Aug.; Bonna Roeraeling, Visser, Londen. - Enigheden, J°r&apos; gensen, Umea. - Martha, Hansen.Wyburg. - Nina, S., Dantzig VLIE, 21 Aug.; Fenna, Smidt, Archangel. - Meika Jacoba. Wiel&lt;&quot;**&apos; Petersburg. - Welgelegen, Nieting, Memel. - Gut Heil, Muller, Koningsb* Johanna, Berg, id. - Amstel, S., Hamburg. T HELLEVOETSLUIS , 22 Aug.; Ena Elisabeth, Smit, Terrano^&apos; Island Queen, S., Hartlepool. - Broederschap, Bakker, Petersb. - J»00 ! Cornelia, Fokkes, id. - Engelina Pietronella, Brouwer, Arendsb. - Job*1110&quot; 1 aulma, Wessels, Riga. - Sprayt, Pott, id. - Haabet, Falck, id. - Sora&apos;&quot;**&apos; Poelman, id. - Ziba, Pcderscn, Windau. - Condor, Kading, Libau.-&gt;&apos;10 Huisman, Dantzig. - Martha, Topzant, id. BRIELLE, 22 Ang.; de Maas, S., Londen, is derwaarts teruggekeerd* Albert, S., Huil. - Grctina, Gortemaker, Libau. 22 Aug, het schip per telegram gemeld. .. ELSENEUR, 18 Aug.; gepasseerd : Elsina, Nanninga, Brake n. de O*»&apos; zee. - Elisabeth, Arends, Dantzig n.Gron. — 19 Aug.; Jan &amp;Jacob, üurê hardt, Rott. n. Riga. - Leentje, Hoedemaker, Newc. n. Memel. HOLTENAU, 18 Ang.; gepasseerd : Etta Johanna, Groenewold, Ode»8, * n. Holland. — 19 Aug.; Elisabeth, Top, Memel n. Brussel. - Tjakio9 Boer, Dost, Grenae n. Amst. GEESTEMUNDE, 21 Aug.; Sophia, Bieze, Delfzijl. BREMERHAVEN, 21 Aug.; Margaretha Hendrika, de Boer, Nerva- SWINEMUNDE, 19 Aug.; Ida Berendina, Op &apos;t Holt, Burnt lil»&quot;4&apos; Hendrika Margaretha, Stel, Middlesbro. DANTZIG, 18 Aug.; Lambert, Kramer, Fraserburgh. - Catharina&amp;CZ drika, Feugen, Kopenhagen. — 19 Aug.; Maria, Ebeling, Colbem. • Vr&quot;11 Roelina, Elbrecht, Newc. RIISOER, 7 Aug.; Eendragt, de Witt, Delfzijl (11 dito derwaarts ter&quot;? gekeerd). — 8 Ang.; Grietje, Niebocr, Edam (11 dito derwaarts teW keerd). —11 Aug; Pilen, Andersen, Amst. - Geertruida, Bontekoe, H»1&apos; y • LONDEN, 19 Aug.; Broedertrouw, de Groot, Petersburg. — 21 &gt;&apos;?&apos;. Jacoba Gesina, Kramer, Alexandrie. - Margaretha, Brambergen, Pote&quot;;!. Domina Geertina, Wolters, Gothenburg, - Pcrseverance, Elliott, M&quot;e»*!f. blik. - Johanna, Oosterkamp, Nyekjöbing. - Aurora, Vaalman, Kougell&apos; Zcldenrust, Knol, Randers. Bij DEAL, 19 Aug.; Vlaardingen, Goudswaard,Lissabonn.BergeJb&apos;, Neptunus, van der Gaast, Harlingen n. Havana. - Presto, Roelfsema, B»18 n. Santos. Bij DOVER. 19 Aug.; Kaapstad Packet,Niewold,Rott.n.Buenos-Ayr&lt;*&apos; Bij PLYMOUTH, .. Aug.; Pieter Adolf, Jaski, Amst. n. Cardiff. FALMOUTH, 20 Aug.; Matahor, Kimme, Raugoon. ALLOA, 17 Aug.; Trio, Barms, Rott. „ (, NEW-CASTLE, 17 Aug.; In lading: Gesina, de Boer, Petersburg. - °e trude, Kramer, Riga. - Mina, Heeren, Lissabon. ROCHESTER, 19 Aug.; Margaretha Hillegina, Pekelder, Groningen- SHIELDS, 19 Aug ; Margaretha Antina, Puister, Stolpemunde. SPALDING, 20 Aug.; Harmonie, Tunteler, Koningsbergen. DUINKERKEN, 20 Aug.; Pietronella, Wirtjes, Koningsb. TRIEST, 18 Ang.; Clio, Roskamp, Porto Cabello. TARRAGONA, 9 Aug.; Willem van den Bey, Lutje, Barcelona. BYDNEY, 7 Junij; Amieus, Ganswijk,</p>
</text>
