<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL,2BMaart;SwaBnïïEfS xi EÏ3 2? Maart; Magnet, S., Londen. - Joséphine, Hansen, ürobachj - Fnts &lt;Jj Betsv, Stuut, Christiansand. HELLEVOETSLUIS 21 Maart; L.J.Enthoven, Koens. Bat. l.v.Zierikzee - LAgriculteur Viaud, Nantes. -W. S. Flower, Flower, Londen.-reiican b., Liverpool. - Eleanor, Doughton, Whitehaven. - Jane and Elle^n\C™dn, w&apos;&quot; *?$ Raglan&apos; S-&gt;Newc-&quot; Aftert, S., Huil. EMDEN, 24 Maart; Fenna, Dirks, Hamburg. LEER, 21 Maart; Anke, Bleeker, Bremen. — 24 Maart; Jacobus Cornehus, Schoon, Delfzijl. - Maria, v.Wijngaarden, Utrecht. HAMBURG, 26 Maart; Jacob Synes, Nip, Londen.—27 Maart; Amsterdam, S„ Amst. LANGESUND, 12 Maart; Ena, Looze, Termunterzyl. - Nyssiena Veltman, id. — 15 Maart; Alida, Feiken, Delfzijl. LAURVIG, 16 Maart; Helena Gesina, Schreuder, Delfzijl TRAVEMUNDE, 24 Maart; Roelfina, Prins, Malmöe. DANTZIG, 25 Maart; Urania, S., Pillau. ELSENEUR, 25 Maart; gepasseerd: Rubbens, S., Amst. n. Dantzig — 26 Maart; Rembrandt, S., id. n. Koningsb. - Triton, Burghout Harlingen n. Falkenberg. &apos; &amp; LONDEN, 28 Maart; Albrecht Frederik, Koens, St. Lucia. PORTLAND, 26 Maart; Elizabeth, Amold, Caen n. Dublin Bij FALMOUTH, 27 Maart; Geortina. Mooi, Port-au-Prince n Antw TEIGNMOUTH, 26 Maart; Elsina, Vlieger, Exeter. LIVERPOOL, 27 Maart; Juno, de Jonge, Galveston. - Zuiderzee de Jong, id. - Lubinka, Sipp, Amst. - August, Bruhns, id. WISBEACH, 25 Maart; Hendrik en Übbo, Boer, Norden. HULL, 26 Maart; Agina Undiua, Brouwer, Dordt. - Alida Margaretha, Eisses, Siioreham. IPSWICH, 26 Maart; Catharina de Boer, Waterborg Groningen. SUNDERLAND, 25 Maart; Belina, Pott, Schiedam? SHIELDS, 26 Maart; Barteld Herman, Easker, Londen. - Karel Bernh ard , Bakker, id. BELFAST, 27 Maart; de Maas, Schabeling, Dordt. - Otto San Rica. HOLYHEAD, 26 Maart; Arme, Oats, Dordtn.Barroii BRISTOL, 26 Maart; Balmoral, S., Rott. SANTANDER, vóór 21 Maart; Phoenix, Glim, San Sebastian. CADIX, 18 Maart; Krommenie, Engelsman, Bahia. LICATA, 7 Maart; Adelina, de Martino, Napels (vertr. 16 Mrt.n.Rott.) LOSINA, 9 Maart; Aaltje Maathuis, do Vries, Triest. TENERIFFE, 9 Maart; Gouverneur Nagtglas, Lieneman, Amst. n. de Kust van Guinea. 10.</p>
</text>
