<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 18 April, N. N. O. — O. N. O.; Alaambra, Moulton, Banjoew.; vertrok 2 Dec. - Gaspar de Robles, v. Slooten, Suriname - Willem Jacobns, de vries, id. - Marsala, Dodero, Ibraïla. - de Hoop, Giezen, Cette. - Heeg, Boontje, Londen. - Vesper, Pond, Liverpool. - Bessie, Morday, Sunderl. - Brilliant, Sandersen, id. — 19 April; Leopard, Mathiesen, Trinidad.- Orion, S., Midd. Zee. - Marie, Quintin, Nantes. - Marie Madelaine, Garnier, id. - George &amp; Charles,Mahy, id.-John &amp; James, Balmford, Middlesbro. -Alert, S., Huil. VLIE, 17 April, 0.N.0.; Lucia, Albers, Straalsund. - Argo, de Boer, Noorw. - Lucia, Albers, Straalsund. - Argo, de Boer, Noorwegen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 18 April, 0.N.0.; Grondwet, Kamminga, Bat., 1. v. Zierikzee. - Bessie Crosby, Crosby, N.-Vork, 1. v.Brouwersh. - Enthoven, Stomp, Bordeaux, n. Petersb.; als bijlegger. — 19 April; Kaleroo, Nijman, Odessa, 1. v. Brouwershaven.-Jules &amp; Félix, Louis, Rédón. - Ary Scheffer, S., Havre.- Harmony, Richmond, Newc. - Adriana Wilhelmina, v. Eijk,id.- Friends Wells, id.-Lyra, Strong, id.-Swanland, 5.,Hu11.-Leeds, S., Gnmsby. „ , BRIELLE, 19 April, Z. 0.; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. - Anna, S., Bergen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 19 April, Z.; Fortune leller,Welch, Par. n. Rott. - Superior, Hutchiu, Runcorn n. id. ZIERIKZEE, 18 April, Z.; Oourser, Whitear, Runcorn naar Dordtrecht.</p>
	<p>LEER, 14 April-, Catharina, Springer, Amst. -Uit Dankbaarheid, Bolmeijer, Groning. — 15 April; Helena Johanna, Rosenboom, id. BREMERHAVEN, 16 April; Trijntje Schuitema, Mooi, Amst. - Jacobus Cornelius, Schoon, Gron. - Hannah Caroline, de Boer, id. - 17 April; Herstelling, Panjer, Firth of Forth. WARNEMUNDE, 17 April; Christine, Dethloff, Dantzig n. Rotterdam.</p>
	<p>DANTZIG, 15 April; Rembrandt, S., Amst. HELSINGBORG, 7 April; Nijverheid, Rumee, Charlestown. RENDSBURG, 14 April; Ma&apos;rgaretha, Giesse, Koningsb. n. n. Gron. — 15 April; Geerdina, Visser, Bremen n. Dantzig. — 16 April; Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Dokkuni n. Friedericia. - Harmina, Gert, Hamb. n. Nyekjöbing. LONDEN, 16 April; Elisabeth, Boon, Groningen. COLCHESTER, 15 April; Aukje Gepkelina, de Vries, Gron. SUNDERLAND, 15 April; Portwallis, Sayer, Nieu wediep. - Beautine, Salado, Harlingen. SHIELDS, 16 April; Nina, Graffione, Nieuwediep. - George, Deacon, Rott. WICK, ...; Friso, Faber, Engelholm. CARDIFP, ik »rviUfWanns, Springer, Bremen. gSföT^xEA^^^elffliKrl^^ri&apos;nesi n. x,iga.--2 Gebroeders, Waterborg, Glouccster. DEAL, 17 April, N. O.; Guortje en Marie, Plens Jhzn., Newcastle n. Batavia.</p>
	<p>Bij BEVEZIER, 17 April; Eddystone, Boates, Padang n. Amsterdam. Bij DUNGENESS, 17 April; Neerlands Vlag, v. d. Broek Humfrey, Banjoew. n. Rott., met een loods aan boord. Bij FALMOUTfI, 15 April; Bengalen, den Broeder, Tjilatj. n. Rott.</p>
	<p>GOUDSTAART, 10 April; Onrust, Weissenbruch, Hamburg n. Engeland, DUINKERKEN, 16 April; Ceres, Remmers, Groningen. CAEN, 13 Aprü; Wilhelmina Petronella, Bijl, Groningen. — 14 April; Dina Adriana, Kwint, id. CAMARET, 10 April; Adèle et Marie, Guellec, Cette n.Rott. St. NAZAIRE, 15 April; Jantina, Boon, Amst BORDEAUX, 16 April; Johanna Margaretha, Ei, Gron. CADIX, 12 April; Wilhelmina, v. d. Weijden, Amst. KONSTANTINOPEL, 6 April; Dawn, Tyrer, Amst. n. de Donau.</p>
	<p>St. HELENA, 16 Maart; Philips van Marnix,Langenbergqq., Batavia n. Rott.; heeft de reis voortgezet. 18en.</p>
</text>
