<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 April; Petrus, Jansen, Ohristiania. ¦• Achilles, Wulsberg, id. - Prithiof, Tornbiornsen.Frederikstad. - Soeblomsten, Petersen, id. — 3 April; Achille Marie, Tcsserot, Nantes. - Stad Enschedé, Veldhuis, Dundee. - Armwell, Ferney, Seaham. - Ellida, Agaard, Christiania. - Comniorsien, Jensen, Frederikstad. - Emanuel, Johnsen, id. - Wenskabet, Abrahamsen, id. - Chelone, Frcdrichsen, Drammen. - Pelgrim, Erichsen,id. VLIE, 2 April; Nora, S., Londen. - Remolia Geertruida, Katoen, Christiania. — 3 April; Amsterdam, S„ Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 3 April; Speculant, Nijland,Bahia.- Gouverneur Schomerus, Verberne, Kust van Guinea. - Diewerdina Alida Pot, Meyering, Nantes. - Balinoral, S., Cardiff. - Betty &amp; Jane, Raine, New- Castle.</p>
	<p>HAMBURG, 2 April; Stoomvaart, S., Amst. • Bonna Roemeling, Visser, Londen.</p>
	<p>GOTHENBURG, 28 Maart; Fcnna, Woudsma, Harlingen. DANTZIG, 29 Maart; Vriendschap, de Vries, Amst. LONDEN, 1 April; de Vrede, Nickus, Rio Jaueiro. Bij DUNGENESS, 1 April; Hendrika Cornelia, ...,New-York n.Amst. Bij DEAL, 1 April; Lady Arm, Philips, Bat. n. Amst. Bij DOVER, 31 Maart; Graafstroom, de Boer, Newc. n. Singapore. - Whampoa, Metz, Sunderland n. Padang. COWES, 31 Maart; Geertruida Janna, van Heyningen, Maroim naar Landscrona (met gebrek aan proviand). FALMOUTH, 1 April; Grietje, Legger, Londen n. Newport. Bij den MEEUWENSTEEN, 30 Maart; Heury B. Wright, Park, Rott. n. Cardiff.</p>
	<p>CHARLESTOWN, 1 April; Sieka, de Groot, Harlingen. - Drie Gebroeders. Feuonga, Soarborough, SUNDERLAND, 30 Maart; Amieitia, Gortemaker, Leer. GLASGOW, 31 Maart-, Majestic, Robertson, Rott. HARTLEPOOL, 30 Maart; Oatharina, van der Meulen, Sandwich. SHÏELDS, 1 April; Jcltina, Korter, Harlingen, - Prudence, Buining, Delfzijl - de Spruit, Pott, Schiedam. - Zeevaart, Engelsmam Pareham. - Cornelia,Voogd, Bremerliaven. - Trijntje, Visser, Brcmcn. - Vriendschap, Lodcwijks, Londen. - Gesina, Deen, Rochcster. NANTES, 30 Maart; Elise, Riensema, Dordt. BORDEAUX. 30 Maart; Annyi, Hubcrt, Newcastle. MARSEILLE, 30 Maart; Anna Paulowna, S., Alcxandrie. CHERBURG, 27 Maart; Avenir, Bossais, Redon n. Amst. Bij OPORTO, 23 Maart; Maria Adolphine, Meuldijk, Sunderland. LÈSINA, 9 Maart; Aaltje Maathuis, de Vries, Triest n. Amst. GIBRALTAR, 16 Maart; Maria Johanna, van Gelderen Sr., Vlaardmgen. - Krommenie, Engelsman, Bahia (zeilkl. n. Triest). MADERA, 9 Maart; de Hand«l,Westerling,Amst.(l6diton.St.lhomas vertrokken). TRIEST. 28 Maart; Triest, S., Rott., enz.</p>
</text>
