<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEX W.; Leontine, Auxray, Nantes. - Trijntje, Visser, Dieppe. - Hawk, S., Huil. — Gisteren nog: Catharina,v. d. Meulen, Lond&apos; VLIE, 28 Nov.,W. N.W.; Olga, S., Londen, 29 dito uit Texel weder derwaarts vertrokken.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 29 Nov., W.; Albert Homan, Scholtens, Genua. - Clarisse, Samzun, Nantes. - Jean, Auvreth, id. - Temperance Star, Meil Caen. - Lion, Flower, id. - Lucy, Mc&apos; Yvor, id. - Triomphante, Borsais! Pontrieux. - St. Joseph, Codbesin, St. Brieux. - Feijenoord, S., Londen - Heron, S., id. - Balmoral, S., Bristol. - Blonde, Choimet, Petersb. 1. v. Vlissingen. BRIELLE, 29 Nov., W.Z.W.; Ary Seheffer, S., Havre.- Edith, S., Huil - Eavensbury, S., Harwich. BEOUWEESHAVEN, 29 Nov., W.; Tyrol, Lowis, Bassein n. Eott - Southern Eights,Williams,Baltim. n. id.-Eoyal Charlie, Ebrigge.Philad. A. n. id. - Wilhèlmina Waitz von Eschen, Zander, Odessa n. id. - Plover&apos; Williams, Par n. Dordrecht.</p>
	<p>EMDEN, 25 Nov.; Antie, Matroos, Hoogezand. —26 Nov.; Nooit Gedacht, Hoogeboom, Sneek. AEENDAL, 18 Nov.; Odin, Jorgensen, Amst. L AURVIG, 15 Nov.; Margaretha Marchiena, Bekkering, Petersburg TONSBERG, 14 Nov.; Enigheden, Gullichsen, Nieuwe Diep. TRA VEMUNDE, 27 Nov.; 2 Gebrüder, Ulrichs, Amst. SWINEMUNDE, 27 Nov.; Meermin, Smith, Bremen. ELSENEUR, 26 Nov.; Wicherdina, Dijken, Dantzig n. Huil.— 27 Nov.; Trijntje Gezina, Bos, Petersb. n. Bristol.- Rembrandt, S., Dantz. n. Amst! HOLTENAU, 23 Nov.; Anke, Bleeker, Bandholm n. Amsterdam. — 24 Nov.; Catharina Alida, Pronk, Ystad n. Schiedam. - 4 Gezusters, Frieling, Kjerteminde n. Zaandam. LONDEN, 27 Nov.; Victor, Reader, Vlissingen. FALMOUTH, 28 Nov.; Aluda, Dallinga, Zante, om order. GLOUCESTER, 27 Nov.; Arme, Rowe, Rott. GREAT YARMOUTH, 27 Nov.; Whim, Smith, Alkmaar. HULL, 27 Nov.; John &amp; Martha, Greaves, Rott. LEITH, 27 Nov.; Aurora, Muller, Drammen. - Wietska, Bos, Petersb. PALERMO, 23 Nov.; Hendrik, Slik, Brussel.</p>
</text>
