<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 15 April, N. O. — N. W.; Daniël Rankin, Hartwell, Batavia, vertrok 24 Dee. - denElsbout, Akkerman, id., vertrok 30 Dcc .- Lynet, Aarve, Soerab., vertr. 21 Dee. - India Packet, vertr. 2 Dee. - Oceaan, Smit,Banjoew.,vertr. 5 Dee. - Hofinung. Heidthoff, Straalsund. - Navigator, Kaass, Frederikst. - Felix, Gundersen, id. — Gisteren nog: Johns, Torgensen, Osterrisoer. VLIE, 14 April, N.N.0.; Frouwkje, de Boer, Assens. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 15Auril;Luctor&amp;Em8i-go, Ouwehand, Padang, 1. v. Zierikzee. - Hendrik Ido Ambacht, Bijl, Banjoew., 1. v. id. - Trino, Cosulich, Triest, 1. v. Brouwersh. - Jeune Noémie, Leguilloux, La Roche Bernard. BRIELLE, 15 April, N.N.0.; Avalon, S., Harwich. ZIERIKZEE, 15 April, N.0.; Grondwet, Kamminga, Bat. n. vertr. 7 Dee. LEER, 11 April; Vooruitgang, Salomons, Dordrecht. - Antina, Bohlen, Borkum. EMDEN, 9 April; Hansina, Obes, Hoogezand. BREMERHAVEN, 10 April; Zwaantina Itskina, Albers, Hamb. — 11 April; Cornelia, Jentsema, Frèderikstad. HAMBURG, 11 April; Seine,S.,Rott.- 12 April; Amsterdam, S., Amsterdam. GOTHENBURG, 8 Aprü; Wilhelmina Magdalena, Jansen, Maroïm. STETTIN, 11 April; Emilie, S., Eott. PILLAU. 9 April; Margaretha, Giesse, Gron. ELSENEUR, 9 April; Tjadda Geziena, Staal, Amst. n. Dantzig. - Amandus, Walker, Antw. n. Pemau. HOLTEN AU, 9 April; Lucia, Albers, Straalsund n. Zaand. FRIEDERICIA, 6 April; Trijntje Meijer, Tonckens, Hamburg n. Nijborg. Bij DUNGENESS, 12 April; Santa Rosa, de Waard, Amst. n. Curacao. - Cortgene, Wemmerus, Rotterdam n. Soerabaya. — 13 April; Jannetje, van Striemen, v. Java n. Rotterd. - Margaretha, Boerhave, v. Buenos-Ayres n. Antwerpen. Bij FOLKESTONE, 13 April; Maria en Elisabeth, Bonjer, v. Batavia n. Rotterdam. Bij DOVER, 11 April; Rio de la Plata, Homer, v.Montevideo n. Antwerpen. PÉTERHEAD, 12 April; Alb. Elzina, Uchtman, Amst. POOLE, 13 April; Heidewiga Regina, Pekelder, Shoreham. &apos; CARDIFF, 13 Apnl; Sador Prince, v. d. Valk, Rott. HARWICH, 13 April; Antina, de Vries, Londen n. Elseneur. IPSWICH, 11 April; NachmaLammechina,Rijnbero- Malmo SUNDERLAND, 13 Aprü; Elsje, Tap, Amst. Z&gt;mauxw- SHIELDS, 11 April; Helena, de Jonge, Gent. - Stella Maris Harding, Amst. - Immanuel, de Jonge, lpswich. - Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Londen. MAROIM, 27 Febr.; Perseverance, Jonker, St. Catharina. — 8 Maart; Prof. Suringar, de Jonge, Rio Janeiro. BOMBAY, vóór 6 April; Maria Elise, van Deursen, Cardiff.</p>
</text>
