<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 11 Nov., O. N. O.; Anna &amp; jbopma, Hoekstra, Bat. - Anna Lena, Visser, Suriname. - Juffer Esse Mensinga, Eefting, Beyruth. - Lion, S., Londen.-Alberdina, Bakker, Newc-Mainz, Teerling, Sunderland. - Eleanor, Memmei, Hartlepool.-Magrietha, de Vries, Middlesbro. -Albatros, Lee, id.- Seahorse, S., Huil. - Marie, Mortcnsen, id. - Anna Andersen, Engeland. - Frederike Louise, Lercke, id.- Chnstian August, Eversen, Frederikstad. - Bethel, Mauritzen, Noorwegen. - Europa, Lorentzen, id. - Dantzig, Christensen, id. - Eichard &amp; Clara, Haijer, id. - Wodan, M einders, Riga. VLIE, 10 Nov., 0.N.0.; Prosper, Martin, Skeen n. Frankrijk. - Anna Margaretha, Olthotr, Avontuur.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 11 Nov., 0.N.0.; LaPlata, Kuiper, Montevideo. - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Ranger; S., id. - Herbert, Thomas, id. - Mary Kellow. Molby, Penzancei - Agnest Grimshead, Cardiff. - Ricliard Warbric&apos;k, Dennison, idi - Pill Castle, Idelow, Liverpool. - Edith, Jones, Ëarrow. - Colltitess of Carthness, Reid, Findhorn. - Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Dante, Gazola, Newc. - Forest Flower, Rymer, id. - Arab, Baxter, id. - Alida, Hart, id. - Elbe Packct, Batt, id. - Juan, Salomon, id. - Bengalen, de Goede, id. - Snaresbrook, Wood, id.-Rrenda, Foster, id.- Svithior, Johnson. id. - Freya, Schmidt, id. - Auspicious, Brown, Seaham. - Swanland, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole.- Amicitia, S., Bergen. - Rebecca, Dahm, Noorwegen. - Abba, Hazeby, id. - Abeloria Kirstina, Jorgensen, id. - Jura, Gronwold, id. - Avenir, Bjornebo, id.-Andover, Holst, id-Germania, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 11 Nov., N. 0.; Sheffield, S., Grimsby. - Percy, Hart, Amble. BROUWERSHAVEN, 11 Nov., N.N.0.; BastiaanPot, Zetteler, Rott. n. Bat. VEERE, 10 Nov.; Zwaan, Riedijk, Oud-Calabar. SWARTVICK, 31 Oct.; Elisabeth, Visser, Amst. MONTROSE. 5 Nov,; Annechina, Smit, Newcastle. GLOUCESTER, 9 Nov.; Goudviscb, Douwes, Cette. FALMOUTH, 6 Nov.; Christiane, Sorle, Koogerp. - Aurora, Bulow, Rott. - Giulietta, Ferrala, id. CARDIFF, 9 Nov.; Wilhelmine, Hazewinkel, Rio Grande. - Stad Appingadam, Kaiser, id.- Anna Maria, Spijkman, St. Thomas. - Hendrik Wester, Drenth, Marseille. LIVERPOOL, 9 Nov.; Veendam, Potjewijd, Barbados. - Zeevaart, Mulder, Cadix.</p>
	<p>CADIX, 5 Nov.; Carolina Cornelia, Peters, Rio Grande. - Ceres, Menldijk, Buenos-Ayres. LISSABON, 30 Oct.; Cornelia Maria, Wietsma, Carloforte n. Antwerpen; (na volbragte reparatie.) - Laurens, de Kromme, Maassluis.</p>
</text>
