<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 8 Mei; Vertrouwen, Kal, Girgenti.-Anna, Hubert, Bordeaux.--2 Broeders, van Kempema, Londen.&apos; Vrouw Anna, Hospes, ïa.-Maltha, Ce_, Newcastle. - Whini, Smit, Yarmouth. - Rembrandt, S., Koningsb. VLIE, 7 Mei; N_&gt;ra, S., Londen. - Malvina, Rees, Liverpool.- Hendrika, Holman, FrM^j^s^. — 8 Mei; Argo, Alta, Christiania. - Jonge Wil- HELCfi yi^^Sj^SjS jjei; Anna Catharina, Henning, Malaga. - Ma-&apos; ria J|ha_ffia,yvU-Mer^r., st. Übes. - George, Richard, Nantes. - Wiebergiia MS_?%iJ&lt;io,ilah. Rédon. - Jeune Célestine, Pillard, idem.- i Motm^^f^m^- Tril» .e Geziaa, Bos, Workington. - Eichard | Warbrick, Dennison, ld. - Friends, Marïn, Newcastle. - Elizabcth, Truoman, id. - Maria Lucia, Detors, Hamburg. BROUWERSHAVEN, 8 Mei; Trewartha. Stool, Liverpool n. Dordt.- Krimpen a/d. Lelt. Rotgans, Rotterdam n. Hongkong. HAMBURG, 5 Mei; Annachiena, Buil, Bremen. — 6 Mei; Jantina, Sievers, Dordrecht. - Alberdina Fokkelina, Schuur, Altona.— 7 Mei; Vriendenlust, Koops, Bremen. KOPENHAGEN, 4 Mei; 3 Gezusters, Breeland, Riga. ELSENEUR, 5 Mei; gepass.: Joséphine, Them, Nieuwediep n. Gefile. — 6 Mei; Stad Worknm, Eisinga, Stettin n. Hartlepool. LONDEN. 7 Mei; Provincie Drenthe, Westerberg, Groningen. Bij DOVER, 5 Mei; Thorbecke, Witting, Hamburg n. Rio Grande, LIVERPOOL, 5 Mei; Maria, Pronk, Livorno. Bij MUMBLES, 6 Mei; Diana, Kraan, Swansoa n. Passages. NK WPORT, 4 Mei; Edouard Marie, van der Kolft&apos;, Rott. - de Weldaad, Pik, Dublin. PORT TALBOT, 4 Mei; Mary Kendall, Young, Rott. SUNDERLAND, 5 Mei; Ocoan, Storm, Rott. - Jaboz, Lucas, Dordt. - Mary Clara, Andrew, id. SHIELDS, 3 Mei; Sophia, Olsen, Amst. - Harmony, Humphry, Nieuwediep. - Elvira, Robinson, Dordt. - Juno and Arm, Leadley, id. — 6 Mei; Albrech- Frederik, Koens, Londen. - Eclbrandina, ten Cate, Yarmouth. CARDIFF, 4 Mei; Otto, Sap, Belfast. NEW-CASTLE, 4 Mei; ln lading: Margricta Marchina,Bekkering, Port a Port. - Neeljfe, de Vries. id. MACDUFF, 5 Mei-, Diana, Fyn, Hamburg. DIEPPE, 5 Mei; de Hoop, Pott, Havre.</p>
</text>
