<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>ÜITGEZEILD t&gt; ÏEXEL, 26 Sept.*, Jeltina, Mulder, Nantes - Zephyr S. Londen. - Mio CTnato, Olivara.Newc. - Bermuda, Hales id. - Nina Earl id. - Hudgill, ÏI.,emB,idl . Guardiana, Scott, Sunderland. - Vmd.Bedlingneld.id. - i&gt;&apos;&apos;Mtcr Thorbecke, S.,Hull. - Alert, S., id. - Thor Buil, Drammen. - CC1**&quot;»! Jansen, id, - Talma.Gullichsen, id. - Jud.th, Chnstensen, ld., do schepon per telegr. gemeld).</p>
	<p>VLIE, 2» Sept.) Noordster, Brouwer, Fredrikikald.»Familiën» Haab, Poulsen, Frederikstad.</p>
	<p>AMELAND. 24 Sept.*, Trientje, Terfehn, Hamburg. OSTMAHORN, 24 Sept.; Broedertrouw, Niezen, Newc. - Wilhelmina, Meijer, Stettin. - Trientje Meijer, Tonkens, Altona, - Vooruit, van Wijk, Avontuur. - Anna Hooites. Visser, id. - Hendrika, van der Veen, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2S Sept.; Mathildo, Haremberg, Buenos-Ayres.- Admiraal Vcrhuell, S., Ilavre.- Frithiof&apos;, Lund, Acksmar n. Antwerpen. - Ranger, S., Londen. - Balmoral, S., Bristol. - Ellen Stewart, Shaw, Cardiif. - Queen, 8., Dundee. - Gle.aner, Press, St. Davids. - Anna, S., Grangemouth. - Maria Stuart, S., Leith. -De Burger, Bartelse, Newc. - Seanorse, S., Huil. - John Wells, S., Goole. - Margaretha, Kampen, Windau. - I&apos;Adorate, Allain. Grimstad n. Lamion. - Amicitia, S., Bergen. BRIELLE. 26 Sept.; Leeds, S., Grimsby. MAASSLUIS, 26 Sept.-, Harvest, Went, Newc. - Mars, Cummings, id. - Elisabeth Lollina, Carst, id. - Cathcrinc, Wilkens, id.- Ocean, Storm, id.- Ellida, Svensen, Snnderl. - M.ary and Jane, Pcarson, Grangemonth.- Dieverdina, de Jonge, Stockton. - Newcastle Packet, Madsen, Stavanger. - Amanda, Lutjens, Stettin. - Balder, lrde, Haugesund. BROUWERSHAVEN, 26 Sept.; Arnold Boniuger, Steenken, Rott. n. New-York. ZIERIKZEE, 26 Sept.; Dugald Stervard, Bishop, Engeland. NORDEN, 18 Sept.-, Nooit Uedacht, Hogeboom, (iromngen. CUXHAVEN, 24 Sept.; Heerenveen, Prins, Liverpool. UDBYHOI, 13 Sept.; 4 Gebroeders, de Boer, Pruisen. AARHUUS, 15 Sept.; Jacoba Catharina, Geltes, Groningen. N YBORG, 19 Sapt.; Tjakiena de Boer, Dost, Amst. WISMAR, 22 Sept.; Martha, Topzaut, Noordzee. — 24 Sept.; Anna, Kamminga, id.</p>
	<p>MEMEL, 20 Sept.; Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Veges. - Hillechina Magr., Joosten, id. — 21 Sept.; Catbarina, Lucht, Brussel. LüN DEN, 24 Sept.; Zeevaart, Engelsman, Elseueur. - Maria, Santjer, Newcastle. St. MARY. 22 Sept.; Ranneys, Pander, Amst. FALMOUTH, 25 Sept.; Aquuisa, Anza, Amst. - Gardner Cobby, Mc. Lellan, Schiedam. - Espérance, Dik, Bcyruth. - Eexta, Lemminga, Kopenhagen. GRANTON, 22 Sept.; Patriot, Brand, Rott. DUBLIN, 24 Sopt.; Amicitia, Areus, Antw. ÏARMOUTH, 23 Sept.; Twee Gezusters, Meijer, Shiclds. HULL. 24 Sept.; Geertje Dijkstra, Veninga, lpswich. SHIELDS, 24 Sept. Zeilklaar: Elisabeth, Meedendorp, Rio Grande. BARCELONA, 21 Sept.; Geertruida en Janna, van Heiningen, Rio- Janeiro.</p>
	<p>SURINAME, 28 Aug.; Albatros, Koch, Amst. — 30 Aug.; Paramaribo, Jaski, id. St. HELENA, 14 Sept; Oscar I, Larson, Java n. Amst.</p>
</text>
