<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 27 April; Harmony, Richinond, Newcastle. AMELAND, 24 April-, Gesina, Noorman, Hamb. - Catharina, DSnokas, Hamburg-. DELFZIJL, 22 April; Snsanna, Barghoorn, Emdon, - Catharina Imkicna, Hulzebos, Leer, — 24 April; Coneordia, &lt;ïeven, Oadsoen. - Catharina, Dykenia, Christiania. - Cornelia, Lecu we, id. - Helena Johanna, Rozeboom, Leer. — 25 April; Eendragt, de Wit, Christiania. - Hillcchiena, Brakke, Lyngoor. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 April-, Trieste, S„ Middoll. Zee. - Gironde, S., Bordeaux.-Feijenoord, S., Londen. - Elisabeth and Asn, Stroug, Newcastle. - Swallow, S., Huil. - Collctis, S., Goole. BRIELLE. 27 April; Ary Schcffer, S., Havre.-Ravenhnry, S., Ilarwich. HAMBURG, 26 April; Jonge Barend, Prins, Terniunterzijl. DRONTHEIM, 15 Aprü; Concurrent, Teensuia, Nantes, AREND AL, 24 April; Aupechiena, Blauw, Croonstad, LANGESUND, 16 April; Beurs van Amsterdam. Toi&apos;te, Amst. - Alida, Feikoii, Delfzijl, - Nyssiena, Veltnian, Terniunterzijl. LAURVIG. 18 April; Trekvogel, Freese, Delfzijl. SARPSBORG, 16 April; Helene, Halvorscn, Nederl. BOLÜERA, 21 April-, Hermine, de Vos, Rott. - 23 April; Wilhelmine, ! Poolman, Ostende. - Scandia, Hutchinson, Nederl. ELSENEUIÏ, 2 . April. Gepasseerd: Gepina, K.ox.. Newc. n. Dantz. - Eendragt, WiUinga, Amst. n. Koningsb. — 24 April; Catharina, Thaden, id. n. Petersb. Bij DUNGENESS.2S April; Sirene, Hermamis,Rott. n. Philadelphia. Bij DEAL, 25 April; Noordhom, van Leeuwen, Antw. n. Exeter. PO RTSMOUTH, 25 A])ril; Sieuwcrten Johan, Looze, Groningen. WÏSBEACH, 25 Aprü; M. J. Enthoven en Zoon, Stomp, Elso«euv, DUNDEE, 24 April; Randolph, Wamel, Rott, --?_, SHIELDS, 24 April; Bctty, Ilughes, Rott. — 25 April; deßniffler, Bartelse, jd. - Victor, Arlington, id. - Telegraph, Spenco, id. - YV ïlliain _ Alico. Hast-ings, Dordt, ? ANTWERPEN, 2? April; Margretb- Amina, -poelman, Bremen. CADlX,22April;()ccaan,Post,Rottcrdam. LISSABON, 23 April; Alberdina, Lodewijks, Amsterdani^ GIB RA LTA R. 20 April-, Juffer Esse Mensinga, Eeitmg, Livoi no. BATAVIA. 8 Maart; W.Cores de Vries, S., Rott. &apos;¦ BT RAAT SUNDA, l_Maart; Ida Maria doßaathde B- ci-.Samarang h. Middelburg. - QHartet, Mulder, Amst. n. Bat, - fct.-Jan, Lonmievso, i Rott n id. - 15 Maart; Dordrecht, Boos, id. (1, van Portsinouth)n. ld.- Johaunes Anthonius, de Voogd van der Straten, ld. n. ia. Senior, BakkerPadang. . .</p>
</text>
