<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>_,-,___,_. T BINNENGEKOMEN. IBXEL, 25 Jung N.N.0.; Elisabeth, Piccard, Newc. - Emanuel, Hansen.Porsgrund. — Gisteren nog: Unity, Simonsen. Fredrikshald. »_ VLIi_. 24 JTunlJ&apos; NT-N-°&lt;; Vrouw Helena, Kraan, Christiania. -25 Junii; Mary Blaer, Jones, Liverpool. y&apos; liïnnlSffiK.- ..25 J. DiJ&apos;N&gt; °-&gt; Harmony, Richmond, Newc. BROUWERSHAVEN, 25 Junij; Aretas, Marshal, Londen n. Dordt. - Be-S^. ï&amp; -.18-I.,ïïewc-n-id- &quot; Julia,vanlLoon, Rott. n. Singapore. _ ?R^K£,AyEN&gt; 24 Junij; Alberdina, Greven, Dordt. - Aaltina Hendnka,Moie,Elbiug. LONDEN, 24 Junij; Frouwke, Heins, Groningen. - Katrina de Boer, Wè»T.^ .&apos;,-&apos;• L?ent.°&gt; Basker, id. - Drie Broeders, Bijkerk, Worknra. 1? Ï.?tÏHv??_5n-&gt;; lodewijk, Box, Rott.n.Banana. 1- S^NGENESS, 21 Junij; Jannetje, van Striemen, Rott. n. Bat. Z&amp;rïrïïW1!?2 Jumï; Aluda&apos;I)allin- •*. Newc. n. Malta. SHOREHAM, 21 Junij; Gazolle, Seagers, Rott. £_ fe.^SP-21 JunV&gt;Stad AsseD- Boer» Ne^c- &quot;■ Bombay. Snni-SM&apos; 21 3mi)&apos; Margaretha Hendrika, Datema, Plymouth. ROCHESTER, 23 Jung; Karsina, Olfers, Groningen. SVL,mV2.2^nv; ZeP hF Whiteley, Rott. HARTLLPOOL, 21 Junij; Hensina, Meeter, Gron. - Elisabeth Geertruda, Janknegt, id. SUNDERLAND, 22 Junij; Violet, Richardson, Nieuwe Diep. - Prince, Swinhoe id. - Jave, Fleming, id. - Cassandra, Fleming, id. - Vivid, Bedingheld.id. - Matthew and Arm, Wilson, id. - Jeune Henri, le Croix, Groningen. — 23 Jamj; Jamcs, Sterry, Schiedam. - Ver, Hall, Rott. - Emma, Paddon, id. SHIELDS, 22 Junij; Léopold graaf v. Limburg Stirum, Keuker, Rott. - Nydia, Scrafton, Nieuwe Diep. - Oriënt, Arthur, id. -Anna Gezina, de Vries, Gron. - Urania, S., Rott. — 23 Junij-, Washburn, White, Nienwed. - Mee Lee, Tinn, id. - Molby, Edward, id. - Janet Izak, Pringle, id. - Grietje Köens, Kuiner, jd. - Waters, Payne, Rott. -Waterwitch, Todd, id.- John &amp; Arm, &apos;Leadley, id. - Sieuwert en Johan, Looze, Groningen. - Vertrouwen, Koeps, id. - Dart, Fuller, Dordt. - Eliza, Pearson, Schiedam. -Ronaldes, Green, id. - Lubbegiena, de Jonge, Gron. - Anna, Collins, Rott- Euretta, Annis, id. -Victoria, Jenkinson, Dordt. - Friends, Wells, id. - Ange, Gron. - Jan Andreas, Dogen, Leeuwarden. - Baltic, Milborn, Dordtrecht. Snpcnor, Hutclnn, id. - Light fr Sign, Robinson, id. MESSINA, 10 Junij; Margaretha, Korte, Genua. — 11 Junij; Orion, S., Palermo. J &apos;</p>
	<p>St. HELENA, 10 Mei; Alblasserwaard, v. Lindern, Padang, vertrok n. New-York. —17 Mei: Aletta Augusta, Tinholt, Padang, vertrok n. Amst. - Macassar, Vitringa Coulon, Samarang, vertrok 18 n. Amst.— 19 Mei; Lomsa, Mellcma, Passaroeang, vertrok 20 n. Amst. - Ida Elisabeth, Dooren, Banjoewangie, vertrok 20 n. Rott. - Alida, Visser, Java, vertrok 20 n. Amst. - Sumatra, Buyser, Banjoewangie, vertrok 20 n. Rott. - Gerard Pieter Servatius, Beckering, Bat., vertrok 20 n. Amst. — 20 Mei; Ida Geertruida, v. Moerkerken, Soerabaya, vertr. 21 n. Eott. — 21 Mei; Ternate, Carst, Banjoewangie, vertr. 23 n. Rott. - Walcheren, v. d. Borden, Banjoewangie, vertr. 22 n. Rott, — 24 Mei; Concordia, v. Zanten, Tafelbaai. — 26 Mei; Bezoekie, Reekers, Banjoewang. n. Rott.-Landbouw, Sissingh, id. n. Amst. - Surat, Dunlop, id. n id. — 27 Mei; Maassluis, Kuchler, id. n. Rott.</p>
	<p>Bij St. HELENA,27 Mei; County of Lanark, Robertson, Javan.h. Kanaal. NEW-YORK, 12 Crest of the</p>
</text>
