<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 19 Oct., Z. W. — N. W.; Maria Veronica, Schol, Batavia vertr. 13 Junij. - Hermanus Izaak, v. d. Veen, Curacao. - Anna Lena, Visser, Suriname. - John Perk, Mc&apos; Donald, Acujutla, 1. v. Queenstown. - Bérénice, S., Middell. Zee. - Varde, Eskesen, Petersburg. - Tjadda Gesin_» Staal, Riga. - Petrus, Johnsen, Drammen. — 20 Oct.; Harraton, S., Snnderland.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 18 Oct., Z.Z.O.—Z.; Wendelina, Hilbrands, Sundswall, me. schade, wegens aanzeiling. - Triton, Burghout, Riga. — 19 Oct.; Pet-* &amp; Jens, Memertz, Petersb. - Johanna Hermina, Hoeksma, id. - Frouwina Duit, Nerva. - Wodan, Meinders, Riga. - Jan &amp; Andreas, Doyen, Leba. ZOLTKAMP, 15 Oct.; Zwaantina,Nieboer, Petersb. —16 Oct.; Zwerver, Ates, id. - Boline, Jorgensen, id. - Ertdanus, Loop, Eckernfiorde. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 20 Oct.,W. Z. W. — Z. W.; Cortgene, Wemm* rus Pzn., Banjoew. 1. v. Brouwershaven. - 3 Sisters, Priest, Berdianski, {• v. id. - Catharina Eugenia, Fire, id. 1. v. id. - Island Queen, Pepperell- Zante. - Qneen S., Dundee. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Ane. Winther, Peters» burg. - Christine, Pedersen, id. - Hermann, Niebuhr, Riga. - Paul Martf Schultz, Wismar. &lt; BRIELLE, 19 Oct., Z. W.; Colletis, S., Gook; 20 dito weder derwaart* teruggekeerd. —20 Oct.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterlo&quot;&apos; S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. LONDEN, 18 Oct.; Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Leeuwarden. Bij NOORD-VOORLAND, 18 Oct.; Eva Johanna, Hordijk, Rott. n. Ba* Bij WIGHT, 180ct.;Macassar, Coulon, Amst. n.Macassar. PORTLAND, 18 Oct.; Jacob, Mulder Drenth, Rott. n. Singapore. MONTROSE, 17 Oct.; Pelikaan, de Jonge, Nerva. SEAHAM, 17 Oct; Falcon, Hamby, Dordt. GRANGEMOUTH, 16 Oct; Latona, Lyllop, Zwolle. BONESS, 16 Oct.; Broeders, de Boer, Gothenburg. CARDIFF, 18 Oct; Hertha, Dordt. - Rosa, Isete, Amst. . DUNDEE, 17 Oct; Eleanor Doleson, Taylor, Vlissingen. -AphroW Roostee, Petersb.</p>
	<p>WEST HARTLEPOOL, 17 Oct.; Gezina, Deen, Londen. BERWICK, 17 Oct.; Francois, Hart, Dordt. HULL, 18 Oct.; Titia Jacobma, Klein, Brugge. ? SUNDERLAND, 17 Oct.; Hendrika, Plukker, Soderham. - 18 0«f&quot; Blackness, Hughes, Nieuwediep. »«,,._ v\c SHIELDS, 16 Oct.; John&amp;Alice Brown, Wells, Dordt. - Raven, ï w ming, id. —17 Oct.; Cornelia, Hengelaar, Middelb. —18 Oct.; Mary An» Cowky, Dordt. - Graces, Carr, id.-Margaret, Emmerson, id.-Ailcgf0; Boeket, id.-Paul #• Frederick, Kreplins, id. - Vernon, La wiek, id---I8&apos; braon, Martini, id. - Courier, Hansen, Rott. - Messenger, Balls, id. - 3oW fy Ann, Truemann, id. - Venture, Stephens, id. - Eleanor, Harrison, _«• Alblasserwaard, Jacobs, id. - Expert, Usher, id. - Jonge Albert, Kw»™ Koningsb. - Anna Wilhelmina, Janssen, Slito.-Zephyrus, Elliot, Nieuw&quot;; diep. - Wm. &amp; Sarah, Rollason, id. - Ligure, Simonette, Schiedam- Rosina, Gambardella, id. - Condor, Johnson, Nieuwediep. - Twee Gebro ders, Persoon, Middelburg. LEITH, 18 Oct.; Stratisla, Roy, Rott. DARDANELLEN, 3 Oct.; Ledaal, ..., Sulina n. Rott. FORTRESS MONROE, 3 Oct.; Nancy, Rott.</p>
	<p>QUEBEC, 15 Oct; Elisabeth, Stabell, Rott RIO-JANEIRO. 19 Sent.: de Waarden, Asttien, Londen.</p>
</text>
