<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Scheepstijdingen. BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>■Rfoss, ld. ; Seinrick von Tliaiö, Meijer, Dantzig. - 23 Mei&apos;; Mary &amp; Ap£ Whitiig,Newc.-Granville,Robi__son,id.-Jansjen,Meijer,KoningsD«&gt;B Nyssiena, Prak, Frcderikstad. BRIELLE, 23 Mei; Albert, S.,Hnll. ..«mm.» BROUWERSHAVEN, 23 Mei; Constantia, Orergtanw, Bar] w n. Rctt,, vertr. 29 Jan. . w;iieoi 1, HAMBURG, 20 Mei: Anna, Reinders, Terranova. — 21 Mei; VY&quot;1 S., Amst. - Jonge Barend, Prins, Termunterzijl. vifler, HARBURG, 9/17 Mei; Neptunus, Scholtens, Malaga. - Tietje, Delfzijl.  florf* BREMERH AVEN, 22 Mei; Catharina, Martcns, Freder.k»haw. -&quot;&quot; Verwachting. Mulder, Hamburg. ELSFLETH, 22 Mei; Maria Edina, Stamhuis, Stadland. EMDEN, 18 Mei; Hermina Johanna, Drijfhout, Amst. DANTZIG, 19 Mei; Janneke Hendrika, Stoorvogel, Dordrecht. .p BOLDERA, 13 Mei; Gesina Alida, Botje, Hamburg. - Drie Znsten- stra, Bergen. — 14 Mei; Salamander, Jacobsen, Harlingen. — lai M*&apos;&apos;g^jdrik Jan Nassau, Roelf&apos;sema, Antw. - Grietje, Nieboer, Edam. -IStaa __ wijk, Wijma, Harlingen. - Cornelia Catharina, Hagedoorn, Middies» 17 Mei; Prudence, Buining, Newc. - Cornelia, Oltmans, Amst. - Pie^ &apos; tervink, Edam. - Twee Zusters, Groenewold, Gent. tt«ibM* WINDAU, 13 Mei; Belina, Pot, Malmoe. — 16 Mei; Wilham, txei&quot; Amst. - Loreley, Schlossmann, id. rti-nisx^ KROONSTAD, 17 Mei; ter reede: Piet Hein, Meijer, Amst. - xxx,»~ Margaretha, Freye, id. - Tjapko Schuringa, Drent, id. HELSINGBORG, 6 Mei; Herraanus Gerardus, Beumé, Newc. LANDSCRONA, 13 Mei; Vollenhoven, Koning, Newc. pc(- Bü KOPENHAGEN, 1 9 Mei; Zaanstroom, Visser, Komngsb. na»* gen. — 20 Mei; Margaretha, Brambergen, Cadix n. Petersburg. .^ ELSENEUR, 18 Mei; gepasseerd: Hoffnung, Sönne, Amst. n. w rj. Maria, Berg, Purmerend n. Sundwall. - Aukje, Teensma, Newc. n. *■ burg. - Aurora, Sörensen, Nieuwe Diep n. Sundswall. Q^f LONDEN, 22 Mei; Hendrika Alida, Keppel, Malmoe. - In lading • truida, Rasker, Amst. - Reina, de Wal, Oldenburg. o-niW* Bij PLYMOUTH, 18 Mei; Havana Packet, Harken, Havana n. «£ .^ Bij SCILLY, 18 Mei; Hendrika, Oudshoorn de Groot Stiflry, x* i n. Amst. „ ... Amst.n11*&apos; Bg het NOORD-VOORLAND, 20 Mei; Agatha, Zeihnga, Am» Cura9ao. - Cornelia Maria, de Joode, Hamburg n. Rio Grande. v $$$■: Bij FOLKESTONE, 21 Mei; Brouwershaven,Huizcr, Amst. n. r Onrust, Weisenbruck, Rott. n. Bat. «.,._. -o * .JÏ»^ Bij DUNGENESS, 17 Mei; Elisabeth, Storm, Shields naar tfat. Hendrika, van Watturn, Bremen naar Napels. — 20 Mei; Ooimer, v Vlaardingen n. Gibraltar. - Westerkwartier, Dijk, Malaga n. Haroo&quot;_ e p- Bij BEVEZIER, 20 Mei; Anna, Bok, Amst. naar Singapore. - o ken, Shields n. Bat. _ . _ .. _ Je*I&quot;*&apos;1&quot;*&apos; HARWICH, 21 Mei; Bonchina, Koster, Dantzig. - Engelina, Nyekibbing. ... .„u n b&apos;re QUEENSTOWN, 22 Mei; Orion, Huges, Platanvier (vertrok u. pool). - Anna Augusta, Kuiper, Haiti. LIVERPOOL, 20 Mei; Viscata, Evans, Rott. a&lt;J t}^&lt; SHIELDS, 21 Mei; Catharina, Duintjer, Boston. - Margaretha. p_i Huil. - Ncedfull. Thomas, Rott. - Jane, Rolsson, Nieuwediep. - re* nie, le Sevin, Schiedam. ,••__.« Cfi^ SUNDERLAND, 19 Mei; Armido, Common, Rett. -Felicita».■ $(?■ id. - Bon Union, Layer, Schiedam. - 20 Mei; Crocus, Philip, Ni°»pr HARTLEPüOL, 19 Mei; Louise Auguste, Sörensen, bclneu» ven, Petersen, id. BORDEAUX, 20 Mei; Iris, Roncour, Llanelly. TRIEST, 19 Mei; Esperance, Hazewinkel, Neweastle. &apos; VENETIË, 18 Mei; Catharina Maria, Mooi, Antwerpen. LISSABON, 14 Mei; Maria Hinrichs, Hes, Hambnrg. „,irik**i_ FERNAMBUCK, 26 April; Deni, Kuiper, Montevideo. - ticnK .^ ser, Gibraltar. — 27 April; Fennegina, Koetze, Triest. — 29 Apnl, Altman, Valparaiso. MATtANHAM. Helios. Wintert Triest.</p>
	<p>TEXEL, 23 Mei; Ondine, S., Bordeaux. - Tra Vermer, Melsow, Porsgrund. - Leonore, Willems, Koningsb. - Cito, Myhre, Drammen. VLIE, 22 Mei; Nora, S., Londen. - Anna Augusta, Kuiper, Windau. - Remelia Geertruida, Katoen, Christiania. - Niord, Andersen, Drobach. - Amsterdam, S., Hamburg HELLEVOETSLUIS, 22 Mei; Redwing, Sterry,Newcastle..-Wanderer,</p>
</text>
