<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>üitviicrhjric »l«nuö. Tan 16 tot en met 22 Februarij 1865. BEVALLEN: E. Giezeu, geb. Versiraaien, Z. —J. Wilhelmy Damste&apos;.geb. van &apos;iHoofl. Z. — A. A. J. Coeberah, geb van Bree, Z. —J. C. Jongbloed, geb. Wiekarl. D. — J. Schroef, geb. Molenaar. Z. — J. C. Vinkestein, geb.Carton Z. — C. U. J.Tiemeijer.geb de kraafl, D —P. A. Janssen, geb. Diepenbach.Z. - S. M. Huner.aeb van Steenbergen, Z — W. de Wringer, geb. Militie, Z. — A. E. Vermeulen, geb. Rikken, I). — C. A. Chrisliaanse, geb. Groen, Z. — H. J. Ooyman.geb. Evens, Z — S. M. Lohman.geb. Hlansjaar, D. — 11. Deldik. geb. Hoorn D — M Kramer,geb. Rene&apos;, Z. — C. Posi.geb. Snyders, Z. — G. Mariin, geb. de Jager, D. — G van Duiiren, geb Schregel, D — M. Duyverman, geb. Bolslier, Z. — C. M. van deu Berg, geb van der Waals, D. — M A. Keyzer, geb. Wouters, D. — E. de Vroede . geb de Bruin, D. — G. de Vroede, geb. Castricum, D. — M J. Evers. geb. Engels, Z. — C. J. F. van lierkei, geh. Hannaarl, Z.&apos;—&apos;J.C. Kroonbergs, geb. Opgeenend, Z. — C. M de Haas, geb. Japikse, D. — A. M. C. Sdier, geb van Troisenburg, D — G. M. Vlek, geb. van Gelder. D. — A. C. S. Beens, geb.Soeiers. I). — F. J. Moene, geb. Dee. D. — H. G. Bender, geb. Verboog. Z. — H. A. Weyer, geb. de Meyer, D. — W. M. van Ilerson, geb Blom, Z. — E. C. Duyverman,geb. Philippo; D. — W Gordijn, geb. de Koer, D. GEHUWD: l. A. Simonis, jm. en VV. Vrymoet, jd. —P. Sandvliet, wedr. en A. E. van Rulle, jd. —A. Mombers wedr en H G Zwanenburg,jd. —D. de Vink, jm.en M Viele, jd. — D. de Gunst. jm. en P Moene. jd. — G. Over■duin, jm. en J. Moene. jd. — A. van Egmond . jm.+n C M. Lindenhof, jd.— N. Schots, wed&apos; en G. Bredeveld, jd. — T. A. Mussen .jm. en J J. Meijer, jd. OVERLEDEN: P. A. C. van den Berg , Z., bijna 3j. - F van der Laaken, Z., ruim 6m. —J. van den Heuvel, D ,9 m. —M. Vylbrief, D . 6w.— A. Bredjjk, geb. Plomp 53 j —N. Roozendaal, Z-. 3w. — A. P. A M. «an den Berg, Z, 17 d — II H. Fles, Z , bijna sm. — C. Botirsse Wils, Z.. 4j en 11 m.— W. F. Kienjei, Z.,4j en 10 m. — Joh» van der Ven , 47 j — J. Blommesieyn. Z., ruim Bm. — Catha Pardon , 50 j. —A. de Hen , Z.. Bm. — W. van Leeuwen , Z., 4 j. en 4m. — C. E. Thomese, I). ,2 in. — C. A. T. Bonnet, geb. van Ewyk. 69 j. — A. M. Karreman, D., 2 j.en 6m. — M. Uilenhosch, geb Wevers, 72 j. —G. «an Hest, 67 j. —J. J. Zitman, Z. ,3j en 2 in — 11. J Roos, Z.,7 m. - P. J. Hariwyk, Z.,Bm. — A. Scheen. 32 j — F M. van Deventer, D., sj.rn3m. — G. W. van Nicuwkerk , Z., Ij. en ruim 6m.—A. J. F. Hartman, 54 j.— D. Pander, Z.,Bm. —A. Steenwijk, Z., ruim Ij. —A. de Lang, -</p>
</text>
