<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 16 Sept.; Cornelia Hendrika, van Straten, Banjoewangie; vertr. 2 Mei. - Catharina Maria, Mooi, Venetië. - Index, Long, Caen. - Hillcchiena Catharina, Hesseling, Riga, - Urania, S., Dantzig. - Constantia, Andersen, Frederikstad.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 15 Sept.; Harmonie, Haverschmidt, Memel. - Mathilda Geertruida, Wiebes, Koningsb. - Jantje, Niewold, Frederikstad. - Willem, de Boer, id. - Egberdina Anna, Schuring, id. -Willem I, S., Hamburg. —16 Sept.; Wnbke Veldman, Kraai, Frederikstad.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Sept.; Louisa, Berrill, Terranova. - Parthenia, Jary, Newc. - Swallow, S., Huil. - Elisa, de Boer, Archangel. - Cbristine, Jacobsen, Uleab. - Johanna, van Wijk, Riga. - Speculation, Bjerkoe, Holmstrand. - Zeemeeuw, Swart, Bergen. - Elve, S., Hamburg. HARLINGEN, 15 Sept.; Wilhelm Carl, Gudmundsen, Christiania. — 16 Sept.; European, S., Huil; is weder derwaarts teruggekeerd. - Harmon ie, Haverschmidt,. Memel. - Jantje, Nieuwold, Christiania. - Willem, de Boer, Frederikstad. - Rapid, Larsen, id. - Egberdina Anna, Schuring, id. BREMERHAVEN, 14 Sept.; Johanna Wilhelmina, Thiernau, Baltimore. - Astrea, Dahl, Rangoon.</p>
	<p>Bij KOPENHAGEN; 13 Sept.; Alida, Veen,Sunderl.n.Riga.- Alber dina, Lodewijk, Aberdeen n. de Oostzee.</p>
	<p>KOPENHAGEN, 13 Sept.; Margaretha Antina, de Boer, Tayport. HARBURG, 12 Sept.,- Hendrika, Bakker, Leeuwarden. CUXHAVEN, 14 Sept.; Jacob en Titia, Prak, Ponce, —15 Sept.; Hammonia, S., Rott. - Stoomvaart, S., Amst.</p>
	<p>FLENSBURG, 12 Sept.; Helena, Albers, Amst&apos;. WISMAR, 13 Sept.; Gesina, Krook, Harlingen. WARNEMUNDE, 13 Sept.; Fronkje, Faber, Dockum. - Drie Gebroeders, Leffers. Franeker.</p>
	<p>SWINEJMUNDE, 14 Sept.; Jantina Margaretha, Pieper, Middlesbro. NORRKOPING, 9 Sept.; Alexandra, Wirkki, Amst ELSENEUR, 12 Sept.; Gepasseerd: Nor, Bugge, Nieuwediep n. Soderhamn. —13 Sept.; Mercurius, Meijer, Grinsby n. de Oostzee. RENDSBURG, 12 Sept ; Gepasseerd: Agatha Jacobina, Kramer, Bandholm n. Amst.-Anna Thedoro, Kuipers, Memeln.de Weser. — 13 Sept.; Hoogezand, van Driesten, Hamburg n. Nerva. - Harmina, Emmelkamp, Sunderland n. Apenrade. - Gebroeders, de Groot, Amst. n. Lubeck. - Catharina Cornelia, de Jonge, Stokholm n. Rott. LONDEN, 14 Sept.; Elisabeth Maria, Smoor, St.Vincent.- Jacobus Begeman, Reijer, Gron. - Jantje Martens, Ates, Rostock. YARMOUTH, 14 Sept.; Fox, Holt, Rott. SHIELDS, 13 Sept.; India, Vonk, Rott. - Alegonda Magrietha, Gort, Dordrecht. - Margaretha, Wilmink, Gron. CARDIFF, 16 Sept.; Minister Pahud, Lipjes, Vlissingen. FOWEY, 14 Sopt.; Kate en Arme, Hoeken, Amst. n. Napels. Bij FALMOUTH, 13 Sept.; Nagasaki, Mos, Bat. n. Rott. TORBAY, 13 Sept.; Alf&apos;red Vittery, Smith, Amst. n. Bristol. Bij DUNGENESS, 13 Sept.; Wilhelmina Catharina, Kiel, .... naar L ivorno. Bij het ZUID-VOORLAND, 14 Sept.; Masonic, Lamphen, Rangoonn. Schiedam. DOVER, 14 Sept.; Lubbegiena, de Jonge, Gron. PORTO, 3 Sept.; Jantina Christina, Bekkering, Sunderland. ¦ CAD. X, 8 Sept.. Meta Elisabeih, Zuhlke, Dantzig. MESSIJ. A, 7 Sept.; Irene, S., Napels. TRIEST, 11 Sept.; Veendam, Hazewinkel, Ancona. NEW-YORK, 31 Aug.; Antonetta, Gnodde, Buenos-Ayres.-Vesta, Dirks Rio Janeiro. - Atalante, Hageman, Bremen. BALTIMORE, 30 Aug.; Argus, Tuk, Havana. - Ceres, Boog, id. HONGKONG, 23 Julij; Jacob fr Anna, Bonger, Chewfoo. SWATOW, voor 6 Julij; Johannes Martinus, Dalloyaux, Hongkong, RIOUW, 6 Julij; de Hoop, van Duyn, Samarang. TRINID AD DE CUBA, 15 Aug.; Argo, Nienaber, Bremen. BATAVIA, 31 Julij; India Packet, Diepering, Amst. KANAGAWA, 6 Julij; Libra, Dirksen, Amst. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 16 Sept.; Nina, S., Bordeaux. - Visseherij, Fortuin, Londen. - Three Sisters, Jefferson, Newc - Zephyrus, Ellior, Sunderl. - Scotia, Lorenoen, Drammen. VLIE, 15 Sept.; Annegiena, Blouw, Arendahl. — lë Sept.; Vriendschap, Lodewijks, Stockholm. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Sept.; Zephyr, S., Londen. - Osprey, S,Liverpool. - Louise, S., Grangemouth. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Gitana, S., Hartlepoól. - Spruijt, Pott, Avontuur. BRIELLE, 16 Sept.; de Maas, S., Londen. - Leo, S., id. - Elizabeth, Yallop, Newc. - Zealous, S., Harwich. HARLINGEN, 16 Sept.; Lion, S., Londen. - Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. - Killarney, S., Goole. FEDDERWARDERSIEL.ISSept.; Geertruida, de Mooi, Amst. - Els.na, de Vries, Burhaversiel. HAMBURG, 14 Sept.; Otto, Sap, Riga. FLENSBURG, 11 Sept.; Twee Gezusters, van der Werp, Kopenhagen, i SWINEMUNDE, 13 Sept.; Zeus, v.a der Tas, Nyearleby. - Hendrika : Margarietha, Steel, Delfzijl.</p>
	<p>RU G-El. WALDE.. 8 S.«st,; Anna Öi-tharisk -feriag. J_ppatbgaè. DANTZIG, 13 Sept.: Anna Elisabeth, Dijk, Koningsbergen n. Amct. MEMEL; 10 Sept.; Vrouw Grietje, Schoon, Bremen. - Schwalbe, Janssen, de Maas. SHIELDS, 14 Sept.; Liduina, van Brink, Kaap de Goede Hoop. HARTLEPOÓL. 14 Sept.; Trijntje, Visser, Koningsb. LIVERPOOL, 13 Sept.; Braganza,, Shelston, Bat. MILFORD, 14 Sept.; Engelina, E vans, Rott. PORTSMOUTH, 14 Sept.; Delfthaven, Freese, Callao n. Hamburg. St. VALERY, 14 Sept.; Union, Hazewinkel, Amst. MESSINA, 6 Sept; zeilkl.: Princess Alexandra,Bovcy, Rott. NEW-YORK, 1 Sept.; zeilkl.: Anna, Laarmann, Rott. &quot; HONGKONG, 27 Julij; Alexander, Dekker, Singapore. - Jan v. Galen, Bra-t, Shanghac.</p>
</text>
