<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>: TEXEL, 13 Jnnij; Thusnelda, Heineken, Batavia, 1. v. St. Thoinj^- Advance, Taylor, id.; vertr. 20 Jan.- Schnelpost,Deige, Nantes. -J» Stoff, Newc. - Morningstar, House, id. - Oscar, Barness, Sunderl. - -&amp;u pean, S., Huil. Tt -let).&apos; VLIE, 12 Junü-, Alberdina, Lever, Newc. - Neptun, de Boer, HaTïf0V Frouwiua, Duit, Windau. - Johanna, Kraeft, Riga. - Creoie, L aneu,» wegeu. j AMELAND, 10 Junij; Margaretha, Glup, Altona. |&apos; OSTMAHORN, 10 Junij; Maria, Diercks, Leer. , HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Junij; Lord Collingwood, Dodds, Rapêo^- I Argns, Tuk, Manzanilla. - Louise, Blanchard, La Roche Bernard. - »:,_. ! burg, S., Londen. - Eweretta, Watson, Newc. - Harmony, &amp;chmpn&lt;***^ • Elisabeth, Pigott, id. - Margareth, Whitefield, id. - Willismi £ Han&quot; ft Wilson.id. - Sir Henry Havelock, Mate.id. - Thetis, March, id. -£ j,. Emery, id. - de Burger, Bartelse, id. - 1 _iends, Wells, id. - Theodor, -»¦ bens, Riga. - Gesina, Stenger, Libau. -ntf&apos; HAMBURG, 11 Junij: Twee Zusters, Dijkstra, Nantes. - Antin».^ tels, Makkuin. - Zwei G&apos;ebrüder, Hicken, id. - Petroneila, Wirtjes, i Cabello. - Hillechina, Gruppelaar, Bordeaux. ALTONA, !2 Junij; Barbara Jonker, Oltmans, Londen. , „. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 10 Junij; Rotterdam. S, Stettin n. Rotterdam*, TRAVEMUN DE. 10 Junij; Jonge Jan $¦ Margaretha, Jelies, Sund&quot;-» . WARNEMUNDE.7 Junij; Neptunus} van Gorknm, Rendsburg. j MEMEL, 9 Junij; Scotia, Lorentzen, Nieuwe Diep. . „„pAii &apos; BOLDERA, 6 Junij-, Dolphijn, Hazewinkel, Hamburg. - Maria ü^ Tap, Delfzijl. - 9 Junij; O&apos;dambt, Schotema, Hamburg. at_tt. : ELSE&apos;NIiUR, 8 Junij; gepasseerd : Mettina Jacobina, Dijken,&amp;¦ n. Termunterzijl. - Johanna Catharina, van Veen, Delfzijl&apos;./[&apos;&quot;&apos;pii&apos;, 9 Junij; B. D.Metcalf,Andersen,Rott.n.Gcfle.-MngriethaAlW&apos;T&apos; „ij; Gron. n.Riga. - Beerta Hendrika,Stuit,Aritw.n.Dantzig._-.».* jj.&quot; Zeehond, I-ènenga, Amst, n.Petersburg.-Lambertha,Karst,ia, oV Broedertrouw, de Groot, Antwerpen n. id. - Engelina Petroneii&apos;, wer, Rott. n. de Oostzee. - Christina, Staal, Harlingen n. ia. TjOö&apos; RENDSBURG, 8 Junij: gepasseerd: Gesina, Krook, Boston - den. - Geerdina Geertruida, Kramer, Amst. n. Odense. /.„.-«li», &amp; LONDEN, 12 Junij; Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, Worcum. - W Jong, Worcum. - Christina, Vos, Dantzig. -im-dii.eIJ | Bij DUNGENESS, 9 Junij; Maria Johanna, van Gelderen, V laa» n. Malta. _ ,_. „ fiatfiï- Bij FOLKESTONE, 10 Junij-, Snperb.van Appen, Soerabaya n.r Bij DEAL, 12 Junij; Lord Collingwood Bangoon n. Kou. Bij DOVER, 11 Junij; Constantia, Brinkerink, Amst. n. Soera-w Bij FALMOUTH, 9 Junij; Jacomina, Kuiper, Liverpool n. *»» _ F ALMOÜT _, 11 Junij; Consul Voel kei, Postuum» •_ _? Mf &gt;_™£ Sffi&apos; YARMOÜTH, 11 Junij; Burgemeester van betten, «oiv* nemunde. f __ ? GUERNSEY, 9 Junij; Aurora, Pakey, Rott. [ HÜLL,llJueij;Ocean,Elliott,Rott.</p>
	<p>HOLYHEAD, Il Jung; Johanna Hermina, Hoeksema, Liverpool n. _^tfIEf,DS&apos; n Juu&apos;J-&apos; Domina Geertina, Wolters, Londen. - Celeritas, jan ver Leest, Huil. - Brotherly Love, Maff.t, Nienwe Diep. - Anna doelman, Duinkerken. SUNDERLAND, 11 Junij; Echo, Robinson, Rott. - Loyal Standard, ¦Jrlong, Amst. . &apos; STOCKTON, 11 Junij; Jantina Alida, Texer, Dantz. W«,ENOCK, 9 Junij; Jacobus, Linker, Fernambuck. LIVERPOOL, 11 Jvmj;Louise Geerdina, Wever, Gioja. Ij&lt;UTH, 11 Junij; Jantina Roelfina, Broekema, Dantz. LYNN, 9 Junij; Reina, Munneke. Stettin. |VVANSEA, 11 Junij; Iris, Roucour, Nantes. vot. ÜBES, 31 Mei; Bernard, Kuper, Lissabon (vertrok 5-Jnniinaar ïlaardingen). St. THOMAS, 18 Mei; Willem van der Voort, Carst, Clyde. AUX CAYES, 6 Mei; Jonge Eduard, Sikkens, Suriname. LAGUAYRA, 17 Mei; Jan Frederik, Klazen, Suriname.</p>
</text>
