<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>VLIE, 23 Nov., Z.W.; Trouhabour, S., Londen. ZOLTKAMP, 21 Nov.; Tjakiena, van Slnis,Riga. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 Nov., Z.W.; Robertns Hendrikus, Mulder, Bat. 1. v. Brouwersh. - J. Cushing, Snap, Bassein, 1. v. id. - Charlie Palmer, Hoffman, id. I. v. id. - Koophandel en Zeevaart, v. d. Kuijl, Bilbao. - Industrie, Puister, Nantes. - Aukje Gepkelina, de Vries, id. - Johanna Petronella, Hillebrand, id. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Eive, S., Hamburg.—Gisteren nog: Louise Marie, Nissen, Marans.</p>
	<p>BROUWERSHAVEN, 24 Nov., Z.W.; Regina, Harvey, Rotterdam n. Boston A.</p>
	<p>DEAL, 21 Nov.; ten anker: Fagel, Smith, Amst. n. Bat DARTMOUTH,22Nov.; Ada Letitia, Rees, Rott. n.Swansea. MILFORD, 22 Nov.; Seiina, ...., Liverp. n. Amst. ABERDEEN, 21 Nov.; Earl Mnlgrave, Hoskins, Rott. FALMO UTH, 22 Nov.; Johanii, Berlin, Bat. n. Amst.</p>
	<p>SWANSEA.2I Nov.; Caroline Heyman, Roltrus, Amst. SCARBOROUGH, 20 Nov.; Idas, Appleyai _, Rott. WARKWORTH.2I Nov.; Perly, Hart, Rott. SEAHAM, 20 Nov.; Breuda, Crosier, Rotterd. - Auspicious, Brown, id. - Juan, Saloman, id.</p>
	<p>BLYTH, 21 Nov.; Celeste Her.ry, Palfresne, Schiedam. ROOHESTER, 22 Nov.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rott. IPSWICH, 21 Nov.; Miss Evans, Davis,Rott. HARWICH, 21 Nov.; Linda Flor, Brown, Rouaan n. Schied. Bij HARWICH, 21 Nov.; Miss Evans, Davis, Rott. n. Ipswich. - John &amp; William, Frost, v. id. n. id.</p>
	<p>BERWICK, 22 _ov.; St. Abbs, Lawson, Rott. SUNDERLAND, 20 Nov.; Swan, Dawson, Nieuwe Diep. — 21 Nov.; Success, Mason, Rott. - Esther, Greenfield, id. - Ethelming, King, id. - Jean, Smith, Schiedam. - Minerva, Gray, id. - Albatross, Brooks, Dordt - Eleanor, Mennell, Nieuwe Diep. - Irt, Eackley, id. - Cornhill, Chappel, Amst. — 22 Nov.; Godelevus Bernar&apos;dus, Timmer, Dordt. SHIELDS, 21 Nov.; J. Meizers, Bnrgess, Schiedam. - Harvest, Walker, id. - Redwing, Claxton, id. - Bengalen, de Goede, Dordrecht. - Whampoa, San „berg, id. - Columbia, Evans, id. - Harald Hildetand, Wikblad, id. - Verwisseling, Dood, id. - Adriana Wilhelmina, v. Eyk, Middelburg. - Fortuna, de Groot, Delfzijl. - Eleanor, flarnson, Vlissingen. - Mars, Patton, Rott. - Nympli, Storm, id. -. Arab, Oxfield, id. - Ex. ei „, TJsher, id. - Forest Flower, Raymer, id. - Frijn, Schmidt, id. - Th. Chalmers, Lewis, id. — 22 Nov.; Persevcrance, Walker, id. - Wellington, Harrison, id. - Jonian, Dew. id. - Planet, Carapbcll, Middelb. - John and Isabella, Younger, Nieuwediep. - Golconda, Allen, Koogerpolder. - Helena, Lange, Dordrecht, - Waterloo, Wordingham, ld. - Friendship, Roberts, id. - Dunnator Castle,, Vallock, id. - Marohant, Beavis, Schiedam. - Adriana Francisca v. Eyk, Vlissingen. - Paragon. Frankland, Zierikzee. MAESEILLE,22 Nov.; Helena, Pybes, Barcelona.</p>
</text>
