<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 11 Oct.;Nina,Earl,Newc.-Europeau,S., Huil. VLJE, 10 Oct.; Lion, S., Lou.en. - Annechiena, Bette, Riga. — 11 0.t.; Stoomvaart, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 11 Oct; Jnlie, Cherpion, Padang 1. v. Brouwershaven; verir. 29 Mei. - Altona, Thavscn, Singapore. -Meteor.S., Londen. - Aurora, 8., id. -I.inghom,S .Leitli.-Lordß.iglan, S., Neu- Castlc. - Bradford, S. Grimsby. - Johanna Margaretha, E). Riga. - Rotterdam, S., Stettin. - Vlaardingeu, Boog, Bergen. - Zwerver, Hoste., id. - Soeblomstcn, Holm. id. - Tiietis, de Zeeuw Bagges, Trenisö. BROUWERSHAVEN, 11 Oct,; Otto, Stehuun Tresliug, Bat. n. Rott., vertr. 20 Junij. - Anna, Hoekstra, Londen n, id. BREMEKHAVEN, 10 Oct.; Maria Geeitruida, Mooije, N.r Jen. STETTIN, 8 Oct.; Roeltina, Prins, Bremeu. DANTZIG, 8 Oct.; Vlinder, de Jonge, Grangemouth. - Maria, Pot, Newe, - Jonge Andries, Stellens, id. SWINEUUNI)E,BOct; Jantina, Blaak, Bergen. BOLDERA, 3 Oct.; Anna, de Weerd, Schiedam. 101S0ER, 28 Sept.; Catharina Luitgardina, Bos, Delfzijl. KLEVEN, 16 Sept.; Margaretha Antina, Speelmin, Stettin n. Rott, — 18 Sept.; Jacobus Anthonie, Mellcma, Riga n. Amst. — &quot;-0 Sept.; Houtvaart, Visser, Sundwall n. Nieuwe Diep. - Concordia, Orts, Stettiu n. Fisherow. — 21 Sept.; Johanna, Gort, Riga u. Amst. UDOFJORD, 21 Sept.; Harmonie, Havcrschmidt, Riga n. Harlbigen. STAVANGER, 16 Sept.; Venator,Reiersen, Amst. — 20Sept.; Cuit Adler, Asbibrnsen, Zwolle. IMfl JU IT BERGEN, 17 Sept.; Zwaantina Thelina, de Boer Sip, Antwerpen.— 20 Sept.; Jan enAudreas, Doyen, Newc. — 23Sept.;Merwestroom, de Goede, Dordt. DRAMMEN, 20/22 Sept,; Dan, Waerner, Amst. AKEN DAL, 25 Sent.; Helios, Sievcrtsen, Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 7 Oet.; Anna Margaretha, Iloeksma, Amst. n. do Oostzee. - Alida Hendrika, Nieuweuliuis, Londen n.id.-Cornelia Wilhelmina, Iloeksma, Amst. n. Petersb. - Fenna, Coerkamp, id. n. id. - Kersteling, Wiersma, Londen n. de Oostzee. - Twee Gezusters, Grcencwoldt, Harlingen n. id. LONDEN, 9 Oct.; Lucia Jantina, Lieffijn, Arehangel. Bij DOVER, 9 Oct.; Europa, Lupcke, Bat. n. Rott. - Success, Douwes, Bassein n. Antwerpen. Bg PORTLAND, .. Oct.; Jane Knoi, Kerr, Nantes n. Rott. Bij PENZANCB. 8 Oct.; dElmina, Demmers, Bat. n. Vlissingen. ALLOA, 6Oct,; Bruno, Visser, Leer. FOWEY, 9 Oct.; William, Johns, Runcorn n. Dordrecht. FALMOUTH, 10 Oct.-, Pieter Adolf, Jaski, Singapore. CARDIFF, 8 Oct.; Favor, Saunes, Rott. - Ida Maria de Raath, de Boer, id. - Maria, Beekman, Schiedam. ROCH ESTER, 9 Oct,; Geertruida Anna, Schrikkcma, Petersburg. SWANSEA, 9 Oct.; Zecploeg, Ludeliug, Londen. IPS WTGH, 9 Oct.; Surah King, Wadsworth, Rott. HARWIGH, 9 Oct,; Vr. Dieuwke, Feenstra, Londen n. Worcum. SHIELDS, 9 Oct,; Maria Adolfina, Meuldijk, Vlissingen. NEWCASTLE,6 Oct. In lading: Ida, Hazewinkel,Para. GREENWK, 10 Oct.; Amicitia, Arends, Cardenas. PORT MAHON, 26 Sept.; Isabella, Kuiper, Falmoulh. VIGO, 1 Oct.; Margaretha Hendrika, Datema, Sunderbnd. BANANA, 15Aug.; President Lincoln, Bakker, Rott, (alles wel aan boord). wm m __L _ W __ mMI</p>
</text>
