<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Sept., W.Z.W.; Louis Meijer, Holtgreve, Bat., vertr.22Moi.- Maria Catharina, Westenenk.id., vertr. 8 Mei. - Spheroid, Coleman, Trinidad, 1. v. Queonstown. - Braziiian. Jacobs, Odessa. - Vikingen, Christofi&apos;ersen, Taganrog, 1. v. Falmouth. - Olga, S., Londen. - Nautilus, Bell, Newc- Nicolaas Albert, de Jonge.Archangel. - Edin, Schmidt, id.-Kaleb,Kaizer, id. - Gustave, Niehls, id. - Fredrik Johanna, Matzen. id. - Franciska, Ehlers, Riga. - Médéa, S., Dantzig. - Welvaart, Ekamp, Fredrikshamn. - Constantia, Andersen, Frederikstad. - Elisabeth, Gjersoe, id. - Bedalia, Kjöloe, id. - J. D. Caroline, Abrahamsen, Osterris. - Amphion, Beek» Drobach.</p>
	<p>VLIE, 13 Sept., W.Z.W.; Zwerver, Höster, Petersburg. -Laramechiena, Duit Jr., id. - Anje, Munning, Frederikst. - Wubke Veldman, Kraai,id. — 14 Sept.; Johanna, Oldenburger, Memel. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 14 Sept., W.Z.W.; Admiraal Ver-Huel, S., Havre.. Ariel, Howes, Sunderland. - Hawk, Morgan, id. - Amazone, Pedersen, Archangel. -Harmonie, Bakker, Petersburg. - Benderika, Glimmen ga, iel. - Carl Milberg, Schmidt, id. - 4 Neeltjes, Koenes, Uleaborg. - Geertje Elisabeth, v. d. Borg, Pitea. - Akler, Pihl, Skeleftea.-Erlen, Savesen, Riga.- Fanny, Johs wiek, Libau. Lonise,Toegsen,Memel.-Fanny,Unger,Christiania. - Médéa, v. Teutem, Texel. BEOUWEESHAVEN, 14 Sept., W.; 2 Cornelissen, Kreije, Tjilatjap n. Rotterdam. LONDEN, 12 Sept.; Jeltina, Korter, Petersburg. - Anna, Weerd, id - Maria, Franke, id. — 13 Sept,; Visscherij, Fortuin, Work. - Perceve ranco, Elliot, Medemblik. ROCHESTER, 12 Sep.fc John &amp; Charles, Charlton, Rotterdam. Bij DOVER, 11 Sept.; Emma Maria, Stoof. Rio-Jan. n. Hamb. FALMOUTH, 13 Sept.; Johanna Meijer, Tholen, Uruguay. HOLYHEAD, 12 Sept.; Fagel, Smit/Liverpool n. Soerab. PETERHEAD, 11 Sept; Lalla Rookh, Bennett, Vlaardingen. ALLOA, 10 Sept.; Lina, Knudsen, Schiedam. NORD SHIELDS, 12 Sept.; Coquctdale, Wood, Amst. - Scheveningen, Annokkee, Rott. - Anna Catharina Wilhelmina, Grilk, Zwolle. - Nuovo Riformo, Molfino, Arast. - Heimdahl, Petersen, Nieuwediep.-Garland, Gibson, id. - William &amp; Sarah, Rollason, id. - Hart, Bezley, id. - Margareth Jones, Jones, id. - Fortnna, Pedersen, Schiedam. - Elvira, Robinson, Dordrecht. - Dr. Kniep, Lorentz, id.-Emily, Steinhold, id. - Ellen Bali, Schmidt. id. SUNDERLAND. 12 Sept.; Waternymph, Reynolds, Nieuwediep. HARTLEPOOL, 12 Sept.; Alona, Lindeman, Amsterdam. LYNN, 12 Sept.; Eppo Hendrik, Schut, Marseille. SOUTHAMPTON, 14 Sept.; La Plata, S., West-Indie. GIBRALTAR, 4 Sept.; Helena, Pijbes, Ibraila n. Vlissingen. PAIMBOEUF, 11 Sept.; Wilhelmina, Meijer, Dantzig. St. ÜBES, 3 Sept.; Maria, van Duyvenboden, Porto. NEWCASTLE iN.Z.W.), 26 Junij; Koerier, Carst, Sydney, 10 Julij n. Java vertrokken. ZWATOW, 20 Julij; Gijsbert Karel Graaf van Hogendorp, Fabritius Ponyan Harbour.</p>
</text>
