<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2] Mei, W.N.W.—NV; Vrouw Dieuwke, Peenstra, Londen. — 3 Mei; Swan, Davison, Sunderland. - Hei-o/Btirlinson,id. VLIE, 3 Mei, Z.Z.0.; Haabet, Lorcntzen, Holmstrand. - Willem I, S., Hamb. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Mei, 0.N.0.; Paul Johan, Koov, Banjoewangie; 1. v. Brouwershav. - Whampoa, Janses, id. 1. v. id. - Annie &apos;troop, Troop, Philad., A., 1. v. id. -Carbon, S., Newcastl. 1. v. id.—3 Mei; Swanland, S., Huil. - Columbine, S., id.- Seine, S.. Hamb. BEIELLE, 3 Mei, Compasrond; Ary Scheifer, S., Havre. - Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Avalon, St.,Harw. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Mei, O. N. O.; Eriendship, Roberts, Newc. n. Rott. - Ocean King, S., Rott. n. Wyburg; heeft de reis voortgezet. — 3 Mei; Ary Scheffer, Kunst. Rott. ELSENEUR, 29 April Oldambt, Schotema, Schiedam n. Windau. PILLAU, 29 April; Jacob Bernardus, Kuiper, Amst. — 30 April; Ida Engelsmau, Duintjer, Newc. Op cle ELVE, 2 Mei; Amsterdam, S., Amst. BREMERHAVEN , 30 April; Hendrika, Scbmidt;-Seville. - Margaretha Hendrika, Datema, Poole. — 1 Mei; Godölevis Bernardus, Kral, Cette. LONDEN, 3 Mei; Setubal, S., Amsterdam. Bij DEAL, 2 Mei; Seringapatam, Wyth, Soerabaya n. Rott. Bij LIZARD, 29 A _iï; A. E._•__&gt;. -.. _ Plas. Banjoeiv. n. Amsterdam. Bij SCILLY, 29 April; Hendrika Huisman, Huisman, Buen.» Ayres n. Antweroen. LIVERPOOL&apos;29 April; Esperance, Dik, Venetië. BRISTOL, 30 April. Geerdina, Nieboer, Groningen. Bij DUNGENESS, 30 April; Seaskimmer, Anderson, Rott. n. New-York. St. ÜBES, 17 April; Jacob den Breems, v. Gelderen, Gron. — 24 April; Merwestroom, de Goede, Palma. GENUA, 28 April; Goldhoorn, Pott, Amst. MESSINA, 21 April; Harmonie, Boer, Amst. KONSTANTINOPEL, 20 April; Sophia, v. Noord, Venetië. BUENOS-AYRES, 12 Maart; Jeannette, Duiven, Amsterd. - Zwaluw, Jaarsma, id. BATAVIA, 12 Maart; Vooruit, Groenewoudt, Amsterd. — 14 Maart; Cornelia, de Boer,&apos; Cheribon. — 16 Maart; Prancina Willemina, v. Winkel, Samarang; de 2 laatsten 19 dito n. Ned. vertr. - Jacobus, v. d. Tas, Macao. — 18 Maart; Nieuwe Waterweg 11, v. Lindern, Samarang; 22 dito n. Nederl. vertrokken — 19 Maart; Gerard Pieter Servatius, cle Joode, Passaroeang. — 21 Maart; Nestor, Brandligt, Soerabaya; de 2 laatsten 25 dito n. Ned. vertr. ilfnv _ TVlaart: Ams7AT,n TTvo,v»ov ,l_.v.i„</p>
</text>
