<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>, TEXEL, 19 Junij, Z. O.; Archimedes, S., Taganrog, 1. v. Dartmouth. - Norval, Neal, Newc. - European, S., Huil. - Alert, S., id.-Abraham, Sjellan, Frederikstad. VLIE, 18 Junij, Z.Z.0.; Zeehond, Fenengii, Pernau. - Johann Heinnch, Burghout, Frederikstad. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 19 Junij, N.N.0.; Sea Queen, S.,Taganrog.-Irontoaster, S., Middlesbro&apos;. - Gironde, S., Petersburg. - Vartry, S., Texel. BPJELLE, 19 Junij, N.0.; Cologne, S., Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 19 Junij, N. O.; Jannetje, van Striemenqq., Rott. n. Bat.</p>
	<p>LEER, 15 Junij; Geertina Kramers, Folkerts, Amst. AALBORG, 7 Junij; Annechina Henriette, v. d. Meulen, Hartlepool. SWINEMUNDE, 16 Junij; Vr. Martha, 801, Amst. DANTZIG, 14 Junij; Hermanus Gerardus, Mulder, Burnt-Eiland. — 15 Junij; Clasina, Dik, Messina. MEMEL, 14 Junij; Capella, Sörensen, Amst. - Gesina, Gortemaker, wloiicester. BOLDERA, 12 Junij; Burgermeister Bencard, Hoif, Amst. - Gesina Alida, Meijer, Rott. - de Spruyt, Pott, Schiedam. - Alberdina, Schuur, Delfzijl. KROONSTAD, 14 Junij; Zeeploeg, Luder, Malaga. - Aduard, Aldershof, Hamburg. — 15 Junij; Jonge Andries, Steffens, Amst. - Lambertha, Hitman, id. - Alida Margaretha, Eisses, id. -Zeemeeuw, Swart, Dordt. - Fax, Mulder. Cadix.-Martha, Pestema,Bordeaux.-Elisabeth,Wiersma,id. NERVA, 11 Junij; Noordster, Schaap, Bergen. - Remilia Geertruida, de Boer, id. - Vlinder, de Jong, Grimsby. — 12 Junij; Stad Steenwijk, Wijma, Amst. - Alida Hendrika, Nieuwenhuis, Grimsby. - Mercunus, de «root, Amst. — 13Jun\j; Goldiiorn, Pott, Liverpool. - Rebecca, Dahm, Nieuwediep. - Drie Gebroeders, Jansen, Kampen. - Martha Theresia, Visser, Dordt. WIJBURG, 3 jHnij; Laura, Johnsen, Nievwe Diep. — 4 Junij; Andreas &amp; Maria, Slik, Dokkum. &quot; &gt; • STOKHOLM, 11 Junij; Vooruit, Hilbrands, Amst. — 12 Junij; Ah&apos;na, Koops, id. — 13 Junij; Eendragt, de Boer, id. SANDHAMN, 15 Junij; Fidelio, Werner, Amst. NORKKOPING, 85 Junij; St. Petersburg, Hoven, Amst. n BERGEN, 3 Junij; Anna, S., Rott. — 7 Junij-, Merwestroom, de Goede, ■Dordrecht Bij KOPENHAGEN, 17 Junij; Helena Gesina, Schreuder,Riga n.Gent. beertje, HoveUng, Stettin n. Newc. LONDEN, 18 Junij; Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, Worcum. Bij GOUDSTAART, 16 Junij; Reina, de Jonge, Amst. n. Messina. FOWEY, 17 Junij; Capella, Bute, Rett. n. Barrow. BRIDLINGTON, 17 Junij; in de baai voor anker: Sir Henry Havelock, toate, Schiedam n. Shields, Tamarac, Foster, Dordt n. id. HULL, 17 Junij; Gesina, Roskamp, Leuven. . SUNDERLAND, 17 Thornley, Meldrum, Nienwdiep. - Eothen, Steel, id. - Lumley, Edwards, id. SHIELDS, 17 Junij; ViÜe de Bordeaux, S., Rott. , LEITH, 17 Junij; Ünion.Flick; Dordrecht. GIBRALTAR, 11 Junij; Hillechina Scholtens, Scholtens, Bnstol. PALERMO, 8 Junij: Orion, S., Amst. NEW-YORK, 5 Junij; Neptune, Hirdes, Rott, to CHINCHAS, 11 Mei;mladiiTg: Netti Merriman.Rollins, Rottodam.- Bethiah Thayr, Cartney, id.</p>
</text>
