<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 18 Dec.W.-N.N.W.; Fredrik Wilhelm, Juni, Alicante - Lion B., Londen. -Wietska, Stieltjes, Inverkeithing. - Jan &amp; Jacob, Burghardt&apos; Gothenburg n. Porto-Torre.als bijlegger, lek, na op Long Sand gestooten&apos; &apos;e hebben. litLUSliif VLIE.I7 Dcc:, W.;-Urania, S^-Koningsbergen. - Louise Charlotte, S«hultz, Schiedam n. Engeland, als bijlegger.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 18Dec, Z.W.; StefanoCavacevich, Stack, Genetschek 1. v. Brouwershaven. - Chieftain, Jacobsen, Triest, l.v.id.- Céleste Marie, Leveux, Eédon. - Advance, Blanpied, Caen. - Albert, S, HulL</p>
	<p>BRIELLE, 18 Dcc, W.-Z.; Leo, S., Londen. - Ravensbury, S., Harwicb. LEER, 15 Dcc; Immanuel, v. d. Molen, Groningen. - Industrie, Tammen, id. LONDEN, 16 Dcc; Meika Jacoba, Wielema, Gothenburg. Bij ZUID-VOORLAND, 17 Dcc; Mathilde, Rötgers, Callao n. Rott. Bd PORTLAND, 16 Dcc; Pres. Liacoln, Bakker, Rotterd. n. Banana. - Nicolaas Frans, Dik, id. n. Montevideo. - Elizabeth, Kruize, Harlingen n PORTSMOUTH, 16 Dcc; Maria Beerta, Roosjes, Groningen. Bij PORTSMOUTH, 16 Dcc; Jeannette, Duiven, Amst. n. Buenos- Ayres. MOTHERBANK, 15 Dcc; Otto, Sap, Schiedam. PLYMOUTH, 16 Dcc; Elisabeth en Jacoba, Zwaneveld, Amst. n. Bat. FALMOUTH, 15 Dcc; Maria Coralie, Bakker, Dordt n. Savona. Bij FALMOUTH, 16 Dcc; Anna, Bok, Shields n. Bat. CARDIFF, 14 Dcc; Jacob #• Willem, Meeter, Gloncester. —16 Dcc; die Palme, Gallas, Amst. - Southern Empire, Dunlop, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 15 Dcc; Sultana, Crogh, Rott. YARMOUTH, 16 Dec.; Aurora, Dijk, Gron. n. Nantes. - Equity, Piot tyman, Rott. HARTLEPOOL, 14 Dec.; Elisa, Nieboer, Gent. SHIELDS, 16 Dcc; Bravo, Redcliff, Rott. BORDEAUX, 14 Dec.; Gironde, S.,Rott. PORT-MAHON, 27 Nov.; Zeevaart, Kester, Rott. OPORTO, 8 Dcc; Kasvu, Vorendijk, Riga. LIVORNO, 13 Dcc; Anna Caecilia, Gnodde, Amst. Bij Sr. HELENA, 15 Nov.; India, Vonck, Bat. n. Nederl. Si. HELENA, 16 Nov.; Wilhelmina $¦ Clara, van Herwerden, Bat n. Amst. - Telegraph, Jones, id. n. Nederland.</p>
</text>
