<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 2 Nov.-, Alert, S., HuU, (benevens het schip per telegr. gemeld.) HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Nov.; County of Reifrew, Mc Nicol, Soerabaya 1. v. Zierikz.-Niagara, Mortensen, Haiti, l.v. Brouwersh. - Ijano Fleicher, Costa,N.-York l.v. id. -Feyenoord, S., Londen-Emma Sr Ahza, Scales.id.- Gazelle, Seagers, Shoreham. - Harmouy,Ricbardson, Newc. - Seagnll, S., Huil. - Providentia, Ahrends, Riga. - Amicitia, fe., Bergen. - Emulation, Johns. Zierikzeo. - Margareth, Chamlet, id. I BRIELLE, 2 Nov.-, Annie, S., Góole. - Zealous, fe., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Nov.; Waterwitcli, Long, Newc. n. Dordt. MAASSLUIS, 2 Nov.; Ary Scheffer, S., Havre. - Leo, S., Londen. CUXHAVEN, 1 Nov.; Hillcchiaa Wilkens, Karssies,Frederikstad n. Op do ELVE, 31 Oct.-, Catharina Agatha,Potjewijd, Rio Grande.— &apos; 1 Nov.;Sagit.a, Ahrens, Portorico. HAMMEEFEST. 28 Sent.; Diana, Kraan HAUGESUND, 4 Oet.; Newcastle Parpiet, Madscn, Schiedam. CHRISTIANIA, 24 Oct.; Hallurn, Ri. nks, Dokkiim. DRAMMEN, 15-18 Oot.; Mathihle, Gunderscn, Amst. -beagnll, Stce;i.ga_rd id. - Pr.ïsto; Thomassen, Nieuwediep. - Bjt/li, Berg, Doldr. GOTHEN Bt. KG, 23 Oct.; Tltia Susanna, Potjer, Stettin. KOPENHAGEN, 30 Oet.} Atentina Roelfina, Boon, Londen. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 30 Oct,) Herroanna, Veling, Newcastle n.laioe. TKAVEMUNUE, 31 Oct; Arentina Roelfina, Leeuwes, Petersb. STETTIN, 30 Oct; Rubbens.S., Amst DANTZIG, 30 Oct.; Frits en Betsy, Stuit, Harlmg. - Ter rcede: Eelt» Lemminga, Kopenhagen. „ »•__________. mmt SAN DHAMN, 26 Oct.; Henriette, Wever, Petersb. _ ELSENEUR 29 Oct; Jantina, Boon, Amst. n. Riga. • 4 Gebroeders, Blok, ... - Maria Jantina, de Boer, ...-Adnana, Paap, ...-31 Oct; Welvaart, Ekamp, Kroonstad n.Flndhorn. - Gnetje LgTistra, Venmnga, Ipswich n. de Oostzee. — 1 Nov.; 2 Vrienden, Leujes, Amst n. id., de laatste heeft een anker en ketting verloren. HOLTEN AU, 28 Oct; Jonge Pieter, Colle, Memel n. Harlingen.— 29 Oct; Adeline, Tiedemann, Odense n. Amst Bg DEAL, 31 Oct.; Hinderika, Walvius, Newc. n. Triest. -Emn latnm Jones, Port Madocn. Rott. _ . - ? Bij DUNGENESS, 29 Oct -, Catharina, Lohman, Petersbnrgn.Rouaan. Bij WIGHT, 30 Oct;Curacao, Takes, Amst. n. St. Thomas. Bg PLYMOUTH, 30 Oct,; Jacoba Johanna, van der Meulen, Londen n. Fernambuck. ¦ , a. ..... LAMLASH, 27 Oct.; Julius, Groenewoudt, Cly de n. St. Kitts. GRIMSBY, 31 Oct; Geertruida Femina, Bakker, Nerva. HARWICH, 31 Oct; Sieuwert &amp; Johan, Looze, Londen n. Elseneur. SUNDERLAND, 30 Oct.; Bella, Bi raker, Nieuw ;diep. -Stad Zierikzee, Philips, Qnebec. SHIELDS, 31 Oct; EWcretta, Annis, Rott GENT, 31 Oct; Compact Goede Trouw, de Vries, Riga. HAVRE, 31 Oot; Johanna Mathilda, Fex, Stokholm. CAMARET, 28 Oct.; Blanche Marie, Kergosien, Hennebon n. Rott LIVORNO, 29 Oct; John Fenwick.S., Amst PORTO, 24 Oct; Harberdin», Bakker, Sunderland. — 26 o*t-, Broedertid.</p>
</text>
