<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 Oct, N. 0.-Z. Z. O.; Joan, Winsness, Newc. - Alert, S, Huil. - Activ, Ulleberg, Noorwegen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Oct, N.-W. Z. W. Fredrik Hendrik, van Ameyden van Duym, Singapore via Brouwersh.-Elizabeth, Henderson, Newc. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. - Ceres, Remmers, Koningsbergen. - Maria, Hansen, id. - Rhöne, S., Stettin. - Louise, S., Bergen. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 12 Oct., N. W.-Z. Z. W.; Edith, S,Huil.- Avalon,S, Harwich.</p>
	<p>BREMERHAVEN, 10 Oct.; Aaltje, Jonker, Amst-4 Gezusters, Wagenmaker, id. - Agatha Agatha, Tonckens, id. - Rensina Willemina, Kramer, id. - Margaretha, Puister, Rott. - Union, Hazewinkel, Riga. - Atlia Hendrika, Meijer, Koningsb. - Jantina Margaretha, Winter, id. - Catharina, Ulrichs, Christiania. - Ida Zwaantina, Pomper, id. - Afiena, Broeckema, Laurvig. - Catharina Annachiena, Alberts, Papenburg. — 12 Oct; Catharina, Buismann, Amst. - Jantina Pietronella, de Boer, Flensburg. HAMBURG, 10 Oct; Zeemeeuw, van Wijk, Riga. - Anna Elisabeth, Muntendam Dik, Denemarken. CUXHAVEN, 10 Oct.; Chronometer, Das, Avontuur. KIEL, 6 Oct.; Willem Frederik, ten Kate, Oostzee. SWINEMUNDE, 9 Oct; Eva, Crosbie, Schiedam.-Prince of Wales, Burlow, id. - Broedertrouw, Niezen, Harlingen. PILLAU, 10 Oct.; Rubbens, S., Amsterdam. MEMEL, 8 Oct.; Tjakina de Boer, Dost, Delfzijl. - Jantje, Rasker, Londen. - Zwaantina, Gmppelaar, Bremen. - Leentje Dost, v. Brederode, id. BOLDERA, 8 Oct; Godelevus Bernardus, Kral, Nederl. - Hillechiena, Gmppelaar, Elseneur. KROONSTAD, 7 Oct.; Jenne Nollen, de Goede, Schiedam. - Geertruida Anna, Schrikkema, id. - Jantje Martens, Ates, Kopenhagen. - Harmina, Emmelkamp, Koningsbergen. FALMOUTH, 12 Oct.; Morning Star, Key, (v. Akyab) Vlaardingen. PAR, 11 Oct.; Hannah Booth, Andrews, Dordrecht. GLASGOW, 11 Oct; Elsje, de Boer, Buenos-Ayres. DONAU, 29 Sept.; Hahn Adelstein, Jensen, Nederland. BALTIMORE, 26 Sept. Zeilklaar: Nancy, Dieckman, Amst. -28 Sept.; Goethe, Deetjen, Rott. —30 Sept.; E. Sherman, Blanchard, id. - Ferdinand, Dannemann, Amst. PHILADELPHIA, 24 Sept. Zeilklaar: Aurora, Jollyman, Rott. — 25 Edona, Smith, id. — 1 Oct; Fidelia, Kindt, id. BATAVIA, 28 Aug.; Henderika, Lusink, Pekalongan; 30 dito uit zee teruggekomen. — 31 Aug.: Elisabeth, Storm, Nederland. - Jacoba Cornelia, Jansen,id. SAN FRANCISCO, 10 Sept; Japara, Leversteyn, Liverpool.</p>
</text>
