<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 28 Mei, Z. W.; Danube, Hansson, Passar., 1. v. Falm, - Nv*»&apos; Mc&apos; Karlêy, id., 1. v. id.- Gebroeders Smit, Smit, Porto Allegro.- Schink zu Lulle, . track, Maroïm&apos;, 1. v. Falm.-Alida Pronk, Schol Lens, Cette- Familietrouw, Jonker, Alicante.-Irene, S., Middell.Zee.-Maria,Tatosfl&gt;| Bordeaux. - British Quoen, Rosenear, Runcorn. - Jacoba Johanna, f\&apos;. Meulen, Liverpool. - Oriënt, Arthur, Newc. - Raisbeck, Barnard, Snnde^ land. - Thornley, Meldrum, id. — Gisteren nog: Annie Worrall, Gi&apos;eC wood, Iquique. - Geerdina, Flik, Triest. VLIE, 28 Mei. W. Z. W.; Zenobia, Child, Yarmouth. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 28 Mei, W. Z. W.; Speculation, van der K&lt;w; | Zanto. - Tammo Sytse, Klein, id. - Thetis, de Zeeuw Bagges, St. Übe* , Bonne More, Moyon, Bayonne. - St. Jean, Jugean, Rédon. - EupbtaB*^ Hervis, id. r Fancy, Amos, Londen. - H. H., Oldtield, Rochester. - Stal&apos;l the West, Searle, id. - Enchantress, Boyness, Par. - Wesley, LecoutW Jersey. - Sisters, Tomün, Swansea. - Mary&apos;s Jane, Scantlebury, JLiverp • Albert, S., Huil. -,_ BROUWERSHAVEN, 28 Mei,Rurik,Hoiden, Alexandria (E.) n. Pör&apos;.,&apos; BREMERHAVEN, 25 Mei; Vr. Gerhardina, Speelman, Varel. - FroOk° Krodor, Dijkstra, id. - Margrieta, Niesen, Antwerpen. -Pietertje,JD° .&apos;&apos; Groningen. - —-&apos; CHRISTIANIA, 18 Mei; Alida, Feiken, Delfzijl. TONNINGEN, 21 Mei. Gepasseerd: Agatha Ebeliena, B&lt;&gt; n. Stockholm. n  LONDEN, 26 Mei; John Snell, Carver, Rott. — 27 Mei; Visscherij,F°r tuin, Worcum.  Bij DUNGENESS, 23 Mei; Wilhelmina,de Groot.Gioja n. Hull.-Jaco^ Johanna, van der Meulen, Liverpool n. Koogerpolder. — 24Mei; A- f Falck, van der Plas, Amst. n. Bat. - Charlestown, , Charlestown&quot;&apos; Dordt. . PORTLAND, 26 Mei; Agenoria, Pitt, Runcorn n. Amst. . f DARTMOUTH,2S Mei; Ëureka,de Groot,Newport n. Randcrs.-HarrieI Hudson, Par n. Dordt. PORTSMOUTH, 25 Mei; Beatitude, Harforth, Rott. FOWEY, 24 Mci; Flora, Geyken, Dartmouth. GBANGEMOUTH, 25 Mei, Haabet, Boge, Schiedam. CARDIFF, 25 Mei, Joachim, Hetmeijor, Amsterdam. HARWICH, 26 Mei, Raisbeck, Barnard, Nieuwediep. Bij HARWICH, 25 Mei; Tradesman, Press, Rott. n. Ipswich. SHIELDS, 26 Mei; Surprise, Balduin, Amsterdam. - Minerva, Dov1* Zwolle. - Anna, Hoekstra, Gron.-Anna,Klontje,Bremcrh.-CeleriW&quot; van der Leest, Dover. LISSABON, 22 Mei; Catharina Louisc, van Aalst, Rott. { SURINAME, 23 April; Zr. Ms. stoomschip Soembing, commando&quot; Phaff, Kust van Guinea (vertrok 2 Mei n. Curaeao). JAMAICA, 25 April; Elsje, do Boer, Clyde. 10Clio, RuardiAmsterdam.</p>
</text>
