<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 10 Junij; Gcm, Carr, Londen. - Lambton, S„ Suuderland. VLIE, 9 Junij; Urania, S., Petersburg. - Johanna Gezina, v. d. Veen, Memel. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 10 Junij; Belina, Vlas Pott, Windau. - Johanna Margrietha, Ei, Libau. - Louis, Philips, Memel. - Julie, Briinn, Frederikst - Cloha, Tonnissen, Christiania. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 10 Junij; Ary Scheffer,S., Havre.&quot; VLISSINGEN, 10 Jnnij; Armonia, Begna, Buenos-Ayres. - Cclestine Marie, Maheo, Camillas. - Puck, Broadhead, Barrow. - Osiris, Warnekc, Riga. - Alberdina Edziena, Uchtman, Dantzig. - Axel, Hansen, Christiana, ■ Cort Adler, Thostensen, Laurvig. S??i^?SA 7?N&apos;-8 JuniJ; Vr&apos; Geerdina, Speelman, Antwerpen. HAMBURG, 9 Jnnij; Jacobina Gesina, Mahlstede, Middlesbro. - Industrie, Straatman, Makkum. TRAVEMUNDE, 8 Junij; Geertje Elisabeth, van den Borg, Cardif. WARNEMUNDE, 6 Junij;Eendragt., Kamminga, Antwerpen. STETTIN, 7 Junij; Willem 111, S., Amst. DANTZIG, 7 Junij; Alberdina, Fokkelina. Schuur, Heiligenhafen. - Agatha, Tonkens, Rostock. - Rensina, Kramer, Fredericia. - Undina Agimi. Braver, Amst. GOTHENBURG, 6 Junij; Coop Roelf Sikkens, Schaaf, Amst. LYSEKIHL, 31 Mei; Broedertrouw, Vos, Koningsbergen n. Bergen. LAURVIG, 27 Mei; Arnoldus Willem, Nanninga, Tap, Bremen. — 28 Mei; Geerdina, Jager, Termunterzijl. - Margaretha Alida,Dik, Dockum. - Eva, Bakker, Delfzijl. - Zwaantje Elisabeth, Jager, Gron. — 30 Mei- Aldershof, Dijkstra, Delfzijl. - Aaltje Bloema, de Jonge, id. - Gezina, Sehrcuder, id. - Cornelia, Jentsema,id. ELSENEUR, 7 Junij; ter reede voor anker; Concurrent, Teensma, Petersburg n. Amst. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 7 Mei; Gertrude, Mandema, Gloucester n. Nerva. KROONSTAD, 3 Junij; Atalante, Looijer, Gallipoli. - Minerva, Boelens, id. - Agatha Catharina, de Weerd, Cette.- Margaretha, Brambergen, Cadix.- Fenna Henderika, Duit, Newc. - Johanna Wilhelmina, Faber, id. - Morgenster, van den Berg, Vlaardingen. - Ebenhaezer, van Wijk, Bergen. - 4 Junij; Alpba, Puister, Gallipoli. - Thetis, Bakker, Triest. - Aukje, Teensma, Newcastle. - Fenna, Coerkamp, id. - Reintjc, Teensma, id - Sjoukina, de Jonge, id. - Arendina Roelfina, Bopn, id. - Leo Sinnige, Kassies, id. - Balmoral, S., Amst. - Jacob Synes, Sehuth, Rott. - Jonge Willem, Jager, Bergen. - Bordeaux, Ouendag Azn., id. — 5 Junij; Catharina, Slinger, ïs&apos;ewc. __T_. PILLAU, 6 Junij; Geziena, Ei, Londen. — 7 Junij, Jantje Tuinema, Sikkens, Newc. - Zephir, Pekeldér, Engeland. - Flying Eagle, Atkins, Rott. CLYDE, 7 Junij; Oranje Nassau, Strang van Hees, Schiedam. In het KANAAL, 8 Junij; Nova Zembla, Mammes, Rott. n. Hongkong. - Kanagawa, Onwehand, id. n. Bat. DARTMOUTH, 9 Jnnij: Bérénice, S„ Middel! Zee n. Amst. BijDUNGENESS, 7 Junij; Anthony van Hoboken, Hazewinkel, Amst. n. Bat. - Johanna Maria Christina, Gorter, id. n. Cardiff. — 8 Junij; Gijsbert Karel, Graaf van Hogendorp, Fabritius, Rott. n. Batt. Bij DOUVRES, 4 Junij; Johann. Meijer, Bremen n. West-Indie. DEAL, 8 Junij; Alegonda Jacoba, Swart, Newc. n. Bat. MARSEILLE, 7 Junij; Irene, S., Amst. DARDANELLEN, 18 Mei; Enpatoria, Hutchinson, Kustendje n. Amst. KONSTANTINOPEL, 1 Junij; Favorite, Whitefield, Abraila n. Amst. ALEXANDRIA, .. Junij; Minich, S., Amst. QUEBEC, 26 Mei; Eagles, Lawson, Rott. KANAGAWA, 12 April; Maria, de Jong, Amst. MACASSAR, 24 Maart; Suzanna Sc Elizabeth, v. d. Heijden, Poelolaut. - 11 April; Koning Willem 111, Kilian, Rott. 1. v. Banjoew. BANANA (Z.W. kust v. Afrika), 28 Maart; Lodewijk, Bax, Rotterdam, alles wel aan boord.</p>
</text>
