<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Junij; Susanna, Moesker, Sinigagha. - Louise Backmann, JBon«e, Konstantinopel. - Elisabeth Jacomina, Kleininga, Aneona. - Harmanca Maria, Wegman, Londen. - Sippe Visser, de Jong, id. Cornelia, oe Jong id. - Theresa Hanni, Randiech, Newc. - Lan* a &amp; Louise, Marks, ;ü. - Mofeawk, Huiiter, id. - Mathilde, Valdebona, id. - Hamilton, Patland.id. - Harlequin, S., Huil. - Palm, Miller, Petersburg. - Speculation, Berkoe, I redriksluvn. - I .ovidentia, Boy, Elseneur. - Eyr, Christensen, Drammen (oenevc-ns de schepcij pérte]&gt;gonicld). VLIE, 1 Jiiaij&apos;; .Aiifta, Hubert, Huil. -Christina Jacoba, Ploeg, Noorwegen. - Tja-ldft Gesiniï,. Staal, Avontuur. - Zenobia, Child, Yarmouth. - Annefiena, B&apos;oüw, JFredei-ikstaa. - Johns, Torjussen, Tvedestrand. - Coallier, lorentssuj H9^trend,</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS, 1 Junij; Ary Scheffer, S., Havre. - Grace, Coward, Newc. - Albert, S., Huil. - Christian Agathen, Kjar, Holmstrand. - Mathilde, Jörgensen, id. - Ingeborg Emilie, Henrichsen, id. - Olivier, Naess, Christiansand. - Thccla, Nielson, Noorwegen. BRIELLE, 1 Junij; Giralda, Gragam, Sunderl.-Aurora,Schuldt,Bremen.- Malangen, Sörensen, Avontuur. MAASSLUIS, 1 Junij; Leveret, Clark, Newc. - Naiad, Granger, id. - Friedrich, Zeplien, Sunderland. - Juliana, Boysen, id. - Wanderer, Kluss, Middlesbro. - Christian, Schultz, Hartlepool. Neerlands Vlag, Meeter, Riga.- Robert, Nietzel, Koningsbergen. - Deux Associés, Coriton, Avontuur (allen wel in zee). - Elizabeth _. Jane, Esson, Newc. ■• Sally Gale, Slaker, id.-Granville, Robinson, id. ZIERIKZEE, 1 Junij. Het schip per tel. gemeld. TRAVEMUNDE, 28 Mei; Jantjedina, Poppelmeijer, Straalsund. WARNEMUNDE, 28 Mei; Madonna, Holthuis, de Oostzee. LONDEN, 30 Mei; zeilklaar: Sieka, de Groot, Petersburg. —31 Mei; Gesina Jantina, Alberts, id. FALMOUTH, 30 Mei; Waalwijk, Sehaafsma, Rio Grande n. Exeter.- Hendrika, van der Veen, Antw. LIVERPOOL, 30 Mei; Grace, Southwork, Harlingen., Constance, Armstrong.id. _~2ff_V3STIU QUEENSTOWN.3O Mei;Orion, Haiti». Rott. SUNDERLAND, 29 Mci; Hillechina, Vos, Dantzig. WATERFORD, 30 Mei; de Haring, Boomgaard, Cardiff. HULL, 30 Mei; Anna, S., Bergen. GIBRALTAR, 24 Mei; zeilklaar: Heerenveen, Prins, Huelva. GENUA, 27 Mei; Louise Geerdina,&apos; Wever, Nizza.</p>
</text>
