<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN,</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Aug.; Nuovo Reforma, Malfino, Taganrog. - Olga, S., Londen. - Troubadour, S., id. - Gleaner, Larseu, Liverpool. - Robert Stride, Tade, Seaham. - European, S., Huil. - Hebe, Stóve, Archangel. - Fortnna, Torgussen, id. - Reiduif, Pedersen, id. - Alfen, Stromstein, Wasa. - Freya, [ Chnstensen, Sundswall.- Grevende Karen Wedel, Roed, id.- Lyua, Knud- Ben, id. - Verena, Jacobsen, id.-Houtvaart, Ekamp, id. - Astrea, Helgesen, id. - Agnar, Knudsen, id. - Alka, Sjöberg,Wyburg. - Zeepaard, Tobiassen, Hernösand. - Médéa, S., Dantzig. - Urania, S., Stettin. - Alma, Ambiornsen, Holmstratd. - Hermanos, Haraldsen, Klompenburg. - Lida, Hof, Hamburg. - Gesina, Rosman, Papenburg. — Gisteren nog: Ceres, Boe, Odessa. - Jane, Fleiaming, Sunderland. - Scetia,W»rner, Sundswall.- Aleida Maria, Sanne, Hudickswall. - Thetis, Lijkke, Drammen.- Cora, Seeberg, Porsgrund. VLIE, 20 Aug.; Chronos, Haayer, Riga. - Cornelia Susanna.Wytsma, Nerva. - Hillechina Magrietha, Joosten, Bandholm. — 21 Aug.; Magnet, Clark, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 21 Aug.; County of Air, Spittall, Soerabaya, vertr. 21 April.- Balmora&apos;, S., Bristol.- Georg, Noale.Runcorn.-Minerva, Buckinghain, id. - Aiendina, Boerhave, Riga. - Antonius, Gonningen, id. MAASSLUIS, 21 Aug.; Leo, S.. Londen. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 21 Aug.; A. Klopman, Schwanbeck, Nicolajeff naar Rott. - Professor van der Boon Mesch, Vrijman, Bunjoew. n. id.- Leonidas, Rizzio, Berdiansk n. id. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 20 Aug.; Zwaluw, Visser, Dokkum n. Riga. »„ ? Imlt1mIt}&apos;19 All^-; AmiaElisabetb, Dih, Newc-Hermanus Gerardus, Mulder, Termunterzijl. BERGEN, 5 Aug.;&apos;Barbara Christina, Vreeland, Newc. — 8 Aug.; Merwestroom, de Goede, Dordrecht. — 9 Aug.; Elisabeth, Bijl, Antwerpen. - Grietje de Weer;!, Pothuis, Grangemouth. LONDEN, 18 Aug.; Heron, VVilson, Rott. — 19 Aug.; Trien*je, Schoon, Oporto. - Mentor/loering, Worcum. FALMOUTH, 19 Aug.; Gezusters, Ridder, Cienfugos n. Amst. DUINS, 19 Aug.; Vico-Admiraal May, de Groot Stiffrey, Sunderland n. Batavia. / Bij PORTLAND, 19 Aug.; La Plata, Kuiper, Antwerpen n.Triest.- Mermos, Potjer, id. n. Sniirna en Salonica. SUNDERLAND, 19 Aug.; Laura $• Adèle, PoKlmeijer, Amst. - Gesina, Voogt, Duinkerken.; Carl Friedrich, Kinde, Schiedam. ABERDEEN, 17 Ang.; Drie Gerustere, Boswijk, Petersburg. STOCKTON, 17 Aug.; Bee, Woodhall, Rott.-Janna, Struving, Middelb. HULL. 19 Aug.; Harmanna, Velsing.Nerva. - Pelikaan, de Jong, id. HARTLEPOOL, 17 Aug.; Omnibus.Evans, Rott. n. Findhorn.-Aurora, Brinkman, Buxtehude. - Margaretha Johanna, Meiners, Brake. SHIELDS, 18 Aug.; Light en Sign, Rohinson, Dordt.- Jan Vissar,Boon, Schiedam. - Garland, Gibson. Nieuvvediep. - Broedertrouw, de Groot, Antw. - Albert, Jaski, Antw. - Corn. Wil heimina, Hseksma, Schiedam. - Conlasierie, Davison, Rott. - Jantje; Meijer, Zwolle.-Spruit, Pott,Schied. j 19 Aug.; Secret, Rule, Dordt. - Nicolaus. Berg, Schiedam.-Johanna, v. d. Baan, Amst. - Zeevaart, Engelsman, Macduff. - Courser, Wheaton, Dordt. LEITH, 19 Aug., Zwaantje Dost, Heijenga, Gotheburh. - John Howard, Crabtree, Amst. Bij GOUDSTA ART, 19 Aug.; Maria Sarah, Pot, Rott. n. Padang. MÏDDLESBRO, 19 Aug.; Gills, Maun, Rott. ODESSA, 7 Aug.; Jason, S., Napels. NEW-YORK, 7 Aug.; Maria Margaretha, Dalen, Montevideo. HAVANA, 31 Julij; Cardena Packet, Ouwehand, Amst.</p>
</text>
