<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 29 Sept.; Tessonia, Meldrum, Sulina 1. v. Falmouth. - Amsterdam Packet, Thiis, Gothenburg. — 30 Sept.; Advcna, Hales, Newc. Lambton, S., Sunderland. - Christiane, Michaelsen, Sundswall. - Enigheden, Foyen, Frederikstad. - Fortuna, Hovland, id. - Zr. Ms. oorlogstoomschip Cycloop, luit. lste kl. baron v. Hekeren , Bat. - Zr. Ms. oorlogstoomschip Maas en Waal, luit. lste kl. Rijk, id. - Aldebaran, Meyboom, id.- Domenieo, Jaccarino, Messina. - Marie, Anderson, Londen. - Perseverance, Elliot, id. - Elianor, Adams, Newc. - Harmina, Tunteler, id. - Emannel, Walloe, Sundswall. - Najaden, Edwardsen, Drammen. - Freya, Christensen, id. - Christiane Parr, Lohman, Drobach. VLIE, 29 Sept.; Sappemeer, Rozenbsrg, Newc. - Annegiena Elsina, Kuiper&apos; Gothenburg. - Margaretha Alida, Dik, Frederikstad. — 30 Sept.; Fortuna, Heddes, Elbing. - Willem I, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Sept.; Admiraal Ver-Huell, S., Havre. - Gipsey Queen, Petrie, Ban- - Telegram, Bogne, dito - Eureka, Deas, Wiek. - Tweed, Wrightmansted, Middlesbro, - Swallow, S. Huil. - Mathilda, Kemp, Reval. - Soeblomstea, Petersen, Frederikstad. BRIELLE, 30 Sept.; de Maas, S., Londen. - is weder derwaarts teruggekeerd. BROUWERSHAVEN, 30 Sept.; Jupiter, Kiewit, Rott. n. Bat.; heeft de reis voortgezet. BREMERHAVEN, 28 Sept.; Hendrika, Bakker, Hamburg. - Jantina Afina, Veenhuis, id. HAMBURG, 28 Sept.; Siefer, Reents, Workum. - Ebenezer, Mudder, Altona. - Henriette, Marshall, Rott. — 29 Sept.; Santina Pietronella, de Boer, Dokkum. OP DE ELVE, 29 Sept.; Urania, S., Bordeaux. - Hammonia, S., Rott. EMDEN, 23 Sept.; Anna, Obes, Harlingen.—24 Sept.; Alberdina.Meijer, Noorwegen. WISMAR, 27 Sept.; Elisabeth, Schoon, Odensee. STETTIN, 27 Sept.; Cornelia S., Amst. DANTZIG, 26 Sept.; Battruïda, Kladder, Amst. - Willem en Clara, S., Rotterdam. MEMEL, 25 Sept.; Alphard, Puister, Koningsbergen. ELSENEUR, 27 Sept.; gepasseerd: Henriette, kapt. Wever. - Margaretha, kapt. Pot. RENDSBURG,26Sept;gepasseerd: Eendragt, Smid, Dantzig n. Heppc_s. - Agatha Oline, Hoekstra, id. n. Dordrecht. - Eendragt, de Boer, Assens n. Gent. —27 Sept; Pieka, Venema, Bremen n. Kopenhagen. - Pietronella, de Vries, Amsterdam n. Aalborg. - Reina, Kruisinga, Russ. n. de Weser. LONDEN, 29 Sept.; Margaretha Mathilda Francina, Dumon, Gron. Bij DEAL, 28 Sept.; Shanghae, Sehnltze, Sulina n. Amst. Bij de OWERS, 27Sept.; Apollonia, Steinhnsen, Amst. n. de Kust van Guinea. Bij WIGHT, 22 Sept.; Johann, Meijer, Gonaïves n. Bremen. JERSEY, 26 Sept.; Wesley, Lecouteur, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 28 Sept.; Alida Carolina, Amst. - Debora, Lloyd, Rott. SHIELDS, 27 Sept.; Salvadore, Manuella, Amst. SEAHAM, 28 Sept.; Hubertus, Nicholls, Nieuwe Diep. MIDDLESBRO&apos;, 28 Sept.; Emannel, Baron, Rott. HARTLEPOOL. 27 Sept.; Neptunus, Scholtens, Archangel. BARCELONA, 25 Sept.; Catharina, Lindeman, Shields. LISSABON, 22 Sept.; Boreas, van Dijck, Rott. - Verwisseling, Nottmeijer, id. BATAVIA, 31 Julij; Susanna, Vonck, Socrab. 10 Aug. n. Padang vertr. - I Ang.; Noord-Brabant, Loos, Samarang, 8 dito n. Nederl. vertr- — 4 Ang.; Elisabeth Maria, Flens Jhzn., id. — 7 Aug.; 3 Gezusters, Fischer, id. — 9 Aug.; Maria Catharina, de Bos.Probolingo, den 14 dito n. Nederl. vertr. — II Aug.; Nieuwland, Pot, Rotterd. — 13 Aug.; Sophia, Koningin der Nederl., Klein, Cheribon.- China, Ahlmann, Padang. -Jaeoba, Schaap, Soerab. MELBOURNE, ..; Professor v. d. Boon Mesch, v. Zanten, Rott. 1. v. Cherburg. PADANG, 11 Julij; Frederik Hendrik, Glazener, Rott. — 13 Julij; Stad Dockum, Jaski, Bat. - China, Ahlmann, Poelolaut. MACASSAR, 25 Julij; Mary, Fox. Singapore.</p>
</text>
