<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>! TEXEL, 7 Dcc; Aurora, S., Londen. - Fenna Johanna, Andriessen Gothenburg. (Benevens de schepen per telegram gemeld). VLIE, 5 Dcc; Remelia Geertruida, Katoen, Memel. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 7 Dcc; Hollander, S., Bordeaux.- Zephyr g Londen. - Advena, Hales, Newc. 1. v. Brouwersh. &apos; &apos;* BROUWERSHAVEN, 7Dec; Dnisbnrg.Uöiljes, Rott. n. New-York VLISSINGEN, 7 Dcc; Gesina, Roskamp, Riga. - Salamander, Kaiser id. - Hendrika, Duit, Koningsbergen. &apos; ELVE, 6 Dcc; Amsterdam, S-, Amst. LANGESUND, 17 Nov.; Actif, Ulleberg, Amst.— 18 Nov.; Fortuna, de Groot, Hamburg. , FLENSBURG, 1 Dee.; Margaretha Henderika, Datema, Koningsb STETTIN, 4 Dcc; Lucina, Schmidt, Amst. DANTZIG, 4 Dcc; 4 Gebroeders, Emmelkamp, Randers. — 5 Dec. Urania, S., Amst. &apos; ELSENEUR, 4 Dcc,; gepasseerd: Allegonda, Smit, Stettin n. Nederland. 5 Dcc; Arentina Jacoba, Menses, Windau naar id. - Leonore, Jongebloed&apos; Riga n.id. SARPSBORG, 20 Nov.; Hedwig, Torgensen, Nienwe Diep. - Mercur Zernikow.id. — 28 Nov.; Gogstad, Sundene, Amst. — 30 Nov.; Margaretha&apos; Huizinga, Christiania. KOPENHAGEN, 30 Nov.; Geertruida Femina, Bakker, Ipswich. LONDEN, 6 Dcc; Wendelbsa, Hilbrands, Gothenb. - Martha Hendrika Meezenbroek, Groningen. - Jan Frederik, Meiborg, Koningsb. -In lading: Domina Geertina, Wolters, Amst. PLYMOUTH, 4 Dcc; Neanthes, Williams, Amst. n. Napels. — 5 Dcc- Cornelia, S., id. n. id. CORK, 4 Dcc; Johanna Margaretha, Ei, Amst. Bij YARMOUTH, 5 Dcc ; Catharina, Duintjer, Holmstadt n. Londen. SUNDERLAND, 4 Dcc; Oriental, Forder, Nieuwediep. — 5 Dec. - Flossie, Gray, id. ANTWERPEN, 6 Dcc; Fenna,de Jong, Dublin. — 7 Dcc; Anna, Jon gebloed, Riga. - Maria, Jongebloed, id. BORDEAUX, 5 Dcc; Johanna Jacoba, van Veen, Triest. DUINKERKEN, 5 Dcc; Union, Hazewinkel, Riga. PAIMBOEUF, 4 Dcc; dc Hoop, Giezen, Plymouth. PALERMO, 28 Nov.; Bérénice, S-, Cagliari. STRAAT SUNDA, 9 Oct; Isis, Torley Duwell, Batavia n. Rott. — 12 Oct.; President Plate, Julius, Rott. n. Singapore. — 23 Oct; Sophia Amalia, v. Overklift, id. n. id. SAMARANG, 15 Oct.; Hendrik Ido Ambacht, Bijl, Melbourne. MACASSAR, 24 Sept.; Louise, Hansen, Soerabaya (in ladingn. Amst.).--11 Oct.; in lading: Galathea, Gerritz, Amst. - Macassar, Vitringa Coulon, Rotterdam.</p>
</text>
