<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 18 Aug.; Ivanboe, S„ Leith, Themis, Lijkke, Frederikstad. - vl Titania, Oelson, Christiania. — 19Aug.;Zuiderzee,dejong,Havana.-Mi- d( chel Angelo, Assante, Odessa. - Lambton, S., Sunderland, - Alfen, Knudsen, sc Nerva. - Activ, Uhlenberg. Sundswall. - Anna, Winter, Bisserup. - Five 0I Sodskende, Agernp, Frederikst. - Odin, Stibolt, Drammen. - Elise, Hanne- ei vig, Drammen. - Aukator, Morck, id. - Cornelia, S., Bremen. „, VLIE, 18 Aug.; Vriendschap, Lodewijks, Dantzig. - Faeder, Brnun, lonsberg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 19 Aug.; H. D. Pook, Tienga, Ibraila. - Pelgrim, Veling, Terranova. - Kleine Heinrich, Meijerdiercks, Aberdeen. - Thames, i«fïcknell&apos; IPswich. - Bauma, Nielsen,Wyburg. - Catharina, Gauthier, Biga.- Elhda, Pedersen, Libau. - Ansgarius, Jacobsen, id. - Elve, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 19 Aug • John &amp; Charlcs, Hopkins, Eochest.- Ruhr, S., Newc. el KOPENHAGEN, 16 Aug.; Maria, Pronk, Petersburg. r , !J,KOPENH AGEN, 16 Aug.; Mathilde, de Jonge, Dordr. n. Uleaborg. - J} Goldhorn, Pot, Nerva n. Duinkerken. - Adriana, Paap, Schiedam n. Nerva. - . Otto en Olaf, Erichsen, Umea n. Harlingen. , HAMBURG, 17 Aug.; Grietje Wolters, Alberts, Zwolle. - Industrie, ™Ttman&apos;Makk™a. - Trientj e, Terfehn, Worcum. ( o-rir AVEN&apos; l 8 Aug-&apos; Willem I, S., Amsterdam. öWINEMUNDE, 16 Aug.; Catharina Hofland, Hazewinkel, Newc«J ohanna Dorethea, Vos, Dantzig. GOTHENBUEG, 15 Aug.; Stad en Lande, Alta, Harlingen. | ELSENEUR, 16 Aug.; de Welvaart, Ekamp, Petersburg. - Gepassjeerd: Hanna, Baldersen, Jaoobstad n. Amst. - Broedertrouw,Vos, Nerva n. id. - Stientje Boemeling, Bruins, Calix n. Gibraltar.- Johan Gerard, Huges, Biga n. Zoltkamp. - Grietje, Lukkien. - Frouwina, Duit. - Harlingen, Hannema. - ° Jan Hendrik, Slager. &apos;* MIDDLESBRO, 17 Aug.; Geertruida, Lindeboom, Hamburg. f SffiS? ?$k 16 Hug&apos;; de Ho°P&apos;Pot&apos; K«ndsburS* 3 SUNDERLAND, 15 Aug.; Courier, Meuldijk, Rott. —16 Aug.; Louise, ° Jacob, Havre. _ SHIELDS, 16 Aug.; Vesta, Pottinger, Carthagena. - Wilhelmina Catha- &apos; nna,Kiel, St. Valery. — 17 Aug.; Catharina Cornelia, Astuling, Harling. - ; J aeobina, Maathuis, Bremen. CHARLESTOWN, 15 Aug.; Ze»ploeg, Ludeling, Ostende. &apos; ABERDEEN, 16 Aug.; Antina, Muller, Hamburg. 15 Aug.; Emanuel, Larsen, Arendahï. &apos;AMODTE, 19 Ang.; Aniicitia, Ahrens, Maroim n. Hamburg, bij WIGHT, 16 Aug.; Adelaar, Potjewijd, Valentia n. Hamb. - Robertus &apos; He&quot;tokns, Mulder, Bott.n. Bat. *.OLKESTONE, 15 Aug.; Gesiena, Kriens, Gron. t&gt;Ti 18 -Aug-; de Hoop, Zeegers, New-Castlen.Barcclona.-Pieter, 1 ; Bekkering, Sunderland n. Sevilie. LISSABON, 7 Aug. • Hermann Niebuhr, Havana. MALAGA, 11 Arg.; Lucia Hendrika, Dekker, Gibraltar. NEW-YORK, 1 Aug.; Alberdina, ..., Vera Crnz.. MAURITIUS, 10 Julij; Duiveland, Plumer, Tafelbaai.</p>
</text>
