<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title></title>
	<p>i3ut.ocrHjfcc &lt;St..uD. Van 31 October tot en mei 6 November I§6?. BEVALLEN: A. Hoofl.geb. Ovcrduin.Z. — J. G. Keiler, geb. van der Linden, Z. —C. Crama.gcb. Gyzcny, Z.— .1. Singerling , geb. Dool, D. — Jl. 11. &apos;ander Slok , geb. Dorsman, Z. — O. Zwets ,geb. Nooreloos, D. — Jl. Schols, ! geb. de Bruin, Z. — P. Crama, geb. Clmal, I).— M. E. Molenaar,&apos;geb. Barendse, Z. — E. C. Bruystens, geb. Schuurman ,D.— W. Enkelaar, geb. Ver- I meer, D. — J. Stafleu, geb. van Heusden, D. —E. Vermey, geb. Hunn ,D: — I E. van der Post, geb. Kramp, Z. — M. Samsom , geb. Splinter, Z. — D. Corne&apos;. lius, geb. van der Steen, Z. —E. Petiet, geb. Bourgeois, D. —M.F. T. Kis&apos;.ermann , geb. Tethof, D. — S. 11. Gerienaar, geb. Lardé, D. —J. Hartevelt, geb. Huygens, D. —A. Hoef hamer, geb. Duyvewaerd , Z. —E. SI. van der Bleel, geb. van der Linden, Z. — J. M. van der Meer, geb. Zilman, Z. — P. A. van Zijp, geb. Pont, ü. —J. Blom, geb. Heymans, D. GEHUWD: H. J. J. Labree, jm. en J. Joosien , jd. — J. J. Cinjee, jm. en S. F.Poelijoe, jd. — L. H. van der Vos, jm. en L. van der Linden , jd. — L. J. C. ! W. U.Philippo.jm.enG. Elienne.jd.— J. J. Mieog, jm.en B.S. van Beek.jd.— &apos; P. Neuteboom , jm. en M. van den Berg, jd. — W. van der Velden , jm.en J.Flan: dcryn, jd. — W. van Berkel, jm. en A. Derogee, wed. — G. N. de Ru, jm. en J. van Wijk, jd. — H. J. van der Kaay, jm.en J. llorree, jd. — J. M. Wijtenburg, wed. enC.Notenbosch.jd. —F. van der Horn.jm. en E.G. Schrijver, jd.— 11. C. de Bruin, jm. en M. A. van der Zwiep, jd. —A. Hollebeek, wed1, en H. Ia Feber.jd. — W. F. Arbouw, jm.en J. S. Langeveld, jd. — H. J.de Baas, wedr. en J.K. de Liefde, jd. — W. G. de Graaf, jm.en T. Amman, jd. OVERLEDEN: E. J. Winterkamp, geb. Zilman ,30j. —J. van der Linde, wed. W. F. llaseveld, 77 j. — L. Stikkelorum, 33 j. —C. W. Schels, D., Ij. — P. J. van der Klugt, Z , 4j. en4m. — P. Kuys, geb. Kukler,46j. — A. W. E. C. Egler, D., sm.— G. van Zwielen , 69j. —E. Boiermans, D., Ij. en 11 m.— J.E. Houbolt.Z. 2j.ensm. — D. J. van Amerom, 76 j. — M. M. van der Zeeuw, geb. van Ark ,56j.— A. C. Dcc, D., 2 m.</p>
</text>
