<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 4 Julij, N.N.0.; India Packet, Dienering, Batavia. - Setubal, S., Londen.- Troubadour, S., id.- Alma, Ilinn, Middlesbro. - Freya, Christensen, Sundswall. - Neptun, Asche houg, id. - A. R. Falck, Hut, Swartvick. - Oriente, Pedersen. Hudickswall. - Adelgunde, Lange, Drammen. - Foreningen, Christensen, id. — 5 Julij; Lumley, S., Sunderl. - Astrea, S., Stettin. - Boni, Visser, Sundswall. . VLIE, 3 Julij, N.; Eider, S., Middlesbro. - Agina Undina, Pekel ler, Frederikstad. &apos;._»__•__, ? T HELLEVOETSLUIS, 4 Julij, N. N. O.; Olga, S., Londen.- Balmoral, S., Brist. - Louise, S.. Grangemoutn. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Middlesbro, S., Middlesbro. - 2 Gezusters, Bemolt, Brouwershaven. — 5 Juüj; Feijenooid.S., Londen. - Thames, S., Stockt. - Seahorse, S.. Huil. - A-bert, S., id. - Annie, S., Goole.- Gothenburg, S., Gothenburg. — Gisteren nog: Osborne, S., Leith. - Bradford, S., Grimsby. BRIELLE, 4 Julij, N.N.0.; Leo, S., Londen.- Avalon,S., Harwich. ?. - • BROUWERSHAVEN, 4 Ju .. N. N. O.; Luctor &amp; Eraergo, Ouwehand, Rott. n. Batavia. LEER, 2 Julij; Vrouw Helena, Giurseky, Amst. 1 _LLAU, 2 jumj; Jacoba Gesina, Kramer, Mem. — Ondine, S., Dantzig. BOLDERAA, 30 Junij; Johanna Adriana, Sikkes, Nederl. KROONSTAD, 30 Junij; Secundus, de Graaf, Leith. - Catharina Geerdina, de Groot, Stockholm. — ] Juhj; Vertrouwen, Kal, Hapenrade. - Meika Jacoba. „ ïelema, Kopenhagen PAR, 30 Junij; Grietje &amp; Fnnke Wiersma, Petersburg. ANTWERPEN. 3 Julij; Beerta, Schoon, Newc. BUENOS AYRES, 15 Mei; Arenduia, Boerhave, Antw. — 19 Mei; Actif, Huisman, Kanaal. BATAVIA, 6 Mei; Hannah Bloomneld, Saunders, Nederl. — 11 Mei; Quatre Bras, Westeryeld, Australië.—l3Mei;lndia, Eckdale, Nederland.— 16 Mei; Maarten van Rossem, La Seur, Samar. - Friesland. Sipkes, Soerabaya. SOERABAYA, 28 April; Oounty of Lanark, Anderson, Nederland. — 3 Mei; Landbouw, Sissingh, China. PASSAROEANG, 2 Mei; General Birch, Krefting, Nederl. PADANG, 18 April; Grootmeester Nationaal, Giesse, Rott. SWATOW, 21 April; Aquarms, Altmann, Shanghae.</p>
</text>
