<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 6 Aug., Z.Z.0.-W.Z.W.; Solo, Devito, Taganrog 1. v. Falm., (benevens de schepen per telegr. gemeld.) VLIE, 5 A ag., Z.Z.W; Nora, S., Londen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 5 Aug., W. Z. W.; Gustav, Kjaer, Akyab. - Thomas, James, Londen. - Zephir, Dack, Rocaester. - John &amp; Charles, Carlton, id. - Gannet, S., Liverpool. - James Rankins, S., Glasgow (benevens het schip per tel. gemeld). BRIELLE, 6 Aug, Z.—W.; Waterloo, S., Londen. - Omnibus, John Evans, Findhorn. - Avalon, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Aug., W.; Regina Maris, Ouwehand, Banjoewangie n. Rott.; vertr. 3 Maart. - Bristolian, Whyte, Akyab n. id. - Angelina. Polumba, Catania n. Dordt. BREMERHAVEN, 4 Aug; Geerdina Geertruida, Kramer, Memel. ELSFLETH, 3 Aug; Eüsabeth, Mjtus, Namsos. - Juliana, Boyesen, Riga, Bij KOPENHAGEN, 5 Aug.; Eordeaux, Ouendag, [Petersburg mar Aberdeen.</p>
	<p>HAMBURG, 5 Aug.; Amsterdam, S., Amsterdam. - Gouverneur van Ewijck, S., id. Op de ELVE, 5 Aug; Hilkea, de Vries, Makkum. NORDEN, 2 Aug.; Stientje Klein, Huizinga, Vegesack. SWINEMUNDE, 4 Aug.; Johanna, Berg, Amst. DANTZIG, 3 Aug.; Ondine, S., Amst. (via Stettin). - Pietronella, de Vries, Rensburg. - Jacoba Margina, Kuil, Kiel. MEMEL, 1 Aug.; Rensina Wilhelmina, Kramer, Kopenh. —2 Aug.; Zwaantina Margaretha, de Vries, Kastrup. LONDEN, 4 Aug.; Cornelia, Vorenkamp, Petersburg. - Sara, Stuit Trouville. - Stad Worcum, van &apos;t Veer, Worcum. Bij DOVER, 2 Aug.; Herman de Ruijter, Esink, Amst. n. Samarang. Bij DUNGENESS, 2 Aug.; Anton en Jacob, Bot, Rott. n. Lissabon. - Rio de la Plata, Hörner, id. n. Buenos-Ayres. Bij WIGHT, 4 Aug.; Afrika, Remmers, Rott. n. Africa. RÖCHESTER, 3 Aug.; Invicta, Hopkins, Rott. PENZANCE, 3 Aug.; Geerdina Afina, Pomper, Buenos-Ayres. FALMOUTH, 4 Aug.; Margaretha, Veen, Rio Janeiro n. Wyburg. — 5 Aug.; Mej. Petronella Knijpmga, Klof kom, Salonica. PENARTH, 2 Aug; Cornelia, de Boer, Rott RYE, 3 Aug.; Integrity, Hamden, Rott. LIVERPOOL, 4 Aug.; Baron van Heemstra, Nepperus Fzn., Bombay. - Helios, Winters, Buenos-Ayres. QUEENSTOWN, 3 Aug.; Alliance, Lewis, Amst. (om order). SHIELDS, 3 Aug.; Samarang, de Groot, Dordrecht. BRISTOL, 4 Aug.; Fidelity, Cole, Amst. BARROW, 2 Aug.; Isabella Hall, Redhead, Rott. CARDIFF, 2 Aug.; Balmoral, S., Bristol. — 3 Aug.; Triest, S., Rott. DUBLIN, 3 Aug.; Vartry, S., Rott. TRIEST, 31 Julij; Elisabeth Johanna, Schenk, Sinagaglia. MONTEVIDEO, 15 Junij; Mathilde, de Jonge, Rott. — 16 Junij; Janna Adriana, Franken, Paranagua (19 dito n. Buenos-Ayres vertrokken).— 18 Junij; Elisabeth, Botje, Buenos-Ayres. - Eltica Meezenbroek, Etazewinkel, id. (vertrok 22 diton. Brazilië). —22 Junij; Immanuel, Strackhalder, Amst. — 27 Junij; Elisabeth, , Paranagua. BAHIA, 22 Junij; Anna, Laarman, Triest.- Waalwijk, Schaafsma, Cardenas n. van.</p>
</text>
