<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 6 Aug., Z.Z.O.—W.Z.W.; Zeester, Zoetelief, Curacao. - Vrouw Anna, Hospes, Londen.-Sir John Bowes, Wright, Newc. - Vestalinden, Mörck, Sundswall.-Drammen, Frost, Drammen.-Achilles, Wulfsberg, Christinastad. VLIE, 6 Aug., Z. Z. W.; Beurs van Amsterdam, Tofte, Sundswall.- Stad Steenwijk, Wijma, Christiania.-Noordster, Dekker, id.-Welvaart, Ekamp, Frederikstad. - Heero, Kreutz, id. - Coneordia, Hendriksen, id. - Onderneming, Kooiman, id. - Geertruida, Dekker, Kragerö. - Vlieland, Visser, Avontuur. - Johanna, Oldenburger, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 6 Aug. W.Z.W.; de Hoop, Manneken, Gibraltar.- Burfleld Brothers, Johns, Londen. - Emïmuel Butcher, Walker, Newc. - Friends, Wells, id. - Victor, Arlington,id.-Sultana, Bell,id.- Andrea, Campadinoco, id. - Venus, Permien, id. - Little Dorritt, Toms, id. - Indiana, Cooper, id. - Cornelia, van Hengelaar, Riga. - Nimrod, Reuneberg, Windau. - Kleinkinderen, v. d. Wal, Christinastad. - Fanny, Unger, id. - Friedrich Ludwig, Voss, Oostzee. - Dauphny, Frederiksen, Frederikstad. BROUWERSHAVEN, 6 Aug.; Kensingtou, Baker, Rott. n. New-York. BREMERHAVEN, 5 Aug.; Onrust, Slankenberg, Rostock. - Jantje, Zuidland, Hamburg. - Trientje Veltkamp, Koopman, Amst.—sAug.; Twee Vrienden, Kuipers, id. - Anna Theodora, Kuipers, Koningsb. - Aaltina Fokkelina, Schuur, id. — 6 Aug.; Cornelia, Leeuw, Laurvig. - Voorwaarts, de Vries, Drammen. - Jacoba Cornelia, Schoon, Gron. - Vr. Geerdina, Speelman, Amst. - Meinsina, Klontje, id.- Anna, Luiken, id.-Dirkje, Poort, id. HAMBURG, 6 Aug.; Grietje, Siepel, Amst. CUXHAVEN, 5 Aug.; Alida Ikea, Pieper Gothenburg. - Jonge Roelof, Douwes, Amst. — 6 Aug.; Aaltje Maathuis, de Vries, Petersb.- Catharina Jantina, Speelman, Friedericia,- Anna &amp; Elise, Lukje, Stettin.- Johannes, Haak, Petersb. - DominaGeertina, Wolters,Gron. -Catharina de Boer, Westenberg, Engeland. - Catharina Margaretha, Riebelmg, Arósund. EMDEN, 2 Aug.; Bonheur, Pommer, Engeland. HOYER, 2 Aug.; Lena Catharina, Ewen, Nederland. — 4 Aug; Antina, Schoon, Engeland. SWINEMUNDE, 4 Aug.; Emilie. Köhn, Rott. BOLDERAA, 1 Aug.; Kap, Reinertsen, de Maas. — 3 Aug.; Louise, Meislahn, id. - Jeantine, Eeftmg, Nederland. ELSFLETH, 4 Aug.; Hendrika, Voss, Frederikshald. COWES, 3 Aug.; Lubberina, Spithorst, Nerva. BERWICK. 4 Aug.; de Zwerver, Hagedoorr, Newcastle. FALMOUTH, 4 Aug. Bristolian, White. Akyab n. Rott. - Mandarm, Mutter, Rangoon n. Z\v ijndrecht. - Thos.and Mary, Thompson, Koogerp. MONTROSE, 1 Aug.; Lucas Wildervank, Riks, Leith. PENTOWAN, 3 Aug.; Vesper, Armitage, Koogerpolder. - Petrei, Jennings, Dordt. - Harmina Petersburg. QUEENSTOWN. 3 Au?.; Wanderer, Murton, Vlaardingen. SCARBOROUGH, 3 Aug.; Anna Catharina, Hughes, Middlesbro. BARCELONA, 28 Julij&apos;; Rival, Doewes, Mahon (moet 7 dagen quarantaine houden.) VENETIË, 1 Aug.; Cycloop, S., Amsterdam. HAVANA, 15 Jnlij. Zeilklaar: Havana Packet, Harken New-York. CARDENAS, 16 Julij; Sagua-Packet, Sluisman, Philadelpma. MONTEVIDEO, 26 Junij; Antonius, de Vries, Buenos-Ayres. - Zeven Sterren, Hemmes, Brazilië. 2. i .___ RIO JANEIRO, 3 Julij; Catharina, Fokkes, New-lork. — 6 Juhj; Elisabeth, Fenster, Falmoiith. BAHIA, 9 Julij; Zeilklaar: Frithjofna, ten Dam Ham, Falmouth.</p>
</text>
