<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 16 Julij, Z.Z.0.-N.0.; Setubal, S., Londen. - Troubadour, S., id. - Heeg,Boontje, id. - Hero, Burlinson, Sunderl.- Neptunus, deVries.Petersb.-Johanna Maria.Feningaid.-Maria Reifina, de Groot. id. - Anna, de Weerd, id.- Lucas Wildervank, Riks, Nerva. - Norden, Dahles, Abo. - Beurs van Amsterdam, Tol&apos;te, Borga. - Minerva, Rafen, Sundswall. - Flaminge, Ceder? gren, id.-Rembrand., S., Stettin. VLIE, 15 Julij, 0.Z.0.; Fenna, Coerkamp, Petersburg -Alida Elisabeth, Potjewijd, Nerva..- Elisabeth, Arends, Riga. — 16 Julij; Jan Visser, Boon, id. HARLINGEN, 13 Julij; Eendragt, Kok Houwink, Nerva. - Nimrod , Rennenberg, Windau. - Morgenster, Christensen, Sundswall. - Bouchina, Koster, Memel. — 14 Ju&apos;ij; Hendrika, Plukker, id.— 16 Julij; Hollandia, S., Londen. - Equator, Huis-, man, Petersb. - Iwau. Johannesen, Windau. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 16 Julij, Z. 0.; 01 ga, S., Londen.- Kinghorn, S., Leith. - Lord Raglan, S., Newc. - Seahorse, S., Huil. ZIERIKZEE, 15 Julij, N.0.; Fleur de Marie, Brooks.Brooks, Liverpool. NERVA, 4 Julij; Esperance, Dik, Liverpool. PILLAU, 13 Julij; Johanna, Klöf kom, Kopenh. — 14 Jn]ij.( Maas, Stoorvogel, Cette n. Riga. v KOPENHAGEN, 15 Julij; Atlas, Block, Rott. Bij KOPENHAGEN, 14 Julij; Wiebe Jacobs, Visser, Nerva n. Amst. - Johanna Wilhelmina, Fabcr, Petersburg n. id. - 4 Neeltjes, Koenes, Memel n. Einden. - St. Ohristoffer, Hansen, SWÏNEMU_.DE,14 Julij; 2 Gebroeders, Wolthuis, Sunderl. DANTZIG, 14 Julij; Weldaad Voogd, Sunderland. - Annachiena, Blonw, Kopenhagen. — ler Reede: Tjapco Schuringa, Drentb, Kopenhagen. STOCKHOLM. 9 Julij; Medea, S., Amst. LONDEN, 14 Julij; Jacobas Verhoef, Meezenbroek, Efea. BiiDEAL, 15July; MarieCornelie,Arnold,Rott.n.de Westk. v. Afrika.</p>
	<p>LIVERPOOL, 14 Julij; Alida Catharina. Nagel, Montev. Bij EDDYSTONE, 13 Julij; Havana Packet, de Boer, Havana n. Antwerpen. BONESS, 13 Julij ;Princess Royal, Gibbs, Amsterdam. LYNN, 13 Julij; Am. Willem Nanninga, Top, Nyekjobin°. GRANGEMOÜTH, 13 Julij; Verwisseling, Öooj, Drammen. HOLL, 14 Julij; Gesina, de Boer, Landscrona. MIDDLESBBO, 14 Julij; Anna Geertruida, Kempen, Rott - SUNDERLAND, 12 Julij; St. Malo, Christian, Rott. - Success, Mason, Delfshaven. -Findon, Robson, Nieuwediep. SHIBLDS, 14 Julij; Minhana, Bakker, Harlingen. LEITH, 14 Julij; Marg. Antina, de Boer, Genua. BELFABT, 12 julij; Neptune, Youn^, Rott. MACAO, 26 Mei; ïsaac da Costa, Klein, Hongkong, laadt v. Samarang. - Estafette, Oepkes, id., laadt voor Batavia. MELBOURNE, 19 Mei; Jacobus, v. d. Tas, Bat., ligt weder derwaarts in lading. HONGKONG, 22 Mei; Katharina Maria, Brandts, Singapore. — 27 Mei; Wilhelmina, Tönjes, Newschwang.</p>
</text>
