<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>Margarctlia. .™sl.^= Agatha Ebelina, Hoekstra, Londen. - Christina, Harns, Fredenkstad. - 3 Zusters, Dijkstra, Lissabon. - Vrede, Mork, Drammen.- Stjernen, 1 hortonsen, id. VLII_, 2 April, W. Z. W.; Urania, S„ Dantzig. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 April, Z. W.; Vriendschap, tsr Bruggen, Bat. 1. v. Brouwersh. - Concurrent, Ouwehand, id.l.v.id., na op strand gezeten te hebben. - Vasco do Gama, van Gelderen, Livorno 1. v^Plymouth. - Arcturus, Richards, Port Madoc. - James Rankins, S., Glasgow. - Rose, Ohamplin, Newc. - Darliugton, Reabv, id. - Echo, Robinson, Sundcrland.- Albtrt, S., Huil. ..&apos; BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 April, W. Z. W.; Althéa, Mork, Haïti n. Rotterdam. - Sarah Arm, Muir, Odessa n. id. - Trewartha, Stede, Charlestown n. id. - Catiierino, Belchuwi, Sunderl. n. id. - Beccles, Bilbj&apos;, New- Castle n. Dordr. - Ironmaster, S., Middlesbro n. id.</p>
	<p>ÉLSENEUR, 29 Maart; gepasseerd: Rieka, Puister,Schiedamn.de Oostzee. — 30 Maart; Weeja, Wortel, Elseneur n. Dantzig. — 31 Maart; Content, Kuiper, Alloa n. Koningsbergen. - de Zwerver, Visser, Nederland n. Da- tzig. LONDEN, 1 April; Twee Zusters. Bakker. Groningen. Bij PLYMOUTH, 30 Maart; Mathilde, do Jonge, Rott.&apos; n. Montevideo. DEAL, 30 Maart; ten anker: Bato, Huizing, Londen n. Montevideo. Bij &apos;DE Ad., 31 Maart; Battruida, Jonkhoft&apos;, Groningen n. Gloucester. Bij ZUID-VOORLAND, 30 Maart; Cornelia &amp; Geertruida, Wielema, New-Orleans n. Bremen. _■__&quot;, GRANGEMOUTH 29 Maart; Barteld Herman, Raskor, Bremerhaven. HARTLEPOOL, 29 Maart; Drie Broeders, Leffers, Ainst. VENETIR, 27 Maart; Neptunns, Scholtens Newc. _ : , • PHILADELPHIA, 16 Maart.; In lading: Maria Adelaide (bark), Rotterdam. - Kensington (id.),id. ._, , N EW-YORK, 20 Maart.; In lading: Merrimac , Rott. HAVANA, 10 Maart; Poseidon, Deddes, Christiansund. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 2 April, Z. W.—N. W.; Irene, S., Middell. Zee. VLIE, 1 April, W. Z. W.; Emanuel, Pedei-sou, Tvdostrand. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 April, Z. W.; Amiciria, S., Bergen. - Elve, S., Hamburg. . , , „TT . , MAASSLUIS, 2 April-, Orion, S., London. - Avalon, S., Harwich. _ FALMOUTH, 30 Maart; Silontium, Schagen van Leeuwen, Kio Janeiro n. Londen. _ . .., - IPSWICH, 30 Maart-, Broedertrouw, Zeven, om dc Noord. PORTSMOUTH, 30 Maart; Karsina, Olfers, Duinkerken. RAMSGATE, 31 Maart; Geertruida Maria, dc Ligny, Dordt n. Urdiff (na geëindigde reparatie.) C HARLESTOWN, 23 Maart; Fenna, Woudsma, Bergen. LIVERPOOL, 30 Maart; zeilkl.: Fenna Gesina, Ymker, Petersb. CADIX, 25 Maart; Adriana Wilhelmina, Dijk, Sevilla. NEW-YORK, 19 Maart; zeilkl.: Hillegonda, Heikamp,Rott.__</p>
</text>
