<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 29 Maart; Mathilda, Kraeft, Odessa. - Aline, Ordronnean, Nantes. — 30 Maart; Lady Alice, Stranaek, Soerabaya, 1. v. Falmouth. - Argo, Bartels, Maroïm, 1. v. id. Cbarlotte Geddie, I orster, Matanzas, I. v. id. - 2 Zustors, Eeenstra, Londen. - Herstelling, van &apos;t Veer, id. - Isabella Sarah, Hall, Newc. - Tonnant, Patterson, id. - Vesta, S., Stettin. - Brittannia, Gyde, Christiania. - Flora, Nyman, Drammen. - Argo, Kotter, Osterrisoer. VLIE, 2ü Maart; Neptnnus, van Gorknm, Londen. AMELAND, 27 Maart: Hoffnung, Oltmans, Eauderfelin. TEEMUNTERZYL, 25 Maart; Nyssiena, Veldman, Langesund, lag op 28 dito zeilkl. n. Noorwegen. - Jonge Barend, Prins, Hamburg, is 28 dito derwaarts teruggekeerd.&quot;— _§ Maart; Ena, Looze, Langesund. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Maart; Seine, S„ Bordeaux. - Louise Désirée, Eivet, Nantes. - Ary Scheffer, S., Havre. - Peyenoord, S., Londen. •¦ Gazelle, Seagers, Shoreham. - Domina Geertina, Wolters, Poole. - Seagull, S., Huli. - Svvallow, S., id. - Colletis, S., Goole. BRIELLE, 30 Maart; Ravensbury, S., Harwieh. EMDEN, 27 Maart; De Hoop, Drewes, Groningen. HAMBURG, 28 Maart; Gesina, Boker, Makkum. BREMERHAVEN, 29 Maart; Twee Gezusters, Geltes, Groningen. Bij LO .VESTOFT, 27 Maart; Graafstroom, de Boer, Newc. n. Singap. Bij LIZARD, 27 Maart; Agatha, Zeylinga, Curacao n. Amst. - Gleaner, Thompson, Java n. id. Bij FALMOUTH, 27 Maart; Pudsey&apos;Dawson, Baker, Eott. n. Liverpool. CARDIFF, 27 Maart; Gruno, Klundert, Amst. - I CHARLESTOW.N, 27 Maart; Helena, de Jonge, Harlingen. SWANSEA, 27 Maart; Niessina Jacoba, Bareids, Londen. LIVERPOOL, 28 Maart; Sirius, Wenke, New-York. HAETLEPOOL, 27 Maart; Margaretlia, de Vries, Hull. SUNDERLAND, 28 Maart; Cassandria, Flomming, Hellevoetsluis. - Bella, Scott, Nieuwe Diep. SHIELDS, 28 Maart; Proteus, Zeven, Amst. - Mettina Jacoba, Dijken, ïd. - Deutsciiland, Stephen, id. - Emma Bauer, Falck, id. - Sikko, Jonker, Delfzijl. CABAIS, 23 Maart; Aline, Ordronneau, Nantes n. Amst. St. NAZAIRE, 28 Maart; Elise, Eiensema, Dordrecht. LIVORNO, 22 Maart; Rotterdam, S., Rott. NAPELS, 22 Maart; Arleehino, Paolillo, Amst. - Marie Elisabeth, Bonjer, Newe. CIVITA-VECCHIA, 19 Maart; Catharina,Visser, Newc. NEW-YORK, 15 Maart; Almena, Swan, Eott. MONTEVIDEO, 29 Jan.; Diana, Masdorp, Antw. UITGEZEILD. TEEMÜNTEEZYL, 25 Maart; Gesina, Fokken, Hanover. - Zwaantje, FokJcen, id. —26 Maart; Hoffnung, Denekamp, Emden.-Hansina, Obes,ïd. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 30 Maart; Francina Willemina,j. Winkel, Bat.-via Brouwershaven.-Ilenriette Gerardina Susanna, Dam, Singapore, via id. - Albert, S., Hull. - Contcst, S., Goole. - Anna, S., Bergen. HAMBURG, 28 Maart;Posseidon, Deddes, St.Marta.- Goede Verwachting, Mulder, Bremen. - Vriendenlust, Koops, id. - Hcinrich, Luken, Zwolle. - Willem I, S., Amsterdam. DANTZIG, 27 Maart; Urania, S., Amst, BRAKE, 29 Maart; Meika Jacoba, Wielema, Havre. - Antje, Teensma, Engeland. DEAL, 28 Maart; Klasina Jarttina, Brouwer, Santander. SANDWIC tl, 28 Maart; Eendragt, Valk, Shorcha-m. [ WATEBFoi.&apos;.D,2BMaart;zeilkl..-Elisabeth^Christina,Eisclier,Amst. FALMOUTH, 28 Maart; de Vrede, Nickus, Londen. - Geertina, Mooi, Antwerpen. COWJES, 28 Maart; Heinrich, Mewcs, Rott. CARDIFF. 27 Maart; Cornelia Hendrika, Marcussen, Singapore. - Maria, Muller St. Thomas. LIVERPOOL, 28 Maart; zeilkl.: Jantje Tiddens, Hazewinkel, Petersburg. Alida Elisabeth, Potje wijd, Nerva. DUBLIN, 28 Maart; zciikl.: Zorg #• Vlijt, Mulder, Lissabon. ROCH!&apos; STEE, 28Maart; Drie Gezusters, Pluktje, Emden. SUNDERLAND, 28 Maart; Prov. Drenthe, Westenberg, Groningen. NANTES, 26 Maart; Cathalina van Calcar, Koning, Liverpool. PAIMBOEUF, 27 Maart; Catharina, Koning, Eott. - Josephine, Clement id. REDON, 21 Maart; Petite Paysamie, Tessero, Schiedam. — 22 Maart; Josophine Désirée, le Dantu, Rott. t ïoo 23Maart; Espcrance, Hazewinkel, Amst. _L4,™4,5ON&apos;,25 Maart; Maria, van Duivenbodcn, Port a Port. TEIËST, 23 Maart; Godelevus, Boer, Rott.</p>
</text>
