<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 21 Nov.; Vrouw Dicuwke, Eeenstra, Londen. - Minister Thorbecke, S., HuU. — 22 Nov.; Hawk, S., Huil. - Zeehond, Eeninga, Petersburg. - Talma, Larsen, Drammen, (benevens het schip per tel. gemeld.) VLIE, 20N0v.; Stad Workum, van &apos;t Veer, Londen. - Jantje, Knol, Newc. - Harmonie, Haverschmidt, Prederikstad. - Willem, Swarts, Oudsoen, met zware schade. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 22 Nov.; Jantina, Douwes, Newport. - Willem de Derde, S., Triest, 1. v. Brouwershaven. -Alexander, Esano, Hennebon.- Admiraal Ver-Huel, S., Havre.- Roland. S., Duinkerken, na aanden grond te hebben gezeten. - Aurora, S., Londen. - Little Dorrit.Toms, Charlestown. - William &amp; John, Frost, Leith. - Geerdina, Nie boer, Petersburg. - Activ, Muller, Pernau. - Gogstad, Angel, Christiania. - Gothenburg, S, Gothenburg. - Condor, S.. Brcmen. BRIELLE, 22 Nov.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. BROUWERSHAVEN, 22 Nov.-, Helena &amp; Anna, van Aalburg, Rott. n. Batavia. BREMERHAVEN, 21 Nov,; St. Petersburg, Hoven, Pstersb. HAMBURG, 20 Nov.; Urania, S., Antw. — 21 Nov.; Anna Hendrika, Dallinga, Emden. - Margaretba, Graafmeijer, Bremen. AL&apos;IONA, 19 Nov.; Harmonie, van Peer, Tromsoe. BERGEN, 4 Nov.; Phoenix, Glim, Dantzig. - Thetis, de Zeeuw Baggus, Vlaardingen. CHRISTIANIA, 7 Nov.; Helena Florentina, Rosonbeek, Newc. DRAMMEN, 9 of 10 Nov.; Foreningen, Borck, Nieuwediep, KOPENHAGEN, 19 Nov.; Alida Hendrika, Wegener, Petersb. LANDSCRONA, 12 Nov.; Jansjen, Meyer, Newc. WARNEMUNDE, 19 Nov.: Sicco, Jonker, Pernau. BOLDERA, 14 Nov.; Annchen, Bette, Amst. - Petronella, Wirtjes, Liverpool. ELfcENEUR, 19 Nov.; gepass.: Geertruida Speelman, Lever.Kroonstad n. Amst. - Zwerver, Visser, id. n. Leer. - Margretha, Kappen, Libau naar Maas. - Renska, Voogd, Riga n. Antw. - Anua, Bruns, id. n. id. - Herstelling, Lukkien, Stettin n. Emden. - Annegiua Hermina, Zuidema, id. n. id. - 20 Nov.; Emanucl, Jenseu, Stralsund n. deMuas. - James and Eleuore, Mattbews, Krooiutad n. Schiedam. - Alida Hendrika, Nleuwenhitis, Pernau n. id. - Welhelinina, Meyer, Dantzig u. Harlingen. - Albion, Nielseu, Stokholm n. Antwerpen. TONNINGEN, 17 Nov.; Catharina, Heyenga, Galatz n. Bergen. - Gepasseerd : Anua Tedora, Kuiper, Eckerntorde u. Amst. - 3 Gebruder,Katt, ld. n.Dordrecht. LONDEN, 20 Nov.; Lion, S., Harlingen. - Magnet, S., Rott. YARMOUTH, 18Nov.;Zenobia. Child, Harlingen. HULL, 19 Nov.; Anna, S., Rott. n. Bergen. BRIDLINGTON, 19 Nov.; Lord Raglau, S., Rott. n. Newc. CHARLESTOWN, 19 Nov.; Louise Auguste, Mortensen, Rott. CARDIFF, 17 Nov.;Cito, Mooi, Schiedam. LEITH, 19 Nov.; Jantje, Stuit, Petersb. Bg St. HELENSBAAI, 20 Nov.; Curacao, Takes, Amst. n. St. Thomas. HaVRE, 15 Nov.; Admiraal Verhnell, S., Rott. —19 Nov.; Gezusters, Ridder, Rio Hache (1. v. Falmouth.) Bt IRDEAUX, 20 Nov.; Economie, Bossinga, Gent. St. ÜBES, 9 Nov.; Anna Maria, van der Kooy, Lissabon. PALEKMO, 14 Nov.; John Fenwick, S., Messina (vertrok n.Amst.) FERNAMHUOK, 19 Oct.;lndustrie, Mulder, Bahia. MANZANILLA DE CUBA.29 Oct,; Hollander, Kruyt,Havana(ligt in n.</p>
</text>
