<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>IEXEL, 23 Oct.; Louise Helena, Aggen, Archangel. -Ygdrasi sen, Christiania. — 24 Oct.; Eendragt, Martens, Grangemouth. - 4 Gebroeders, Woudstra, Newc. - Norway, Rowlands, Sunderland. - Come-On, Fr«e&apos; man, id. - Wilsons, Rich, Archangel. - Alert, Abrahamsea, Umea. - Jolt!»&quot;&apos; Mulder, Riga. - Sieka, Douwes, Osterrisoer. - Vaaren, Johansen, Laurvig- VLIE, 23 Oct.; Stoomvaart, S., Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 24 Oct.; Clipper, Forster, Liverp. - Tradesm»&quot;&apos; Press, Boness. - Mary Tweedlie, Dawson, id. - Louise, S., Grangemouth.&apos; Everetta, Annis, Newc. - Lncy, Clark, id. - Mary, Witten, id. - Tban^9&apos; Longstaff, id. - Albert, S., Huil. - Aurora, Bollen, Archangel. - Venns, A»&apos; thonissen, Petersb. - Amicitia, _? Bergen. - Catharina Johanna, Mulder&apos; Tromsö. - Johan, Severin, id. - Hammoma, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 24 Oct.; Leo, S., Londen, is derwaarts teruggekeerd. BROUWERSHAVEN, 24 Oct.; Elena, Bremer, Rolt. n. New-York- * Elise, Coopen, Newc. n. Rott. - Chilona, Lammcrs, Drammen n. Dordt. HAMBURG, 21 Oct.; Elve, S., Rott. —22 Oct; Willem I, S„ Amst. BREMERHAVEN, 23 Oct.; Gesina, Nissen, Amst. NORDEN, 19 Oct.; Frau Anna, Kernper, Amst. LANDSCRONA, 5 Oct.; Gebroeders, Loodijzen, Engeland. _? GOTHEN.3URG, 17 Oct.; Frits fr Betsy, Stuit, Harl- AnnechinakIsini, Kuiper, id. ELSEMEUR, 19 Oct.; gepasseerd: Anna,Kromke, Umea n. Dordr- • Fenna Gesina, Ymker, Riga n. Nantes. — 20 Oct.; Louise Christine, Bolvig&apos; Nerva n. Amst. - 21 Oct.; 2 Vrienden, Ebes, Riga n. Purmerende. - 22 0&amp;- &gt; Catharina Hendrika, Tengen, Dokkum n. Kopenhagen. - Jeltina, Wessel*/ Amst. n. de Oostzee. - Z. us, v, d. Tas, Carleby n. Nederland.</p>
	<p>oSS-SSïi!J79&amp;,o**.™. »*#*MJB*TtakMfcfi.at.lsa. Fenna b i *&apos; A.mst&apos; &quot;1S set.| Anna Meta, Ul&apos;icbs, Koningsb. n. Grom- Mt^&apos;T!™&apos; Aast- n- Rostock.— 19 Oct.; Bonna Riiinelingh, Visser, HOLTT. Wa rr &quot;Jenanna- Klof körn, Dokkum n. Sonderburg. .1 - M_\ - ._oct-i gepasseerd: Concordia, Speelman, Stettin n. Delf- Jacabina _V_ ¦ I*!llechiena, Pekelder, Rostock n. Londen. —20 Oct.; LONnpto .UAS&apos;Danu&apos;n&apos; Gron&apos; persma W„!™„ „&apos; aria&apos; v- Buren- Archangel. - Drie Gebroeders, Kasker, Amst * Catharina, de Wal, Petersb. -In lading: Harmonie, Bak- AB__DEEWfi9_oocti Three Brothers, Carlton, Rott. GRIMSBY _. _ oct&apos;; Anrora&gt; KuiPer Sunderl. FALMO U-TH Cbristina Maria, Nielsen, Dordt. rosn Hnr_u_ ü,22 oct.; Time-is-Money, van Lessens Balsters, Matamo- Bii&apos; _ri7l&apos;,&apos;W,lln» Hl, S., Middellandsche Zee. H.TT ri. _ 0tt-&apos;&lt;d® Proef. Visser, Newc. n. Genua. SHr. Rn i _&apos;&apos;&apos;Anna&apos; St., Rott. n. Bergen. BRTnT tw.2. .? et&apos;; Christina Jacoba, Ploeg, Dundee. GENT „V n &apos;21 0ct&apos;&apos; Elizabeth and Mary, Arno, Zierikzee n.Newc. Stella MarisH &apos;&apos;fj.Ca*arma Hillechina, Boekhaut, Petersburg. — 23 Oct.; GENUA 1i3Q(r-t&apos;; Hollander, Kruyt, Newcastle. 119 Oct.; Wilhelmina, Jansen, Rio Janeiro. TE-T7T .... UITGEZEILD. Naess __Z_ ¦Pat&apos; Al&lt;=&quot;. S., Huil. - Whim, Smith, Yarmouth. -de Vrede, Krageroe ?fstad- ¦ Olga, Fredrikson, Drammen. - Alida, Tortensen, id. - kens Provei F &apos; raScroe- - Rozenklippcn, Nielsen, Stavangcr. - Lijk- Noorweeen&apos; sen&gt; Tonsberg. - Oscar, Bjöuess, id. - Wilhelmine, Nielsen, Libert. ir . , :&apos; Ivanhoe, S., Leith. - Concordia, Schlossman, Windau. - HErT7-^?l.ICC,er&apos;l&apos;rede&apos;&apos;ikstad. Cekomo Ï.OETSLÜIS&apos;24 °et-i Astrea, Mulder, Buenos Ayres, is terug- Hart! &quot; &apos;lot&apos; S Londen. - Maria Stuart, S., Leith. - Admiral Cator, S., Dra &apos;.Erederick Stonald, Heron, Middlesbro. - Okin Catharine, Movig, a^R. ELLE, 24 Oet.; Cologne, S., Londen. - Batavier, S., id. - Zcalous, S., MAASSLUIS, 24 Oct.; Carl Rudolph, Inge, Riga. ÜAMBURG, 23 Oct.; Alida, Valomstra, Nederland. G_. i B&apos; 16/&gt;2O oct,; Imanael&lt; ?• d. Meulen, Gron. - Cath. Elisabeth, eertsema, id. • Uit Vriendschap, Bolmeijer, id. - Helena Joh., Rozenboom, &apos; .-ri?OUW 6eertruida&apos; Pronk, id. - Bouwina, Heins, id. Mtót Ï,TIN&apos; w 0ct&apos;!Etta Johanna, Groenewold, Nederland. -2 Gezusters, n x&apos; Groningen_*iir&apos; TZI(ï. 20 Oct.; Zwaantina Hendrika, Vissinga, Amst. — 21 Oct.; A^e.rdmaEdziena,Uchtman,id. &apos;6, T&gt;v__9£TH&apos;22oct-&apos;Charlotte, Lange, Javan. Antw. Hn. I?,HEAD&apos;21 oct&apos; Zeilkl-: ünie-Posta.Rott_„n__TAD&apos; 2l oct&apos;; Annßeer&apos; Hanson,Liverpooln.Dordrecht. Horton Dd 2° °Ct&apos;; Martha and EUen&apos; Mor6an&gt; Ara3t- &quot; Harkaway, Int. J.3?RLAND&apos; 21 oct-iJan van Schaffelaar, van Duyn, Singapore. T x_ _EAUX-22 Oct.; Johanna Maria, Schummelketel, Brussel. _at._!OS&apos; 17 0ct&apos;i Antonen Jacob&gt; Ouwehand, Faro. H&lt;3ire. r E&apos; 7 °Ct&apos;; zeilkl&apos;: Neptune, Sherman, Amst. - Duisburg, _M^NTEVIDEO, 3 Sept.; Zoutkamp, Mulder, Antwerpen.</p>
</text>
