<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 14 Junij; Diana, S., Londen. - Whim, King, Yarmouth. VLIE, 13 Junij; Anna &amp; Metthie, Hansen, Randers. — 14 Ji.nj; Jac &gt;ba Geertruida, Bontekoe, Noorwegen.</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLUIS , 14 Junij; Three Brothcrs, Gilbert, Roeliester. - Koning Willem 111, S., Glasgow. - Ainalia, Kaiser, Riga. - Czar, Uekerniaim, id. BIIIELLE, 14 Junij; Concordia, S., Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich. BROUWERSHAVEN, 14J_nij: Magdalcna, Henkc, Rott.n.Newyork. HAMBURG, 10 Junij; Vr. Margaretha, de Groot, Brussel. — 12 Junij; Prima, Sobmg. Makkum. - Gesina, Boeker, id. BRAKE, 1 Junij; Elisabeth, de Jonge, Memel. - 4 Junij; Aurora, Schuldt, Rotterdam. EMDEN, 9 Junij; Susanna, Barghoorn, Gron. STETTEST, 9 Junij; Ida, Woitge, Dordt. - Hendrika, Vos, Pentowan - Hydra, Munneke, Liverpool. SWINEMUNDE, 11 Junij; Zwei Gebriider, Ulrich, Amst. DANTZIG, 10 Junij; Cornet, Niebers, Amst. - Tarandus, Evcrtscn, Harlingen. - Alida, Feiken, Tcrmunterzijl. - Hillechien Wolkammer, Vos, New- Castle. - Alida A&apos;ntonia, Visser, Eanoe. - Lubbina, Hazelhof, Hamburg. — 14 Junij; Roelfina, Prins, Hadersleben. MEMEL, 7 Junij; Christina Jantina, Dood, Londen. BOLDERA, 8 Junij; Medborgcren, Christensen, Nederland. - Renske, Pot, Delfzijl. - Ada, Reid, Dordt. - Willem Frederik, Visser, Londen. - .astor, Boekhout, Elsfleth. — 10 Junij; Twee Gebroeders, Butter, Amst. WIND AU, 4 Junij; Johan Cornelis, Groenewoud, Hamburg.</p>
	<p>GOTHENBURG, 7 Junij; Gothenburg, S., Rott. HEPPENS, 12 Jnnij; Elisa, Janssen, Eott.-llerold, Fesefeld, id. - Gebina, de Buhr, id. - Aaltje, Greiff, id. - Wilhelmina, Bus, id. - Reina,Kruisinga, id. LEER, 10 Junij; Bouwina, Heins, Groningen. NERVA, 2 Junij; Wilhelmina Catharina, Kiehl, Lira-pool. — 3 Junij ; Argo, Koster, Amst. — 6 Junij; Hendrika Margaretha, Stel, Bergen. _ELSENEUR, 10 Junij; Gepasseerd: Unie, Putte!» Koningsbergen ii. Leith. ■ Sophia, Pniil*e_, Riga _. Nieuwediep, LGHDSSj i_ Jangj Ödphis, Haösen, Dajft.ig.</p>
	<p>Bij DUNGENESS, 10 Junij; Philips van Marnix, van Ruijven, Rott. n. Batavia.-Betje Pronk, Vos, Barbados n. Lonten. — 12 Junij; Elisabeth, Bijl, Lissabon n. Hamburg. - Alida Sinnige, Dik, Gioja n. Petersburg. Bij POETLAND, 10 Junij; Staatsraad van deer Houven, Kip, Amst. n. Soerabaya. FALMOUTH, 12 Junij; Grietje, Lukkien, Gioja n. Petersb. BLAKENEY, 11 Junij; de Zwerver, Ates, Koningsb. , GBIMSBY, 11 Junij; Vertrouwen, Pot, Stolpemunde. - Aaltje Willemina, Jurrcma, Libau. - GENT, 12 Junij; Maria, Jongebloed, Biga. - Harmonie, Lange, Memel. LISSABON, 6 Junij; Alida, Zellien, Newcastle. POETO, 3 Junij; Harmonie, van Peer, Hamburg. KONSTANTINOPEL, 4 Juni); Jane and Arm, Hocksen, Galatz (zeilklaar naar Amsterdam )■</p>
</text>
