<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>UITGEZEILD.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 22 Jan.; Henriette.Verbeek, Coro. -Sjofröken, Faleye, Havana.- Fuchsia, Ketchman, Dublin. - Celeritas, Magnusscn, Newc. HELVOETSLUIS.2I Jan.; Hillechiena, Grappelaar, Newc. — 22 Jan.; Adeliue,Wijbrands, Hong-Kong. - Triton, Sandberg, Manzanilla.- Lodewijk, Bax, Kust van Afrika. - Alida Sinnige, Dik, Napels. - Maria Johanna, Stam, Lissabon. - Dankbaarheid, Roodenburg, id.- Feijenoord, S., Londen.- Hawk, S., id. - Maria, Pieper, Jersey. - Elisa, Breton, Belfast. -Martha, Topzant, id.- Laurens, de Haan, id. - Chevy Chase, S., Newc. - Enid, Chase, id. - Windwards, Elridge, Sunderland. - Albert, S., Huil. - Magnet, S., id. - Killarney, S., Goole. - Thames, Cracknell, Ipswich. - Eagle, Hawkins, id. - Harwieh, S. Harwich. BRIELLE, 21 Jan.; Leo, S., Londen. BROUWERSHAVEN, 21 Jan.; Harriet, S., Middlesbro. — 22 Jan.; Henny, Ohlcrich, Rott.n. New-York. - Sara, S., Londen. EMDEN, 19 Jan.; Helene, Wessels, Gibraltar. - Susanna, Barghoorn, Groningen. - Martha, Kuiper, id. - Catharina Groenewoïd, Velvis, id. - Frau Fenna, Dirks, id. LEER, 18 Jan.; Agatha, Wortel, Amst. MEMEL, 18 Jan.; Dirkje, Burghout, Harlingen. DEAL, 20 Jan.; Egbcrtus, Schrik, Genua. CARDIFF, 18 Jan.; Professor Suringar, Kuiper, Rosario. — 19 Jan.; Castor, Kloppenburg, Bahia. SWANSEA, 19 Jan.; Anna , Napels. LIVERPOOL, 19 Jan.; Jonge Eduard, Sikkens, Amst. - Albatros, S., Rotterdam. - Geertina, Mooi, Matamoras. - Clio, Roskamp, Laguayra RAMSGATE, 19 Jan.; Eendragt, Boer, Par n. Antw. ARDROSSAN, 18 Jan.; Cornelia, Vorenkamp, Barcelona. SCILLY, 20 Jan.; Jeannette Roelina, Hoeksma, Bremen. ANTWE BPBN, 22 Jan.; Gooregt, Hughes, Buenos-Ayres. REUNION, 6 Dec.; Arme et Léonie, Raflïay St. Paul,&quot; Amst. St. HELENA, 29 Nov.; Amsterdam, Doekzen, Bat. n. Amst. RIO JANEIRO, 23 Dcc; zeilkl.: de Vrede, Niekus, Santos. RIO GRANDE, 2 Dcc; Anna Ceeilia, Gnodde, Antw. FERNAMBUCK, 16 Dcc; Mina, Heeren, Kanaal. RANGOON, vddr 12 Dcc; zeilkl.: Loopuyt, v. d. Hidde, Singapore.</p>
</text>
