<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 26 Aug.; Minister Thorbecke, S., Hull. —27 Aug.; Diana, S- Londen. - Brotherley Love, Moffett, Newc. - Ark, Evans, Sunderl. - Elisabeth, Ward, id. - Alert, S., Hull. - Venator, Reyerse. Ri-a. VLIE, 27 Aug.; Argo, Koster, Frederikstad. - Egberdiua Anna, Scha&apos; ring. id. AM ELAND 24 Aug.; Aaltje, (&apos;ruilt&apos;, Kiel. - Ettina, Henrichs, Bremen. OSTMAHORN, 23 Aug.-, Familietrouw, de Boer, Koningsbergen.-&quot; 2&quot;) Aug,; Hilke Kat, de Vries, Bremen. DE_FZ YL, 23 Ang.; Margretha, de Groot, Breinen. —24 Aug.; Dankbaarheid, Schohiia, id. - Margretha, Gust, id. - Juffer Aaltje, Martens, id. - Catharina Annechina, Alberts, id. - Catharina Imkina, Hulzebos. Leer. — 25 Aug.; Agatha, Brackeri, Falkenberg. - Harmke, Harkenia» Leer. - Kleine Julia. Burmann, Oldenburg. - Geeroma, Siemers, Emden. TERMUNTERZYL, 22 Aug.; Jan Gysbert, Smit, Laurvig, 26 dito naaf Noorwegen vertr.— 25Aug.; Jeltina, Bloem, Langesund. - Jonge Barend, Prins, Hamburg. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 27 Aug.; John Ritson, Gibson, Bassein, 1. *• Brouwersh. - Marie 4&quot; Joseph, Gouret, Nantes. - Ranger, S., Londen.&quot; Louise, S., Grangem. - Osborne, S., Leith. - Rapid, Anthonissen, Ystad. BRIELLE, 27 Aug.; Batavier, S., Londen. - Johanna Albertha, Dinse* Kouingsb. - Jonge Jan 4&quot; Margaretha, Jelis, Wolgast. BROUWERSHAVEN; 27 Aug. De schepen per tel. gemeld. NORDEN, 20 Aug.; Vr. Geertje, Kuiper. Groningen. BREMERHAVEN, 24 Aug.; Theresia, Wekenborg, Laguayra. MEMEL. 21 Aug.; Vr. Giiarlotte, Noordenbos, Kiel. KROONSTAD, 22 Aug.; Grietje Koens, Kuiper, Lond.n. - Enjetta, de Boer, Grimsby. TONNINGEN, 21 Aug.;gepassecrd:Foolken, Roskamp,Kiel n. Amst.- Anke, Bleeker, id. n. id. - Elisabeth, Bos, Memel n. Groningen.—22 Auf* &apos;• Reena, Munneke, Dantzig n. Londen.- Trientje Meyer, Tonkens, Koningsbergen n. Groniugen. — 23 Aug.; Gesina, Deen, Kiel n. Hull. - 4 Gezusters, Wagemaker, Stettin n. Bremen. AIIEHDEEN, 27 Aug.; Phénix, Veldhuis, Riga; alles wel aan boord. SWANSEA, 23 Aug.; Maria Geertruida, Caspers, Hamburg.</p>
</text>
