<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 13 Dcc; Minister Thorbecke, S., Huil. — 14 Dcc; Leo, S., Londen. - Alida, v. d. Veen, Frederikstad. VLIE, 12 Dcc; Wijbrandns Udo, Kfisrs, Boness. - Amsterdam, S., Hamb. ZOLTKAMP, 11 Dcc; Magritha Hillegina, Pekelder, Engeland. - Andreas en Maria, Slik, Dover. — 12 Dcc; Export, Taylor, Londen. - Catharina Cornelia, Astuling, Newc. - Fortuna, de Groot, Langesund. DELFZIJL, 11 Deo; 3 Gebroeders, Klein, Bremerhavon. - Jonge Joltje, Visser, Emden. - De Arend, Visser, id. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Dcc; Lord Raglan, S., Newc. —14 Dcc; Zephyr, S., Londen. - o.&lt;prey, S., Liverp.-Meglee, Brown, Newc - Hawthorn, Young, id. - Perseverance, Harens, id. - Hillechicna, Gruppelaar, id. - Htnriëtte, Wever, Ystad. - Spruyt, Pott, Riga. - Bouchina, Koster, Dantzig. BRIELLE, 14 Dcc; Orion, S., Londen. AKUNDAt, 25 Nov.; Vier Gebroeders, Balkema, Dantz n. Bordeaux. — 28 Nov.; Electo, Brun, Geflo n. Amst. LONDEN, 12 Dcc; Jantje, Smit, Holmstadt. - Eendragt, Smit, Gron. — 13 Dcc ; Margaretha, Panman, Petersburg.- Petronella Knijpinga, Klofkorn, Groningen. - Maroim, Kuiper, id. - Blijham, Lusing, Helsingborg.-In lading: Houwina, Leurs, Rio Janciro. Bij DUNGENESS, 11 Dcc ; Jeannette en Comelia, Romijn, Rott. n. Bat.- Lodcwijk, Bax, id. n. Banana. PORTSMOUTH, 12 Dcc; Voorwaarts de Vries, Groningen. GREENOCK, 12 Dcc; Hooyland, Mc Kcnzie, Rott. COLCHESTER, 11 Dec&apos;; Soranus, Poelman, Holmstad. HULL, 12 Dcc; Hendrika, Kuiper, Petersburg. NEW-CASTLE, 9 Dcc; In lading: Christina, Heerma, Genua. lIARTLEPOOL, 11 Dcc; VTr. Martha, Ebes, Riga. MIDDLESBEO, 12 Dcc; John and Jane, Austwick, Rott. C ADIX, 6 Dec.; Maria Johanna, van Gelderen, Villanova. NAPELS, 5 Dcc; San Giovanni Guiseppe, Caeace, Amst. LISSABON, 2 Dcc ; Noordster, Hartog, Leith. NEW-YORK, 29 Nov.; in lading: Frei, Gallas. Rott. - Jeannette, Hassing, id. UITGEZEILD. TEXEL, 14 Dcc; Aurora, S., Londen. - Alert, S., Huil. -Vesta, S., Gothenburg. - Gouverneur van Ewyck, S., Hamburg. DELFZIJL, 12 Dcc; Anna, Luken, Bremen. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 13 Dcc; Admiral Cator, S., Hartlep. - Seahorse, S-, Huil. —14 Dec.; Nieuwe Waterweg, Heymeriks, Bat. via Brouwcrsh. - Admiraal Vcr-Hucll, S., Havre.-Vartry, S., Dublin. -Maria Stuart, S., Leith. - Elma, S., Middlesbro. - Albert, S., Huil. - Ariel, §? Dantzig. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 14 Dcc; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. i Londen.- Ravensbury, S-, Harwich. CUXHAVEN, 12 Dcc ; Alida Adriana, Kramer, Avontuur. DEAL, 12 Dcc; Entreprise, Hut, Londen n. Montevideo.- Lucia Jantina, Lieffijn, id. n. Aspinwall. FALMOUTH, 12 Dcc; Catharina, Visman, Brazilië n. Havre. LEITH, 12 Dcc; Twee Gebroeders, Bakker, Inverkcithiag. HULL, 12 Dcc; Charlotte, Klein, Grimsby. PORTLAND, 9 Dcc; Orion, Lindeboom, St. Valery.-Nannette, Campen, Rio-Janeiro. — 11 Dcc; Anna Maria, Brandt, Cette (allen bijleggers). LIVERPOOL, _2 Dcc; Amphitrite, Lindholm, Batavia. LIVORNO, 3 Dcc; Margaretha, Boerhave, Liverpool. - Wilhelmina Cath-rina. Kiel, id. LISSABON, 7 Dcc; Zeemeeuw, Zwart, St. Übes.</p>
</text>
