<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 18 Aug., W.Z.W.-W.; Nautilus, Bell, Newc. - Beecks.Baines, id. - Hawk, S.. Huil. - Ciiristina, Audersen, Sundswall. VLIE, 17 Aug., W.Z.W.;Eendragt, Dorenbos, Newc. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 18 Aug., W.Z.W.-W.; Osborne, S., Leith. - Seahorsc, S., Huil. - Hammonia, S., Hamburg. BRIELLE, 18 Aug., W.Z.W.-W.; Prins van Oranje, S., Duinkerken. - Waterloo, S., Londen. - Zealous, S., Harwich. - Sheffield, S., Grimsby. BROUWERSHAVEN, 18 Aug., W.; Mary Ar HiUegonda, Walters, Bat. n. Rott., vertr. 20 April. - Iro, Martinolich, Taganrog n. id. - Immaculata, Gnisepimicali, Licata n. id. - Vivid, Eng. Stooinj., Woolwich, (is derwaarts teruggekeerd). - Osborne, Eng. Stoomj. id. n. Dordrecht. HARLINGEN, 15 Ang.; Jantina Roelflna, Broekema, Newc. n. Leeuwarden. — 18 Aug.; Eendragt, Dorenbos, id. ZOLTKAMP, 15 Aug.; Alida Sara, Mooi, Dantzig. BREMERHAVEN, 17 Aug.; Jantina, de Veen, Elmshorn. HEPPENS, 15 Aug.-, ChristineElisabeth,Albers,Rott.-Elise,Henrichs, id. - Magretha, Schoon, id. - Regina, de Wall, id. BOLDERA A, 10 Ang.; Vrede, Nickus, Liverpool. STOCKHOLM, 13 Aug.; Zeeploeg, Luder, Petersb. STETTIN, 15 Aug.; Farailietrouw, de Boer, Amst. DRAMMEN, 2/3 Aug.; Petrus, Jahnsen, Purmerende. — 5/7 Aug.; Preciosa, Thomsen, id. - Marke Ein, Eriksen, Nieuwe Diep. KROONSTAD, 13 Aug.; Froukje, Koops, Liverpool. - Antje Haverbult v. Heuvelen, id. LONDEN, 16 Aug.; John Allan, Hover, Rott. FALMOUTH, 16 Aug.; Cornelis Smit, Wiedenaar, Akyab n.Bremerh. NORTH SHIELDS, 16 Aug.; Catharina, Wilkens, Rott. - Lyra, Strong, id. - Cort Adler, Larsen, Schiedam. - Harmonie, Arens, id. - Ronaldus, Green, id. • William Martland, Clarkson, id. - Zwaantina Jantina, Weganer, Antwerpen. - Anna Catharina, Akkersen, Koogerpolder. —17 Aug,; Burgemeester van Middelburg, Hoek. Middelburg. GIBRALTAR, 7 Aug.; Jantina Margaretha, Vos Peper, Livomo n. Hamburg. PAR, 15 .Ang.; Broedertrouw, Zeven, Teignmonth. SEAHAM, 16&apos;Aug.; Elisa, Williamsen, Nieuwediep. LI VER POOL, 16 Aug.; Maria Regina, van der Plas, Amst. GRIMSBY, 16 Aug.-, Harmonie, Luders, Huil. BRIDLINGTON, 16 Aug.; Claudina, Shaw, Amst. n. Newc RUNCORN, 15 Aug.; Acadia, Boer, St. Johns (N. B.) SULINA, 1 Ang.; Wijbrandus üdo, Kiers, Newc. KONSTANTINOPEL, 3 Aug.; Jason, S„ Napels. MONTEVIDEO, 13 Julij; Catharina, .... Rott.</p>
	<p>BUENOS-AYRES, 7 Julij-, Maria Catharina, Beekman, Antw. BAHIA, 12 Julij; Anna, Laarman, Triest. - Waalwijk, Schaal&apos;sma, Cardiff. St. THOMAS, 19 Julij; Zcenimph, Schipper, Cardiff.</p>
</text>
